<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
	<string id="igi_task_text_arszi_scout_title">
		<text>Scout</text>
	</string>
<!-- Cold -->
<!-- mar_smart_terrain_base_stalker_leader_marsh_task_arszi_scout -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_smart_terrain_base_stalker_leader_marsh_task_arszi_scout_title">
		<text>Scout the area in the Great Marsh.</text>
	</string>
    <string id="igi_task_text_mar_smart_terrain_base_stalker_leader_marsh_task_arszi_scout_descr">
		<text>Cold has asked me to scout an area in the Great Marsh.</text>
	</string>
    <string id="igi_task_text_mar_smart_terrain_base_stalker_leader_marsh_task_arszi_scout_job_descr">
		<text>Listen, I need someone who will do some reconnaissance. All you have to do is to check some of the derelict buildings in the marsh and report back to me. I repeat, this is a reconnaissance mission! Do not try to be a hero, I need you back alive! Doing some killing won't yield any extra rewards this time! If you find any kind of resistance, flee and report back to me! This information would help us a lot to plan our next moves and keep ourselfes safe from harm in the marsh.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_st_mar_smart_terrain_base_stalker_leader_marsh_task_arszi_scout_finish">
		<text>What did you find? I see ... Thank you for you work, here is your reward!</text>
	</string>
<!-- Fanatic -->
<!-- esc_2_12_stalker_fanat_task_arszi_scout -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_2_12_stalker_fanat_task_arszi_scout_title">
		<text>Scout the area around Rookie Village</text>
	</string>
    <string id="igi_task_text_esc_2_12_stalker_fanat_task_arszi_scout_descr">
		<text>Fanatic has asked me to scout the area around Rookie Village</text>
	</string>
    <string id="igi_task_text_esc_2_12_stalker_fanat_task_arszi_scout_job_descr">
		<text>I would have a request for you. It is not easy to keep Rookie Village safe. To the south we have a merry bunch, called the military. To the north we have bandits, mutants and occasionally mercenaries ... It would be a great help for us if you could scout the area to the north and report back about the situation there. Knowing where the bandits and mutants camp can prevent fatal encounters for the rookies. I do not ask you to encounter them, just look around, try to avoid harm and come back safely. Not for free, of course.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_st_esc_2_12_stalker_fanat_task_arszi_scout_finish">
		<text>Well, it could be worse ... Thank you, I will tell everyone which areas to avoid for some time. Here is your reward, as promised!</text>
	</string>
<!-- General Voronin -->
<!-- bar_dolg_leader_task_arszi_scout -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_bar_dolg_leader_task_arszi_scout_title">
		<text>Scout the area around Rostok.</text>
	</string>
    <string id="igi_task_text_bar_dolg_leader_task_arszi_scout_descr">
		<text>General Voronin has asked me to scout the area around Rostok.</text>
	</string>
    <string id="igi_task_text_bar_dolg_leader_task_arszi_scout_job_descr">
		<text>Excellent, I have orders for you! We have to gather intel about the movement of the enemy and the mutants. I am interested in the areas of Rostok, Garbage, Army Warehouses and Truck Cemetery. You will be sent to one of these areas, and your mission is to scout the enemy and report back! You are allowed to open fire upon encounter, but try to avoid it, if possible. The information you are about to gather is crucial in the planning of future operations! You will be compensated upon your return.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_st_bar_dolg_leader_task_arszi_scout_finish">
		<text>Well done, this information will advance our plans. Here is your reward.</text>
	</string>
<!-- Sultan -->
<!-- zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_arszi_scout -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_arszi_scout_title">
		<text>Scout the area around the hideout.</text>
	</string>
    <string id="igi_task_text_zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_arszi_scout_descr">
		<text>Sultan has asked me to scout the area around the hideout.</text>
	</string>
    <string id="igi_task_text_zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_arszi_scout_job_descr">
		<text>Ah, look what the cat dragged in! Listen to me stalker, if you want some money for your playboys and vodka I need you to do me a solid. Go out there and take a peak at the southern and western parts of Dark Valley. Look for any information you think might be useful and there might be a reward in it for you! Just watch your ass around that damn lab and those fucking military guys. Them and some loners have been a pain in the ass for me recently. Now go, and don't come back till you have something interesting to tell me!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_st_zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_arszi_scout_finish">
		<text>Well well, look who's back in one piece. And what's that, you even have some interesting information for me? Good job. Here's your payment. Don't waste it all on drinks, you hear me? We need capable men like you to do more business!</text>
	</string>
<!-- Major Kuznetsov -->
<!-- agr_smart_terrain_1_6_near_2_military_colonel_kovalski_task_arszi_scout -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_agr_smart_terrain_1_6_near_2_military_colonel_kovalski_task_arszi_scout_title">
		<text>Scout the area around the base.</text>
	</string>
    <string id="igi_task_text_agr_smart_terrain_1_6_near_2_military_colonel_kovalski_task_arszi_scout_descr">
		<text>Major Kuznetsov has asked me to scout the area around the base.</text>
	</string>
    <string id="igi_task_text_agr_smart_terrain_1_6_near_2_military_colonel_kovalski_task_arszi_scout_job_descr">
		<text>I have orders for you, soldier! I want to know what is going on around here. You will be sent on a reconaissance mission to gather intel about the surrounding area of the base. I am interested in the area of Agroprom, the northern part of the Great Marsh and HQ requested us to aid the scientists too. Gather intel and report back, try to avoid confrontation, this is a reconnaissance, not an elimination mission!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_st_agr_smart_terrain_1_6_near_2_military_colonel_kovalski_task_arszi_scout_finish">
		<text>So this is the situation. Well done, soldier! Here is your reward and some extra.</text>
	</string>
<!-- Lukash -->
<!-- mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_arszi_scout -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_arszi_scout_title">
		<text>Scout the area around the warehouse.</text>
	</string>
    <string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_arszi_scout_descr">
		<text>Lukash has asked me to scout the area around the warehouse.</text>
	</string>
    <string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_arszi_scout_job_descr">
		<text>I would like to ask you to help defending our home. There have been a concerning amount of Duty and Monolith sightings recently, not to talk about bloodsuckers lurking closer and closer with every day from that cursed village. We require information about the current situation in the Army Warehouses. Check the spots which I marked you on the map, and report back. Try to avoid fighting if possible. Come back safely!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_st_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_arszi_scout_finish">
		<text>Feels like a calm before the storm. Thank you, we are grateful for your aid.</text>
	</string>
<!-- Dushman -->
<!-- cit_killers_merc_trader_stalker_task_arszi_scout -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_cit_killers_merc_trader_stalker_task_arszi_scout_title">
		<text>Scout the area around Dead City.</text>
	</string>
    <string id="igi_task_text_cit_killers_merc_trader_stalker_task_arszi_scout_descr">
		<text>Dushman has asked me to scout the area around Dead City.</text>
	</string>
    <string id="igi_task_text_cit_killers_merc_trader_stalker_task_arszi_scout_job_descr">
		<text>Listen, I am looking for volunteers to scout areas which will be subjects for future operations. You will infiltrate the operational area, gather intel, and report back. Low level of risk, acceptable reward. Occasional encounters might happen. What do you say?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_st_cit_killers_merc_trader_stalker_task_arszi_scout_finish">
		<text>Well done! Here is your reward and some extra.</text>
	</string>
<!-- Krolik -->
<!-- pri_monolith_monolith_trader_stalker_task_arszi_scout -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_pri_monolith_monolith_trader_stalker_task_arszi_scout_title">
		<text>Scout the area around Pripjat.</text>
	</string>
    <string id="igi_task_text_pri_monolith_monolith_trader_stalker_task_arszi_scout_descr">
		<text>Krolik has asked me to scout the area around Pripjat.</text>
	</string>
    <string id="igi_task_text_pri_monolith_monolith_trader_stalker_task_arszi_scout_job_descr">
		<text>Brother! The infidels are drawing closer to the heart of our holy land every day! They are crawling like worms everywhere! I ask you to find the the stones under which they crawl and the holes where they hide. The moment we learn their location, we will strike in the name of the Monolith! Go brother, and return with the information safely! It is not a shame not to encounter them and not to die an honourable death, there are situations when you can cause them more misery when you are just watching and listening, preparing for the strike! May the Monolith watch over you on your mission!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_st_pri_monolith_monolith_trader_stalker_task_arszi_scout_finish">
		<text>Praise the Monolith! You did a great service for your brothers!</text>
	</string>
</string_table>
