<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
<!-- Butcher -->
<!-- hunter_gar_trader_task_common_trophy -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_trophy_title">
		<text>Find common mutant trophies</text>
	</string>
    <string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_trophy_descr">
		<text>Butcher has asked me to bring him some common trophies</text>
	</string>
    <string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_trophy_job_descr">
		<text>Meat is not the only part of mutants, which might be valuable. Some stalkers prize specific parts of mutants as trophies or lucky charms. You know, like a nice pseudodog fang necklace or a fluffy cat tail hanging from the belt. Anyone can hunt down a mutant and wear its parts as a symbol of achivement, but to create exceptionally spectacular items, it requires real skill! - Bring me some trophies, and I'll craft some stylish accessories out of them. Are you in?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_trophy_finish">
		<text>Some fine materials you've gathered. Well done, hunter.</text>
	</string>
<!-- hunter_gar_trader_task_common_hide -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_hide_title">
		<text>Find common mutant hides and pelts</text>
	</string>
    <string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_hide_job_descr">
		<text>The weather is growing colder and colder ... Mutants in the Zone have learned how to survive the hazards of the local weather by growing warm fur. It is time to gather some pelts! Also, pelts are not just for keeping you warm, but they have many utilities like repairing weary armour or giving you an edge against anomalies! Gather some hides for me, and you will be rewarded.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_hide_finish">
		<text>See, skinning some mutants wasn't that difficult, was it, hunter?</text>
	</string>
	<!-- hunter_gar_trader_task_psy_dog_fur -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_psy_dog_fur_title">
		<text>The finest pelt - Find a Psy-dog pelt for Butcher</text>
	</string>
    <string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_psy_dog_fur_descr">
		<text>Butcher has asked me to bring him a rare Psy-dog pelt.</text>
	</string>
    <string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_psy_dog_fur_job_descr">
		<text>There is a creature which dwells deep in the heart of the Zone. It is quite a rare sight and not many stalkers survive an encounter with it. Its howl freezes your blood and its eyes see into your mind and soul! This creature is called Psy-dog, a creature of both beauty and death with a unique silvery fur. The finest pelt many hunters long for. Bring me a Psy-dog pelt, hunter.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_psy_dog_fur_finish">
		<text>Do you have it? Yes! One of the finest pelts I have ever seen in my life. Here is your payment, hunter, and something else, which I found in the days around and have not much use for.</text>
	</string>
	<!-- hunter_gar_trader_task_arszi_fetch_beak -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_beak_title">
		<text>Legends of the Zone - Find a mutated crow beak for Butcher</text>
	</string>
    <string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_beak_descr">
		<text>Butcher has asked me to bring him a rare mutated beak of a crow.</text>
	</string>
    <string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_beak_job_descr">
		<text>There are many legends about the Zone. But there are only a few which interest us, hunters. The magical mutated beak of an elder crow is one of these legends. Some stalkers believe if you make a drink out of it and drink it, you will gain supernatural abilities temporarily. This means, there are some stalkers, who would pay handsomely for it. Bring me a mutated beak of an elder crow.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_beak_finish">
		<text>So this is that legendary beak. It looks kind of different indeed. Here is your payment, hunter.</text>
	</string>
	<!-- hunter_gar_trader_task_bloodsucker -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_bloodsucker_title">
		<text>Exquisite jewelry</text>
	</string>
    <string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_bloodsucker_descr">
		<text>Butcher has asked me to bring him bloodsucker jaw.</text>
	</string>
    <string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_bloodsucker_job_descr">
		<text>People say, Bloodsuckers are rare. Well, it is not entirely true. People do not see too much of them, because most stalkers do not survive the encounter to tell about it ... In reality, Bloodsuckers are swarming everywhere. During the day they hide, and come out to hunt during the night. I can make exceptionally fine jewelry using their jaws. Collect me some bloodsucker jaws, and be careful during the hunt! If you do not see them, it does not mean, that they do not see you ...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_bloodsucker_finish">
		<text>Excellent! I hope they did not taste you during the hunting. Here is your payment, hunter.</text>
	</string>
	<!-- hunter_gar_trader_task_chimera -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_chimera_title">
		<text>The ultimate hunter</text>
	</string>
    <string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_chimera_descr">
		<text>Butcher has asked me to bring him part of chimera</text>
	</string>
    <string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_chimera_job_descr">
		<text>Back then humans feared animals, then animals feared humans. But everything changed again, when the Zone appeared ... There are no hunters and prey in the Zone, but hunters only. Today you are the hunter, tomorrow you might be the hunted one. There is a creature, the ultimate hunter, the Chimera. The pinnacle of evolution. Are you brave enough to face the ultimate test as a hunter? If yes, then hunt down a Chimera, and bring me a trophy. I will wait for your return!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_chimera_finish">
		<text>The finest trophy you have brought for me! Here is your reward, master hunter, and something else, which I found in the days around and have not much use for. You have earned it!</text>
	</string>
<!-- Fanatic -->
<!-- esc_2_12_stalker_fanat_task_meat -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_meat_title">
		<text>Food for the rookies</text>
	</string>
    <string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_meat_descr">
		<text>Fanatic has asked me to bring him some supplies</text>
	</string>
    <string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_meat_job_descr">
		<text>More and more rookies arrive each day, and because of this Rookie village is a bit low on supplies. I would like to ask you to go and fetch some meat, so we can aid the rookies in need with a warm meal.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_meat_finish">
		<text>Thank you my friend, here is your reward for helping us out!</text>
	</string>
<!-- Wolf -->
<!-- esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_night -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_night_title">
		<text>Night terror on Cordon - Eliminate mutants</text>
	</string>
    <string id="igi_task_text_night_descr">
		<text>Wolf asked me to eliminate dangerous nightly mutants.</text>
	</string>
    <string id="igi_task_text_night_job_descr">
		<text>Can't sleep either? Maybe for the better. Listen, I just received a report from some frightened rookies, that they heard strange sounds in the area. Based on the description of the sounds, it must be some kind of dangerous nightly mutant. I want you to find the source of the sounds, and hunt it down for the safety of the village! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_night_finish">
		<text>Thank you for your hard work, Rookie village is safe, for now ... Here is your reward.</text>
	</string>
<!-- Sakharov -->
<!-- yan_stalker_sakharov_task_mutant_parts_specimen_monster_common -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_monster_common_title">
		<text>Collecting common mutant samples</text>
	</string>
    <string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_monster_common_descr">
		<text>Sakharov has asked me to bring him some common mutant samples</text>
	</string>
    <string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_monster_common_job_descr">
		<text>We are out of common mutant samples. While our priority of research is on rare humanoid mutants and artefacts, we are still interested in the changes happening in the local wildlife. Apart from personal interest, there might be still things we can learn about the unique ways of evolution the animals took in the Zone. Several species show promising abilities, which we can use to develop new medicines or just understand more about the Zone itself. Would you like to help science? All you have to do is to bring me some samples!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_monster_common_finish">
		<text>Thank you, young man! Here is your reward.</text>
	</string>
<!-- yan_stalker_sakharov_task_mutant_parts_specimen_zombie -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_zombie_title">
		<text>Collecting zombified humanoid samples</text>
	</string>
    <string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_zombie_descr">
		<text>Sakharov has asked me to bring him some zombified humanoid samples</text>
	</string>
    <string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_zombie_job_descr">
		<text>There are many unique phenomeons in the Zone. We are especially interested in Psy-related effects, like the ability which certain mutants or anomalies bear. On the other hand, the result of these effects are astonishing. Victims of these effects are still &quot;alive&quot; in a way, while they should not be. This changes many theories about &quot;life&quot; itself. As you might have guessed already, I am talking about those so called &quot;zombiefied&quot; people, but I find the term highly unscientific. I am always eager to study the biological processes which took place in them after the brain became severely damaged by contact with high levels of Psy emissions. Please bring me some samples!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_zombie_finish">
		<text>It is sad indeed, to end up like this ... Oh yes, here is your reward.</text>
	</string>
<!-- yan_stalker_sakharov_task_mutant_parts_specimen_humanoid -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_humanoid_title">
		<text>Collecting humanoid samples</text>
	</string>
    <string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_humanoid_descr">
		<text>Sakharov has asked me to bring him some humanoid samples</text>
	</string>
    <string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_humanoid_job_descr">
		<text>The Zone has changed life as we know it. Not for animals only, but for humans too! There is a considerable amount of reports about heavily mutated humans, with new, fascinating abilities. Mind control, superhuman strength, regeneration, and many more. We are most interested in samples of these mutated humans, or if we can say, humanoid mutants. Naturally, their curious intellect makes them far more formidable than the pigs or dogs that less experienced stalkers are used to. It's certainly a dangerous request, but if you bring me a sample, you'll be a wealthy stalker indeed!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_humanoid_finish">
		<text>Fascinating! These samples might open a door for science beyond imagination. Your reward, as promised!</text>
	</string>
<!-- yan_stalker_sakharov_task_mutant_parts_specimen_mutant_rare -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_monster_rare_title">
		<text>Collecting rare mutant samples</text>
	</string>
    <string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_monster_rare_descr">
		<text>Sakharov has asked me to bring him some rare mutant samples</text>
	</string>
    <string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_monster_rare_job_descr">
		<text>Mutated animals exist, which can be considered apex predators, exist in the Zone. Only very few stalkers survive contact with them, which makes them very rare specimen for us. Rumours say, some of them can even survive the harshest conditions, like high radiation or contact with anomalies. I want to prove scientifically, if these rumors are true or not. Many things are possible in the Zone, which even I would have considered unscientific back then ... It will be a dangerous mission. Bring some samples, you will be rewarded well, stalker!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_arszi_fetch_monster_rare_finish">
		<text>We can rarely work on excellent specimen like these. They hold so many secrets to be uncovered! Here is your reward.</text>
	</string>
</string_table>