<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<string_table>
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Lukash (Freedom Honcho) Stop Enemy Assault Task -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_1_title">
		<text>Destroy the Enemy Detachment</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_1_descr">
		<text>A detachment of stalkers has been causing problems for Freedom's friends. Lukash is offering a bounty to whoever takes these punks out.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_1_job_descr">
		<text>Do you feel like helping Freedom for a reward? We've got some damn punks who won't settle down, and it's time to teach them a lesson. These rascals have been sneaking into our territory. They have been shooting at our friends. And, to top it all off, they have the gall to gaslight my men! It's time to give them a lethal education on personal space. Can you do it? </text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_1_finish">
		<text>Ah, great! Maybe now we'll get some goddamn peace and quiet around here, eh?</text>
	</string>

	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_2_title">
		<text>Raid the Enemy</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_2_descr">
		<text>I have been tasked to raid enemy territory for Freedom. I should report back to Lukash after the job is done.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_2_job_descr">
		<text>I have a dangerous but important mission if you are willing. With Monolith to the north and Duty to the south, things are getting a little claustrophobic for my liking. I need a certified badass to raid an enemy camp and give us more breathing room. Do you dare to be that badass?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_2_finish">
		<text>Ha! You actually did it, you mad man! Here, you've earned this, along with my respect.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_3_title">
		<text>Eliminate the Monolith Convert</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_3_descr">
		<text>A Freedom member has converted to the Monolith. Lukash has tasked me with finding and killing him.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_3_job_descr">
		<text>I've got some real heavy news, man. One of our Freedom fighters has fallen under the influence of the Monolith. He was a good man, and I know he wouldn't have wanted to continue living as some alien crystal's brainwashed killer. Please, find him and take him down. Otherwise, his old friends are going to have to do it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_3_finish">
		<text>It's done? Good. I know this was rough. Our brothers at the Barrier will drink to their fallen comrade. As for you, here's your payment.</text>
	</string>


	<!-- ASSASSINATE DUTY FOR FREEDOM TASK -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_4_title">
		<text>Deal with the Problematic Stalker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_4_descr">
		<text>Lukash will reward me for capping a troublesome stalker.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_4_job_descr">
		<text>There's a fellow who's walking around not far from here. He shot one of ours down once. And something like that cannot be forgiven. Will you take the job to whack him? We'll pay, don't worry.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_4_finish">
		<text>Hell yeah! That'll teach 'em to mess with us. Here's your reward, as I promised. Good job, stalker.</text>
	</string>


	<!-- FIND WEAPON FOR FREEDOM TASK -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_5_title">
		<text>Bring Lukash a Reliable gun</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_5_descr">
		<text>Lukash has asked me to find a specific firearm in mint condition. I should return to him as soon as I find what he wants.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_5_job_descr">
		<text>While Freedom's benefactors keep the lads supplied with the weaponry they need, I could really do with a new weapon for personal reasons. If you happen to find one in excellent condition, I would be willing to give you a substantial payment for it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_5_fetch_job_descr">
		<text>While Freedom's benefactors keep the lads supplied with the weaponry they need, I could really do with a new weapon for personal reasons. If you happen to find one in excellent condition, I would be willing to give you a substantial payment for it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_5_fetch_finish">
		<text>Well done. This new shooter will make an enormous difference should the worst come to pass. Here is the payment I promised.</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- Lukash (Freedom Honcho) Decimate the Enemy Task -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_bs_fetch_patches_title">
		<text>Trigger Happy</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_bs_fetch_patches_descr">
		<text>Lukash is promoting aggression against some of Freedom's enemies. I can bring patches to him for a sweet bounty.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_bs_fetch_patches_job_descr">
		<text>Well, right now, we're stuck in a hammer and anvil situation. Y'know, zealots to the north, extremists to the south, and sprinkle in some military goons for good measure. How about you explain to them what we think of their edicts and commands the old-fashioned way? There'll be a sweet reward at the end for you, don't worry.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_bs_fetch_patches_finish">
		<text>Hey, nice job, man. Here's your money.</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- Lukash (Freedom Honcho) Mortal Sin Unquenchable Flame Tasks -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_7_job_descr">
		<text>Hey man. Here's a thing. Remember those Sin folks? They didn't get the memo the last time you kicked their collective asses, so I think it's high time for an encore. Loki said they've been spotted being unruly in Zaton, especially around the area of abandoned substation workshops. Go put them down.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_7_finish">
		<text>Some of the newer stalkers among Freedom are starting to think you're the Second Coming of Rambo. That you keep coming back alive and well from jobs like this makes me think they may be onto something. So here. A little something for our Rambo.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- Lukash (Freedom Honcho) Rescue the Freedom Agent Task -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_8_title">
		<text>Zoneraker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_8_descr">
		<text>A Freedom spy needs to be extracted from an enemy faction. I'll need to kill the other members of the squad, then escort him back to the base. The spy has an SVD.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_8_job_descr">
		<text>One of my best men is currently hiding out among the enemy, trying to learn their secrets. He's usually a solid guy, so when he begins missing our contact times, I begin to worry. I have a hunch he's been ratted out, and that the squad he's with is now quietly waiting for the perfect opportunity to silence him permanently. We need to get him home. He left me a location ping, but he's with other stalkers. You need to take care of them and bring my man back in one piece. You will recognize him by his rifle, an SVD. He will have to shoot at you to maintain his deception when you attack the group, but he won't be aiming too well, so don't hold a grudge.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_8_finish">
		<text>Fine work. Time to grease this guy's nuts for his knowledge.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_8_msg_join">
		<text>Hey man, stop! I'm the Freedom spy! Sorry for taking potshots at you. I had to keep my cover just in case...luckily you made it. If you bring me to Army Warehouses safely, Lukash will reward you well. Lead the way, I'll follow!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_8_msg_leave">
		<text>Thanks for pulling my nuts out of the fire, stalker! See you around!</text>
	</string>
	
	
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_9_title">
		<text>Why We Can't Have Nice Things</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_9_descr">
		<text>Lukash has asked me to destroy the military vehicles in Cordon before they do any damage in the Zone. I'll need to bring explosives.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_9_job_descr">
		<text>Do you have explosives? If so, I've got a big job for you. Right now, the military is bringing armoured vehicles into the Zone to reinforce their troops. I ask you, is this fair? Look at the rusty, dysfunctional pieces of junk we have rotting in our warehouses! If we can't have tanks that work in the Zone, then neither can the government! My spies say these vehicles are arriving to be stationed at the Cordon checkpoint as we speak. Don't worry, they'll make sure the vehicles are unmanned when you pay your visit, so you can destroy them without being turned into swiss cheese. You want in? Then pack your pineapples and get going!</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Skinflint (Freedom Mechanic) -->
	
	<!-- FIND MUTANT MEAT FOR FREEDOM TASK -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_10_freedom_trader_stalker_task_1_title">
		<text>Bring Wild Game for Freedom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_10_freedom_trader_stalker_task_1_descr">
		<text>Skinflint said he'd pay me to bring him mutants parts. Time to go hunting.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_10_freedom_trader_stalker_task_1_job_descr">
		<text>I have just the job for you, man, if you are not afraid of a few mutants. Are you interested?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_10_freedom_trader_stalker_task_1_fetch_job_descr">
		<text>So, some of the guys are planning a dinner party to celebrate Bob Marley's birthday. Better late than never, right? Anyways, the more meat we can get for the feast, the better - so if you are out and about, bring me enough meat, and I'll make it worth your while. Jah will never forget you!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_10_freedom_trader_stalker_task_1_fetch_finish">
		<text>Ah, this'll make for a fine meal once the chef gets his hands on it. Here's your payment. Why not buy some vodka and celebrate?</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Skinflint (Freedom Mechanic) Deliver Equipment Dynamic Task -->

	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_10_freedom_trader_stalker_task_2_title">
		<text>Deliver Locked Case to Skinflint</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_10_freedom_trader_stalker_task_2_descr">
		<text>Skinflint has a delivery that needs to be picked up.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_10_freedom_trader_stalker_task_2_job_descr">
		<text>One of our couriers was supposed to bring a package through today. Sadly, they had to hide it somewhere safe when a Duty patrol caught wind of them. They sent me the stash coordinates before going invisible on the network, so if you're willing to walk on over and finish the job by fetching the goods, I'll give you a cut of their pay.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_10_freedom_trader_stalker_task_2_finish">
		<text>Let's take a look-see...ah yes. Just what we needed. Thank you stalker, here's your cut of the pay.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Skinflint (Freedom Trader) Night Terror Task -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_10_freedom_trader_stalker_task_3_title">
		<text>Phantoms in the Dark</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_10_freedom_trader_stalker_task_3_descr">
		<text>Skinflint will pay me to stop a terrible mutant that haunts the Bloodsucker Village. I'll need to keep myself alert.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_10_freedom_trader_stalker_task_3_job_descr">
		<text>Sleep has been a little harder around camp lately. Each night we hear screaming, but before we can do anything about it, yet another one of our men on the road gets swallowed by the darkness. We find their mangled remains strewn about the Bloodsucker Village the next day.\n \nLukash thinks a rare breed of bloodsucker may be in town. A darker, stronger, more vicious motherfucker that only comes out at night. A few of our war-dogs think we should cease night hikes until it migrates and hopefully starts messing up Duty instead, believing it's too risky for us to go after it directly.\n \nWell, I say if you've got the stones to wait for it in the Village after nightfall, I'd be thrilled to shower you in roubles for killing the bastard, and the rest of the lads around here will be grateful to get a good night's sleep again. Or at least as good as sleep gets this close to the Brain Scorcher. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_10_freedom_trader_stalker_task_3_finish">
		<text>Wow, you actually did it! You lunatic. I'll let the camp know the good news. Glad we have a hunter like you around.</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Skinflint (Freedom Trader) Scarce Supplies Task -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_10_freedom_trader_stalker_task_4_title">
		<text>Scarce Supplies</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_10_freedom_trader_stalker_task_4_descr">
		<text>Skinflint needs medical supplies to help keep Freedom's medic stocked. I've agreed to help him.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_10_freedom_trader_stalker_task_4_job_descr">
		<text>Hey man. Some of our guys can get a bit too adventurous from time to time. We haven't got enough supplies to treat all of 'em.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_10_freedom_trader_stalker_task_4_fetch_job_descr">
		<text>Yeah. You know how rough and tumble life can be in Freedom, right? Dodging bullets and fighting fanatics is just part of the daily life around here. As badass as it makes Freedom's fighters feel, it also means we're getting short on meds. Since Solid is too high off his ass to organize medical supplies, that responsibility now falls to me. If you can help out by bringing in some medical supplies, you'd have Freedom's gratitude. And some of my roubles. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_10_freedom_trader_stalker_task_4_fetch_finish">
		<text>Ah, brilliant. I'll make sure these stay out of Solid's sight until his patients need it. Thanks a lot, stalker.</text>
	</string>
	
	
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_10_freedom_trader_stalker_task_5_title">
		<text>Amass Artefact Hunting Equipment</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_smart_terrain_7_10_freedom_trader_stalker_task_5_job_descr">
		<text>Well, there is something important that needs looking at. Here's the thing: short of risking our luck in Belarus, there are precisely two scientific bunkers that Freedom can contact for anomaly-diving supplies. No more, no less. One is sandwiched between Duty thugs, military goons, and who knows what else. The other is a light jog away from Pripyat. And both...are sponsored by the very government we fight against. We need to start stockpiling new artefact hunting equipment NOW in case either of those places suddenly becomes cut off from our runners. I need you to begin gathering Bear detectors and artefact containers wholesale. I understand everything I'm requesting will take a while to obtain. Don't fret, your payment will be adequate. If you go the extra mile and get some batteries, you'll even get a bonus, too. So, you in?</text>
	</string>
		
	<!-- Solid (Freedom Medic) -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_freedom_medic_task_1_title">
		<text>Find drug-makin kit for Solid</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_freedom_medic_task_1_descr">
		<text>A drug-making kit is required by Solid for his work on medical supplies. I should bring it back to him if I find one.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_freedom_medic_task_1_job_descr">
		<text>Maintaining what's left from medical supplies storage with this number of injuries I have to treat on daily basis is worrying. I'm gonna run out of bandages and medkits soon or later. I need you to find me one of those old drug-making kits. They will come in handy for sure.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_freedom_medic_task_1_fetch_job_descr">
		<text>You bet your sweet ass there is. I've been looking all over for a drug-making kit. It should contain just the right cocktail of ingredients I need to make all sorts of drugs. For medicinal use, of course. I know the things some of the lads around here say about me. Don't listen to that bullshit. All I need is some decent kit, and I'll be able to get my little clinic into decent shape again.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mil_freedom_medic_task_1_fetch_finish">
		<text>Great job! I owe you big time.</text>
	</string>

</string_table>
