<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Beard (Loner Trader) Clear Mutants from SkadovskTask -->

	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_a2_stalker_barmen_task_bs_assault_monster_online_title">
		<text>Clear area of mutants</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_a2_stalker_barmen_task_bs_assault_monster_online_descr">
		<text>Mutants are about. Hunt them down and clear the area.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_a2_stalker_barmen_task_bs_assault_monster_online_job_descr">
		<text>Shh... Listen, hear that? Some mutants howling. Still gives me the chills after all this time. How about you go out there and take care of them? I'll make it worth your while.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_a2_stalker_barmen_task_bs_assault_monster_online_finish">
		<text>Haha! Well done, stalker! Have a drink on Beard!</text>
	</string>


	<!-- FIND ARTEFACT FOR BEARD TASK -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_a2_stalker_barmen_task_2_title">
		<text>Find the Artefact for Beard</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_a2_stalker_barmen_task_2_descr">
		<text>Beard wants you to find the artefact for him.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_a2_stalker_barmen_task_2_job_descr">
		<text>I deal in artefacts. I usually don't buy them from stalkers, but there is one in particular I would like to get my hands on. Do you want to try to get it for me?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_a2_stalker_barmen_task_2_fetch_job_descr">
		<text>I'm looking for the artefact. You ever seen one? If you can find it, I'll make sure you're well paid.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_a2_stalker_barmen_task_2_fetch_finish">
		<text>Good hunting, stalker! Have a drink on the house!</text>
	</string>


	<!-- ASSASSINATION FOR BEARD TASK -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_a2_stalker_barmen_task_3_title">
		<text>My Brother's Keeper</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_a2_stalker_barmen_task_3_descr">
		<text>Kill the Military Stalker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_a2_stalker_barmen_task_3_job_descr">
		<text>There's a guy; used to be a regular stalker just like anyone else on this ship. One day, some Military officers came and offered him a commission. The next thing we knew, he's found murdering his former brothers in cold blood! We cannot stand for that! Find this traitor and avenge the men he shot in the back.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_a2_stalker_barmen_task_3_finish">
		<text>Ah, you killed him? Help yourself to a drink. I'm sure we could all do with one...</text>
	</string>
	
<!-- Noah -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_task_noah_2_1">
		<text>Benefactor: get in the teleporter anomaly on the hill</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_task_noah_2_2">
		<text>Benefactor: clear out the mutant lair</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_task_noah_2_3">
		<text>Benefactor: tell Noah about the successful mission</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_task_noah_2_descr">
		<text>Snorks have been threatening Noah for a while. He wants me to clear out a lair at the southern plateau.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_task_noah_1_1">
		<text>Benefactor: help Noah get a new rifle</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_task_noah_1_2">
		<text>Benefactor: bring Noah an Armsel Protecta</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_task_noah_1_descr">
		<text>Noah wants my help getting an Armsel Protecta so that he can rest easy at night.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_stancia_trader_merc_task_bs_fetch_patches_title">
		<text>Collect patches</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_stancia_trader_merc_task_bs_fetch_patches_descr">
		<text>A mercenary has asked me to collect patches.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_stancia_trader_merc_task_bs_fetch_patches_job_descr">
		<text>You feel like arranging a real safari? You will hunt people and bring their patches. We will be raising the standards of the faction.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_stancia_trader_merc_task_bs_fetch_patches_finish">
		<text>That's what I'm talking about! Here's your money.</text>
	</string>

<!-- Axel (Loner Medic) -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_b22_stalker_medic_task_1_title">
		<text>Find drug-making kit for Axel</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_b22_stalker_medic_task_1_descr">
		<text>drug-making kit is required by Axel to work on medical supplies. You should bring them back to him if you find any.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_b22_stalker_medic_task_1_job_descr">
		<text>Maintaining what's left from medical supplies storage with this number of injuries I have to treat on daily basis is worrying. I'm gonna run out of bandages and medkits soon or later. I need you to find me one of those old drug-making kits. They will come in handy for sure.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_b22_stalker_medic_task_1_fetch_job_descr">
		<text>There is. I've been looking all over for a drug-making kit. It should contain some tablets and ampoules I need to do work on medical supplies. I'll pay you for one of these kits if you can bring a full set back to me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_b22_stalker_medic_task_1_fetch_finish">
		<text>Great job! I own you big time.</text>
	</string>
</string_table>
