<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Sidorovich (Loner Trader) Eliminate Car Park Bandits Task -->

	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_m_trader_task_1_title">
		<text>Assault the Car Park</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_m_trader_task_1_descr">
		<text>Stage an assault on the car park and eliminate the bandits that occupy the location.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_m_trader_task_1_job_descr">
		<text>Bandits have taken up base in the old car park. Those assholes mug or kill anyone who use the roads leading in and out of the camp. It's disrupting local activities for my clients and the stalkers who take refuge in camp. It's hurting business! I need you to 'take care' of them. Talk to Fanatic if you need any help.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_m_trader_task_1_finish">
		<text>Great work, stalker! You and I will be best of friends if you keep this up! Here is what I promised.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_m_trader_task_bs_kill_stalker_nearby_title">
		<text>Contract Killer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_m_trader_task_bs_kill_stalker_nearby_descr">
		<text>I've agreed to remove a thorn from Sidorovich's side. Once I'm done, I should return for my reward.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_m_trader_task_bs_kill_stalker_nearby_job_descr">
		<text>I have a list of outstanding bounties that need taking care of. These people tend to be unwanted plotters, frauds, slanderers... many of them have even roughed up my couriers or harassed my tourists in the past. In other words, they're all bad for business.\n \nPut one of these scumbags out of my misery, won't you? I'll be happy, the Zone will be a cleaner place, and you'll be well paid. Everyone wins!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_m_trader_task_bs_kill_stalker_nearby_finish">
		<text>You got rid of that filthy freak? Good riddance! Here is what I promised, and let it never be said that uncle Sidorovich doesn't reward good work.</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Sidorovich (Loner Trader) Decimate the Enemy Task -->

	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_m_trader_task_3_title">
		<text>Mobbing the Mob</text>
	</string>	
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_m_trader_task_3_descr">
		<text>Sidorovich wants to send the bandit leaders a message. I've agreed to help him out by collecting patches.</text>
	</string>		
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_m_trader_task_3_job_descr">
		<text>Listen, stalker. This is supposed to be a safe place for rookies to get to know the Zone. What they do get to know are the business ends of some bandit guns instead. The thugs disrupt our routes and steal our loot. Go teach them a lesson, will ya?</text>
	</string>		
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_m_trader_task_3_fetch_job_descr">
		<text>Recently, some dandy bandit lord, up in Dark Valley, has decided to make another move on my business.  He calls himself something stupid, like Sultana. What's next? Riesling? Muscadine?\n \nSo, let's send the bloated grape a message. Remind him who the real boss is. I know his men are skulking about - they usually make their way down to the Cordon through Darkscape or Meadow to harass the rookies and disrupt my routes. I'd like you to do me a favour and off a few of them. Then, bring me their patches, and I'll sort out the rest. </text>
	</string>		
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_m_trader_task_3_fetch_finish">
		<text>Finally, you're back. You've got the badges? All right, here is your reward. I'll handle the rest.</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Wolf (Loner Honcho) -->
	
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_bs_assault_monster_online_title">
		<text>Eliminate the Mutant Threat from Cordon</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_bs_assault_monster_online_descr">
		<text>I've agreed to clear out a mutant lair for Wolf, which will no doubt make life much easier for stalkers in Cordon. I'll need to return to him for payment once the job is complete.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_bs_assault_monster_online_job_descr">
		<text>Though this is the border of the Zone, newbies have it tough even here. The bandits are only half the problem - they at least understand Russian. But the mutants - it's really tough with them. If you're an able hunter, there's a mutant lair not far from here that needs to be cleared out. If you manage to do this, I'll owe you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_bs_assault_monster_online_finish">
		<text>Thank you, stalker. Maybe the rookies around here will take this chance to learn a thing or two before becoming pig food. Ah, right. I said I'd owe you. Here's your payment.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Wolf (Loner Honcho) Stalker Search and Rescue Dynamic Task -->

	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_2_title">
		<text>Rescue the Courier</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_2_descr">
		<text>One of Sidorovich's new couriers has been kidnapped by some brigands. I have agreed to rescue him and escort him back to Wolf.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_2_job_descr">
		<text>Another one of Sidorovich's new delivery men got caught up in some trouble, and I've been asked to organize his retrieval. I know where he's being held, but I need a competent fighter to free him from whatever band of scoundrels is holding him, and bring him back to camp safely. Will you do this? Otherwise, I'll need to go myself, and I don't want to leave the village only half-guarded.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_2_finish">
		<text>Good job, stalker. Sidorovich's man doesn't seem much worse for wear. Now it's time for him to square off some business with his boss. As for you, your job is done. Here's your reward. </text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Wolf (Loner Honcho) Stalker Guide Dynamic Task -->

	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_3_title">
		<text>Tourist Safari</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_3_descr">
		<text>Wolf has trusted me to guide some tourists on their mutant hunt.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_3_job_descr">
		<text>Some foreign tourists have paid Sidorovich good money to go on a light hunting trip through the Zone. They're actually not bad shots, but they don't know the first thing about anomalies or the kind of monsters we have around here. As if I wasn't babysitting enough people already.\n \nCould you be their guide? Nothing fancy - people like this are usually happy with a short stroll through Cordon with some shooting at the end. Just make sure they don't do anything stupid. It'd save me a little headache, and it's ample pay for simple work.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_3_finish">
		<text>Okay, looks like the tourists got what they asked for. Sidorovich will be pleased. As for you, here's your cut.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Nimble (Loner Trader) Find Weapon Task -->

	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_2_12_stalker_nimble_task_1_title">
		<text>Find the gun</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_2_12_stalker_nimble_task_1_descr">
		<text>Nimble has asked you to find a specific firearm. It needs to be in mint condition. Return to him when you find what he is looking for.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_2_12_stalker_nimble_task_1_job_descr">
		<text>I have a client looking for a specific firearm and I need someone to help me find it. If you are interested I will give you more details. What do you say?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_2_12_stalker_nimble_task_1_fetch_job_descr">
		<text>I need to find specific firearm, but it must be in mint condition. The client is paying top dollar, and he doesn't want a rusty piece of shit that will jam up in a life or death situation. I'll give you most of the profit since you are doing all the work. Come back when you find it, man.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_2_12_stalker_nimble_task_1_fetch_finish">
		<text>This is a fine weapon. I think my client will be pleased when I deliver this to him. Here is what I owe you.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Nimble (Loner Trader) Retrieve PDA Dynamic Task -->

	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_2_12_stalker_nimble_task_2_title">
		<text>Retrieve PDA for Nimble</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_2_12_stalker_nimble_task_2_descr">
		<text>Nimble has a PDA he needs retrieved.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_2_12_stalker_nimble_task_2_job_descr">
		<text>I need you to pick up a PDA for me. It's hidden in a spot a little while away from here.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_2_12_stalker_nimble_task_2_finish">
		<text>Thank you stalker!</text>
	</string>

	<!-- \\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\ -->

<!-- (Military Trader - Southern Outpost) -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_3_16_military_trader_task_bs_fetch_patches_title">
		<text>Cordon Crackdown</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_3_16_military_trader_task_bs_fetch_patches_descr">
		<text>The checkpoint commander, Major Zhurov, has asked me to bring patches. It should help remind stalkers who's in charge.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_3_16_military_trader_task_bs_fetch_patches_job_descr">
		<text>The top brass has launched an unofficial program, you wanna take part? As proof, I require patches from criminals in the Zone.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_3_16_military_trader_task_bs_fetch_patches_finish">
		<text>Your actions have gone above and beyond the call of duty. Here, take your commendation and be proud today.</text>
	</string>
	
<!-- Fanatic -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_2_12_stalker_fanat_task_bs_assault_monster_online_title">
		<text>Destroy the Mutant Lair</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_2_12_stalker_fanat_task_bs_assault_monster_online_descr">
		<text>I've agreed with Fanatic to destroy a mutant lair for the sake of the stalkers in Cordon.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_2_12_stalker_fanat_task_bs_assault_monster_online_job_descr">
		<text>Yeah, there's a small issue that needs sorting out. Cordon is supposed to be one of the safest places in the Zone, yet a new mutant lair has sprung up not too far from here. It needs to be cleared before it gets too large - otherwise, the rookies here will be in for a grave time. So, what do you say? Will you do it?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_2_12_stalker_fanat_task_bs_assault_monster_online_finish">
		<text>Great work. Thanks to you, the rookies will have more room to breathe without being thrown into the deep end. Here's your payment - they all contributed a little to it. </text>
	</string>

	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_2_12_stalker_fanat_task_2_title">
		<text>Find a Battery Artefact for Fanatic</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_2_12_stalker_fanat_task_2_descr">
		<text>Fanatic needs a Battery to help some of his old friends bribe their way out of the Zone.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_2_12_stalker_fanat_task_2_fetch_job_descr">
		<text>So, here's the deal. A lot of dirty work has to happen to keep this village unmolested by the local soldiers. Sidorovich keeps the village itself safe in this way, but I have a few friends who want to leave, and there isn't any real way out for them.\n \nThat's the thing with the military's border patrols - they're not too careful about keeping people from getting in. But they'd rather kill you in cold blood than let you get out. So, my friends are stuck here.\n \nThe checkpoint guards won't let them through alive unless we bribe them with a Battery artefact. Have you heard of it? They can be found in Electro anomalies.\n \nIt's incredibly rare. I've already sent every stalker I can to find one, but no one has gotten back to me yet. Will you help out too?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_esc_2_12_stalker_fanat_task_2_fetch_finish">
		<text>Ah, you've found a Battery? Excellent! I'll let my comrades know the good news. I'm going to miss them terribly, but I know they'll also get another chance at an ordinary life out there. Thank you, stalker.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- Seryoga --> 
	<string id="igi_task_text_army_south_mechan_mlr_task_4_job_descr">
		<text>Some jackass keeps shooting at the speaker, I have no idea if it's some stalker from the village or maybe even somebody in here. Anyway, I need some parts to repair it. Can you look for them?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_army_south_mechan_mlr_task_4_title">
		<text>Find the Repair Parts for Seryoga</text>
	</string>
	
</string_table>
