<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>

<!-- Butcher -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_hunter_gar_trader_task_bs_assault_monster_online_title">
		<text>Cull Hunting</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_hunter_gar_trader_task_bs_assault_monster_online_descr">
		<text>Butcher tracked down a mutant lair that needs clearing. I've agreed to do the dirty work of flushing it out.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_hunter_gar_trader_task_bs_assault_monster_online_job_descr">
		<text>Hmm. I've scouted out a mutant den that could do with clearing. It's starting to give local stalkers some trouble, but a well-prepared hunter shouldn't have any issue flushing it out. So, feel like some hunting today? I'll pay you for your skill, and you can sell me any meats or trophies you've collected once you get back.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_hunter_gar_trader_task_bs_assault_monster_online_finish">
		<text>Once again the local ecosystem is in balance... hehe. Here's your reward for a job well done.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="igi_task_text_hunter_gar_trader_task_2_title">
		<text>Find trophy for Butcher</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_hunter_gar_trader_task_2_descr">
		<text>The Butcher needs mutant part and has asked me to bring him some.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_hunter_gar_trader_task_2_job_descr">
		<text>Some people pay good money for mutant meat.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_hunter_gar_trader_task_2_fetch_job_descr">
		<text>On occasion, I cure mutant meats and send them off to Barkeep and other traders to help them supplement their imported food. Right now, I'm looking to prepare meat to send off wholesale. If you can bring me the raw goods for this, it'll mean some good cash in your pocket.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_hunter_gar_trader_task_2_fetch_finish">
		<text>Ah, brilliant! These meats may look disgusting now, but just you wait until they're prepared. They'll be delicious!</text>
	</string>

	
<!-- Flea Market -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_baraholka_trader_night_task_1_title">
		<text>Find the artefact</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_baraholka_trader_night_task_1_descr">
		<text>The trader at the flea market wants me to find an  artefact.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_baraholka_trader_night_task_1_job_descr">
		<text>You want to earn some loot looking for artefacts of the less common variety? I can offer you some good equipment.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_baraholka_trader_night_task_1_fetch_job_descr">
		<text>Feel like earning some loot while looking for rare artefacts? I can offer you some more stuff.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_baraholka_trader_night_task_1_fetch_finish">
		<text>Ah, great work, stalker. Here, for you.</text>
	</string>


</string_table>
