<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Cold (Clear Sky Honcho) Decimate the Enemy Task -->
	
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_smart_terrain_base_stalker_leader_marsh_task_bs_fetch_patches_title">
		<text>Great Swamp Clean-up</text>
	</string>	
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_smart_terrain_base_stalker_leader_marsh_task_bs_fetch_patches_descr">
		<text>Cold wants to root out Clear Sky's enemies from the Great Swamp. Collect patches.</text>
	</string>		
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_smart_terrain_base_stalker_leader_marsh_task_bs_fetch_patches_job_descr">
		<text>At first we were almost grateful that the military barged in on our bandit clean-up. Sadly, later they set up a few permanent outposts to the north. Their patrols aren't exactly friendly to our guys either, not to mention they did a shoddy job and there's a constant trickle of bandits harassing our outposts. Show them what we're made of.</text>
	</string>		
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_smart_terrain_base_stalker_leader_marsh_task_bs_fetch_patches_finish">
		<text>Here you are, our professional hitman. I suppose those bastards will think twice before they dare visit our Swamp again. I hope. Here's your reward, by the way.</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Cold (Clear Sky Honcho) Night Terror Task -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_smart_terrain_base_stalker_leader_marsh_task_2_title">
		<text>Night Terror</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_smart_terrain_base_stalker_leader_marsh_task_2_descr">
		<text>Cold wants to eliminate a dangerous mutant which roams not far away from the Hidden Base.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_smart_terrain_base_stalker_leader_marsh_task_2_job_descr">
		<text>Mutants rarely stray close to our base. But our guys reported that the previous night some giant beast tore apart the whole team that manned the lookout tower to the north west. Four well-armed people just smeared all over the perimeter. Those weren't dogs for sure. I know you're a tough guy, so maybe you could visit the place and get rid of that nasty fucker?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_smart_terrain_base_stalker_leader_marsh_task_2_finish">
		<text>Hey, great job, man! I hope this reward's good enough for you. That and the stories people'll tell.</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Cold (Clear Sky Honcho) FDefend the pump station Task -->

	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_smart_terrain_base_stalker_leader_marsh_task_4_title">
		<text>Defend the pump station</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_smart_terrain_base_stalker_leader_marsh_task_4_descr">
		<text>One of our patrols captured some bandits fucking around the pump station, after a good beating they confessed they're preparing an assault. We don't know when they'll hit, I already sent some guys over there but any help is welcome... and rewarded of course.</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Kalancha (Clear Sky Medic) Lost to the Zone Tasks -->
	
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_smart_terrain_base_doctor_task_1_title">
		<text>Unnatural Selection</text>
	</string>	
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_smart_terrain_base_doctor_task_1_descr">
		<text>Collect mutant parts samples for Professor Kalancha.</text>
	</string>		
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_smart_terrain_base_doctor_task_1_job_descr">
		<text>Mutants of the Zone have displayed numerous peculiar adaptations to its anomalous conditions. Please, collect some tissue samples for my research. They might help us persevere in this environment as well.</text>
	</string>		
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_smart_terrain_base_doctor_task_1_fetch_job_descr">
		<text>Mutants of the Zone have displayed numerous peculiar adaptations to its anomalous conditions. Please, collect some tissue samples for my research. They might help us persevere in this environment as well. Collect mutant parts samples.</text>
	</string>	
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_smart_terrain_base_doctor_task_1_fetch_finish">
		<text>The samples are in good condition. Very well, I will get to research immediately. Thank you.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_smart_terrain_base_doctor_task_2_title">
		<text>Scientific Progress</text>
	</string>	
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_smart_terrain_base_doctor_task_2_descr">
		<text>Find one artefact for Professor Kalancha.</text>
	</string>		
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_smart_terrain_base_doctor_task_2_job_descr">
		<text>Artefacts may provide invaluable data for our research. However, with the many threats we face our men cannot really afford to collect them for me all that often. Could you help me?</text>
	</string>		
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_smart_terrain_base_doctor_task_2_fetch_job_descr">
		<text>Artefacts may provide invaluable data for our research. However, with the many threats we face our men cannot really afford to collect them for me all that often. Could you help me? Find one artefact.</text>
	</string>	
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_smart_terrain_base_doctor_task_2_fetch_finish">
		<text>Even after all these years they never cease to amaze me. What a wonderful specimen. Thank you for your assistance.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_smart_terrain_base_doctor_task_3_title">
		<text>Scarce Supplies</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_smart_terrain_base_doctor_task_3_descr">
		<text>Professor Kalancha requires a medical supplies</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_smart_terrain_base_doctor_task_3_job_descr">
		<text>You see, Spore does his best to provide supplies for us. But even after all these years we are still in a difficult situation. There is no shortage of injuries to treat but our medical supplies are limited. Please, help me supplement our stock.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_smart_terrain_base_doctor_task_3_fetch_job_descr">
		<text>You see, Spore does his best to provide supplies for us. But even after all these years we are still in a difficult situation. There is no shortage of injuries to treat but our medical supplies are limited. Please, help me supplement our stock. Procure some medical supplies, please.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_smart_terrain_base_doctor_task_3_fetch_finish">
		<text>We are all deeply indebted for your help.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_smart_terrain_base_doctor_task_5_title">
		<text>Find medical supplies for Professor Kalancha</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_smart_terrain_base_doctor_task_5_descr">
		<text>%s is required by Professor Kalancha to work on medical supplies. You should bring them back to him if you find any.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_smart_terrain_base_doctor_task_5_job_descr">
		<text>Maintaining what's left from medical supplies storage with this number of injuries I have to treat on daily basis is worrying. I'm gonna run out of bandages and medkits soon or later. I need you to find me one of those old drug-making kits. They will come in handy for sure.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_smart_terrain_base_doctor_task_5_fetch_job_descr">
		<text>There is. I've been looking all over for a drug-making kit. It should contain some tablets and ampoules I need to do work on medical supplies. I'll pay you for one of these kits if you can bring a full set back to me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_smart_terrain_base_doctor_task_5_fetch_finish">
		<text>Great job! I own you big time.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Spore (Clear Sky Trader) Deliver PDA Task -->

	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_base_owl_stalker_trader_task_1_title">
		<text>Deliver PDA to Nimble</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_base_owl_stalker_trader_task_1_descr">
		<text>Spore needs you to deliver an encrypted PDA to Nimble in Zaton.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_base_owl_stalker_trader_task_1_job_descr">
		<text>Okay, hotshot. Need a job? This PDA needs delivered to a dude who hangs out in Zaton; his name is Nimble. He will compensate you on delivery. Don't drop it in a puddle or some dumb shit like that... or I'll have your ass. While you're there, check out what he has to offer; he can get his hands on some nice equipment... for a price.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- DESTROY HELICOPTER FOR SPORE TASK -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_base_owl_stalker_trader_task_2_title">
		<text>Destroy the helicopter</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_base_owl_stalker_trader_task_2_descr">
		<text>Spore is fed up and wants you to destroy the helicopter. He will offer you a discount if you follow through.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_base_owl_stalker_trader_task_2_job_descr">
		<text>That damn chopper is driving me nuts. I have bad tinnitus, and every time that fucking thing is patrolling the southern border, it makes my ears scream! Makes me want to bludgeon a baby flesh! Down the fucking thing and I'll give you a discount, please, before I get somebody killed.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ESCORT SCIENTISTS FOR CLEAR SKY TASK -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_base_owl_stalker_trader_task_3_title">
		<text>Escort the Ecologists</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_base_owl_stalker_trader_task_3_descr">
		<text>Clear Sky scientists have hired you to guide them to a specific location for study. Once their research has been successfully conducted, return them safely to camp; where you will be compensated.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_base_owl_stalker_trader_task_3_job_descr">
		<text>Scientists here in camp need an experienced stalker to lead them out into the field for study. Are you up for it? Your job is to keep them alive and guide them to their destination. Failure will give you a bad reputation around here.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_base_owl_stalker_trader_task_3_finish">
		<text>Thank you, stalker. You may have this as payment for your services.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- HUNT MUTANTS FOR CLEAR SKY TASK -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_base_stalker_barmen_task_bs_assault_monster_online_title">
		<text>Clear area of mutants</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_base_stalker_barmen_task_bs_assault_monster_online_descr">
		<text>Mutants have been spotted near this location making the area dangerous for some of the locals. You have been tasked to eliminate the mutant threat within the area. Report back to Librarian after the job is done.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_base_stalker_barmen_task_bs_assault_monster_online_job_descr">
		<text>Are you an avid hunter? We've been looking for someone to keep the marshes a bit safer by clearing out mutants in areas that our faction frequents. Would you like the job?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_base_stalker_barmen_task_bs_assault_monster_online_finish">
		<text>Fantastic! Here is your payment. I'll make sure to pass the word around that it's safe there once again. Thank you, stalker.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ASSAULT BANDIT CAMP FOR CLEAR SKY TASK -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_base_stalker_barmen_task_2_title">
		<text>Assault the bandit camp</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_base_stalker_barmen_task_2_descr">
		<text>You have been tasked to eliminate the bandit threat within the area. Report back to Librarian after the job is done.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_base_stalker_barmen_task_2_job_descr">
		<text>We have a big problem with bandits in the area. Those murderous thugs have been ambushing our camps outside the main base, trying to take the territory over. It'll deny us passage through many safe routes through the marshes as long as they're in the area. We need an experienced stalker who is not afraid to get his hands dirty. Will you help us out?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_base_stalker_barmen_task_2_finish">
		<text>Fantastic! Here is your payment. I'll make sure to pass the word around that it's safe there once again. Thank you, stalker.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- FIND MUTANT MEAT FOR CLEAR SKY TASK -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_base_stalker_barmen_task_3_title">
		<text>Procure mutant parts</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_base_stalker_barmen_task_3_descr">
		<text>Field dress freshly dead mutants to collect game meat. Then deliver some mutant meat to Librarian in the Clear Sky base camp.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_base_stalker_barmen_task_3_job_descr">
		<text>If you are good with a rifle and not afraid of a few mutants, then I have a job for you. Are you interested?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_base_stalker_barmen_task_3_fetch_job_descr">
		<text>Rations are running low, and I need to keep everyone in camp's bellies full. Some of the guys bring me back a kill or two every now and again. But it's been slow lately... So if you aren't too busy and you are out and about, I need meat. I kill and process the meat, right here in my kitchen. Keep in mind that getting the mutants all riled up makes the meat tough because of the adrenaline. Also, the lesser the bleeding, the better the meat tastes. So, just be careful with your shots, okay?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_mar_base_stalker_barmen_task_3_fetch_finish">
		<text>Great, you are a good hunter after all! I have payment for you.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ESCORT SCIENTISTS DIALOGS -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_ecolog_companion_task_1_start_dialog_1">
		<text>You are our guide? I will mark the location on your PDA. Lead the way, and we will follow. After we complete our analysis escort us back safely. Speak to me again when we return to camp.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_ecolog_companion_task_1_start_dialog_2">
		<text>Yes? We should get moving. The longer we wait around, the more dangerous it gets.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_ecolog_companion_task_1_complete">
		<text>Thank you, stalker. You did your job well. Here is your payment.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_ecolog_companion_task_1_actor_reply">
		<text>Okay.</text>
	</string>
</string_table>
