<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Kuznetsov (Military Honcho) Stop Unauthorized Incursions Task -->

	<string id="igi_task_text_agr_smart_terrain_1_6_near_2_military_colonel_kovalski_task_bs_assault_stalker_online_title">
		<text>Under the Rug</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_agr_smart_terrain_1_6_near_2_military_colonel_kovalski_task_bs_assault_stalker_online_descr">
		<text>Colonel Kuznetsov has asked me to terminate a group of stalkers at the marked location.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_agr_smart_terrain_1_6_near_2_military_colonel_kovalski_task_bs_assault_stalker_online_job_descr">
		<text>There's one delicate matter. The presence of illegals near our base is not advantageous for our future operations. The assignment is this: any authorized personnel or Duty forces you find at the marked location are allowed to go free, but otherwise all those present must be terminated, no matter what agreements they think they have with us. Do you understand? </text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_agr_smart_terrain_1_6_near_2_military_colonel_kovalski_task_bs_assault_stalker_online_finish">
		<text>Great job. Keep it up, and you'll be in line for a commendation.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Kuznetsov (Military Honcho) Capture Territory Task -->

	<string id="igi_task_text_agr_smart_terrain_1_6_near_2_military_colonel_kovalski_task_2_title">
		<text>Peer Punishment</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_agr_smart_terrain_1_6_near_2_military_colonel_kovalski_task_2_descr">
		<text>I have been ordered by the Military to retaliate against a site where Ecologists were attacked.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_agr_smart_terrain_1_6_near_2_military_colonel_kovalski_task_2_job_descr">
		<text>Lately, there's been an increase in illegal stalking activities in the Zone. One such criminal group has attacked some of our scientists. The individuals who perpetrated this despicable act may have disappeared, but there will be punishment nonetheless. Go to the scene of the attack, and enforce martial law on any stalkers camping there. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_agr_smart_terrain_1_6_near_2_military_colonel_kovalski_task_2_finish">
		<text>The task is done? Good job. Maybe now they'll think twice before interfering with the business of our civillians.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Kuznetsov (Military Honcho) Capture Enemy Combatant Task -->

	<string id="igi_task_text_agr_smart_terrain_1_6_near_2_military_colonel_kovalski_task_bs_kill_stalker_nearby_title">
		<text>Martial Justice</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_agr_smart_terrain_1_6_near_2_military_colonel_kovalski_task_bs_kill_stalker_nearby_descr">
		<text>The Zone is a popular haven for all manner of scum and villainy. Colonel Kuznetsov has singled out a target for me to execute.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_agr_smart_terrain_1_6_near_2_military_colonel_kovalski_task_bs_kill_stalker_nearby_job_descr">
		<text>The SSU keeps me furnished with a list of its most-wanted targets. Some of them are known spies or enemy tacticians. Others - I'm ashamed to say - are deserters, dishonourable insects who have abandoned their comrades-in-arms.  And others still are little better than common scum - criminals from the outside world who fled into the Zone to escape justice. The exact crime committed doesn't matter. What matters is one such target has made himself vulnerable. If you are willing to be his executioner, you can expect a bonus in your next paycheck. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_agr_smart_terrain_1_6_near_2_military_colonel_kovalski_task_bs_kill_stalker_nearby_finish">
		<text>Outstanding work! The ministers at Internal Affairs will be pleased.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Kuznetsov (Military Honcho) Tight Security Task -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_agr_smart_terrain_1_6_near_2_military_colonel_kovalski_task_bs_fetch_patches_title">
		<text>Tight Security</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_agr_smart_terrain_1_6_near_2_military_colonel_kovalski_task_bs_fetch_patches_descr">
		<text>Colonel Kuznetsov is running a competition to keep his troops sharp. I can take part by collecting patches, which I can then turn in for a reward.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_agr_smart_terrain_1_6_near_2_military_colonel_kovalski_task_bs_fetch_patches_job_descr">
		<text>Some of my friends among the top brass have launched an unofficial program. Guard duty gets dull as the months turn into years. So, to keep everyone sharp, the men will be sent out on patrol more often, and the first squad out of each platoon to come back with enough patches is entitled to a reward. If you're interested, you're more than welcome to take part yourself.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_agr_smart_terrain_1_6_near_2_military_colonel_kovalski_task_bs_fetch_patches_finish">
		<text>Hm, let me count the patches... well done, soldier. You've earned this prize.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="igi_task_text_agr_smart_terrain_1_6_near_2_military_colonel_kovalski_task_5_title">
		<text>Collect Expedition Reports</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_agr_smart_terrain_1_6_near_2_military_colonel_kovalski_task_5_descr">
		<text>I've been tasked by Colonel Kuznetsov to bring some mysterious reports back to base.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_agr_smart_terrain_1_6_near_2_military_colonel_kovalski_task_5_job_descr">
		<text>Our contact in Cordon has sent us vital information regarding stalker activity in the surrounding areas. You'll need to proceed to the dead drop location I'll highlight on your PDA, extract the documents you find within, then report back immediately. It is not glorious work, but it's a decent commission for minimal risk. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_agr_smart_terrain_1_6_near_2_military_colonel_kovalski_task_5_finish">
		<text>Excellent job, soldier. If you glanced at the contents, I hope for your sake you won't go blabbing about them to anyone else.</text>
	</string>

<!-- (Military Medic) -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_agr_1_6_medic_army_mlr_task_1_title">
		<text>Find Drug-making kit for Lt. Rogovets</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_agr_1_6_medic_army_mlr_task_1_descr">
		<text>Drug-making kit is required by Lt. Rogovets to work expand his selection of medical supplies. I should bring them back to him if I find any.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_agr_1_6_medic_army_mlr_task_1_job_descr">
		<text>We're short on medical supplies and our next bird will not be dropping by any time soon. However, I heard that some stalkers and traders started smuggling those drug-making kits in the Zone. They will come in handy for sure. Will you help me out?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_agr_1_6_medic_army_mlr_task_1_fetch_job_descr">
		<text>There is.  While I can treat the men at base just fine, my ability to keep them supplied while they're out in the field is limited. So, I've been trying to requisition a Drug-making kit. It'll let me prepare medicine for almost any potential threat or injury a soldier could encounter while out on patrol.\n \nOr at least, it would, but my request keeps getting postponed. Every second could save a life, so my proposition is this: if you find a decent kit, I'll pay you out of my own wallet for it, no fuss. Just bring one to me as soon as you can. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_agr_1_6_medic_army_mlr_task_1_fetch_finish">
		<text>You managed to find a decent kit? Let me see. Oh, wow. This'll be good. I expect the survival rate of our patrols to increase dramatically from today. </text>
	</string>
</string_table>
