<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Sultan (Bandit Honcho) Mob Hit Task -->

	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_bs_kill_stalker_nearby_title">
		<text>Mob Hit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_bs_kill_stalker_nearby_descr">
		<text>Sultan has sent me to eliminate some bum, then return for my payment.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_bs_kill_stalker_nearby_job_descr">
		<text>See this list? This is a list of rats I need exterminated.\n \n...Cheapskates who chose to cut and run rather than pay their debts.\n \n...Misers who answered with bullets when my boys begged them for bread.\n \n...Bitches and traitors that left Dark Valley to kowtow to Rostok or Sidorovich.\n \nThey can all go fuck themselves. Here; a name off my list. I'd like you to let me know when I can cross it out.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_bs_kill_stalker_nearby_finish">
		<text>Ah, cold satisfaction. I like it when shit goes down smoothly. Here, a token of my gratitude.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Sultan (Bandit Honcho) Eliminate Military Presence Dynamic Task -->

	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_2_title">
		<text>Eliminate the Military Presence</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_2_descr">
		<text>Sultan wants me to eliminate a nearby Military patrol before they do something stupid.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_2_job_descr">
		<text>Those Military fucks are creeping around here again. Most likely to harass our tenants, or take another crack at the nearby lab...\n \n...morons. Those bitches are already dead men walking, but I'll pay you remove them before their idiocy hurts anyone I know.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_2_finish">
		<text>You've impressed me, stalker. Wish more of the boys around here had your spunk.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Sultan (Bandit Honcho) Stalker Elimination Dynamic Task -->

	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_3_title">
		<text>Stalker Elimination</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_3_descr">
		<text>Sultan has sent me to enact vengeance on some stalkers that harassed one of his boys.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_3_job_descr">
		<text>Alright, listen up. A group of stalkers tried to gang up on one of my boys not too long ago. Luckily he escaped, and is busy recovering in the medical hangar, but we can't let that kind of disrespect go.\n \nYou might need to round up your own posse before you take them on, but these guys tried to massacre my boy. Show them what happens to chucklefucks who try that.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_3_finish">
		<text>Done? ...Good.</text>
	</string>
	
	
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_bs_fetch_patches_title">
		<text>Collect patches</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_bs_fetch_patches_descr">
		<text>Sultan asked me to collect patches</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_bs_fetch_patches_job_descr">
		<text>It's time to remind those retards who the bandits really are. I've got a good mind as to how we'll do this; just tear off their patches and bring them to me, and I'll handle the rest.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_bs_fetch_patches_finish">
		<text>Got them? Great work! Here's your payout.</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Sultan (Bandit Honcho) Unwelcome in the Hood Task -->
	
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_5_title">
		<text>Eviction Notice</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_5_descr">
		<text>Sultan wants me to drive off the squatters on his farm.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_5_job_descr">
		<text>Here's a job for you; some squatters have moved into my farm down south. They refuse to pay rent, and are even scaring prospective tenants away. This simply won't do. Go take some guys and politely escort them out, won't you?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_5_finish">
		<text>So they tried to pay you with bullets, huh? Typical free loaders. As for you, here's your props.</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Sultan (Bandit Honcho) Night Terror Task -->
	
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_6_title">
		<text>Night Terror</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_6_descr">
		<text>Sultan wants me to get rid of a dangerous monster.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_6_job_descr">
		<text>Another nightmare has managed to worm its way out of the local lab. Tore up of the younger boys real good. I'll give you its last known location. Go find it and kick its ass.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_zat_b7_bandit_boss_sultan_task_6_finish">
		<text>Maybe that'll teach those dumb mutants not to mess with us. Anyway, here's your reward.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Olivius (Bandit Trader) Eliminate Mutants Task- -->

	<string id="igi_task_text_val_smart_terrain_7_4_bandit_trader_stalker_task_bs_assault_monster_online_title">
		<text>Eliminate Mutant Threat in Dark Valley</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_val_smart_terrain_7_4_bandit_trader_stalker_task_bs_assault_monster_online_descr">
		<text>Olivius has sent me to do some housecleaning. I should return to him for payment once I've cleared the mutants off the marked area.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_val_smart_terrain_7_4_bandit_trader_stalker_task_bs_assault_monster_online_job_descr">
		<text>Yeah, stalkers aren't moving in as often anymore. Why? Because they see the mutants, shit themselves, then leave. If this keeps happening, we won't be able to collect rent, borrow goods... you get the picture? It's time to give the Valley a spring clean.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_val_smart_terrain_7_4_bandit_trader_stalker_task_bs_assault_monster_online_finish">
		<text>Fantastic! Here is your payment. I'll make sure to put a good word in for you with the boss.</text>
	</string>



	<string id="igi_task_text_val_smart_terrain_7_4_bandit_trader_stalker_task_bs_assault_stalker_online_title">
		<text>Turf War</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_val_smart_terrain_7_4_bandit_trader_stalker_task_bs_assault_stalker_online_descr">
		<text>I've agreed to stick up a stalker camp for Olivius. He mentioned that I might need to bring friends.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_val_smart_terrain_7_4_bandit_trader_stalker_task_bs_assault_stalker_online_job_descr">
		<text>This one is a real cinch. Sultan's got a mind to shake down a nearby stalker camp; shake things up, remind them who's in charge around here. You'll need to get your own little gang together for this, but there's big props in it for you if you can pull it off.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_val_smart_terrain_7_4_bandit_trader_stalker_task_bs_assault_stalker_online_finish">
		<text>Ha! Well done! I hope you stripped off all the loot you could; here's a little extra from me.</text>
	</string>



	<string id="igi_task_text_val_smart_terrain_7_4_bandit_trader_stalker_task_3_title">
		<text>Chiki-Briki i v Damke</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_val_smart_terrain_7_4_bandit_trader_stalker_task_3_descr">
		<text>I've been hired to guide a bandit gang around as they "borrow" from local stalkers.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_val_smart_terrain_7_4_bandit_trader_stalker_task_3_job_descr">
		<text>There are a few guys who've been needing someone to take them shopping, if you catch my drift. Scout out some prime targets for them, and you'll get a nice cut when the job is done.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_val_smart_terrain_7_4_bandit_trader_stalker_task_3_finish">
		<text>Nice take, eh? Here is your cut.</text>
	</string>


	<!-- ASSASSINATION FOR OLIVIUS TASK -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_val_smart_terrain_7_4_bandit_trader_stalker_task_bs_kill_stalker_nearby_title">
		<text>Hit Man</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_val_smart_terrain_7_4_bandit_trader_stalker_task_bs_kill_stalker_nearby_descr">
		<text>Olivius has contracted me to run a hit on some poor sucker, then return for payment.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_val_smart_terrain_7_4_bandit_trader_stalker_task_bs_kill_stalker_nearby_job_descr">
		<text>I've got a list of people who've rubbed me the wrong way. I want you to rub one of them out. What do you say?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_val_smart_terrain_7_4_bandit_trader_stalker_task_bs_kill_stalker_nearby_finish">
		<text>Good, you got rid of that asshole! Here is what I promised.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- \\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\ -->
	<!-- (Bandit Medic) -->
	<string id="igi_task_text_bandit_main_base_medic_mlr_task_1_title">
		<text>Find Drug-making kit for the Bandit medic in Dark Valley</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_bandit_main_base_medic_mlr_task_1_descr">
		<text>Drug-making kit is required by the bandits medic to work on medical supplies. I should bring them back to him if I find any.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_bandit_main_base_medic_mlr_task_1_job_descr">
		<text>Maintaining what's left from medical supplies storage with this number of injuries I have to treat on daily basis is worrying. I'm gonna run out of bandages and medkits soon or later. I need you to find me one of those old drug-making kits. They will come in handy for sure.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_bandit_main_base_medic_mlr_task_1_fetch_job_descr">
		<text>There is. I've been looking all over for a Drug-making kit. It should contain some tablets and ampoules I need to do work on medical supplies. I'll pay you for one of these kits if you can bring a full set back to me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="igi_task_text_bandit_main_base_medic_mlr_task_1_fetch_finish">
		<text>Great job! I owe you big time.</text>
	</string>

</string_table>
