<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>

<!--
	Devices
-->

<string_table>

	<string id="st_pda_name">
		<text>PDA</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_pda_descr">
		<text>PDA with information about the Zone, digital logs, detailed maps of the Zone and locations of anomalies. Trading value could be high if you find the right buyer.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] low electric power consumption\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_pda_1_name">
		<text>PDA</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_pda_1_descr">
		<text>A pocket-sized electronic device meant to encompass the basic and most vital functions of a computer. The PDA is essential for daily information sharing. It comes with pre-installed GPS module to provide geolocation and time information to the user.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] low electric power consumption\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_pda_2_name">
		<text>PDA (Version 2.0) with KilTrak™</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_pda_2_descr">
		<text>A pocket-sized electronic device meant to encompass the basic and most vital functions of a computer. The PDA is essential for daily information sharing. It comes with pre-installed GPS module to provide geolocation and time information to the user. The module in this version has been improved to retrieve and process the position of other modules connected to the network in a radius of 300 meters, which makes this PDA compelling among stalkers.\n 
		\nThis particular device is also able to locate the dead bodies of targets eliminated by the owner because somebody has jailbroken it and installed a pirated version of IMI KilTrak software.\n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] low electric power consumption\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] shows location of nearby squads from your group.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_pda_3_name">
		<text>PDA (Version 3.1)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_pda_3_descr">
		<text>A pocket-sized electronic device meant to encompass the basic and most vital functions of a computer. The PDA is essential for daily information sharing. It comes with pre-installed GPS module to provide geolocation and time information to the user. The module in this version has been greatly improved to retrieve and process the position of other modules connected to the network, which makes this PDA compelling among stalkers. Unlike usual GPS modules, this one relies on sets of codes that allows the module to acquire special privileges on the connected channel to acquire more information.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] low electric power consumption\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] shows location of nearby natural squads.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_detector1">
		<text>Echo detector</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_detector1_descr">
		<text>This dated anomalous activity detector produces an alarm signal when anomalous particles enter a special chamber as you approach an anomaly. It can also register the presence of artefacts and measure the distance to the nearest one. The distance is indicated by the frequency of the sound the detector emits. To switch to artefact search mode, open the device's front cover. Due to its simple design, Echo can only be used to locate the most common artefacts.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2]  moderate electric power consumption\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_detector2">
		<text>Bear detector</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_detector2_descr">
		<text>This last generation anomalous activity detector can be used to locate anomalous formations and has a colour diode panel, which not only indicates the direction of artefacts, but also measures the distance to them. To switch to artefact search mode, open the device's front cover. Unfortunately, the device is programmed with a somewhat outdated list of detectable artefacts.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] moderate electric power consumption\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_detector3">
		<text>Veles detector</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_detector3_descr">
		<text>A next generation scientific detection scanner. Thanks to three modernised detection chambers, the position of artefacts is shown on a special display screen. When closed, the device registers only radiation and anomalies. To switch to artefact search mode, open the front LED display. When in search mode, the detector is capable of locating all artefacts known to science.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] high electric power consumption\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_detector4">
		<text>Svarog detector</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_detector4_descr">
		<text>A prototype of an expanded functionality anomalous frequency scanner. This device comes with a program used to identify static areas of anomalous activity stored in its database, while retaining the ability to locate artefacts. The position of anomalous areas and artefacts is displayed on a special screen. The artefact search mode, which can be activated by opening the front LED display, has been modified to detect anomalous formations currently unknown to science.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] high electric power consumption\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_detector9">
		<text>RF receiver</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_detector9_descr">
		<text>RF (Radio frequencies) receiver is a small device with a highly-sensitive RF module used for basic communications. Quite common among soldiers despite the old technology. As the name suggests, it has the ability to interact with radio signals in a radius of 200 m. The device is able to process radio waves with a frequency range between 30 and 300 MHz.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] moderate electric power consumption\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_detector8">
		<text>Anomalous measurement device</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_detector8_descr">
		<text>The first prototype has been designed in 2008 under Professor Sakharov's supervision in the mobile lab in Yantar. More copies has been made after proven success in study fields. This device is able to take and record measurements of anomalous fields. The improved framework and sensors guarantees operation even in hostile environments. High sensitivity during acquisition or while tracking allows for use in many different environments and under toughest operating conditions.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] moderate electric power consumption\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_broken_pda">
		<text>Broken PDA</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_broken_pda_descr">
		<text>This PDA seems badly damaged, half the screen is broken and the GPS module doesn't work properly. The interior remained safe for the most part.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_device_torch_name">
		<text>Headlamp</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_device_torch_descr">
		<text>A standard head-mounted flashlight in fully working order. Useful for stalkers who find themselves out and about after dark, but may attract trouble if used unwisely.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] moderate electric power consumption\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_device_torch_nv_1_name">
		<text>Headlamp w/ 1PN93-1 Nightvision\n
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_device_torch_nv_1_descr">
		<text>A standard head-mounted flashlight in fully working order. Useful for stalkers who find themselves out and about after dark, but may attract trouble if used unwisely. This head lamp comes with a standard-issue 1PN93-1 Russian Military Forces night-vision device. Offers generation 2+ image intensification, especially useful for operations at night or in low-light conditions.\n \n
		%c[d_orange]- Long press the "On" button to turn your NVG on\n
		- Short presses on the "On" button will adjust the NVG brightness\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] nightvision: %c[ui_gray_1]1PN93-1.\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] moderate electric power consumption\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_device_torch_nv_2_name">
		<text>Headlamp w/ PN21KL Nightvision\n
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_device_torch_nv_2_descr">
		<text>A standard head-mounted flashlight in fully working order. Useful for stalkers who find themselves out and about after dark, but may attract trouble if used unwisely. This head lamp comes with an IIT generation 2+ image intensification, intended for operation at night under natural illumination and in the complete darkness with the switched on infrared illuminator.\n \n
		%c[d_orange]- Long press the "On" button to turn your NVG on\n
		- Short presses on the "On" button will adjust the NVG brightness\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] nightvision: %c[ui_gray_1]PN21KL.\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] moderate electric power consumption\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_device_torch_nv_3_name">
		<text>Headlamp w/ Oracle psy-stimulator</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_device_torch_nv_3_descr">
		<text>A standard head-mounted flashlight in fully working order. Useful for stalkers who find themselves out and about after dark, but may attract trouble if used unwisely. This head lamp has an electric powerate of lenses and image-processing software that removes video noise and enhances image-intensifying capabilities of PN21K unit, thus making it a full-fledged IIT generation 3+ night vision device.\n \n
		%c[d_orange]- Long press the "On" button to turn your NVG on\n
		- Short presses on the "On" button will adjust the NVG brightness\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] nightvision: %c[ui_gray_1]Oracle.\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] moderate electric power consumption\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_device_flashlight">
		<text>Flashlight</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_device_flashlight_descr">
		<text>A general-purpose hand-held flashlight. Unfortunately, it cannot be used along most of the weaponry since it requires a free hand. Thus is can be simultaneously used only with pistols and other single-handed equipment.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] moderate electric power consumption\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_batteries_dead">
		<text>Old batteries</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_batteries_dead_descr">
		<text>Only one out of ten batteries found in the Zone still carry some juice. Stalkers seem to throw them out when they're depleted since it's almost impossible to find a battery recharger. Their outer layer is corroded and covered in dirt, which is a strong indication that these are almost dead. Still, like everything in the Zone they also have their purpose and may prove useful for frequent electric power recharges.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_batteries">
		<text>Battery pack</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_batteries_descr">
		<text>A pack of batteries. Someone must have used them since they are already half drained. Intended for use in your flashlight, PDA, nightvision goggles and other electronic devices. Remember to change regularly.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_batteries_ccell">
		<text>Military battery unit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_batteries_ccell_descr">
		<text>A pack of fully charged military batteries. Very valuable and in high demand due to the relative scarcity of batteries in the Zone. Used by all factions and Zoners of all levels, from rookies to master stalkers. Supplied to traders by corrupt military officers trying to earn some extra dough in the Zone.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_geiger_dead">
		<text>Geiger counter</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_geiger_dead_descr">
		<text>A Geiger counter measures ionising (radioactive) radiation. It detects the emission of alpha particles, beta particles and gamma particles. Invented in 1908, Geiger counters remain popular technological object used for measurements in health, physics, industry, geology and other fields of activity. Made of simple electronic circuits.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological device \n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] measures the level of radioactive contamination\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] moderate electric power consumption\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] operates in 3 modes\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_electric power">
		<text>Universal Power Device (electric power)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_electric power_descr">
		<text>Cold War era power unit about the size of a small walkie-talkie. Accepts almost any type of batteries. Utilises every bit of energy from inserted batteries and supplies electronic devices with power in an enhanced stream through a set of micro wires. These can be connected to any piece of equipment, regardless of its complexity or age. Allows stalkers to use and handle numerous electronic devices even if they have only one battery.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] portable energy source\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] supports most modern devices\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] accepts all battery types\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] storage capacity 
		%c[ui_gray_1]3 Ah (ampere-hours)\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="extension_pda">
		<text>Multimedia PDA</text>
	</string>
	<string id="exten_sion_pda">
		<text>An expensive moisture- and shock-resistant PDA, featuring a chat client and an integrated music player.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] allows for playback of music and interaction in the stalker network\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_gps_tracker">
		<text>Military GPS module</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_gps_tracker_descr">
		<text>A prototype of the next generation of GPS navigation devices. Only few copies are made. Distributed among the highest military ranks exclusively, although some of these have been leaked out to other sides. The improved module guarantees operation even in hostile environments. High sensitivity during acquisition or while tracking allows for use in many different environments and under toughest operating conditions. Unlike usual GPS modules, this one relies on sets of codes that allows the module to acquire special privileges on the connected channel. It retrieves the position of other connected modules in a radius of 300 meters. On the other hand, this module consumes a considerable amount of electrical power while operating. An automatic switching circuit is included inside the module to turn it off after 20 seconds of continuous scanning.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] very high electric power consumption\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_musicplayer">
		<text>Radio</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_musicplayer_desc">
		<text>A modified radio, designed to be able to communicate with other radios yet filter out as much interference as possible. \n \n%c[ui_gray_2]PROPERTIES:\n \n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] Technological Item\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_weather_radar">
		<text>Doppler weather radar kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_weather_radar_descr">
		<text>An advanced pulse-Doppler weather radar mini-kit. This kit considered as a miracle in meteorology field. It sends directional pulses of microwave radiation, on the order of a microsecond long, using a cavity magnetron connected by a waveguide to a parabolic antenna to collect weather data.\n
		Two scientists found out that using Meatchunk artefact near the antenna can greatly amplify the pulse power, to the point it alters the ions in the Troposphere layer of the atmoshphere and completely change its properties.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] meteorology equipment\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] powerd by a Meatchunk artefact\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_dosimeter_mode">
		<text>Dosimeter Mode</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_actor_rads">
		<text>Body Radiation</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_environment_rads">
		<text>Environmental Radiation</text>
	</string>
</string_table>