<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
	<string id="ls_header">
		<text>S.T.A.L.K.E.R. G.A.M.M.A. 0.9</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_number">
		<text>Manual, Lore, and Stories #</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_1">
		<text>Guns must be repaired to progress since you can't buy them from traders. Indeed, the EU and UN decided to put a stop to the bloodshed in the Zone as well as gun smuggling from the Zone to nearby countries by trying to limit guns traffic. No faction wants to have problems with more Private Military Companies paid by these organizations, since PMCs are already crawling throughout the Zone.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_2">
		<text> A gun's condition is separate from its parts' conditions. A gun's condition represents how clean it is and will impact how fast parts degrade. Barrel condition affects ammo damage and penetration. Other parts condition will affect how often the gun jams. Parts can be swapped in the field by drag and drop.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_3">
		<text>Collect gun parts that are above 60 percent condition and repair them with the appropriate tool to 100 percent condition (check the part details). Moving parts in and out of the gun will make it dirtier.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_4">
		<text>"Limiting gun traffic?! Tell that to the politicians when you have a horde of Monolithans in front of you! Why do they think the Monolith are back after all these years?! Fuck the EU and the UN!" - Illich Popov, Veteran Loner.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_5">
		<text>Armors and helmets can be repaired by collecting and repairing parts above 50 percent condition and swapping them in the workbench menu (right-click any toolkit to open the workbench). You need the appropriate repair kit.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_6">
		<text>To progress quickly, perform tasks, kill mutants, collect their parts, keep these parts to accomplish stalkers tasks, collect stash coordinates, visit those stashes, get fat loot, get toolboxes, repair the fat loot. Do tasks, get goodwill, sleep, visit traders, buy new shiny ammo for your juicy loot.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_7">
		<text>Use basic healing items like medkits or bandages to heal your main health. It will also heal your limbs temporarily (yellow HP). To convert temporary HP to permanent HP for your limbs (yellow to white HP) use post heal items (like Ibuprofen, with white dots in their description).</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_8">
		<text>Crafting is essential to survive. Right-click any toolkit to "open workbench". From there you can access the craft menu where most recipes are already unlocked. Be sure disassemble armors and guns you don't need as well as junk items, which have a small gear on their icon, to collect crafting items.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_9">
		<text>Holding Left Ctrl key on an item will reveal its stats, as if the item is repaired to maximum condition.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_10">
		<text>While accessing a container (chest, body etc.) holding shift key while hovering an item will move it to your inventory quickly.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_11">
		<text>Ammunition can be quite heavy, but disassembled ammo parts are very lightweight: keep these parts and craft ammo on the go with your gunsmith toolkit. Be sure to disassemble all unneeded ammo.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_12">
		<text>You can right click and mark some items as "Favorite" and others as "Junk". This will give you an easy access to the important items that will always be on the top of every inventory containers. It's the opposite for junk: it will always be at the bottom of inventories.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_13">
		<text>You don't need every medical items to heal your body. Mark the most important ones as favorite for easy access.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_14">
		<text>Mineral Water is much better weight-wise than canteens to quench your thirst. Keep the canteens in your main stash to cook mutant food that is better than imported goods to fill your belly.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_15">
		<text>"Hello Stalker, you're new around here, right? No fancy ammunition for you, we don't trust you just yet... I see that you have that old PPSh from your grandfather, don't you? Here is some 7.62x25 ammo, that's all you gonna get for today. Now, go hunt these mutants and make the Zone a safer place." - Petrenko</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_16">
		<text>"What the hell do you mean there's no coffee?! You're telling me that we can import gallons of vodka, beer, sparkling water and energy drinks, but I can't get some fucking coffee beans in this God forsaken place?"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_17">
		<text>Traders will mostly sell supplies and some accessories. You can increase their supply level by doing tasks for the trader's faction. The goodwill thresholds are: 500, 1000, 1500 and 2000 goodwill. This is the main way to secure a constant income of good ammunitions. Check your PDA relation tab and "show number" to check your goodwill with all factions.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_18">
		<text>Traders are either of the WP (Warsaw Pact) or NATO type. This will influence the kind of supplies that they sell (ammo and attachments mostly). NATO factions: Mercenaries, Clear Sky, Freedom, UNISG. WP factions: Military, Loner, Duty, Bandits, Renegades, Monolith.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_19">
		<text>Some traders sell very specific items, like Prof. Sakharov and Hermann. They sell the Artefacts Melter, a specific toolkit that let's you empower and craft artefacts (and break down artefacts to replenish the melter's power). They also sell exoskeletons' PSU recipes at high supply level.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_20">
		<text>Maintaining an exoskeleton is a money sink since you often need to buy expensive exo batteries in numbers... Or you can grab them from the cold bodies of your enemies.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_21">
		<text>You character will be tired at the end of the day. You have to sleep replenish your energy. You can only sleep if you are tired enough. Using sleeping pills will allow you to forcefully sleep. Drinking vodka and eating calorie-rich meals also helps you sleep. On the contrary, caffeine tablets and energy drinks will make you stay awake later.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_22">
		<text>You'll have a chance to wake up early when not using proper sleeping equipment (sleeping bag and sleeping mat). If you sleep in "free" beds, be sure to try to sleep longer than you intend to, since they are uncomfortable and other stalkers can be noisy and you might wake up early.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_23">
		<text>Be sure to use the appropriate ammo against any given target. Heavy armored stalkers will need high caliber AP ammo to be killed easily, while mutants hate HP and buckshot ammo. The latter might work on the average bandit, but not on Monolith clad in Nosorog exos.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_24">
		<text>Once you gathered some goodwill with a faction, you'll get random messages that are telling you to find some packages in certain areas. To find them, equip your RF Receiver and press the detector key. Put your weapon away and start changing the frequency of the RF Receiver to match the one from the message using your mouse buttons and shift key.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_25">
		<text>Stashes must be marked to contain anything. Unmarked stashes will always be empty. Stashes content is tied to the map they spawn in: the more Northern a stash is in the Zone, the better the loot. You can receive stash locations by completing tasks or by finding them on dead enemies and their PDA.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_26">
		<text>Storing stuff in stashes is safe: it won't be looted by other stalkers and even if the stash is marked at some point, content will spawn in the stash on top of what you previously stored.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_27">
		<text>To cook you don't necessarily need coal, just stand near a campfire and open the cooking menu from a cooking kit. If that does not work, stand closer to the campfire.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_28">
		<text>Artefacts spawn in low "condition", they are almost useless rocks, just slightly bending reality in their vicinity. However, you can empower them by fusing two artefacts of the same kind using the Artefacts Melter that you can buy from Prof. Sakharov to make them much stronger and eventually defy the laws of physics...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_29">
		<text>The Artefacts Melter, that you can buy from the Ecologists, is able to fuse different artefacts to generate new, stronger ones.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_30">
		<text>"Pressing LAlt key while in the looting screen will loot and scavenge everything valuable automatically. The looting behavior can be configured in the Mod Config Menu (MCM)."</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_31">
		<text>Wearing other faction's armors allows you to disguise as a member of that faction if the patch of the faction's armor is on. Don't push your luck though, if you get too close, stalkers will see through your trickery. Tear the patch off to identify as your own faction.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_32">
		<text>Radiation will slowly reduce your health and will reduce your max stamina. The more irradiated you are, the worse critical organs will be damaged by radioactive particles. This results in the bad coughs and severe injuries. Remember to wear an appropriate gas mask for the location you are heading to.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_33">
		<text>The more to the north you go, the more dangerous the radiations will be. Be sure to have a proper gas mask before going into northern areas. Army Warehouses without a gas mask can kill you if you just hit one bad radiation patch without proper anti radiation medication.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_34">
		<text>Avoid encumbrance, it will slow you down and eventually get you killed. Remember to periodically sell those extra items you don't need, or stash them for future use. Backpacks bought from traders can be used as stashes.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_35">
		<text>Hunting mutants will net you some of their parts. Additionally, you'll get their meat, which you can cook for food if you're low on cash. You can boil the meat to reduce it's radiation. If not, have something around to get rid of the radiation after such a meal.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_36">
		<text>Basic, advanced, and expert toolkits are required by many mechanics in order to perform certain upgrades on weapons and outfits. Such items can often be found in stashes received as rewards for completing tasks.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_37">
		<text>It's best to familiarise yourself with sewing kits, gun oil and glue tubes - these items can help keep your gear pristine in the field for much longer. Full repair kits are more potent, but also rarer, heavier and more expensive.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_38">
		<text>Truck Cemetery is a large graveyard of irradiated agricultural, civilian, and military vehicles. As a great place to hide a stash, an eagle-eyed stalker may find many valuables among the wreckage.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_39">
		<text>Artefacts are the strongest armor attachments a stalker can have. Do not forget to check their maximum stats by pressing Left Ctrl while hovering them.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_40">
		<text>Rank has eight different levels and can be increased through almost any in-game activity. Certain features may require reaching a high rank before they can be used or fully unlocked.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_41">
		<text>Reputation is a representation of how a stalker is viewed by their faction. It is gained and lost by helping or harming non-hostile stalkers respectively.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_42">
		<text>Remember to ask regular stalkers if they have any jobs available. Just because they aren't anybody important doesn't mean they won't be willing to pay you to do their dirty work.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_43">
		<text>Rostok's arena hosts two types of competitions: the traditional fights where stalkers battle each other for cash rewards, or challenges where they attempt to kill increasingly harder mutants.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_44">
		<text>Going in your PDA "Taskboard" panel will allow you to search and take jobs from nearby stalkers.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_45">
		<text>Cold, Spore, and the rest of Clear Sky's major characters can be asked about their story. Doing so can help shed light on their faction's overall survival... and might get you new missions to accomplish.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_46">
		<text>Freedom completely occupies Yanov Station in Jupiter after Shulga left to fight the resurgent Monolith. Many stalkers who had previously left Freedom had since rejoined to help bolster its position.</text> 
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_47">
		<text>A strong psy barrier will prevent you to pass through the red forest and further up north. Get the psy helmet from Sakharov to be able to pass through.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_48">
		<text>It is much easier to avoid detection when travelling during the night or through heavy rain. However, you risk encountering fierce nocturnal mutants.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_49">
		<text>If you are not tired enough to sleep, drinking beer and vodka or using sleeping pills will help you fall asleep. Sleeping will heal your limbs, but not your main HP.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_50">
		<text>It's a good habit to compare prices of clean, healthy food at barkeepers and carry some of it with you. Don't forget to get something to quench your thirst while you're at it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_51">
		<text>If things are getting a little too tough for you, you could try reducing the difficulty through the progression menu. You can access this by pressing F1 while in the main menu after loading the game.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_52">
		<text>Faction bases usually have a medic who can heal you and remove your radiation for a low fee. You can also purchase medicine for prices lower than elsewhere.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_53">
		<text>Ecologists never have enough mutant parts, especially from the rare kinds. These could fetch a nice price, and the scientists might task you with finding specific samples for an even higher pay.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_54">
		<text>Always carry a flashlight and consider investing in night vision goggles, you never know when you'll find yourself at night far from somewhere safe.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_55">
		<text>Take every single bullet regardless of the type and stash it, maybe tomorrow you'll need it. And maybe not, but take it nonetheless; disassembling them will net you ammo crafting parts that a gunsmith kit can make use of.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_56">
		<text>Investing in psy protection will get you far in the Zone. At the very least consider getting some psy-block pills, you never know when you'll run into a controller.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_57">
		<text>Trust your ears. Sound carries over hills and through dense bushes. A faint but familiar sound may be all you need to brace yourself for a sneak attack.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_58">
		<text>Don't throw your pistol out, keep it for backup. Light-weight, easy to handle, and cheap to maintain, if you take care of it your pistol is certain to take care of you, especially .45 Hydrashock or .357 HP pistols against mutants.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_59">
		<text>Traders will give you more difficult tasks as you earn more reputation with their factions. Despite being well-paid, they are more dangerous than the rest and will test your skills.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_60">
		<text>Consider keeping some of the artefacts you find, their properties might open the door to getting new ones later on.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_61">
		<text>If you end up heavily outnumbered and outgeared, consider escaping. Not only will you save your life, you will also save your money and medicine.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_62">
		<text>If you're being shot at: remain calm, count their rounds, and pounce when they reload.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_63">
		<text>Always carry something that can stop bleeding. A medic can inexpensively patch your wounds later but only if you don't bleed out on your way there.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_64">
		<text>Most stalkers prefer to hunt for artefacts in the southern parts of the Zone, but experienced stalkers know that the best spots are all north of the Red Forest. Few survive long in such parts unprepared, however.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_65">
		<text>If you confront a controller, try to get an object to block its line of sight (tree, rock, wall). If it doesn't see you, it can't control you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_66">
		<text>Stimpacks are quite useful. They'll heal you much faster than medkits.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_67">
		<text>Painkiller stims will give a very valuable damage reduction as well as bleeding control. Use them before charging into battle.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_68">
		<text>MP7 and P90 are lightweight SMGs with great recoil control and handling, you can even use them one handed.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_69">
		<text>The RF Radio will help you find things far and hidden from you. You can change the radio's frequency through LMB, RMB, Shift LMB/RMB, and Alt LMB/RMB while having your other hand free.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_70">
		<text>Remember to check the PDAs of deceased stalkers, you can get useful information out of them. If you can't access them you could try asking someone tech-savvy to crack them open for you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_71">
		<text>Listen to the sounds of anomalies: your sense of hearing can sometimes better indicate the position of an anomaly than your sight.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_72">
		<text>Carry as little as possible when going out, so you can pick up more goodies and sell them to traders when you return.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_73">
		<text>Have your artefact detector out as often as possible near anomalous fields. You would surprised how common artefacts are in the Zone.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_74">
		<text>Being a scummy, treacherous stalker might be economically rewarding, but eventually those who hate you will want to get rid of you. Even if you lay low, you will be hunted.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_75">
		<text>Remember the sounds given off by mutants. Knowing what's creeping up on you makes it easier to deal with the situation in the best possible way.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_76">
		<text>Rumors say that an heavily armored stalker with specific artefacts successfully butchered an entire regiment of brainwashed Monolith soldiers with only an axe.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_77">
		<text>Always carry a clip of armor-piercing rounds for whatever gun you have. Mutants might not wear armor, but hostile stalkers do.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_78">
		<text>Butcher is considered a legend in the southern parts of the zone. When he came to the Garbage, it was crawling with mutants and the area was inhospitable to stalkers. I don't believe the stories some tell that he cleared it by himself, but he does know a lot about mutant hunting.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_79">
		<text>Drug-making kits are used to craft your own medicine using objects you would otherwise throw away and save a lot of money in the process.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_80">
		<text>Drag and drop repaired parts on a gun to change them. This will reduce the chance of the gun jamming, but will get a bit of dirt and dust in it. Just remember to clean your gun after swapping parts.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_81">
		<text>Barrel condition affects bullet damage and penetration. Do not use broken guns. By right clicking a gun and "maintain parts" you can clean a barrel within a gun if its condition is above 60 percent using the appropriate cleaning kit. Otherwise, use a repair kit to directly replace the barrel.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_82">
		<text>Gun's condition is separated from parts conditions. The gun condition represents how clean a gun is and will impact how fast parts degrade. Barrel condition affects ammo damage and penetration. Other parts condition will affect how often the gun jams. Parts can be swapped in the field by drag and drop.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_83">
		<text>Collect gun parts that are above 60 percent condition and repair them with the appropriate tool to 100 percent condition (check the part details). Moving parts in and out of the gun will make it dirtier.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_84">
		<text>"Pressing LAlt key while in the looting screen will loot and disassemble everything automatically. The looting behavior can be configured in the Mod Config Menu (MCM).</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_85">
		<text>Armors and helmets can be repaired by collecting and repairing parts above 50 percent condition and swapping them in the workbench menu (right-click any toolkit to open the workbench). You need the appropriate repair kit.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_86">
		<text>Sin is a dangerous group of cultists that plotted in the dark corners of the Zone for a long time. They mastered specific aspects of the Zone and the Noosphere, thus making them much more resistant than a normal human being.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_87">
		<text>Use basic healing items like medkits or bandages to heal your main health. It will also heal your limbs temporarily (yellow HP). To convert these temporary HP to permanent HP for your limbs (yellow to white HP) use post heal items (like Ibuprofen, with white dots in their description).</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_88">
		<text>Crafting is essential to survive. Right-click any toolkit to "open workbench". From there you can access the craft menu where most recipes are already unlocked. Be sure disassemble armors and guns you don't need as well as junk items, which have a small gear on their icon, to collect crafting items.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_89">
		<text>Holding Left Ctrl key on an item will reveal its stats, as if the item is repaired to maximum condition.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_90">
		<text>While accessing a container (chest, body...) holding shift key while hovering an item will quickly move it to your inventory or back into the container.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_91">
		<text>Ammunition can be quite heavy, but disassembled ammo parts are very lightweight: keep these parts and craft ammo on the go with your gunsmith toolkit. Be sure to disassemble all unneeded ammo.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_92">
		<text>You can right click and mark some items as "Favorite" and others as "Junk". This will give you an easy access to the important items that will always be on the top of every inventory containers. It's the opposite for junk: it will always be at the bottom  of inventories.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_93">
		<text>You don't need every medical item to heal your body. Mark the most important ones as favorite for easy access.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_94">
		<text>Mineral Water is much better weight-wise than canteens to quench your thirst. Keep the canteens in your main stash to cook mutant meat, which is better than imported goods to fill your belly.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_95">
		<text>"Hello Stalker, you're new around here, right? No fancy ammunition for you, we don't trust you just yet... I see that you have that old PPSh from your grandfather, don't you? Here is some 7.62x25 ammo, that's all you're gonna get for today. Now, go hunt these mutants and make the Zone a safer place." - Petrenko</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_96">
		<text>"What the hell do you mean there's no coffee?! You're telling me that we can import gallons of vodka, beer, sparkling water and energy drinks, but I can't get some fucking coffee beans in this God forsaken place?"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_97">
		<text>Traders will mostly sell supplies and some accessories. You can increase their supply level by doing tasks for the trader's faction. The goodwill thresholds are: 500, 1000, 1500 and 2000 goodwill. This is the main way to secure a constant income of good ammunitions. Check your PDA relation tab and "show number" to check your goodwill with all factions.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_98">
		<text>Traders are either of the WP (Warsaw Pact) or NATO type. This will influence the kind of supplies that they sell (ammo and attachments mostly). NATO factions: Mercenaries, Clear Sky, Freedom, UNISG. WP factions: Military, Loner, Duty, Bandits, Renegades, Monolith.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_99">
		<text>Some traders sell very specific items, like Prof. Sakharov and Hermann. They sell the Artefacts Melter, a specific toolkit that let's you empower and craft artefacts (and break down artefacts with it to replenish the melter's power). They also sell exoskeletons' PSU recipes at high supply level.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_100">
		<text>Maintaining an exoskeleton is a money sink since you often need to buy expensive exo batteries in numbers... Or you can grab them from the cold bodies of your enemies.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_101">
		<text>Guns must be repaired to progress since you can't buy them from traders. Indeed, the EU and UN decided to put a stop to the bloodshed in the Zone as well as gun smuggling from the Zone to nearby countries by trying to limit guns traffic. No faction wants to have problems with more Private Military Companies paid by these organizations, since PMCs are already crawling throughout the Zone.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_102">
		<text>You'll have a chance to wake up early without proper sleeping equipment (sleeping bag and sleeping mat). If you sleep in "free" beds, be sure to sleep longer than you intend to. They are uncomfortable and other stalkers can be noisy, so you'll have a chance to wake up early.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_103">
		<text>Be sure to use the appropriate ammo against any given target. Heavy armored stalkers will need high caliber AP ammo to be killed easily, while mutants hate HP and buckshot ammo. The latter might work on the average bandit, but not on Monolith clad in Nosorog exos.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_104">
		<text>Once you gathered some goodwill with a faction, you'll get random messages that are telling you to find some packages in certain areas. To find them, equip your RF Receiver and press the detector key. Put your weapon away and start changing the frequency of the RF Receiver to match the one from the message using your mouse buttons and shift key.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_105">
		<text>Stashes must be marked to contain anything. Unmarked stashes will always be empty. Stash content is tied to the map they spawn in: the more Northern a stash is in the Zone, the better the loot.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_106">
		<text>Storing stuff in stashes is safe: it won't be looted by other stalkers and even if the stash is marked at some point, content will spawn in the stash on top of what you previously stored.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_107">
		<text>To cook you don't necessarily need coal, just stand near a campfire and open the cooking menu from a cooking kit. If that does not work, stand closer to the campfire.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_108">
		<text>Artefacts spawn in low "condition", they are almost useless rocks, just slightly bending reality in their vicinity. However, you can empower them by fusing two artefacts of the same kind using the Artefacts Melter that you can buy from Prof. Sakharov to make them much stronger and eventually defy the laws of physics...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ls_tip_109">
		<text>Sin is a dangerous group of cultists that plotted in the dark corners of the Zone for a long time. They mastered specific aspects of the Zone and the Noosphere, thus making them much more resistant than a normal human being. </text>
	</string>
</string_table>
