<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
	<!-- The Living Fire -->
	<string id="baraholka_trader_the_living_fire_1_0">
		<text>Snitch told me to meet you. You know something that could shed some light on the "fiery" stalker from the rumors, right?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="baraholka_trader_the_living_fire_1_1">
		<text>Ah, yes... I've got something, but don't get your hopes too high. Some time ago we've observed weird flashes happening at night behind the huge garbage pile south of us, followed by some terrifying howling of mutants. Some loners were curious what's happened there and visited the place during the day. They've found some dead fleshes there which were... well.. slightly grilled. At first we thought that those fleshes got into some hardly visible anomaly that disappeared the next day or encountered a flame poltergeist, but there was one peculiar thing about one of them. It had something that looked like a brand on its back - it was in the shape of a human hand. It could have been a simple accident... or not? Who knows...\n \nYou could have a look around here at night if you'd like to find out more. If that guy really exists, then his affinity with fire might be a good clue where you should look for him.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="baraholka_trader_the_living_fire_1_2">
		<text>Hmm... this still sounds like some veteran story to scare rookies. Either way, I'll try to find out something more. Thanks.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="baraholka_trader_the_living_fire_1_3">
		<text>Yeah... I've got to admit it sounds nuts. You should still watch your back. The Zone is a strange place...\nAnyway - Snitch owes me one round for this, no matter what's the outcome of your investigation.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="baraholka_trader_the_living_fire_2_0">
		<text>I'm back from my sear...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="baraholka_trader_the_living_fire_2_1">
		<text>Let me guess. You've just wasted time chasing yet another rumor for Snitch, am I ri...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="baraholka_trader_the_living_fire_2_2">
		<text>I saw him... that stalker from the rumor.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="baraholka_trader_the_living_fire_2_3">
		<text>You saw... what? Are you serious now? Wait... you look a little pale... You're serious?! Does it have something to do with that loud explision that we heard?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="baraholka_trader_the_living_fire_2_4">
		<text>Yes. He was doing some sort of... ritual... at the Greek Fire anomaly. There was fire everywhere around. A stray flesh came close and got... evaporated?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="baraholka_trader_the_living_fire_2_5">
		<text>How the hell are you alive then, huh? Did you talk with him?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="baraholka_trader_the_living_fire_2_6">
		<text>I don't know. He has certainly been aware of my presence from the beginning, even though he didn't see me. When I wanted to ask who he is, he interrupted me saying that everyone will know his name and disappeared in a fiery explosion shortly after.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="baraholka_trader_the_living_fire_2_7">
		<text>Everyone will know his name, huh? That doesn't sound good. Well - at least Snitch will be happy to hear that you've found something. Now he definitely owes me a whole bottle.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_2_0">
		<text>Snitch - we need to talk.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_2_1">
		<text>The rumor turned out to be true. I know... I've already received a message from my friend. You've done well. Here - you've earned it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_2_2">
		<text>Five thousands? Are you out of your mind? I could have died there!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_2_3">
		<text>Shhh... shut it. There's more to come. Work for me a bit more and you'll get it. We need to find out more. People won't pay much just for the information that this stalker exists. Well... maybe Petrenko will, given that he's lost two men because of him.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_2_4">
		<text>So what's the plan now? We don't know where he went or what's his goal. We have no leads.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_2_5">
		<text>We do. When you've been doing your investigation, I've overheard a talk between two scientists about some abnormal anomalous activity exactly at the place where you've met the stranger. You should go and talk with Sakharov and offer your help investigating the issue.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_2_6">
		<text>Fine. I'll be on my way then.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_2_7">
		<text>Just one more thing. Don't mention to him that it was me who was eavesdropping on his colleagues. I don't want them to be more cautious around me. Scientific information tends to be pretty valuable.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_1_0">
		<text>Professor - may I have a word with you?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_1_1">
		<text>Not now young man. We're busy investigating some recent incident.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_1_2">
		<text>Is that matter by any chance related to the Greek Fire anomaly?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_1_3">
		<text>How did you know? Did you intercept some message that I sent to my assistants?! This information is classified!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_1_4">
		<text>Don't get upset, professor. It's irrelevant how I did find out. The thing is - I've been there not long time ago when something weird happened and I'm willing to share my knowledge with you if you agree to disclose what you know. This would be mutually beneficial. Maybe I could assist you with...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_1_5">
		<text>Didn't I make myself clear?! This information is class... wait... You say you've seen something there? What was it?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_1_6">
		<text>Knowledge for knowledge professor. I can assure you that my information is worth it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_1_7">
		<text>Damn you... so be it. Our scanners have been showing some abnormal readings from that anomaly for a few days now - sudden spikes in the energy it emitted. Just as if the anomaly was expanding and going back to its base state. We've seen fluctuations like this in other anomalies before, although not with this frequency. We've decided to ignore it. Not long time ago our readings went off scale at night for a short time before going back to normal. This is very worrying. We might be in big trouble if anomalies start to expand uncontrollably.\n \nNow please tell me, what have you seen there? I assume you've seen many anomalies in your life, so it had to be something extraordinary.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_1_8">
		<text>Yes - it was. Just like you said, the anomaly was really active at that time. It was spewing a lot of flames. What's the most interesting is that there was a man among those flames. He was performing some kind of ritual. What I found out later is that he can somehow control the fire. He literally disintegrated a flesh on my eyes. After a short time, he bursted into flames and disappeard. That's also when the flames went dormant again.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_1_9">
		<text>That's fascinating! So it was him who empowered the anomaly. Did you have a chance to talk with him?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_1_10">
		<text>No - unfortunately not... though he said that in time everyone will know his name.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_1_11">
		<text>This doesn't sound well given what power he has. We need to find out what he wants to achieve.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_1_12">
		<text>I agree and I've got to say I hoped that you could tell me where I should head next.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_1_13">
		<text>I'm afraid I can't help you with that. Our scanners didn't show anything else for... wait... there it is! The scanners are showing unnatural activity at the Fault anomaly. You should head there immediately!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_1_14">
		<text>Thank you, professor! I'll be going then.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_2_0">
		<text>Bad news, professor. I didn't manage to get there in time to meet that man.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_2_1">
		<text>I'd say it's some wonderful news. Our readings have shown a really extreme spike in the energy emitted by that anomaly. If you were closer to it, you'd probably get obliterated.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_2_2">
		<text>Oh, well... lucky me I guess...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_2_3">
		<text>I'm also glad that you've made it back in one piece. Now please tell me, how did you manage to stop the anomaly from branching?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_2_4">
		<text>Eh - branching? I just destroyed a bunch of flame poltergeists at that place. They didn't seem to be special. I've seen a few of those already.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_2_5">
		<text>They actually were very special, young man. You see - our scanners detected them as separate entities with a similar energy to other thermal anomalies, just a bit weaker. They were a sort of proto-anomalies. If you didn't stop them there, they'd turn into another big anomalous zones, given enough time.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_2_6">
		<text>Hmm... I guess that man is even more dangerous than we thought then.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_2_7">
		<text>Yes, indeed. We need to find out what his motives are as fast as possible. Unfortunately, I don't think I can help you with locating him again. Our readings went back to normal once more.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_2_8">
		<text>That's alright, professor. I'll continue the investigation on my own. Goodbye.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_3_0">
		<text>I'm back from Yantar. Got some more news for you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_3_1">
		<text>That's great! But first, let me tell you something. People are actually paying some good money to learn more about The Living Fire. A catchy nickname, right? I came up with it myself, since you didn't learn his true name yet. Here's your share mate. Now - what did you learn?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_3_2">
		<text>Now that's better. As for my findings - the scientists indeed did notice the increase in anomalous activity on Garbage. They've also sent me to investigate another suspicious activity at the Great Swamp. I was late there and the party started before I got there, but later on I found out it was good - otherwise I'd probably not be talking with you right now. This time that man managed to somehow create some things called "proto-anomalies" by Sakharov that could later on turn into big anomalous zones. I've managed to get rid of them in time.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_3_3">
		<text>Woah! So we've got an impending doom where we'll all burn in hell? I smell some good money here.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_3_4">
		<text>Wha... Are you serious? You're not worried? Even a bit?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_3_5">
		<text>We're all gonna die sooner or later my friend. People with money tend to die later though and it looks like our partnership will make me pretty rich soon. I'll leave the Zone just in time if anything is to happen.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_3_6">
		<text>Yeah... I don't share your optimism.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_3_7">
		<text>You don't have to. It's just a business. You're also into unveiling the mysteries of the Zone, right? So you have double gains here.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_3_8">
		<text>Maybe you are right. Anyway - scientists didn't see any other spikes in anomalous activity yet, so we might be in a dead end right now.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_3_9">
		<text>Not exactly - you forgot about me. Good old Petrenko dropped by recently with his walkie-talkie and so it happens that I've been nearby to hear some interesting stuff. He was talking with some officials. You see - the military squad guarding the X-18 laboratory had some unexpected guest. The last survivor has managed to send an S.O.S signal, also mentioning that his comrades were turned to ash before he also broke the connection. I'm pretty sure it was the guy we're looking for.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_3_10">
		<text>Right - and you expect me to chase him?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_3_11">
		<text>Why not? You've survived your last encounter with him, right? Maybe there's a reason for it. He might know something about you that actually saved your life. Besides - do you want to leave this mystery unsolved? Have you forgotten about the end of the world? *laughs*</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_3_12">
		<text>Damn you, Snitch. You should take it more seriously. I don't think I have any choice though... I'll go there.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_3_13">
		<text>Now that's the spirit! I hope you come back with some more valuable information.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="the_living_fire_prometheus_the_living_fire_1_0">
		<text>It's not some kind of a trick, right?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_prometheus_the_living_fire_1_1">
		<text>Why would it be? If I wanted to kill you, we'd not be talking right now.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_prometheus_the_living_fire_1_2">
		<text>Why didn't you then? I've seen your power... that flesh on the Garbage bursted into flames.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_prometheus_the_living_fire_1_3">
		<text>I know you, stalker. I know that you've seen the Wish Granter and didn't make a selfish wish, like many others would. You're pure at heart. Now - I believe you have many questions.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_prometheus_the_living_fire_1_4">
		<text>You're damn right. Who are you?! Why are you doing all of this... and... what exactly are you doing?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_prometheus_the_living_fire_1_5">
		<text>I'm just a simple stalker - like you. I've mainly sticked to the souther parts of the Zone before a certain accident, but we'll get to it. I was going by the name of Boris... a simple newbie that came to the Zone to make some money and pay off my debts. I was mainly running some errands for the local traders... mainly for that scumbag Sidorovich.\n \nYou see - one day I've received a task to deliver some package to the scientists at Yantar. Seemd like some easy money. It didn't turn out well for me... I got captured by a squad of military and they offered to let me go free if I pay them. Once they got the money, they took everything from me and beat me up so badly that I could barely walk... fucking corrupted bastards.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_prometheus_the_living_fire_1_6">
		<text>Yeah... fairness is not a trait you can find among our soldiers and officials... what happened next?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_prometheus_the_living_fire_1_7">
		<text>I've managed to get to the Garbage, where I've stayed at the hangar. The Butcher took care of me for a few days and helped me heal my wounds. He knows a lot about the Zone and knows some ointment made out of some mutant fat that makes the wounds heal faster.\n \nOnce I've regained my strength, I've went back to Cordon. I wanted to get some supplies from my stash there, but guess what - some bastard stole all my stuff again.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_prometheus_the_living_fire_1_8">
		<text>Tough luck, huh? Things like this happen in the Zone.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_prometheus_the_living_fire_1_9">
		<text>You wouldn't expect to get robbed by your fellows though, right? I know that for a fact that it was one of my "friends" that took my stuff and went further north to avoid confronting me. With no gun and no money, I had to turn to Sidorovich for a loan. He refused, because I did not deliver my package that got taken by military. He offered me another task though - he told me to fetch some uncommon artifact that can only be found in thermal anomalies. He gave me an old PM and a pack of bullets that I had to return after my task is done. He also said that he'll place the bounty on me if I don't return to him with that artifact in three days.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_prometheus_the_living_fire_1_10">
		<text>Sidor is a greedy bastard, but this is rather extreme, even for him... What did you do next?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_prometheus_the_living_fire_1_11">
		<text>I couldn't refuse... There are no thermal anomalies around Cordon, so I had to go somewhere else. Darkscape and Great Swamp are very dangerous, especially if you have only a PM. I've decided to look around the Greek Fire anomaly. I've spent two days hanging around the Flea Market, eating some leftovers, avoiding the fight and visiting the anomaly once in a while. The traders there saw my misery and shared a loaf of breat with me one time.\n \nAt the third day the luck has finally smiled at me... or so I thought. The right artifact has appeared and I've been trying to reach for it without ending up as a crisp. It drifted towards me and I got it in my hands. Then, out of a sudden, a flesh jumped out of the bushes and pushed me straight into the anomaly. I felt a terrible pain all over my body and lost my conciousness shortly after. I thought that's my end... getting devoured by the flames.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_prometheus_the_living_fire_1_12">
		<text>How are you still alive then?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_prometheus_the_living_fire_1_13">
		<text>Patience, my friend. I woke up one day later, completely naked, surrounded by the flames that I couldn't feel... I felt a burning pain at my heart though. I was trying to gather my thoughts there when I saw some stalker approaching and aiming straight at me - it was the bounty hunter sent by Sidorovich. I've begged for mercy and reached out with my hand, but he fired anyway. His bullets didn't reach me... they've melted inside the wall of flames that appeared in front of me. That's when I understood - the Zone has granted me this new power. The bounty hunter was also shocked seeing me still alive after the flames extinguished. Before he managed to pull the trigger again, a fireball shot out of my hand straight at him, turning him into a pile of dust. The Zone has repaid me for all the suffering and humiliation. I was chosen by her.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_prometheus_the_living_fire_1_14">
		<text>Eh, chosen? Do you really think this was some kind of destiny? Strange things happen in the Zone every day... it could have been a simple accident.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_prometheus_the_living_fire_1_15">
		<text>That may be, but I know for sure that Boris has died that day. I've taken a new name - Prometheus.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_prometheus_the_living_fire_1_16">
		<text>Prometheus? That's... poetic.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_prometheus_the_living_fire_1_17">
		<text>Yes... it's a tribute to the anomaly that granted me my powers.\n \nI've spent a few more days there, learning how to use my powers properly and conciously. The day that we've met, I've ascended to a new level... I've learned how to draw energy from the anomalies and also empower them. I also felt your presence at the Great Swamp, so I guess it was you who stopped my little experiment. Then I've came here to meditate further on my powers and look who's here again. Why do you chase after me, stalker?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_prometheus_the_living_fire_1_18">
		<text>I... I guess I was mainly driven by curiosity. What's your ultimate goal?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_prometheus_the_living_fire_1_19">
		<text>My ultimate goal? Well - it's... *sigh*... I think we have some uninvited guests. Till next we meet, stalker - farewell.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_prometheus_the_living_fire_1_20">
		<text>Wait! Wha..</text>
	</string>

	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_4_0">
		<text>Yo Snitch. I...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_4_1">
		<text>Our savior is back! You've made it out alive again - that's great! Did you finally deal with the legend?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_4_2">
		<text>He turned a squad of military into crisps, so you can guess I didn't... but I had a chance to talk with him.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_4_3">
		<text>That's even better! What did you learn?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_4_4">
		<text>I've learned his name - it's Prometheus. He's...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_4_5">
		<text>The Living Fire, Prometheus - born in the Greek Fire! Holy shit! That's even more catchy! What else...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_4_6">
		<text>Screw you, Snitch! You're out of your mind! All you care about is money! I'm not telling you anything else!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_4_7">
		<text>What? But what about our deal? Didn't you also want to make some money?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_4_8">
		<text>I'm out. Keep your filthy money.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_4_9">
		<text>You're gonna regret this, stalker...</text>
	</string>

	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_trader_the_living_fire_1_0">
		<text>Sidorovich - we need to talk.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_trader_the_living_fire_1_1">
		<text>What is it? I'm pretty busy right now.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_trader_the_living_fire_1_2">
		<text>Do you remember a newbie stalker named Boris?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_trader_the_living_fire_1_3">
		<text>Nah... there's a lot of newbies passing through our village - can't remember everyone.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_trader_the_living_fire_1_4">
		<text>Well then - have you heard about The Living Fire?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_trader_the_living_fire_1_5">
		<text>The new stupid rumor? Yes, I did. Why the hell are you asking so stupid questions? I don't have time for this.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_trader_the_living_fire_1_6">
		<text>And what if I tell you that your life is in danger? Boris now goes by name Prometheus and he's that Living Fire from the rumor. Let's say he doesn't like you much... because you're a dickhead that sent him for a certain death.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_trader_the_living_fire_1_7">
		<text>Quit that shit! Why should I believe you?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_trader_the_living_fire_1_8">
		<text>I had a chance to talk with him. He was your unlucky courier that got beaten up by the military and that you've later sent with a PM to find an uncommon artifact. Does it ring a bell now?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_trader_the_living_fire_1_9">
		<text>How do you know all of that?! Oh shit - you're serious! Why didn't you put the bullet in his head when you had a chance?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_trader_the_living_fire_1_10">
		<text>You've clearly missed the important parts from that rumor, didn't you? You're not the only one valuing your life. I don't think he can be killed with a weapon. Our best shot is just to reason with him. Now since you've remembered everything with some good motivation, do you know something that'd help me find him again?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_trader_the_living_fire_1_11">
		<text>I know that this miserable weakling had a friend around here named Andrei. They sticked together because they were both unlucky and poor. He's not here anymore. Reportedly he headed north not so long time ago. That fool is probably dead by now.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_trader_the_living_fire_1_12">
		<text>Fuck... that doesn't help me much. Anyway - I'd suggest you hire some guards and install some heat-resistant doors. If that guy decides to pay you a visit, it might save your life... I doubt it though.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_trader_the_living_fire_1_13">
		<text>Hah... funny guy...</text>
	</string>

	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_3_0">
		<text>What's the situation, professor?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_3_1">
		<text>It's good to see you, young man. The situation is very serious, so I'll be quick.\n \nWe've spotted an extreme spike in anomalous activity in the X-16 underground complex. I've never seen a thing like this. It's surely the doing of our mysterious stalker. If an energy of this magnitute turns into an actual anomalous field, this whole place is going to turn into hell!\n \nWe've sent a small group of mercenaries to investigate the place and they've met a single stalker at the entrance that opened fire on sight. The mercenaries had the numbers, so they've stormed the place. This was a mistake. They've managed to kill that stalker, but something unexpected happened soon after. They've started to rally near his body and then it suddenly exploded. Only one man from the mercenary squad has survived - his body was badly burned.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_3_2">
		<text>That definitely sounds like some trick of Prometheus...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_3_3">
		<text>Prometheus? Is that the name of that stalker we've been looking for?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_3_4">
		<text>I'm sorry professor, but I don't think I have time to explain you everything in details.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_3_5">
		<text>Ah, you're right young man. You've once managed to stop the branching of the anomaly, so I hope you can do it again.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_3_6">
		<text>I hope so too. I'll be on my way.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="the_living_fire_prometheus_the_living_fire_2_0">
		<text>Wha... What happened here? What are all these burnt bodies?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_prometheus_the_living_fire_2_1">
		<text>These are fellow stalkers which share my vision. They've came looking for me after my friend Andrei whom I've met recently started spreading my message. I'm going to purify this world of all the unjust filth and they agreed to aid me in this endeavor. They've suffered enough - just like me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_prometheus_the_living_fire_2_2">
		<text>Why are they all dead then?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_prometheus_the_living_fire_2_3">
		<text>It's not all of them - those are just some failed experiments. You've met some of the successful ones on your way here.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_prometheus_the_living_fire_2_4">
		<text>What did you do to them? Doesn't killing those people and turning them into walking bombs put you in line with the "filth" that you want to eradicate? Killing a man is the worst crime.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_prometheus_the_living_fire_2_5">
		<text>Watch your words - you're treading on thin ice... All of them came to me willingly and agreed to whatever comes. Besides - it was you who killed the living ones. I've started to like you, so I won't kill you on spot - I'll let you witness my Magnum Opus.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_prometheus_the_living_fire_2_6">
		<text>Your what? What are you planning?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_prometheus_the_living_fire_2_7">
		<text>I've imbued those people with my power. Unfortunately not all bodies are able to withstand it. They will serve me as a power relay when the time comes. There's one more place that I have to visit personally - no relay would be able to harness its power. Then... you will see what happens next. Farewell, stalker.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_prometheus_the_living_fire_2_8">
		<text>I'll find a way to stop you, Prometheus...</text>
	</string>

	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_4_0">
		<text>Prof...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_4_1">
		<text>You've done it again, young man! The readings are going back to normal. I...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_4_2">
		<text>It's not over yet. Prometheus has escaped and he's planning something. I don't know what it is, but it's definitely not something good. I'll need your help.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_4_3">
		<text>Oh - what can I do for you?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_4_4">
		<text>The man that the mercenaries have killed is one of Prometheus followers. He has imbued them with his power and he's planning to use them as some kind of power relay. We'll need to use your connections with authorities.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_4_5">
		<text>I see. You want me to request the military to protect as many thermal anomalies as possible and dispose of suspicious stalkers when they come close, right?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_4_6">
		<text>Not exactly. I think Prometheus will feel it when he loses connection with his followers. We need to make him think that everything is alright. He'll try to use all this power at once, so if we dispose of all his power relays at the same time, he'll probably drain too much of his own power before he realises what happened. This might give me some window of opportunity to end his life.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_4_7">
		<text>That's a very risky plan... I don't think we have any other options though.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_4_8">
		<text>Probably not. I'll try to use some powerful weapon to increase my chance of success. The Gauss rifle should be good enough.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_4_9">
		<text>This sounds like a plan. Do you know where he is now?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_4_10">
		<text>He said he'll need to visit some anomaly personally to harness its power. Do you know which anomaly he was speaking of?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_4_11">
		<text>There's one anomaly with exceptionally high energy. It's located in the Red Forest. I doubt military will agree to send some people there. It's too risky. You'll need to secure it yourself first. If it also starts branching, I hope you'll manage to stop it again.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_4_12">
		<text>Thank you, professor. I'll let you know when the place is safe. Goodbye.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_5_0">
		<text>You little rat. Tell me why I shouldn't put a bullet in your head now?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_5_1">
		<text>What? What are you talking about?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_5_2">
		<text>I've met the bounty squad you've sent after me. They're all dead and now it's your turn.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_5_3">
		<text>Wait! I didn't hire any bounty squad! Some serious people visited me some time ago and started asking about Prometheus. I've just told them that you're the one who knows the most about him. I didn't know they'd assault you. It was just a business.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_5_4">
		<text>I don't give a shit, Snitch. I could have died... so now I'll repeat my question. Why shouldn't I kill you now?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_5_5">
		<text>Wait! How about some free information in exchange for my life? Let's call it a compensation for your losses. I assure you it will be of use to you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_5_6">
		<text>I'm all ears...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_5_7">
		<text>The freedom guys caught some kind of a preacher in their base. Apparently it was a friend of Prometheus. Freedom has squeezed some more info from him. They'll be gathering at the Outskirts for "something grand". He mentioned the Prometheus Movie Theater.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_5_8">
		<text>Shit... his Magnum Opus... couldn't have thought of a better place.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_5_9">
		<text>His what? What are you...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_the_living_fire_5_10">
		<text>You've redeemed yourself, Snitch. I need to go now.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_5_0">
		<text>I'm back, professor. Prometheus is no more - I've seen him explode with my own eyes. That wouldn't be possible without your connections. What is it that you wanted?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_5_1">
		<text>I wanted to thank you, young man. Maybe the military did aid us in stopping Prometheus, but it was you who actually investigated this issue and led it to the end, risking your own life.\n \nI'm not sure what Prometheus was doing at that moment, but he somehow managed to remotely empower the biggest anomaly in the zone that's located further north than the CNPP. If you wouldn't stop him, many people would have died. You have my gratitude.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_5_2">
		<text>Well - he also wanted to kill me, so it's not like I had any other choice.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_5_3">
		<text>That may be *laughs*\n \nAnyway - you still deserve a reward. My colleagues have assisted the military near the anomalies that Prometheus visited personally. After his death, an exceptional artifact was born in the Greek Fire. I'd like you to have it. It seems to have some bad influence over my colleagues and I'd rather not have another power-crazy man emerge again.\n \nYou've survived multiple encounters with Prometheus, so he saw something in you... I believe that thing will protect you from the influence of this artifact.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_the_living_fire_5_4">
		<text>Thank you, professor. I hope I'll not lose my sanity either.</text>
	</string>
</string_table>
