<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<string_table>
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_new_tasks_addon_dead_night_name">
		<text>Dead Night</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_new_tasks_addon_dead_night_text">
		<text>Loners are disappearing without a trace during the night in the Darkscape. Sidorovich asked me to find out what's going on.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_new_tasks_addon_dead_night_about">
		<text>Our lads have reported that some Loners have disappeared recently on their way from the Darkscape sawmill to our village. The path was always relatively safe, so folks often traveled at night to avoid bandits and soldiers. Their screams in the dark were heard by the guys staying at the sawmill, but noone was brave enough to risk their life trying to help them. The bodies of the missing stalkers have not been found after the dawn. Stalkers around here have gathered a small sum for someone willing to investigate what happened.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_new_tasks_addon_dead_night_finish">
		<text>What a horrible fate... thank you for putting the dead to their final rest and making sure no more lads will join their forces. Here - you've earned it.</text>
	</string>
    <string id="dead_night_details">
        <text>Investigate the place during the night</text>
    </string>

	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_skyfall_name">
		<text>Skyfall</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_skyfall_text">
		<text>The military has received reinforcements in form of new Mi-24 helicopter that might be used for assaulting the old military warehouses where Freedom resides. Lukash has tasked me with taking down this flying beast. I should get to Agroprom as soon as possible.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_skyfall_about">
		<text>You know - the Duty is not our only problem around here. The army would also like to take back our base to set control over the center of the Zone. What's holding them back is resources stretched thin... or at least that was the case till recently. One of our squads was blasted to pieces by a Mi-24 helicopter. Only one man has lived to tell the story. We need to act before they gather more forces. \n \nNow - I won't say it's an easy mission... there's a big chance you'll not come out of it in one piece, but if you succeed, a good money will be waiting for you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_skyfall_finish">
		<text>Now that's my man! I don't think we'll need to worry about those fuckers after they saw your fireworks.</text>
	</string>
    <string id="skyfall_details">
        <text>Destroy the helicopter</text>
    </string>
	<string id="skyfall_stealth_message">
        <text>You sneaky bastard! So you've decided to take care of it silently. I couldn't have planned it better myself! Now don't screw it and try to plant some explosives somewhere where noone will see them.</text>
    </string>
	<string id="skyfall_run_fail_message">
        <text>So you've ran away... I had a feeling I've chosen the wrong person for this job...</text>
    </string>
	<string id="skyfall_confrontation_message">
        <text>You think we can't see you, stalker? Coming here was your last mistake.</text>
    </string>
	<string id="skyfall_cover_blow_message">
        <text>We've got a sneaky rat here!</text>
    </string>
	<string id="skyfall_blow_cover_run_message">
        <text>I see you! You're not gonna get away, stalker!</text>
    </string>

	<string id="bar_dolg_general_petrenko_stalker_task_hold_the_ground_name">
		<text>Hold the Ground</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_dolg_general_petrenko_stalker_task_hold_the_ground_text">
		<text>Bandits are preparing to storm the Garbage with big numbers and establish a full control over it. Petrenko asked me to bunker down at the Flea Market and push them back.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_dolg_general_petrenko_stalker_task_hold_the_ground_about">
		<text>Our scouts have reported a huge congregation of bandits close to the passage between the Dark Valley and Garbage. Letting them establish control over the Garbage is unacceptable. We do have problems with manpower though because of the damn hippies in the north... and that's why I'm going to send you on this mission alone. I know - it sounds like a madness, but you should receive some help from the loners that often visit that place, provided that they weren't already ambushed by some smaller detachment of bandits.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_dolg_general_petrenko_stalker_task_hold_the_ground_finish">
		<text>Great job, comrade! Here - this is for you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="hold_the_ground_on_position_message">
        <text>The enemy has started the advance! Prepare for battle, stalker!</text>
    </string>
	<string id="hold_the_ground_defended_position_message">
        <text>That should be the last of them. Report to me immediately stalker!</text>
    </string>
	<string id="hold_the_ground_run_fail_message">
        <text>Pathetic... shouldn't have trusted you on this job</text>
    </string>
	<string id="hold_the_ground_details">
        <text>Defend position</text>
    </string>

	<string id="cit_killers_merc_trader_stalker_task_no_step_back_name">
		<text>No Step Back</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cit_killers_merc_trader_stalker_task_no_step_back_text">
		<text>Mercenaries have been steadily loosing control over Limansk and Dushman is worried that the Dead City will soon be under attack by Monolith. I've got to take back the territory up to the bridge and destroy any possible reinforcements they might receive.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cit_killers_merc_trader_stalker_task_no_step_back_about">
		<text>Listen up mate - I've got a personal contract for you. The status quo in Limansk has been steadily shifting in favor of Monolith recently. We might have shinier gear, but they have weapon that we've been underestimating so far - zealotry.\n \nOur lucrative business around here might end soon - some of my contractors have already left this place, because they're afraid fanatics might come here any time. Here's the deal - go to Limansk and bring back the status quo - push Monolith back behind the bridge and destory any detachments that might try to cross it again.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cit_killers_merc_trader_stalker_task_no_step_back_finish">
		<text>Well done. Now we can go back to the business as usuall. Here - take it. I'll make it back in no time when the new contractors find out that it's safe here again.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="no_step_back_on_position_message">
        <text>Our radars are showing an enormous group of Monolithians coming to reinforce the lost position. Brace yourself!</text>
    </string>
	<string id="no_step_back_defended_position_message">
        <text>Great job, partner. Radars show no further hostile activity in the region. Now come - we have to talk.</text>
    </string>
	<string id="no_step_back_run_fail_message">
        <text>You've just lost your contract mate. Should have hired real fighters...</text>
    </string>
	<string id="no_step_back_details">
        <text>Defend position</text>
    </string>

	<string id="simulation_task_gambling_with_life_name">
		<text>Gambling with Life</text>
	</string>
	<string id="simulation_task_gambling_with_life_text">
		<text>I've accepted a bet with a Freedomer that I'll kill a healthy bloodsucker using only a knife. Hippies on high have weird ideas, but money is money, so...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="simulation_task_gambling_with_life_about">
		<text>Yesterday I've had a trip of my life with one of my dudes. I'm not sure where he took that shit from, but man... it was kicking as hell...\n \nAnyway - back on track. You see - we both like gambling and he came up with a fucked up dare. He said he'd bet a nice sum on anyone killing a bloodsucker using only a knife. One of our fellas - still high as fuck - overheard his talking and went out of the base that night. He never came back, but the bet still stands. Poor guy... wondering what happened to him...\n \nNow where was I? Ah, right - the bet! You seem like a tough guy. Wouldn't you like to try your luck? I'll mount a small camera on your suit so that I can later show that video to my pal. What - you didn't think that I'd tell you his name here, right? Want something for myself out of this as well.\n \nRemember - there's one catch - the mutant has to be healthy. My pal will be able to see any prior wounds on the video and there won't be a payout.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="simulation_task_gambling_with_life_finish">
		<text>You've really impressed me, man! Now let me take this recording to my friend. Here's your share.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gambling_with_life_details">
        <text>Fulfill the bet</text>
    </string>

	<string id="simulation_task_vengence_amplified_name">
		<text>Vengence Amplified</text>
	</string>
	<string id="simulation_task_vengence_amplified_text">
		<text>A bandit wants me to chop the chimera to pieces with an axe to avenge his friend. Taking on this task was probably a mistake...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="simulation_task_vengence_amplified_about">
		<text>You've heard about chimeras, right? Fucking huge and ugly bastards... to hell with them all! They've sent a brother of mine to the other side. We were patroling the perimieter at night and we were ambushed by one of these abominations. It jumped straight at my brother and tore his leg off. His screams alarmed the rest of the camp and we've managed to fend off the beast. It took too long though and my brother died of the blood loss...\n \nHere's the deal - strap this camera to your suit and chop off the leg of one of these bastards! Or you know what? Chop it to pieces! I want to see it suffer the unbearable pain!\n \nThey're really tough, so it will be fine if just the finishing blow will be made with an axe.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="simulation_task_vengence_amplified_finish">
		<text>You've been cruel in your methods, my friend. I appreciate it. Seeing the ferocity change into fear and the pain in the eyes of this beast made me feel... satisfied...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="vengence_amplified_details">
        <text>Chop the beast to pieces</text>
    </string>

	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_brain_game_name">
		<text>Brain Game</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_brain_game_text">
		<text>Sakharov needs a controller with undamaged brain to perform further research on its psi abilities.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_brain_game_about">
		<text>I'm always glad seeing young people so eager to contribute to scientific projects! You see - we've been researching the mysteries of the Zone for a very long time now and yet there's still so much to learn. One of the most fascinating and at the same time most dangerous marvels of the Zone are controllers. Stalkers usually tend to avoid confrontation with them and when it's inevitable, they - understandably so - want to eliminate it as soon as possible by shooting it to the head. That's why most of the brain samples we get are of very little use to us. It would be most appreciated if you'd kill one of these without damaging its brain and informed us of this event as soon as possible, so we can send a group that'd secure it and make sure it gets to us before its tissues start decomposing.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_brain_game_finish">
		<text>Thank you for your contribution to our scientific community, young lad.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="brain_game_details">
        <text>Hunt down the specimen</text>
    </string>
	<string id="brain_game_success_report">
        <text>Professor - I've managed to get you the specimen that you requested. I'm sending over the coordinates.</text>
    </string>
	<string id="brain_game_success_response">
        <text>Excellent job! I'll send one of our teams right away. Please do visit me at our bunker - your reward awaits.</text>
    </string>

	<string id="urgent_orders_name">
		<text>Urgent Orders</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_dolg_leader_task_urgent_orders_text">
		<text>A fellow Duty soldier has been critically wounded by a new type of bloodsucker and requires medical treatment from scientists. I need to hurry up!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_dolg_leader_task_urgent_orders_finish">
		<text>Great job, solider! You've saved your brother in arms. Keep up the good work.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_dolg_leader_task_urgent_orders_report">
        <text>Soldier! This is General Voronin! I've got an urgent order for you. One of our brothers was wounded and poisoned by some new kind of bloodsucker. Our medic is not able to help him. I've contacted Professor Sakharov asking for help and there is a chance that his experimental medicine might help our brother.\n \nYou need to depart towards Yantar at once and escort a group scientists to our base. Do not fail me, soldier!</text>
    </string>
	<string id="bar_dolg_leader_task_urgent_orders_scientists_response">
        <text>Greetings, lad! I've received information about your arrival from your general. My assistants have everything they need to cure your friend and will join you shortly.</text>
    </string>
	<string id="bar_dolg_leader_task_urgent_orders_fail">
        <text>Our brother just gave his last breath. You've failed me, soldier... you've failed all of us.</text>
    </string>

	<string id="agr_smart_terrain_1_6_near_2_military_colonel_kovalski_task_urgent_orders_text">
		<text>A fellow soldier has been critically wounded by a new type of bloodsucker and requires medical treatment from scientists. I need to hurry up!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="agr_smart_terrain_1_6_near_2_military_colonel_kovalski_task_urgent_orders_finish">
		<text>Great job, solider! You've saved your brother in arms. Dismissed.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="agr_smart_terrain_1_6_near_2_military_colonel_kovalski_task_urgent_orders_report">
        <text>Soldier! This is Colonel Kuznetsov! I've got an urgent order for you. One of our brothers was wounded and poisoned by some new kind of bloodsucker. Our medic is not able to help him. I've contacted Professor Sakharov asking for help and there is a chance that his experimental medicine might help our brother.\n \nYou need to depart towards Yantar at once and escort a group scientists to our base. Do not fail me, soldier!</text>
    </string>
	<string id="agr_smart_terrain_1_6_near_2_military_colonel_kovalski_task_urgent_orders_scientists_response">
        <text>Greetings, lad! I've received information about your arrival from Colonel Kuznetsov. My assistants have everything they need to cure your friend and will join you shortly.</text>
    </string>
	<string id="agr_smart_terrain_1_6_near_2_military_colonel_kovalski_task_urgent_orders_fail">
        <text>You're late, soldier... our medic just confirmed the demise. Pray for higher-in-command to not call for the court-martial.</text>
    </string>

	<string id="bar_visitors_barman_stalker_trader_task_baba_yaga_name">
		<text>Baba Yaga</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_visitors_barman_stalker_trader_task_baba_yaga_text">
		<text>Some stalkers have been observed to disappear in thin air at night around the Witches' Jelly anomaly trying to grab a seemingly free artifact. I need to investigate what's going on.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_visitors_barman_stalker_trader_task_baba_yaga_about">
		<text>When you're spending all your days in a place like this you hear a lot of interesting stories. Most of them are plain bullshit, but there's one that came from the Butcher himself. Man's quite a legend around here... tough guy made Garbage a habitable place... to an extent of course.\n \nNow to the story - right before calling it a day, the Butcher went outside of the hangar for a smoke. He saw a group of newbies from afar that stopped by the Witches' Jelly anomaly to pick up an artifact. After one of them reached out for it, they've disappeared in a brief flash. Their screams were heard from the woods for a few seconds. Butcher knew it's already too late to save them, so he stood there and waited. For a brief moment, he saw a thin silhouette of an elderly woman. He didn't feel like chasing a ghost at night, so he went there next day just to find bare bones of the stalkers. He tried to hunt down the monster during the day, but it never showed up. He warned all stalkers that passed by about it and that's how the story of Baba Yaga was born among the stalkers - you know... that scary old lady from children's tales living at the swamp or in the forest that abducts children venturing too far away from home.\n \nButcher has also paid me a visit recently. He was trying to find out what's haunting that place, but it seems like the monster is smart enough to avoid that killing machine. Since a lot more experienced stalkers visit Rostok, he asked me to find someone willing to deal with that hag. What do you say?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_visitors_barman_stalker_trader_task_baba_yaga_finish">
		<text>So the hag is real after all! The Zone will never stop to surprise me. You're saying you did not find the body? Too bad - let's hope she won't come back ever again.\n \n*muttering* Baba Yaga... holy fuck... *muttering*</text>
	</string>
	<string id="baba_yaga_details">
        <text>Investigate the place during the night</text>
    </string>

	<string id="mar_smart_terrain_base_stalker_leader_marsh_task_house_of_horrors_name">
		<text>House of Horrors</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mar_smart_terrain_base_stalker_leader_marsh_task_house_of_horrors_text">
		<text>An eviscerated body of Clear Sky member has been found at the north-eastern checkpoint. Cold has asked me to find out what's prowling out there at night.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mar_smart_terrain_base_stalker_leader_marsh_task_house_of_horrors_about">
		<text>You know - the swamp has always been a pretty dangerous place. We've fought hard to establish our base and safeguard the surroundings. Nowadays mutants rarely come close to us. Renegades are still assaulting our outer outpost from time to time, but they always regret their decisions.\n \nSpeaking of - something weird has been happening around there lately. Our lads have been reporting mysterious barking and whispers coming out of nowhere. Since there were not mutants to be found around, we've been ignoring... till one of our sentries' massacred body has been found behind the building after going to take a piss at night and not coming back for a long time.\n \nI've remembered one thing then... Back in the time when Lebedev was our leader, one old-timer loner dropped by our bar and told a story about a peaceful family with a dog that used to live in that place before the Chernobyl accident. The man has also started hearing voices which have driven him into madness. He lost his mind and killed his whole family in the sleep, including the dog. Next day, after realising what he's done, he hanged himself... I have a bad feeling that these incidents might be connected. We still need to keep that place guarded, but I cannot risk losing another man. Are you willing to look into this thing?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mar_smart_terrain_base_stalker_leader_marsh_task_house_of_horrors_finish">
		<text>I guess the old man was saying the truth then... what a story. We'll need to double our security there so it never happens again. Here - this is for you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="house_of_horrors_details">
        <text>Investigate the place during the night</text>
    </string>

	<string id="zat_a2_stalker_barmen_task_mirage_name">
		<text>Mirage</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_a2_stalker_barmen_task_mirage_text">
		<text>A rescued artifact hunter claims that he was shot by another stalker that looked exactly like him. Beard asked me to visit the place and have a look around.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_a2_stalker_barmen_task_mirage_about">
		<text>I've got a task for you. As you may already know, I always have some contracts from collectors for some rare artifacts and there's no better place to find them. One of my contractors has been recently brought back with a bullet in his guts after a trip to the Iron Forest. That bastard was lucky that someone catched his SOS signal. After waking up from anesthesia he said some unbelievable story.\n \nHe claims that when he was bowing down to pick up an artifact, he heard someone calling him. When he turned around, a person was standing not far behind him, aiming a gun straight at him. He immediately lost his shit when he realised that this person looked exactly like him, but didn't have time to panic, as right after that he took a bullet. After he fell and looked back again, the shooter was nowhere to be seen. He immediately sent an SOS and fainted not so long after. He was found by a squad that was not far from there. The rescuers were saying that they've all heard some whispers as they were leaving the place, but weren't so eager to find out what it was. Here's the deal - find out what's lurking in that place and you'll get some good money, eh?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_a2_stalker_barmen_task_mirage_finish">
		<text>Woah... I knew burers can manipulate the matter, but didn't expect they can do this to this extent! I don't think visitors will believe me when I'll tell them your story. Here, you've earned it.\n \nGood hunting, stalker... *laughs*</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mirage_details">
        <text>Investigate the place</text>
    </string>

	<string id="jup_b220_trapper_task_big_game_name">
		<text>Big Game</text>
	</string>
	<string id="jup_b220_trapper_task_big_game_text">
		<text>A band of pseudogiants have taken refuge in the southern train tunnel in Jupiter. Trapper asked me to take care of them.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="jup_b220_trapper_task_big_game_about">
		<text>Are you interested in improving your hunting skills? The scientists from the bunker have reported a loud rumbling and roars coming out from the souther train tunnel and offered a hefty price for anyone willing to investigate the site and take care of the potential threat. Without a doubt it has to be a pseudogiant... or even a pair of them. Perfect opportunity for honing your skills in taking down these majestic yet dangerous monsters. What do you say? Are you up for some big game hunting?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="jup_b220_trapper_task_big_game_finish">
		<text>What a story! I didn't think pseudogiants can reach these sizes... now I regret I didn't come back from my retirement just to claim that kill for myself. Anyway, here's the bounty.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="big_game_details">
        <text>Investigate the place</text>
    </string>

	<string id="agr_smart_terrain_1_6_near_2_military_colonel_kovalski_task_enforce_embargo_name">
		<text>Enforce Embargo</text>
	</string>
	<string id="agr_smart_terrain_1_6_near_2_military_colonel_kovalski_task_enforce_embargo_text">
		<text>A stalker is planning to sell an artifact to a collector from outside the Zone. I need to intercept it and bring it back to the Colonel.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="agr_smart_terrain_1_6_near_2_military_colonel_kovalski_task_enforce_embargo_about">
		<text>At ease, soldier. There's one thing that needs to be taken care of. Our undercover agent has overheard a chat between two stalkers in 100 Rads bar. They've been talking about their most recent contract on delivering one of those shiny things called artifacts to a collector outside the perimeter - quite uncommon one to be precise. That's where we come in. You need to intercept that thing and bring it back to me, understood?\n \nOne more thing - if the target dies and the package gets intercepted by someone else, that's on you. You're also not supposed to break the seal on the box. We'd like to pay a visit to the client and have a nice talk with him.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="agr_smart_terrain_1_6_near_2_military_colonel_kovalski_task_enforce_embargo_finish">
		<text>Great job, soldier - keep it up. Dismissed.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_cold_blooded_betrayal_name">
		<text>Cold-blooded Betrayal</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_cold_blooded_betrayal_text">
		<text>Sidorovich asked me to bring an ex-loner that killed his squadmates to justice. I also need to bring back an artifact that was the cause of his crimes.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_cold_blooded_betrayal_about">
		<text>I've got a rather unusual artifact-hunting job for you. I've received a request for an uncommon artifact from a client beyond the perimeter and the contract was picked up shortly after by a group of two newbies led by some more experienced guy. Two days later I've received a message from them that they've found it around the Garbage and are heading back next day. I was kinda surprised by that... you usually find just some trash around there.\n \nNow to the interesting part. They've decided to spend the night at the hangar. The Butcher mentioned that one of them was particularly nervous after having some beef with the group leader. Just a moment before laying down to get some sleep, he heard shots coming from the campfire's direction and loud steps of someone dashing out of the hangar. When he got to the campfire with his gun in the hands, he saw only two bodies and none of them was the suspicious guy that he remembered. He found a note about the contract on leader's body and let me know about the incident.\n \nThat bastard has probably seen an artifact like this for the first time and decided to kill his brothers just to snatch it, while also double-crossing me. That was his last mistake. Put the bullet in his head and bring back what he stole.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_cold_blooded_betrayal_finish">
		<text>So the justice has been served... Good job, stalker.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="val_smart_terrain_7_4_bandit_trader_stalker_task_shakedown_name">
		<text>Shakedown</text>
	</string>
	<string id="val_smart_terrain_7_4_bandit_trader_stalker_task_shakedown_text">
		<text>Olivius wants me to bring him an artifact that scientists found on the bandits' turf.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="val_smart_terrain_7_4_bandit_trader_stalker_task_shakedown_about">
		<text>Listen up, mate. As you should already know, we call this place ours and we treat it really seriously. From time to time we have visitors that seem to not understand that and they usually end bad. Our boys have spotted a group of eggheads sniffing around the Glowing Pit. Since they usually carry some advanced artifact detectors and that place is quite dangerous, our boys decided to let the eggheads do the dirty job and then take whatever they find there from their dead bodies. When they spotted that our guests are packing some sparkling goodies to the lead box, one of our best shots lifted his SKS, getting ready to shoot. Right at that same moment his head literally exploded... he took a sniper round to the head. The rest of his squad did not know where the shot came from, so they ran for their lives as fast as they could. When a bigger group went back there, they were nowhere to be found. They also took our dead brother's stuff.\n \nIt's us who take stuff from others here - not the other way around... Find these bastards, teach them this lesson and bring the box back to me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="val_smart_terrain_7_4_bandit_trader_stalker_task_shakedown_finish">
		<text>Hah - there it is. It won't bring our brother back to life, but will definitely lift the spirits around.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_stolen_specimen_name">
		<text>Stolen Specimen</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_stolen_specimen_text">
		<text>Scientists have lost a rare artifact to the Sin squad. I've agreed to retrieve it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_stolen_specimen_about">
		<text>I think I might have a job for you. We've sent an expedition to Limansk recently aiming to do some measurements of anomalous activities in that region. Since it's a place of constant battle between mercenaries and Monolith forces, we've decided to hire some experts from their ranks to cover our colleagues. Everything went according to the plan... up to some point.\n \nOur lads have gathered the required data and found some pretty rare artifact. When they've been preparing to depart, a strong emission hit the place. They took cover in the basement of a nearby building. When things went quiet, the mercenaries went outside to scout the surroundings. Not long after our colleagues heard a shootout. They didn't even have time to grab their guns when a grenade landed in the basement, tearing two scientists into pieces. The last one - barely alive - crawled to the farthest wall, holding on to the container with the artifact. Three men with pale faces entered the basement, aiming the gun at him. When their leader saw the container, he reached out with his hand and pointed at it. Not thinking twice, the survivor tossed the box at him, already saying his prayers. The fanatics however did not end his life, seeing he's already dying. They've grabbed the box and left in silence. Our lad fainted at that moment and was found by a nearby squad of mercenaries that arrived late at the place. Thankfully, he's alive.\n \nHere's my request. We need that artifact back. It's a crucial reference for the gathered data. The box had a GPS tracker on it, so you'll be able to find those fanatics. I'm a pacifist, but there's no reasoning with a blind faith. Do what you have to do.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_stolen_specimen_finish">
		<text>Great job, lad. Now we can continue our research... in memory of our fallen colleagues.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="trader_pri_a15_mlr_task_blood_stained_coin_name">
		<text>Blood-stained Coin</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trader_pri_a15_mlr_task_blood_stained_coin_text">
		<text>The Cashier tasked me with retrieving a rare artifact that was taken by the squad of ISG scientists.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trader_pri_a15_mlr_task_blood_stained_coin_about">
		<text>You look like someone that likes to take some risk, huh? I've got a very lucrative contract for a rare artifact. In fact, another stalker brought me that artifact a few days ago. You might ask why is the contract still standing, right? Well... a squad of very dangerous people was tailing that stalker. When we were about to make a deal here, they've stormed inside, taking everyone by surprise. You could tell right away they were all experts in their craft - wearing some top notch armor and barrels. No shots were fired however - we knew we were doomed, so we surrendered. Their leader slowly approached me, punched me in the face with his ironclad fist and took the container with artifact and the payment that was prepared for the stalker. He warned us that if anyone was to follow them, they'd leave noone alive here. So we just stayed there the whole day...\n \nThe original contractor wasn't happy with how things turned out. The box had a GPS tracker on it, so he went out to look for these men. Given that I haven't seen him in a long time, I assume he's biting the dust. We had no luck finding a similar artifact and the client is getting impatient. So I've been thinking - would you be willing to pay them back in my name and bring back the package?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trader_pri_a15_mlr_task_blood_stained_coin_finish">
		<text>Color me impressed, stalker. I didn't expect to see you back alive. Here - you've earned it.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="jup_a6_stalker_barmen_task_the_keepsake_name">
		<text>The Keepsake</text>
	</string>
	<string id="jup_a6_stalker_barmen_task_the_keepsake_text">
		<text>I've agreed to avenge the death of certain stalker's brother and bring back the cause of his death as a keepsake.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="jup_a6_stalker_barmen_task_the_keepsake_about">
		<text>Listen, friend. You're not afraid to kill for money, right? Especially when it comes to scumbags...\nHere's the thing - some stalker visited Yanov few days ago. His face was expressionless... I knew he saw some shit. He came up to me and ordered two bottles of vodka. He just stood here in silence, taking a sip after sip, looking at the bottom of his mug. It wasn't even one hour when one bottle was gone. Then he finally broke the silence with these words - "Today I've lost my brother... not like a true friend, but an actual brother...". He then proceeded to tell me the whole story. They've came to Jupiter for their last contract before leaving the Zone for good. They've agreed to find some very rare artifact for a good price and this place seemed perfect for that task - far enough north and relatively safe. After few days of searching, they've found one at the Concrete Bath anomaly... or rather his brother found one when he went a bit away into the bushes to do his business. When he was about to go back, he heard a sniper rifle shot and short after saw his brother falling on the ground. He took cover in the bushes again. A squad of heavily armored Monolith fanatics approached his body. The stalker knew he couldn't do anything at this point. They took the container with the artifact, threw the body into the anomaly and left shortly after. Before he managed to get close, his brother's body has already dissolved.\n \nHe didn't care about the contract at this point. He left a good chunk of money here with the contact info and said that whoever kills those bastards and brings back the artifact can have it. He wants it as a memento. What do you say? It seems like a very noble cause. The box had a localizer on hit, so you won't have issues finding the target, though you might need to go to some dangerous place.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="jup_a6_stalker_barmen_task_the_keepsake_finish">
		<text>You've done a good thing today, stalker. Our friend has already left the Zone, but I'll make sure that this package gets to him.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- The Living Fire -->
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_task_the_living_fire_name">
		<text>The Living Fire</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_task_the_living_fire_text">
		<text>Snitch wants me to find out more about the recent rumors about a mysterious stalker that seemingly can control the fire.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_task_the_living_fire_about">
		<text>You know my friend - knowledge is power... and I'm the one who likes to know a lot and turn that power into something more useful - money. There's one thing that I don't know yet and that would lead to me making some small fortune. There's a rumor going around about a stalker that showed up recently in the Zone who - reportedly - has some kind of power to manipulate the fire. At first I thought it's just a rumour like many that go around, but when some important people started asking me whether I know more, I've realizsed there's something in it. Even Colonel Petrenko has recently dropped by and asked me some questions, as they've found two of their soldiers burnt to crisp at the Truck Cemetery where there was no thermal anomalies. I don't think I have to tell you that saying "I don't know" to most of his questions brought me no money, right? So here's the deal - you find out more about that guy and I pay you some good money. Are you in?\n \nMy friend at the Flea Market reported that there's been some weird stuff happening at the Garbage recently. I'd start my search by talking with him.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_informator_mlr_task_the_living_fire_finish">
		<text>Pleasure doing business with you, partner! Now let me contact all my clients. I'm sure they will gladly pay to find out more about our friend. Drop by some time later. I feel like we've picked up the trail something big and there's more money to be made here.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_prometheus_name">
		<text>Prometheus</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_mysterious_stalker_name">
		<text>Mysterious Stalker</text>
	</string>

	<string id="the_living_fire_garbage_actor_msg_1">
		<text>What was that sound?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_garbage_prometheus_msg_1">
		<text>Filthy mutant - begone...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_garbage_actor_msg_2">
		<text>Who are...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_garbage_prometheus_msg_2">
		<text>You will know my name... Everyone will...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_garbage_actor_msg_3">
		<text>What the hell just happened? I have a bad feeling about this...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_swamp_actor_msg_1">
		<text>Fuck... I'm late.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_swamp_sakharov_msg_1">
		<text>What happened there, stalker? Our readings went off scale again! It looks like the anomaly is branching. We need to stop this!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_swamp_sakharov_msg_2">
		<text>You've done it! The readings are going back to normal again. Come back to me. We need to talk.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_yantar_snitch_msg_1">
		<text>Oi, stalker! Are you still alive? I'm still waiting here for you report from Yantar.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_yantar_actor_msg_1">
		<text>Yeah... I was about to head back to you. I'll meet you soon.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_dark_valley_actor_msg_1">
		<text>I guess those are the unlucky soldiers...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_x18_prometheus_msg_1">
		<text>You're very persistent, stalker... Very well - come up to me. I guess you want to chat.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_x18_military_msg_1">
		<text>Unit 1 and 2 - safeguard the retreat route. Rest - search the last level. Open fire on sight, take no prisoners.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_bar_actor_msg_1">
		<text>I should visit Sidorovich and ask him if he knows something more about Prometheus. If he finds out in what deep shit he's in, he'll probably quickly remember everything.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_escape_sakharov_msg_1">
		<text>Stalker - you need to come to my bunker immediately! We've spotted a great increase in anomalous activity nearby.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_yantar_barman_msg_1">
		<text>Hey stalker. I've seen Snitch talking with some shady people - some big money was involved. I've heard you two had some beef and I know you were his main source of information regarding Prometheus. You better watch your back.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_x16_prometheus_msg_1">
		<text>It's you again, stalker. I really admire your dedication. I guess you want to continue our previous conversation...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_red_forest_actor_msg_1">
		<text>Professor - I've managed to clear the region around the anomaly.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_red_forest_sakharov_msg_1">
		<text>Good job, lad. I've managed to convince the military about the urgency of this matter. They've agreed to help. We'll be waiting for your signal.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_red_forest_actor_msg_2">
		<text>I guess those were the people that Barman has warned me about. It's time to pay Snitch a visit...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_bar_actor_msg_2">
		<text>Professor - I know where Prometheus will execute his ultimate plan. I'll head there as soon as possible. Be ready for my signal.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_bar_sakharov_msg_1">
		<text>Great news, young man. I wish you good luck. Don't forget to take the weapon you've mentioned. Aim straight at the head. We might have only one chance to stop him.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_outskirts_actor_msg_1">
		<text>Professor - tell the military to get in positions.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_outskirts_prometheus_msg_1">
		<text>You're here... Witness the birth of the new world order.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_outskirts_prometheus_msg_2">
		<text>You can't stop it anymore... Brothers - aid me!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_outskirts_sakharov_msg_1">
		<text>The soldiers are on positions. Give the sig...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_outskirts_actor_msg_2">
		<text>Now! Do it NOW!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_outskirts_prometheus_msg_3">
		<text>What? What's... you! It's your doing!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_outskirts_actor_msg_3">
		<text>Now's my only chance!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_outskirts_actor_msg_4">
		<text>It's over professor. Prometheus is gone.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="the_living_fire_outskirts_sakharov_msg_2">
		<text>Great job, young man! I'm awaiting you at the bunker. I've got something for you.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_tlf_prometheus">
		<text>Prometheus</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_tlf_prometheus_descr">
		<text>A unique artifact that was born in the Greek Fire after the stalker of the legend with the same name has been slain. It gives the user immense resistance to heat and makes the wounds heal faster.</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- The Living Fire end -->

	<string id="nta_intercept_item">
		<text>Intercept an item:</text>
	</string>
</string_table>
