<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<string_table>

<string id="st_wpn_steyr_scout">
		<text>Steyr Scout 5.56</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_steyr_scout_descr">
		<text>The Steyr Scout sniper rifle is a renowned firearm celebrated for its exceptional accuracy and versatility. Chambered in 5.56x45mm ammunition, this rifle combines precision with portability, making it a favorite among marksmen and military professionals. Its compact design and lightweight construction allow for easy maneuverability in various tactical scenarios, while its robust build ensures durability and reliability in the field. Equipped with advanced optics and a user-friendly interface, the Steyr Scout offers quick target acquisition and superior performance at medium to long-range distances. With its 5.56x45mm chambering, it delivers impressive stopping power and exceptional ballistic performance, making it an ideal choice for both urban and open-field operations. \n \n
				%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
        %c[d_purple] - %c[ui_gray_2] Surefire SOCOM556-MONSTER suppressor. \n \n</text>
	</string>

<string id="st_wpn_steyr_scout_big">
		<text>Steyr Scout 7.62</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_steyr_scout_big_descr">
		<text>The Steyr Scout sniper rifle is a highly regarded firearm known for its precision and adaptability. Chambered in the powerful 7.62x51mm ammunition, this rifle combines formidable stopping power with impressive accuracy, making it a favorite among marksmen and military professionals. Its ergonomic design and lightweight construction allow for easy handling and swift target acquisition, ensuring effectiveness in various tactical situations. The Steyr Scout's robust build guarantees durability and reliability in the harshest environments, making it a trusted choice for snipers and sharpshooters. With its 7.62x51mm chambering, it delivers excellent long-range performance, making it ideal for engaging targets at extended distances with high accuracy and lethal impact. \n \n
				%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
        %c[d_purple] - %c[ui_gray_2] Daniel Defence Wave QD suppressor. \n \n</text>
	</string>

<string id="st_mag_steyr_556">
		<text>Steyr Scout 5.56 magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_steyr_556_descr">
		<text>Standard magazine for the Steyr Scout 5.56 rifle. \n \n</text>
	</string>	

<string id="st_mag_steyr_762">
		<text>Steyr Scout 7.62 magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_steyr_762_descr">
		<text>Standard magazine for the Steyr Scout 7.62 rifle. \n \n</text>
	</string>		
</string_table>
