<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<!--===========================================================
<
< TEXT  STRINGS FOR TASKS ON ESCAPE (CORDON) MAP
<	CoC 1.4.08 - DoctorX Questlines 1.6
<
<	Modified by: DoctorX
<	Last revised: October 07, 2016
<
<===========================================================-->

<string_table>


	<!-- /////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////
	<!--
	<!-- STORYLINE TASK TEXT  STRINGS
	<!--
	<!--	Modified by DoctorX
	<!--	for DoctorX Questlines 1.6
	<!--	October 07, 2016
	<!--
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Sidorovich (Loner Trader) Default Storyline Task -->

	<string id="drx_sl_esc_m_trader_default_task_name">
		<text>Get Next Task</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_m_trader_default_task_text">
		<text>Sidorovich has given me a contact who has some work lined up. I shouldn't keep him waiting.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_m_trader_default_task_about">
		<text>I don't have anything for you, but I know someone who might. I've marked his location on your map.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_m_trader_default_task_finish">
		<text>Good luck stalker.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Sidorovich (Loner Trader) Mutant Safari Storyline Task -->

	<string id="drx_sl_esc_m_trader_task_1_name">
		<text>Mutant Safari</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_m_trader_task_1_text">
		<text>I have been tasked to lead a group of tourists on a mutant hunt.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_m_trader_task_1_about">
		<text>I have a group of tourists coming through and they want to see what it's like to kill a mutant. Take them out on a hunt, give them a thrill. Just make sure they don't get themselves killed. It's bad for business.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_m_trader_task_1_finish">
		<text>Back from the hunt? Good. Here is your payment.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Sidorovich (Loner Trader) Rookie Initiation Storyline Task- -->

	<string id="drx_sl_esc_m_trader_task_2_name">
		<text>Rookie Initiation</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_m_trader_task_2_text">
		<text>I've agreed to take a group of rookies into the Zone and show them how to survive.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_m_trader_task_2_about">
		<text>The new rookies in the camp are very green. I'm concerned they won't last a day in the Zone. It's bad for business if they die, you see? That many less customers for me. I want you to take them on an expedition into the Zone. Tell them what to watch out for, show them an anomoly, teach them how to stay alive.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_m_trader_task_2_finish">
		<text>Ah, my customers are still alive. And they need to buy more ammo from me, hehe. Thank you stalker. Take this for your trouble.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Xenotech (Loner Mechanic) Default Storyline Task -->

	<string id="drx_sl_esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_default_task_name">
		<text>Get Next Task</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_default_task_text">
		<text>Xenotech knows a guy who might need my help. I should go see who it is.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_default_task_about">
		<text>A friend of mine could use your services. I've marked his location on your map.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_default_task_finish">
		<text>Good luck stalker.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Xenotech (Loner Mechanic) Rescue Missing Stalker Storyline Task -->

	<string id="drx_sl_esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_1_name">
		<text>Rescue Missing Stalker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_1_text">
		<text>A stalker is missing from Xenotech's camp. I must find him.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_1_about">
		<text>I need your help. A stalker from my camp went out for supplies and hasn't come back. I fear something may have happened to him. I will mark his last known location on your map, see if you can find him.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_1_finish">
		<text>You saved him! Excellent work stalker. Take this as a sign of my gratitude.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Xenotech (Loner Mechanic) Track Wounded Attacker Storyline Task -->

	<string id="drx_sl_esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_2_name">
		<text>Track Wounded Attacker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_2_text">
		<text>A rogue military squad attacked Xenotech's camp and murdered them. One of the attackers managed to escape. I've been asked to track him down.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_2_about">
		<text>Where have you been? A military squad came through here and tore up the place. Between them and that damn helicopter they wiped out nearly everyone in the camp. We were able to take out most of them, but one of them managed to get away. He may be injured, see if you can follow the blood trail. I'll show you the direction he was headed.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_2_finish">
		<text>Thank you stalker. Take this as a gift for your actions.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- \\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\ -->


	<!-- /////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////
	<!--
	<!-- CHANGE FACTIONS TASK TEXT  STRINGS
	<!--
	<!--	Modified by DoctorX
	<!--	for DoctorX Questlines 1.6
	<!--	October 07, 2016
	<!--
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Sidorovich (Loner Trader) Payoff Change Factions Task -->

	<string id="drx_sl_esc_m_trader_cf_task_1_name">
		<text>Burning Bridges</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_m_trader_cf_task_1_text">
		<text>Sidorovich will get me out of my current faction commitments for a modest fee of 10,000 RU.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_m_trader_cf_task_1_about">
		<text>Well, it's good you've come to me then. I have a lot of connections here in the Zone. I can get you out of your commitment to your faction, but it won't be cheap. I will need to grease some palms, you know. If you can get me, say... 10,000 RU I'll see what I can do for you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_esc_m_trader_cf_task_1_finish">
		<text>Ah, this should do well. I'll make the necessary arrangements, enjoy your new life as a Free Stalker.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- \\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\ -->


	<!-- /////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////
	<!--
	<!-- DYNAMIC TASK TEXT  STRINGS
	<!--
	<!--	Modified by DoctorX
	<!--	for DoctorX Questlines 1.6
	<!--	October 07, 2016
	<!--
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Sidorovich (Loner Trader) Eliminate Car Park Bandits Task -->

	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_1_name">
		<text>Assault the Car Park</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_1_text">
		<text>Stage an assault on the car park and eliminate the bandits that occupy the location.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_1_about">
		<text>Bandits have taken up base in the old car park. Those assholes mug or kill anyone who use the roads leading in and out of the camp. It's disrupting local activities for my clients and the stalkers who take refuge in camp. It's hurting business! I need you to 'take care' of them. Talk to Fanatic if you need any help.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_1_finish">
		<text>Great work, stalker! You and I will be best of friends if you keep this up! Here is what I promised.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_2_name">
		<text>Contract Killer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_2_text">
		<text>I've agreed to remove a thorn from Sidorovich's side. Once I'm done, I should return for my reward.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_2_about">
		<text>I have a list of outstanding bounties that need taking care of. These people tend to be unwanted plotters, frauds, slanderers... many of them have even roughed up my couriers or harassed my tourists in the past. In other words, they're all bad for business.\n \nPut one of these scumbags out of my misery, won't you? I'll be happy, the Zone will be a cleaner place, and you'll be well paid. Everyone wins!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_2_finish">
		<text>You got rid of that filthy freak? Good riddance! Here is what I promised, and let it never be said that uncle Sidorovich doesn't reward good work.</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Sidorovich (Loner Trader) Decimate the Enemy Task -->

	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_3_name">
		<text>Mobbing the Mob</text>
	</string>	
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_3_text">
		<text>Sidorovich wants to send the bandit leaders a message. I've agreed to help him out by collecting %s.</text>
	</string>		
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_3_about">
		<text>Listen, stalker. This is supposed to be a safe place for rookies to get to know the Zone. What they do get to know are the business ends of some bandit guns instead. The thugs disrupt our routes and steal our loot. Go teach them a lesson, will ya?</text>
	</string>		
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_3_fetch_about">
		<text>Recently, some dandy bandit lord, up in Dark Valley, has decided to make another move on my business.  He calls himself something stupid, like Sultana. What's next? Riesling? Muscadine?\n \nSo, let's send the bloated grape a message. Remind him who the real boss is. I know his men are skulking about - they usually make their way down to the Cordon through Darkscape or Meadow to harass the rookies and disrupt my routes. I'd like you to do me a favour and off a few of them. Then, bring me their %ses, and I'll sort out the rest. </text>
	</string>		
	<string id="esc_m_trader_task_3_fetch_finish">
		<text>Finally, you're back. You've got the badges? All right, here is your reward. I'll handle the rest.</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Wolf (Loner Honcho) -->
	
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_1_name">
		<text>Eliminate the Mutant Threat from Cordon</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_1_text">
		<text>I've agreed to clear out a mutant lair for Wolf, which will no doubt make life much easier for stalkers in Cordon. I'll need to return to him for payment once the job is complete.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_1_about">
		<text>Though this is the border of the Zone, newbies have it tough even here. The bandits are only half the problem - they at least understand Russian. But the mutants - it's really tough with them. If you're an able hunter, there's a mutant lair not far from here that needs to be cleared out. If you manage to do this, I'll owe you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_1_finish">
		<text>Thank you, stalker. Maybe the rookies around here will take this chance to learn a thing or two before becoming pig food. Ah, right. I said I'd owe you. Here's your payment.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Wolf (Loner Honcho) Stalker Search and Rescue Dynamic Task -->

	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_2_name">
		<text>Spring Cleaning</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_2_text">
		<text>Bandits have harrassed Cordon Loners for a long enough time: it's time for a payback. Purge all the Bandits from Cordon.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_2_about">
		<text>Bandits have always been an issue around here in Cordon. Our brothers simply go wandering around the base to find themselves ambushed by bandits. If they are lucky enough they survive, but we have lost enough of our friends to the hands of these mongrels. It's time to make them pay: clean Cordon for the Bandits groups we have spotted. Will you do this? Otherwise, I'll need to go myself, and I don't want to leave the village only half-guarded.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_2_finish">
		<text>Good job, stalker. Bandits will not annoy us anymore. Your job is done. Here's your reward. </text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Wolf (Loner Honcho) Stalker Guide Dynamic Task -->

	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_3_name">
		<text>Tourist Safari</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_3_text">
		<text>Wolf has trusted me to guide some tourists on their mutant hunt.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_3_about">
		<text>Some foreign tourists have paid Sidorovich good money to go on a light hunting trip through the Zone. They're actually not bad shots, but they don't know the first thing about anomalies or the kind of monsters we have around here. As if I wasn't babysitting enough people already.\n \nCould you be their guide? Nothing fancy - people like this are usually happy with a short stroll through Cordon with some shooting at the end. Just make sure they don't do anything stupid. It'd save me a little headache, and it's ample pay for simple work.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_wolf_task_3_finish">
		<text>Okay, looks like the tourists got what they asked for. Sidorovich will be pleased. As for you, here's your cut.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Nimble (Loner Trader) Find Weapon Task -->

	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_nimble_task_1_name">
		<text>Find %s</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_nimble_task_1_text">
		<text>Nimble has asked you to find a specific firearm. It needs to be in mint condition. Return to him when you find what he is looking for.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_nimble_task_1_about">
		<text>I have a client looking for a specific firearm and I need someone to help me find it. If you are interested I will give you more details. What do you say?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_nimble_task_1_fetch_about">
		<text>%s... That is what I need, but it must be in mint condition. The client is paying top dollar, and he doesn't want a rusty piece of shit that will jam up in a life or death situation. I'll give you most of the profit since you are doing all the work. Come back when you find it, man.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_nimble_task_1_fetch_finish">
		<text>This is a fine weapon. I think my client will be pleased when I deliver this to him. Here is what I owe you.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Nimble (Loner Trader) Retrieve PDA Dynamic Task -->

	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_nimble_task_2_name">
		<text>Retrieve PDA for Nimble</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_nimble_task_2_text">
		<text>Nimble has a PDA he needs retrieved.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_nimble_task_2_about">
		<text>I need you to pick up a PDA for me. It's hidden in a spot a little while away from here.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_nimble_task_2_finish">
		<text>Thank you stalker!</text>
	</string>

	<!-- \\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\ -->


	<!-- /////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////
	<!--
	<!-- MECHANIC TASK TEXT  STRINGS
	<!--
	<!--	Modified by DoctorX
	<!--	for DoctorX Questlines 1.6
	<!--	October 07, 2016
	<!--
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Xenotech (Loner Mechanic) Find Level 1 Toolkit Task -->

	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_1_name">
		<text>Find %s for Xenotech</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_1_text">
		<text>%s are required by Xenotech to install basic equipment upgrades, I should bring them back to him if I find any.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_1_about">
		<text>I need a favour, man. A lot of stalkers have come by here asking if I can tune their weapons a certain way but I can't. Between the bandits and the military, I've lost all my tools. If you could get me some more - even just some basic ones - I could start performing upgrades on equipment and maybe help the Cordon become more than just a place for rookies. So, man, will you help me out?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_1_fetch_about">
		<text>Great! I'll pay a real premium for the kit, too - much more than you'd get selling it to Sidorovich or any other trader. Once you have the goods, well, you know where to find me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_1_fetch_finish">
		<text>Finally! I've been looking forward to holding a half-decent set of tools in my hands. As for you, here; take this as my way of saying thanks.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_2_name">
		<text>Find %s for Xenotech</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_2_text">
		<text>%s are required by Xenotech to install advanced equipment upgrades, I should bring them back to him if I find any.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_2_about">
		<text>My business is starting to grow a bit, thanks to the tools you brought me, but I could really use a better set so I can keep up with the demand. You brought me a decent toolkit last time, but I'll need something of real quality now. If you find me an advanced set of tools, I'll pay you well.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_2_fetch_about">
		<text>You're just full of good news, aren't you? Take care of yourself out there.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_2_fetch_finish">
		<text>Yes, yes! This is just what I needed! Help yourself to some roubles, stalker. Your help is appreciated.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_3_name">
		<text>Find %s for Xenotech</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_3_text">
		<text>%s are required by Xenotech to install expert equipment upgrades, I should bring them back to him if I find any.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_3_about">
		<text>My business is booming now; more and more stalkers come to me when they need their weapon fine-tuned... but I know I could do better. You brought me a quality toolkit last time, but I need an even higher quality set. If you're up for it, I need a set of tools worthy of an expert. So, will you go find this for me?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_3_fetch_about">
		<text>Thank you, stalker. Remember, these are expert tools for calibration work. Try not to break them on a pseudogiant or something. But in all seriousness - I appreciate you agreeing to do this. Take care.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_smart_terrain_5_7_loner_mechanic_stalker_task_3_fetch_finish">
		<text>You've proven yourself a true friend, stalker. You'll always be welcome in my workshop.</text>
	</string>
	
	
<!-- (Military Trader - Southern Outpost) -->
	<string id="esc_3_16_military_trader_task_1_name">
		<text>Cordon Crackdown</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_3_16_military_trader_task_1_text">
		<text>The checkpoint commander, Major Zhurov, has asked me to bring %s. It should help remind stalkers who's in charge.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_3_16_military_trader_task_1_about">
		<text>The top brass has launched an unofficial program, you wanna take part? As proof, I require patches from criminals in the Zone.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_3_16_military_trader_task_1_fetch_about">
		<text>The top brass has launched an unofficial program. While we've been asked to avoid the nearby village, we need to show the locals that we're still a force to be respected and obeyed. Shoot down any illegals you find on sight, and collect their patches as proof. Once you have enough %ses, return to me for a nice bonus to your paycheck. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_3_16_military_trader_task_1_fetch_finish">
		<text>Your actions have gone above and beyond the call of duty. Here, take your commendation and be proud today.</text>
	</string>

	
<!-- (Military Mechanic - Southern Outpost) -->
	<string id="army_south_mechan_mlr_task_1_name">
		<text>Find %s for Seryoga</text>
	</string>
	<string id="army_south_mechan_mlr_task_1_text">
		<text>Seryoga, a military technician, has asked me to find %s.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="army_south_mechan_mlr_task_1_about">
		<text>I do, actually. A while back, all our tools were ordered to the research complex in Yantar, which is why I can't even repair the BTR here. I need tools - basic ones. Mind helping out?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="army_south_mechan_mlr_task_1_fetch_about">
		<text>I do, actually. A while back, all our tools were ordered to the research complex in Yantar, which is why I can't even repair the BTR here. I need tools - basic ones. Do you think you can acquire a set for me, off the books?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="army_south_mechan_mlr_task_1_fetch_finish">
		<text>Let me see... wow, these really are basic, aren't they? Still, they're better than what I had been left with by our quartermaster. Here's a little something to say thanks.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="army_south_mechan_mlr_task_2_name">
		<text>Find %s for Seryoga</text>
	</string>
	<string id="army_south_mechan_mlr_task_2_text">
		<text>Seryoga, a military technician, has asked me to find %s.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="army_south_mechan_mlr_task_2_about">
		<text>Sadly, the tools that you gave me aren't enough, as they only work for the most basic of upgrades. I need more advanced tools. Since I doubt logistics is going to send us any anytime soon, could you find some for me?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="army_south_mechan_mlr_task_2_fetch_about">
		<text>Sadly, the tools that you gave me aren't enough, as they only work for the most basic of upgrades. I need more advanced tools. Since I doubt logistics is going to send us any anytime soon, could you find some for me?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="army_south_mechan_mlr_task_2_fetch_finish">
		<text>Alright, let's take a look... okay, these are good. It's not enough for the BTR, but maybe now I can buff up the armour of the conscripts around here. That'll be good for morale - no one wants to go around thinking they'll die to a stiff breeze. As for your reward, here. You did well.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="army_south_mechan_mlr_task_3_name">
		<text>Find %s for Seryoga</text>
	</string>
	<string id="army_south_mechan_mlr_task_3_text">
		<text>Seryoga, a military technician, has asked me to find %s.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="army_south_mechan_mlr_task_3_about">
		<text>Alright, so the bad news is that nothing is going to bring this particular BTR back to life. The good news is that we won't have to. Some Military Stalkers are showing an interest in my work. It's time to get our guys equipped with some proper gear. But for me to do that, I'll need the best tools in the Zone - calibration tools. I can assign you to recover some. Are you up for that?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="army_south_mechan_mlr_task_3_fetch_about">
		<text>Alright, so the bad news is that nothing is going to bring this particular BTR back to life. The good news is that we won't have to. Some Military Stalkers are showing an interest in my work. It's time to get our guys equipped with some proper gear. But for me to do that, I'll need the best tools in the Zone - calibration tools. I can assign you to recover some. Are you up for that?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="army_south_mechan_mlr_task_3_fetch_finish">
		<text>You know, I never thought I'd see the day where I'd have access to such sophisticated equipment again. I thank you, on behalf of all military forces in the Zone. Your contribution today will doubtless save many lives.</text>
	</string>

	
<!-- Fanatic -->
	<string id="task_fanat_training_1_1">
		<text>Training Day: Boar Hunting</text>
	</string>
	<string id="task_fanat_training_1_3">
		<text>Training Day: Speak to Fanatic</text>
	</string>
	<string id="task_fanat_training_1_4">
		<text>Training Day: Reach the Anomalous Area</text>
	</string>
	<string id="task_fanat_training_1_5">
		<text>Training Day: Speak to Fanatic</text>
	</string>
	<string id="task_fanat_training_1_9">
		<text>Training Day: Get the Jellyfish Artefact</text>
	</string>
	<string id="task_fanat_training_1_6">
		<text>Training Day: Return to the Village</text>
	</string>
	<string id="task_fanat_training_1_7">
		<text>Training Day: Speak to Fanatic</text>
	</string>
	<string id="task_fanat_training_1_8">
		<text>Training Day: Speak to Fanatic</text>
	</string>
	<string id="task_fanat_training_1_10">
		<text>Training day: Put the Jellyfish Artefact inside the Lead Container</text>
	</string>
	<string id="task_fanat_training_1_descr">
		<text>Fanatic seems to be one of the more experienced stalkers in the village. He has decided to teach me a trick or two.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="task_fanat_training_2_1">
		<text>Training Day - Challenge: Find the Stash</text>
	</string>
	<string id="task_fanat_training_2_2">
		<text>Training Day - Challenge: Speak to Fanatic</text>
	</string>
	<string id="task_fanat_training_2_descr">
		<text>My next challenge is one of perception - I have to find a stash located somewhere in the Rookie Village. Fanatic called it a "nest egg" - maybe that's a clue?</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="task_fanat_training_3_1">
		<text>Training Day - Rite of Passage: Clear out the Vehicle Station</text>
	</string>
	<string id="task_fanat_training_3_2">
		<text>Training Day - Rite of Passage: Speak to Fanatic</text>
	</string>
	<string id="task_fanat_training_3_3">
		<text>Training Day - Rite of Passage: Return to the Village</text>
	</string>
	<string id="task_fanat_training_3_4">
		<text>Training Day - Rite of Passage: Speak to Fanatic</text>
	</string>
	<string id="task_fanat_training_3_descr">
		<text>This is the final and most important task Fanatic has given me. Together, we are going to get rid of the bandits at the vehicle station.</text>
	</string>


	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_fanat_task_1_name">
		<text>Destroy the Mutant Lair</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_fanat_task_1_text">
		<text>I've agreed with Fanatic to destroy a mutant lair for the sake of the stalkers in Cordon.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_fanat_task_1_about">
		<text>Yeah, there's a small issue that needs sorting out. Cordon is supposed to be one of the safest places in the Zone, yet a new mutant lair has sprung up not too far from here. It needs to be cleared before it gets too large - otherwise, the rookies here will be in for a grave time. So, what do you say? Will you do it?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_fanat_task_1_finish">
		<text>Great work. Thanks to you, the rookies will have more room to breathe without being thrown into the deep end. Here's your payment - they all contributed a little to it. </text>
	</string>

	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_fanat_task_2_name">
		<text>Find a Battery Artefact for Fanatic</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_fanat_task_2_text">
		<text>Fanatic needs a Battery to help some of his old friends bribe their way out of the Zone.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_fanat_task_2_fetch_about">
		<text>So, here's the deal. A lot of dirty work has to happen to keep this village unmolested by the local soldiers. Sidorovich keeps the village itself safe in this way, but I have a few friends who want to leave, and there isn't any real way out for them.\n \nThat's the thing with the military's border patrols - they're not too careful about keeping people from getting in. But they'd rather kill you in cold blood than let you get out. So, my friends are stuck here.\n \nThe checkpoint guards won't let them through alive unless we bribe them with a Battery artefact. Have you heard of it? They can be found in Electro anomalies.\n \nIt's incredibly rare. I've already sent every stalker I can to find one, but no one has gotten back to me yet. Will you help out too?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_fanat_task_2_fetch_finish">
		<text>Ah, you've found a Battery? Excellent! I'll let my comrades know the good news. I'm going to miss them terribly, but I know they'll also get another chance at an ordinary life out there. Thank you, stalker.</text>
	</string>
	
<!-- Hip -->
	<string id="toz34_sk2_return">
		<text>Return the TOZ-194 and ammunition to Hip for payment</text>
	</string>
	<string id="toz34_sk2_find">
		<text>Find a TOZ-194 and ammunition for Hip's client</text>
	</string>
	<string id="toz34_return_descr">
		<text>Hip told me a wealthy client is willing to pay an exhorbitant amount for a TOZ-194 and 20 12x76 Buckshot rounds. Problem is, no famous trader south of the Barrier seems to stock them.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="artefacts_to_sidor_return">
		<text>Bring artefacts to Sidorovich</text>
	</string>
	<string id="artefacts_to_sidor_find">
		<text>Find artefacts for Sidorovich</text>
	</string>
	<string id="artefacts_to_sidor_return_descr">
		<text>Hip and I are on a collaborative artefact hunt for Sidorovich. He wants her to bring a Gravi, Lobster Eyes, and Moonlight.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="go_to_barmen_1">
		<text>Visit Barkeep</text>
	</string>
	<string id="go_to_barmen_2">
		<text>Visit Barkeep</text>
	</string>
	<string id="go_to_barmen_descr">
		<text>Hip wants to further her connections in the Zone by going to see Barkeep. His job sounded urgent, so we should hurry to secure it.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="go_to_lukash_1">
		<text>Meet and talk to Lukash</text>
	</string>
	<string id="go_to_lukash_2">
		<text>Meet and talk to Lukash</text>
	</string>
	<string id="go_to_lukash_descr">
		<text>Hip wants to see Lukash about delivering meds to stalker communities north of the Barrier. It sounds urgent, so we shouldn't waste time.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="go_to_boroda_1">
		<text>Take artefact containers to Beard</text>
	</string>
	<string id="go_to_boroda_2">
		<text>Take artefact containers to Beard</text>
	</string>
	<string id="go_to_boroda_descr">
		<text>Barkeep wants us to deliver artefact containers to Beard in Zaton, aboard the Skadovsk.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="go_to_loki_1">
		<text>Take bags with medicine to Loki</text>
	</string>
	<string id="go_to_loki_2">
		<text>Take bags with medicine to Loki</text>
	</string>
	<string id="go_to_loki_descr">
		<text>Lukash wants us to deliver medicine to Loki in Jupiter, at Yanov Station.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="army_south_mechan_mlr_task_4_about">
		<text>Some jackass keeps shooting at the speaker, I have no idea if it's some stalker from the village or maybe even somebody in here. Anyway, I need some parts to repair it. Can you look for them?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="army_south_mechan_mlr_task_4_name">
		<text>Find the Repair Parts for Seryoga</text>
	</string>
	
</string_table>
