<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes">
		<text>Notes</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes__state">
		<text>Equipment State</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes__state_text">
		<text>
			Equipment condition list.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes__ironman">
		<text>Ironman State</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes__ironman_text">
		<text>
			Ironman states:\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_mysteries_of_the_zone">
		<text>Mysteries of the Zone</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_mysteries_of_the_zone_text">
		<text>
			An old friend of Strelok is hiding somewhere around here. It might be a great opportunity for me to meet him and learn more about the Zone. Only problem is that I have no clue about his location.
			\nThe old man in Red Forest, "Forester", might know who and where he is. They have some sort of connection as it seems.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_living_legend">
		<text>Strelok's back?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_living_legend_text">
		<text>
			According to rumours, a legendary stalker has returned recently. He was one of the very few who made it to the centre of the Zone.
			\nPeople are making a big deal out of this. %s probably wants to see me.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_mortal_sin">
		<text>New clan?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_mortal_sin_text">
		<text>
			Tension fills the air. Mysterious stalkers have been seen wandering around, preaching and convincing others to join their "clan", but little is known about their true motives and goals. 
			\nSeems like a storm is brewing. I must see %s.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_recipe_cooking_1">
		<text>Chef's notes</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_recipe_cooking_1_text">
		<text>
			A couple of handwritten pages, contains detailed recipes regarding marinating mutant meat in alcohol by certain temperatures. According to the notes, it reduces the harming effects of irradiated meat. Seems like the author is an experienced zoner.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_memoirs_1_of_2">
		<text>A stalker's journal #1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_memoirs_1_of_2_text">
		<text>
			An old, faded notebook slipped into a card sleeve in order to protect it from wear and tear. However, it didn't withstand the passage of time well and only a small part of the text is legible:
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_memoirs_1_of_2_text2">
		<text>
			\n \n" I have to write this down, somehow I feel it will lessen my burden, and I can only hope that someone will read it so that my legacy remains after I'm gone and no one makes the same mistakes I did.
			\nI don't have a lot of friends, and I most certainly don't have any friends here in the Zone. The traders all look at me like I'm some kind of outcast. That bearded fellow in Zaton smiles sarcastically every time he sees me, and the Hawaiian trader mocks me with his easy-going attitude. Fuck those bastards, all I need from them is some ammo, food and water from time to time.
			\n \nI started writing this so at least someone would know what I went through that night, what happened, and maybe understand why I prefer to be alone at all times. I came here on my own, but immediately paired up with this newbie. It turned out he was a mineral enthusiast.
			\nHe had a hobby of collecting rocks, and had so many different ones, so naturally the artefacts, strange rocks, unique to the Zone, were his next step up. He got so many of them I can only assume that it was thanks to them that he got this fat tumour in his stomach. Frequent throwing up, diarrhoea, stress and the like, you know. He was like a pregnant woman, but instead of a baby he had this malignant, gigantic tumour. He even named it after his first pet puppy.
			\nI didn't object, he was good company, and I needed that at the time. We never attacked bandits, avoided most mutants, and just hung around anomalies, picking interesting rocks and sometimes grabbing a few artefacts if we were lucky. "
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_memoirs_2_of_2">
		<text>A stalker's journal #2</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_memoirs_2_of_2_text">
		<text>
			An old, faded notebook slipped into a card sleeve in order to protect it from wear and tear. However, it didn't withstand the passage of time well and only a small part of the text is legible:
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_memoirs_2_of_2_text2">
		<text>
			\n \n" There was talk about this anomaly, reportedly located deep inside a cave or fissure in the ground. There were supposed to be crazy amounts of artefacts, but for some reason nobody wanted to go there.
			\n"Cowards and fools," we thought. Why the hell wouldn't anyone jump at the chance to get rich, and live an easy life ever after? 
			\n \nSo we felt this sudden surge of courage, packed up, and went directly to the cave. We didn't even manage to peer into the cave, and this dark shadow flew over us. I tripped, struck my head when I feel, and just blacked out.
			\nAfter a while I came to, and heard something or someone moaning. "Animals,” I thought at first, but then I realized that it was my friend lying in front of me. I saw his skin ripped all over his body, saw his muscles bleeding all over and saw the bones sticking from disgusting wounds. He was clumsily holding his now exposed guts with his hand, while he was crawling further out of the cave. It was miracle he didn't die on the spot. 
			\n"What the hell happened?," I couldn't make sense of anything. I still had my backup pistol, and by a defense mechanism of some sort I started shooting towards the darkness of the cave. I had 20 rounds in that pistol, and switched to single fire. When I still had 7 rounds, something grabbed my hand, and made me pull the trigger. 
			\nAt that time I didn't even realize where my gun was pointed and where I was shooting but I couldn't stop. And suddenly the force let go of me, but I was in such a shock that I kept pulling the trigger a few minutes after the magazine was already empty. I knew if I had stopped, I'd have had to face what I did to my friend. I didn't even have the courage to take his dog tags. I just ran. 
			\n \nHow could I talk to someone or have another friend, when the Zone could take them too? It's better to be alone. Friendship comes with a price and a risk. The short-lived warmth of friendship is not worth it, if you could lose that friendship in the worst imaginable way. I have this bump on my head now to remind me of that. "
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_freedom_manual_1_of_2">
		<text>Interrogation techniques: the basics #1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_freedom_manual_1_of_2_text">
		<text>
			An instructional leaflet with a large Freedom emblem at the upper right corner and a simple drawing of a hand-gun pointing at a kneeling human figure. It is titled "Interrogation techniques: The basics" and is written in a typical, laid-back slang of the faction:
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_freedom_manual_1_of_2_text2">
		<text>
			\n \n" I shouldn't even tell this 'cause it's so obvious, but really, don't spread the word, don't show this manual around, don't sell it.
			\nThrow it away, burn it or only give it to those that you trust most. You don't want everyone knowing this. What if they use it against you? Do you have a stash? So do yourself a favor and keep this to yourself. Don't say I didn't warn you.
			\n \nEveryone has a stash. Even the poorest, most miserable bandit that has ever lived in the Zone has a couple of food rations and some ammo rounds. It's just the way things work here. You gather some money, sell a few artefacts or mutant parts, loot some dead but usually still warm bodies, and you buy food or weapons so when the shit hits the fan you don't have to stare directly at the fan with a stupid grin on your face but instead have some stuff up your sleeve that can save your sorry ass.
			\n \nThese are harsh times and this is a harsh place, and when you fail here, nobody's gonna help. "
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_freedom_manual_2_of_2">
		<text>Interrogation techniques: the basics #2</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_freedom_manual_2_of_2_text">
		<text>
			An instructional leaflet with a large Freedom emblem at the upper right corner and a simple drawing of a hand-gun pointing at a kneeling human figure. It is titled "Interrogation techniques: The basics" and is written in a typical, laid-back slang of the faction:
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_freedom_manual_2_of_2_text2">
		<text>
			\n \n" But guess what, you can take advantage of that better-safe-than-sorry attitude. If you wanna get a nice, juicy info about the whereabouts of someone's stash, remember to choose your victim carefully.
			\nWhen that's done and when all preparations are complete, you know, the place, there's no one around and the sort, just fuck with them psychologically. Shoot them in the legs or arms, get them to shit themselves, make them feel pain until they see you as their closest friend in the whole world. And one moment they will just throw their weapons and kneel before you.
			\nTalk to them, be nice but firm, helpful but persuasive. Don't kill them, they are human beings after all and the mutants are so numerous, so let's not make the Zone worse than it already is. Besides, you still want the stash, don't you? Tell them you'll cut their face off, scare the daylight out of them, make them think it's actually the end so that they won't even need the stash after you're done with them. They usually give it up immediately and run away. "
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_stalker_letter_1_of_2">
		<text>Memoir #1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_stalker_letter_1_of_2_text">
		<text>
			A couple of pages torn off from a memoir. Handwritten in blue ink that got smudgy due to the effect of environmental factors, which makes the text extremely hard to make out. Author unknown.
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_stalker_letter_1_of_2_text2">
		<text>
			\n \n" I can still feel the heat of that anomaly on my back. It burns even when I'm sitting in Skadovsk, in a safe place, far from danger and as far from any of those fucking furnaces as it gets. So really, you can only imagine what I have to go through when I do get near an anomaly.
			\nAh, hell, it burns even more of course. It's my organic anomaly detector now, for God’s sake. When you get hit by a burner anomaly or poisoned by a toxic one, that shit doesn't come off easily or even at all. It's like you've taken a part of the Zone inside you, for life. "Marked by the Zone," I guess.
			\n \nBut the nightmares... They are the worst. When you experience those abominations of physical laws, you lose every drop of confidence you've ever had.
			\nImagine that: I can handle ten bloodsuckers that appear in front of me in the dead of night. This stuff is easy, I'm a hardened warrior, you see. But the fact these anomalies violate every single law of science is just frightening. Is it even possible? Is what I know to be real real at all? I can't stop thinking that the Zone itself is a bad dream and I want to wake up so much that I wake up into another nightmare, right into the Zone again. That repeats a few times until my heart starts pounding and I jump out of the bed screaming and all sweaty.
			\nYou'll go deep down the rabbit hole if you follow this logic. "
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_stalker_letter_2_of_2">
		<text>Memoir #2</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_stalker_letter_2_of_2_text">
		<text>
			A couple of pages torn off from a memoir. Handwritten in blue ink that got smudgy due to the effect of environmental factors, which makes the text extremely hard to make out. Author unknown.
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_stalker_letter_2_of_2_text2">
		<text>
			\n \n" Every time I think about it, my back shivers in pain and turns into this red mess.
			\nI haven't even been close to an anomaly for the last 4 months, trying to make my living through hunting, but you know that its never an option in the long run for those like us. 
			\nThat fucking thing still reacts as if it had a mind of its own. Sometimes I wish I hadn't escaped from that burning farmstead. Maybe I'd have been of more use to everyone if I had become food for those boars. Probably not... But the boars, they are stupid fuckers too, running into burners by the dozens.
			\nIf that farmstead didn't exist, Skadovsk would be overrun by boars in a matter of days. No amount of ammo could keep them at bay, if it wasn't for the Burnt Farmstead, this barbecue factory. And the boars are so freaking useless, the meat's horrible, so charred that no cook can make it even remotely edible.
			\n \nSometimes I go to Zaton to watch the fireworks, even though the skin on my back hurts so much I can barely hold my backpack. I come back 'cause I feel that I've left something there, something that calls onto me from time to time. Because of that wretched scar on my back and the feeling of burning, I have to sleep on my stomach or sides.
			\nI hate sleeping on my sides, I've always been a back sleeper. The Zone forces changes on you and doesn't ask for permission. "
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_ecologist_report_1_of_3">
		<text>Walking Dead Findings field report 39B rev. 2 (part 1)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_ecologist_report_1_of_3_text">
		<text>
			A machine-typed document stamped with the Ecologist research team emblem. Classified as strictly confidential and signed by: %c[pda_white]Arkady Cvetkovsky%c[ui_gray_1]
			\nJunior Science Officer of Laboratory and Research Bunker RX12
			\n \nWalking Dead Findings field report 39B rev. 2 
			\n \n• Date: %c[pda_white]19.03.2014%c[ui_gray_1]
			\n• Packet: %c[pda_white]34%c[ui_gray_1]
			\n• Page: %c[pda_white]1%c[ui_gray_1] of %c[pda_white]3%c[ui_gray_1]
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_ecologist_report_1_of_3_text2">
		<text>
			  \n \n" These "zombies", which is the term locals use when referring to the specimens, are barely a living being, let alone sentient.
			  \nScientific data indicates that their brains do not conduct any thought processes and their neurological activity is virtually nonexistent, thus making them fundamentally brain-dead. However, field trials have proven that, for reasons as of yet unknown to science, they are capable of simple mechanical reactions (reminiscent of instinct, but their logic substantially differs).
			  \n \nOne theory states that this is the result of a never ending neurochemical barrage that compels the body to move in a specific manner in response to certain stimuli. When threatened, they demonstrate extremely violent behaviour, so it is advisable to approach them with great care and caution.
			  \n \nAs far as their physiology is concerned, out test have revealed a peculiar, and potentially scientifically fruitful, ability to self-sustain body parts, which means that such parts are able to function even when separated from the main body and without access to any nutrients whatsoever. One of the most successful endeavours of the scientific team entailed sustaining a liver and a heart for over 3 months despite them being not connected to other organs and bloodstream.
			  \nFurther analysis does not suggest any molecular or subatomic peculiarities. "
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_ecologist_report_2_of_3">
		<text>Walking Dead Findings field report 39B rev. 2 (part 2)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_ecologist_report_2_of_3_text">
		<text>
			A machine-typed document stamped with the Ecologist research team emblem. Classified as strictly confidential and signed by: %c[pda_white]Arkady Cvetkovsky%c[ui_gray_1]
			\nJunior Science Officer of Laboratory and Research Bunker RX12
			\n \nWalking Dead Findings field report 39B rev. 2 
			\n \n• Date: %c[pda_white]21.03.2014%c[ui_gray_1]
			\n• Packet: %c[pda_white]34%c[ui_gray_1]
			\n• Page: %c[pda_white]2%c[ui_gray_1] of %c[pda_white]3%c[ui_gray_1]
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_ecologist_report_2_of_3_text2">
		<text>
			\n \n" Our findings could provide the basis for a valid explanation as to why, after being shot numerous times in their limbs or pelvis, in their peripheral organs and other areas, they are capable of functioning almost indefinitely without severe difficulties.
			\nWalking is usually impeded, running is completely out of the question, but the reflex of aiming with weapons and pulling the trigger seems unaffected. This also applies to the use of other tools and some of the less complicated devices.
			\n \nPlease abstain from using the terms "kill" or "destroy" when referring to the deactivation of a specimen. This stems from the psychological argument that the term "deactivation" is more neutral than "destruction", and can serve as a way of distancing ourselves from the seemingly human form they manage to maintain and of suppressing the feeling of remorse after "deactivating" a specimen.
			\nDeactivation requires physically severing the link to their motor system. This would entail inflicting damage to the brain or spinal area, preferably by means of ballistic trauma.
			\n \nEvery member of the scientific team should bear in mind that their limbs will remain mobile even after deactivation, therefore special precautions are advised. Especially effective is the physical removal of cervical vertebrae or brain stem with surgical instruments or, in case of their unavailability, any sharp object. "
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_ecologist_report_3_of_3">
		<text>Walking Dead Findings field report 39B rev. 2 (part 3)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_ecologist_report_3_of_3_text">
		<text>
			A machine-typed document stamped with the Ecologist research team emblem. Classified as strictly confidential and signed by: %c[pda_white]Arkady Cvetkovsky%c[ui_gray_1]
			\nJunior Science Officer of Laboratory and Research Bunker RX12
			\n \nWalking Dead Findings field report 39B rev. 2 
			\n \n• Date: %c[pda_white]29.03.2014%c[ui_gray_1]
			\n• Packet: %c[pda_white]34%c[ui_gray_1]
			\n• Page: %c[pda_white]1%c[ui_gray_1] of %c[pda_white]3%c[ui_gray_1]
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_ecologist_report_3_of_3_text2">
		<text>
			\n \n" In extremely rare cases certain "zombies" exhibit behaviour reminiscent of more sophisticated animals:
			\nthey drop their weapons or refuse to engage in a fight altogether. These specimens are of great value to our research, hence deactivation is not advised. 
			\nIsolation and further analysis in laboratories is of utmost importance. Neuropsychologists are an especially interested party due to the potential for brain stem transplants that could theoretically aid patients in late stages of Alzheimer's and other diseases.
			\n \nWhenever possible, avoid damaging kidneys and heart upon deactivation as these organs possess immense potential provided transplants ever prove viable. Harvesting organs from immobile "zombies" is also a possibility, however it is recommended to be cautious of local stalkers who might have emotional ties to some specimens.
			\n \nIf an encounter with a stalker is unavoidable while harvesting, there are two courses of action one can take in order to minimize the chance of combat. 
			\nFirst, when dealing with inexperienced stalkers showing them the eyes of a given specimen has proven very effective, especially since the pupils are completely unresponsive and the eyeballs as such appear inhuman.
			\nSecondly, more seasoned stalkers are usually easier to be reasoned with as they can suppress emotions better. However, it is still advisable to make us of psychological expertise when dealing with local human population as in some cases rational communication is completely out of the question. "
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_monolith_prayer_1_of_3">
		<text>Monolith prayer #1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_monolith_prayer_1_of_3_text">
		<text>
			An untitled document comprising a few paragraphs one below another. Frequent references to the Monolith indicate a religious nature of the written text. The paper is preserved very well, which suggests that it has been treated with great care and respect so that its condition doesn't deteriorate. The text of the prayer reads:
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_monolith_prayer_1_of_3_text2">
		<text>
			\n \n" Oh Monolith!
			\nWe are praying to You!
			\nOh Monolith!
			\nOur only Light in the darkness
			\nOh Monolith!
			\nWith hope in our hearts we march!
			\nWe march forward towards the infidels!
			\n \nOh Monolith!
			\nForgive our sins!
			\nOh Monolith!
			\nShow us our Destiny!
			\nOh Monolith!
			\nGive us Power to fulfill our purpose!
			\nOh Monolith!
			\nGive us Hope to slay Your enemies!
			\nOh Monolith!
			\nShare your Light with us!
			\n \nOh Monolith!
			\nWe pray to you!
			\nOh Monolith!
			\nWe are your progeny!
			\nOh Monolith!
			\nOur only hope at redemption!
			\nOh Monolith!
			\nYour name is in our hearts! "
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_monolith_prayer_2_of_3">
		<text>Monolith prayer #2</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_monolith_prayer_2_of_3_text">
		<text>
			An untitled document comprising a few paragraphs one below another. Frequent references to the Monolith indicate a religious nature of the written text. The paper is preserved very well, which suggests that it has been treated with great care and respect so that its condition doesn't deteriorate. The text of the prayer reads:
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_monolith_prayer_2_of_3_text2">
		<text>
			\n \n" Warriors of Monolith, we stand!
			\nOh Monolith, our Light!
			\nTake our souls, our minds
			\nAnd cleanse them!
			\nRid them of doubts and hesitation!
			\nOh Monolith, our Hope!
			\nWe are Your soldiers!
			\nWe want to give our lives for You
			\nWe want to give our souls for You
			\nAnd we want to be one with You!
			\nOh Monolith, we shall remove all obstacles from Your path!
			\nTake our flesh!
			\nTake our blood!
			\nTake our souls!
			\nAnd make them whole again!
			\nYou are in us, oh Monolith. "
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_monolith_prayer_3_of_3">
		<text>Monolith prayer #3</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_monolith_prayer_3_of_3_text">
		<text>
			An untitled document comprising a few paragraphs one below another. Frequent references to the Monolith indicate a religious nature of the written text. The paper is preserved very well, which suggests that it has been treated with great care and respect so that its condition doesn't deteriorate. The text of the prayer reads:
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_monolith_prayer_3_of_3_text2">
		<text>
			\n \n" Oh Monolith!
			\nYou are our destiny.
			\nAnd we are brothers.
			\nWe are brothers of the Monolith's Light.
			\nWe shall die for Your cause.
			\nWe shall die in Your name.
			\nWe shall die for Your Light.
			\nDeath is only the beginning.
			\nWe march with Your name on our lips, oh Monolith! "
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_monolithian_thoughts">
		<text>Monolithian's journal</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_monolithian_thoughts_text">
		<text>
			A hand-written sheet of paper. At the beginning, the writing of the note is extremely chaotic and untidy as if the person writing it was suffering from a severe mental disorder. Interestingly, the further down the sheet, the text becomes more plain, letters much clearer and the last words are written with an almost perfect, machine-like precision. The text of the note reads:
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_monolithian_thoughts_text2">
		<text>
			\n \n" As far as I can remember, there was darkness around me, and I couldn't see anything. Nothing... For hours. But suddenly I saw a light! A light so bright, a light so cozy... I wanted to touch it, I wanted to feel it. I knew that it was trying to help me, to save me. I knew...
			\n \nAnd after I touched that light, I forgot everything. There was no life behind me, there was only darkness behind me. The only light was in front of me.
			\nIts name is Monolith. It saved me, and I'm eternally grateful.
			\nSometimes I can see the faces, faces from the past... A woman and a child... My family? I'm dressed in white overalls... Maybe I was a scientist... This weird word... Radar... NO! This is that darkness! It wants me to die! I WON'T LET IT KILL ME!
			\nThere is no way back! There is only light in front of me! Towards the light! For the Monolith! "
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_letter_to_outside">
		<text>A letter to Natalie</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_letter_to_outside_text">
		<text>
			A letter apparently written by one of the stalkers to someone outside the Zone, most probably his wife or lover. The fact that you hold it in your hands suggests that it never reached the intended recipient.
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_letter_to_outside_text2">
		<text>
			\n \n" Hello, Natalie!
			\n \nHow are you? How are the kids?
			\nTell Sanya that if he won't listen to you, I will smack him good when I return home.
			\n \nWhat about me? Well, I don't think that you'll understand. The Zone... This place is... Unique. Only here can I really feel the bonds with other people. Only here can I see them for who they truly are. 
			\nThere are no masks here, only truth. But, like I said, I'll tell you more next time we meet.
			\nI've earned some good money here! We can finally buy you that necklace you wanted so much.
			\nOh, and thank you for your letters. They really lift my spirits. When I think about you, everything seems a lot better. We will meet each other soon. Say hello to the kids for me!
			\n \nLots of love.
			\n - Your Michail. Your brave Stalker. "
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_military_stalker">
		<text>Military stalker's note</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_military_stalker_text">
		<text>
			A note found in a stash. Looks like someone was killing time during a long and boring night and then decided to leave the result of his work behind rather than throw it into the campfire. The text of the note reads:
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_military_stalker_text2">
		<text>
			\n \n"So. I guess I got the clean life I wanted. I'm finally a military stalker, legally endorsed to carry out operations within the Zone.
			\nAll it took was a few years of scrounging a living, surviving in this hellhole. Now, the military goons that wanted me dead have to salute me. "Yes sir", they say. "No, sir. Three bags full, sir". They do whatever I ask. It's unreal. Even Spetsnaz and OMON treat me with respect, and yet if I met them last week they wouldn't have hesitated to put a bullet between my eyes.
			\n \nSo now, they outfit me with the best armour they have. The best weapons. The best gadgets and provisions. I eat like a king now, and today's the first time I haven't felt sick in years. I even make enough cash to send some back to the wife.\n \nThere's just one catch. I'm not allowed to let regular stalkers come up to me while I work. My commander says if they get too close, I am expected to open fire immediately. Well, all my stalker friends are already dead, so it's not like I'll be capping anyone I know, but I do wonder. I do wonder if people will look at me, and see the same kind of iron-booted monster I'd hide away from all those years ago."
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_mercenary">
		<text>Mercenary's note</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_mercenary_text">
		<text>
			A note written by one of the Mercenaries. Looks like he decided to write down some thoughts concerning his activities in the Zone. The purpose of it is unclear.
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_mercenary_text2">
		<text>
			\n \n" So, from what I can see, there is nothing special here.
			\nWe are still mercenaries, we are still soldiers of fortune. However, we can choose what we do and what we don't. Sometimes we don't even apply for a certain job because it is too "dirty" for us. If the client wants to kill some good folks earning a living by sweat and toil, fuck this bastard. They always can go to the Zone and deal with their problems themselves.
			\nWhat about marauders, deserters and other scumbags, always yours. Any time, any place. When we have to PROTECT ourselves, it's another matter. But if you want to kill an innocent man, ask those American dolls. They're not so choosy as who to kill.
			\n \nWe're different. Bear this in mind next time you give us your money. "
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_military_log">
		<text>Communication log / MSRC operation / 05.04.2014 18:36:21</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_military_log_text">
		<text>
			A printed transcription of the radio transmission between military units stationed in the Zone. The fact that it was in possession of one of the SKAT unit members indicates that he must have been involved in a clandestine operation, most probably concerned with the extraction of surveillance data. The transcription reads:
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_military_log_text2">
		<text>
			\n \n" - HQ, this is MSRC 1-03. We've got photos of NII. 240 photos of an anomaly in the Swamps, about 1400 photos of the main base. When do we return?
			\n- MSRC 1-03, this is HQ. Do not come back for now. There are some problems at the Military Warehouses. MSRC 4-07 is asking for help. Again. This time, however, their SOS signal is strong so we at least know that they are alive.
			\n- Eh, roger that, HQ. Chopper?
			\n- Negative. There are too many anomaly fields in NII Agroprom now, it's too dangerous. Go to Yantar, our MI-24 will pick you up there.
			\n- Roger. Any information about the next blowout?
			\n- Positive. Sacharov said that there are two days left at least. But hurry anyway. Their information has never been reliable.
			\n- Understood. We are on our way, tell the Bird to be at Yantar in 7 hours. MSRC 1-03 out.
			\n- Wait, 1-03. What about the underground in N-2? Did you find anything there?
			\n- Positive. We have found that new anomaly. It looks like some sort of teleport. This should be interesting for those bigheads from Yantar, our detectors fried when we tried to measure psi-fields. Dunno why, possibly because of electronic waves.
			\n- Roger that, MSRC 1-03. Good luck on your way to Yantar. Hear from you in 7 hours. HQ out. "
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_stalker_letter_3">
		<text>Letter to Nikolai</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_stalker_letter_3_text">
		<text>
			A hand-written letter addressed to Nikolai. Most probably a part of a longer written conversation between two stalkers. Although correspondence in the Zone is conducted mainly by means of PDA messages, some prefer a traditional manner of communication, especially in case of most private matters and between friends. These letters are then handed to couriers who, like guides, are entrusted with some of the most difficult and dangerous tasks. It often takes a few days before a letter reaches its recipient, but still the probability of intercepting the message is much lower than in case of PDA communication. The courier profession is highly regarded among fellow stalkers and entails a position of significant influence in the stalker community. The letter reads:
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_letter_stalker_letter_3_text2">
		<text>
			\n \n" Nikolai,
			\n \nI've just got back from my trip to the centre of the Zone. It was hell.
			\nThe Monolith and the army are still going at it, bent on exterminating each other for no reason. One moment it looked like they would conclude a cease-fire, but eventually nothing came of it.
			\nConstant havoc and destruction followed and I didn't have any other choice but to escape from this place. I almost got killed once, freaking psycho bastards. 
			\nBut I don't  blame them, entirely my fault, I just wasn't paying attention when it mattered most. This way or another, after some hardships, I made my way to Pripyat and I plan to lie low here for a while
			\n \nGetting back to what we discussed previously, it seems like we're gonna have to put off our mission until it gets safer out there. I didn't get a moment of sleep after I got back, but I wanted to let you know I'm good, at least physically. We'll stay in touch.
			\n \nTake good care, Rua. "
		</text>
	</string>

	
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_recipe_basic_1_text">
		<text>
			This guide details basic survival skills, and provides an overview of common survival kits. The later chapters describe the creation of basic gear out of common materials.
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_recipe_basic_2_text">
		<text>
			This guide details basic survival skills, and provides an overview of common survival kits. The later chapters describe the creation of basic gear out of common materials.
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_recipe_basic_3_text">
		<text>
			This guide details basic survival skills, and provides an overview of common survival kits. The later chapters describe the creation of basic gear out of common materials.
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_recipe_basic_4_text">
		<text>
			This guide details basic survival skills, and provides an overview of common survival kits. The later chapters describe the creation of basic gear out of common materials.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_recipe_advanced_1_text">
		<text>
			Manual of mechanical engineering. Some people read such books to expand their expertise and learn more about the facilities and factories in the Zone. Contains details about basic mechanical and electrical equipments.
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_recipe_advanced_2_text">
		<text>
			Manual of mechanical engineering. Some people read such books to expand their expertise and learn more about the facilities and factories in the Zone. Contains details about basic mechanical and electrical equipments.
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_recipe_advanced_3_text">
		<text>
			Manual of mechanical engineering. Some people read such books to expand their expertise and learn more about the facilities and factories in the Zone. Contains details about basic mechanical and electrical equipments.
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_recipe_advanced_4_text">
		<text>
			Manual of mechanical engineering. Some people read such books to expand their expertise and learn more about the facilities and factories in the Zone. Contains details about basic mechanical and electrical equipments.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_recipe_expert_1_text">
		<text>
			Manual of industrial engineering. Quite informative. It describes the operation of modern electronics: operational amplifiers, semiconductor diodes, bipolar junction transistors, and field effect transistors. The second part of this manual deals with troubleshooting electrical devices.
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_recipe_expert_2_text">
		<text>
			Manual of industrial engineering. Quite informative. It describes the operation of modern electronics: operational amplifiers, semiconductor diodes, bipolar junction transistors, and field effect transistors. The second part of this manual deals with troubleshooting electrical devices.
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_recipe_expert_3_text">
		<text>
			Manual of industrial engineering. Quite informative. It describes the operation of modern electronics: operational amplifiers, semiconductor diodes, bipolar junction transistors, and field effect transistors. The second part of this manual deals with troubleshooting electrical devices.
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_recipe_expert_4_text">
		<text>
			Manual of industrial engineering. Quite informative. It describes the operation of modern electronics: operational amplifiers, semiconductor diodes, bipolar junction transistors, and field effect transistors. The second part of this manual deals with troubleshooting electrical devices.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_recipe_drug_1_text">
		<text>
			A couple of pages torn off from a book. Handwritten in blue ink that got smudgy due to the effect of environmental factors, which makes the text extremely hard to make out. The written notes describe the creation of varies types of drugs and medicines using common medical supplies.
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_recipe_drug_2_text">
		<text>
			A couple of pages torn off from a book. Handwritten in blue ink that got smudgy due to the effect of environmental factors, which makes the text extremely hard to make out. The written notes describe the creation of varies types of drugs and medicines using common medical supplies.
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_recipe_drug_3_text">
		<text>
			A couple of pages torn off from a book. Handwritten in blue ink that got smudgy due to the effect of environmental factors, which makes the text extremely hard to make out. The written notes describe the creation of varies types of drugs and medicines using common medical supplies.
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_recipe_drug_4_text">
		<text>
			A couple of pages torn off from a book. Handwritten in blue ink that got smudgy due to the effect of environmental factors, which makes the text extremely hard to make out. The written notes describe the creation of varies types of drugs and medicines using common medical supplies.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_recipe_ammo_1_text">
		<text>
			Every stalker should learn to choose a gun, but also know how to choose ammunition for it. This guide provides informations about various types of ammunition, plus an in-depth view about the basic components of cartridges.
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_recipe_ammo_2_text">
		<text>
			Every stalker should learn to choose a gun, but also know how to choose ammunition for it. This guide provides informations about various types of ammunition, plus an in-depth view about the basic components of cartridges.
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_recipe_ammo_3_text">
		<text>
			Every stalker should learn to choose a gun, but also know how to choose ammunition for it. This guide provides informations about various types of ammunition, plus an in-depth view about the basic components of cartridges.
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_recipe_ammo_4_text">
		<text>
			Every stalker should learn to choose a gun, but also know how to choose ammunition for it. This guide provides informations about various types of ammunition, plus an in-depth view about the basic components of cartridges.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_note_from_spirit">
		<text>Note from Spirit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_note_from_spirit_text">
		<text>
			Spirit's got a bad habit - he's willing to give me military supplies in exchange for vodka.
			\nLet's see:\n
			\n• 4 mags of 9x18 mm rounds for 5 swigs of Nemiroff (about 2 bottles) 
			\n• 2 mags of 5.45 mm rounds for 5 swigs of Nemiroff 
			\n• 4 mags of 5.45 mm rounds for 10 swigs of Nemiroff (just over 3 bottles)
			\n• 3 boxes of 12x70 shot rounds for 10 swigs of Nemiroff 
			\n• 1 mag of 7.62mm 7N1 rounds for 10 swigs of Nemiroff 
			\n• 3 mag of 7.62x54 mm PP rounds for 15 swigs of Nemiroff (exactly 5 bottles) + 7000 RU on top
			\n• Basic Tools for 20 swigs of Nemiroff (nearly 7 full bottles) 
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_note_from_aslan">
		<text>Note from Aslan</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_note_from_aslan_text">
		<text>
			Aslan's got a questionable hobby. He's a patch collector, "it's an optimal method for our guys to earn some spoils of war" he says.
			\nThis is what he said:
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_note_from_aslan_text2">
		<text>
			\n \n"you bring me patches from stalkers, you get some gear or nothing at all. All of it for twenty-five patches of any faction, apart from those of Ecologists and the Monolith, you have a chance to get a subpar artefact, or not get jack shit. With fifty patches, you'll have a chance to get a decent artefact and some rather solid gear, but there's also a chance that you won't get anything. And for twenty-five Monolith or Ecologist patches, you will get a pretty good artefact with the same chance as for fifty patches of any other faction. Fifty Monolith or Ecologist patches will guarantee you an outstanding item and good equipment dedicated only to the most experienced of stalkers, no chance of losing. You might ask, "why so generous?"... Because many people prefer to keep the patches for themselves as combat trophies."
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_note_from_trunk">
		<text>Note from Trunk</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_note_from_trunk_text">
		<text>
			Trunk says he can provide me ammunition in exchange for other types. They're probably trading surplus rounds for ammo they actually need.
			\nThis is what interests him:\n
			\n• He will exchange 100 mags of 9x18 mm +P+ rounds for 100 mags of 9x19 mm FMJ rounds.
			\n• He will exchange 100 mags of 5.45x39 mm rounds for 100 mags of 5.56x45 mm rounds.
			\n• He will exchange 20 M209 grenades for 10 F1 grenades.
			\n• He will exchange 3 RPG warheads for 10 RGD-5 grenades.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_note_from_meeker">
		<text>Note from Meeker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_note_from_meeker_text">
		<text>
			Despite the poor situation Griffin's group are in, Meeker has access to some special gear. I need to place an order first to get what I want.
			\nAccording to him, I can place one order at a time, and he works without prepayments. Once the shipment is ready, I will receive a message from him. So this is what I can order:
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_note_from_meeker_text2">
		<text>
			\n• The Steppe Eagle - a hand-made pistol based on the Desert Eagle design. Finely tuned to achieve incredible accuracy. It'll cost me 8,000 RU.
			\n• Alpine - a modified SIG P220 with an extended magazine. It'll cost me 65,000 RU.
			\n• March - modified UDP Compact, high caliber and quick-firing. It'll cost me 7,000 RU.
			\n• The Frasier - a handmade sub-machine gun based on the MP5. Increased caliber, improved characteristics over standard counterpart. It'll cost me 9,500.
			\n• The Carabiner - an army-modified SPAS-12 with reduced recoil and automatic firing mode. It'll cost 11,000 RU.
			\n• The Armsel Protecta - a shotgun based on the design of the Striker shotgun. It'll cost me 17,000 RU.
			\n• Storm - a modified OTs-14 Groza manufactured for Spetsnaz special forces, secretly leaked to the masses. One of the advantages worth noting is the increased magazine capacity. It'll cost me 19,000 RU.
			\n• The H&amp;K G36 - a rare sight in the zone. It'll cost me 14,000 RU.
			\n• The FN F2000. A Belgian rarity and a decent assault rifle. It'll cost me 17,000 RU.
			\n• The Tide - an exclusive modification of the VSS Vintorez. Lower rate of fire, but increased stopping power. It'll cost me 20,000 RU.
			\n• The SVU2-A - an evolution of the SVUmk-2 sniper rifle. This weapon used to belong to Max, the legendary guardian of Freedom. It'll cost me 24,000 RU.
			\n• The SVD Lynx - an army modification that combines increased accuracy and stopping power. It'll cost me 18,000 RU.
			\n• Gauss rifle. A trophy weapon - you can count the number of these in the Zone on your fingers. Absolute accuracy and damage with almost no recoil included. The price is 150,000 RU.
			\n• A Monolith exoskeleton - the best combination of protective characteristics. In addition, you won't get this anywhere else, unless you are a certain representative of the brotherhood. The price is at a 100,000 RU.
			\n• A mercenary exoskeleton - perhaps one of the most reliable means of protection. It'll cost me 75,000 RU.
			\n• Bandit exoskeleton. Exclusivity in its purest form. It'll cost me 65,000 RU.
			\n• A Monolith suit featuring a closed-cycle breathing system; as with the exoskeleton, you are unlikely to see it anywhere else. It'll cost me 70,000 RU.
			\n• A Mercenary suit with a closed breathing system. Excellent protection from anomalies and a real rarity for the average stalker. It'll cost me 50,000 RU.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_note_from_grifon">
		<text>Note from Griffin</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_note_from_grifon_text">
		<text>
			Griffin and his team are stuck in the Outskirts for a while now, and he can't return with empty hands. One of the hidden labs (X-8) is somewhere around the northern side, the mercs are hoping to find important documents in there.
			\nHe's offering a good reward if I can get him anything I can find there. His words:
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia__notes_note_from_grifon_text2">
		<text>
			"We actually came here to retrieve info from Lab X-8, which is located near the Yubileiny service centre north of here; inside, there was an elevator that allowed us to go down to "minus first floor", but we got interrupted by the fucking Monolith. It's because of them that we've ended up this deep in shit. Dushman's going to kill us anyway, but maybe there are a few documents left... we'd have something useful to leave with, at least. I'd head over there again with the guys, but there aren't many of us left and it'd be too much to handle, since we'd rather not spend any more manpower than we need to trying to somehow get away from the centre of the fucking Zone. Maybe you could head down to X-8 - there could be something left, and, well... you'll earn some good money at the same time."
		</text>
	</string>
	
</string_table>