<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<string_table>
 <!-- 5.45 -->
	<string id="st_mag_ak74_5.45x39">
		<text>Standard 5.45x39 AK-74 Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_ak74_5.45x39_descr">
		<text>
		30-round Bakelite magazine that is standard issue with the Ukrainian military. One of the most common magazines in the Zone. Designation "6L20".
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_mag_ak74_5.45x39_extended">
		<text>60-round 5.45x39 AK-74 Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_ak74_5.45x39_extended_descr">
		<text>
		60-round quad-stack magazine for the AK-74 series. Extremely rare to find in Russia as only small batches were produced, but it is rumored the Ukrainian SSU started producing their own to fit their needs of controlling the Zone. Designation "6L31".
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_ak74m_5.45x39">
		<text>Standard 5.45x39 AK-74M Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_ak74m_5.45x39_descr">
		<text>
		30-round polymer magazine that is standard issue with the Russian military, shipped with the AK-74M. One of the most common magazines in the Zone. This magazine can be tweaked to accommodate different calibers. Designation "6L23".
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_ak74_fast_5.45x39">
		<text>Fast-loading 5.45x39 AK-74M Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_ak74_fast_5.45x39_descr">
		<text>
		Modern PMAG-style AK magazine holding 30 rounds. The build quality is very high and loading rounds in is quite effortless. Magazines like these are usually only found on Spetsnaz black ops units along with cutting edge Alpha AKs.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_mag_rpk74_5.45x39">
		<text>Standard 5.45x39 RPK-74 Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_rpk74_5.45x39_descr">
		<text>
			45-round Bakelite magazine that comes standard with the RPK-74 LMG. This magazine also fits into AK-74 derivatives. Designation "6L18"
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_rpk74_5.56x45">
		<text>Modified 5.56x45 RPK-74 Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_rpk74_5.56x45_descr">
		<text>
			Modified RPK magazine to fit 5.56 NATO rounds. Also compatible with the export AK-101 and AK-102.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_ak_7.62x39">
		<text>Standard 7.62x39 AKM Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_ak_7.62x39_descr">
		<text>
		30-round steel 7.62x39 magazine. Magazines like these are quite old but still function relatively well. 
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_ak103_7.62x39">
		<text>Standard 7.62x39 AK-103 Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_ak103_7.62x39_descr">
		<text>
		30-round AK-103 Magazine in 7.62x39. Modern materials and construction have made the magazine far lighter than its steel counterparts. In addition, this magazine can be modified to accommodate other calibers.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_mag_ak103_fast_7.62x39">
		<text>Fast-loading 7.62x39 AK-103 Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_ak103_fast_7.62x39_descr">
		<text>
		PMAG-style 7.62x39 magazine made from polymer. The build quality and design allows for fast loading of rounds. Such a piece of equipment is an unusual sight in the Zone.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_rpd_7.62x39">
		<text>Standard 7.62x39 RPD Drum</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_rpd_7.62x39_descr">
		<text>
			Drum magazine with a belt for the RPD. The box holds 100 rounds in a belt. While the RPD was ultimately supplanted by the more accurate and flexible RPK, being able to shoot off 100 rounds is nothing to scoff at. 
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_mag_rpk_7.62x39">
		<text>Standard 7.62x39 RPK Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_rpk_7.62x39_descr">
		<text>
		Steel 40-round RPK Magazine. This is also compatible with the AKM and other 7.62x39 AK rifles.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_mag_rpk_7.62x39_drum">
		<text>95-round RPK Drum Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_rpk_7.62x39_drum_descr">
		<text>
		95-round drum magazine for the RPK.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	
	<!-- 5.56 -->
	
	<string id="st_mag_ace21_5.56x45">
		<text>Standard 5.56x45 Galil ACE-21 Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_ace21_5.56x45_descr">
		<text>
		Proprietary ACE-21 Magazine that holds 35 rounds. The outdated model found in the Zone requires proprietary Galil magazines, which makes the weapon a fancy novelty more than anything else.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_ak101_5.56x45">
		<text>Standard 5.56x45 AK-101 Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_ak101_5.56x45_descr">
		<text>
		30-round magazine for the export AK101 and AK102. This magazine can be tweaked to fit different calibers.
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_aug_5.56x45">
		<text>Standard 5.56x45 AUG Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_aug_5.56x45_descr">
		<text>
			Proprietary 30-round magazine for the first generation of AUG rifles. Later variants have a magwell that adapts them to use the standard STANAG pattern.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_mag_g36_5.56x45">
		<text>Standard 5.56x45 G36 Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_g36_5.56x45_descr">
		<text>
		Standard semi-translucent G36 Magazine with capacity for 30 rounds of 5.56x45 ammunition.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_mag_stanag">
		<text>Standard 5.56x45 STANAG magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_stanag_descr">
		<text>
		30-round HK STANAG magazine used by a majority of NATO assault rifles, including the M4 carbine, M16, LR-300, L85 and FN F2000. It is rumored that Freedom is covertly supplied by NATO or another Western power, which explains this magazine's strange abundance in the Zone.
		</text>
	</string>


	<string id="st_mag_nato_5.45x39">
		<text>Modified 5.45x39 STANAG Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_nato_5.45x39_descr">
		<text>
			30-round STANAG magazine modified to feed 5.45x39 rounds. Why anyone would modify a rifle in this way is anyone's guess.
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_nato_5.56x45_fast">
		<text>Fast-loading 5.56x45 STANAG magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_nato_5.56x45_fast_descr">
		<text>
		Modern PMAG-style magazine holding 30 rounds. Considerably lighter than its steel counterpart, the ergonomic design facilitates quick loading of cartridges.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_mag_nato_5.56x45_extended">
		<text>Extended 5.56x45 STANAG Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_nato_5.56x45_extended_descr">
		<text>
			Extended 40-round polymer magazine compatible with most NATO rifles. 
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_nato_5.56x45_casket">
		<text>60-round 5.56x45 STANAG Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_nato_5.56x45_casket_descr">
		<text>
			60-round quad-stack magazine compatible with NATO rifles. Offers a lot of firepower, but is extremely heavy and the quad-stack nature makes it difficult to load in rounds quickly.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_mag_sig550_5.56x45">
		<text>Standard 5.56x45 SG550 Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_sig550_5.56x45_descr">
		<text>
		Swiss-made SG550 Magazine holding 30 rounds. Compatible with the SIG SG550, SG552 and SG550-1 Sniper.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_sig550_sniper_5.56x45">
		<text>20-round 5.56x45 SG550-1 Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_sig550_sniper_5.56x45_descr">
		<text>
		Swiss-made SG550-1 Magazine holding 20 rounds. Used in the SG550-1 Sniper variant, but is compatible in other rifles of the same family.
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_m249_5.56x45">
		<text>Standard 5.56x45 M249 Box</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_m249_5.56x45_descr">
		<text>
			Box containing a belt with capacity for 100 5.56x45 rounds. The M249 is a common sight at Freedom foreposts, providing a high volume of suppressive fire against Monolith encroachers.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_mag_xm8_5.56x45">
		<text>Standard XM8 Magazine calibre 5.56x45</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_xm8_5.56x45_descr">
		<text>
		Standard XM8 Magazine calibre 5.56x45.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_type63_7.62x39">
		<text>Standard 7.62x39 Type 63 Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_type63_7.62x39_descr">
		<text>
		20-round magazine for the Type 63 rifle made of stamped steel. Most Type 63s found in the Zone have the bolt hold-open device removed so they can fit more common AKM magazines. This magazine will also fit into AK-style rifles as well.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_mag_type63_7.62x54">
		<text>Modified 7.62x54 Type 63 Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_type63_7.62x54_descr">
		<text>
			Type 63 magazine modified to fit large 7.62x54R rounds. The Type 63 is a favorite of bandit clans; conversion to the full-size rifle round is the speciality of the bandit technician Limpid.
		</text>
	</string>
	<!-- 9x39 -->
	<string id="st_mag_val_9x39_pab9">
		<text>20-round 9x39 AS VAL Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_val_9x39_pab9_descr">
		<text>
			Standard 20-round AS VAL magazine, also compatible with SR-3M and VSS rifles. Designation "6L25". 
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_vihr_9x39_pab9">
		<text>30-round 9x39 SR-3M Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_vihr_9x39_pab9_descr">
		<text>
		30-round 9x39 magazine that comes standard with the SR-3M "Vihr" rifle. Also compatible with the VSS and AS VAL rifles. Designation "SR3M.130"
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_mag_vintorez_9x39_pab9">
		<text>10-round 9x39 VSS Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_vintorez_9x39_pab9_descr">
		<text>
		Standard 10-round VSS Magazine, also compatible with the AS VAL and SR3M rifles. Designation "6L24".
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_mag_vsk94_9x39_pab9">
		<text>Standard 9x39 Box Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_vsk94_9x39_pab9_descr">
		<text>
			20-round box magazine used in the 9A-91 and VSK-94 rifles.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_mag_groza_9x39_pab9">
		<text>20 round 9x39 Groza Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_groza_9x39_pab9_descr">
		<text>
			20-round magazine of 9x39 that comes standard with the OTs-14 Groza assault rifle. Design is similar to the AK-style magazines.
		</text>
	</string>
	

<!--
sniper rifles / full size rifles
-->
	
		
	<string id="st_mag_g43_7.92x33">
		<text>Standard 7.92x57 G43 Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_g43_7.92x33_descr">
		<text>
			Standard 10-round box magazine for the Gewehr 43.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_galil_7.62x51">
		<text>Standard 7.62x51 Galil Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_galil_7.62x51_descr">
		<text>
		Standard 25 round box magazine for the Israeli Galil battle rifle.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_mag_stanag_7.62x51">
		<text>Standard 7.62x51 STANAG Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_stanag_7.62x51_descr">
		<text>
			Standard STANAG-style Magazine for 7.62x51 NATO rounds. Used in the HK417, SCAR and SR-25. Holds 20 rounds.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_mag_stanag_7.62x51_ext">
		<text>Extended 7.62x51 STANAG Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_stanag_7.62x51_ext_descr">
		<text>
			Extended STANAG-style Magazine for 7.62x51 NATO rounds. Used in the HK417, SCAR and SR-25. Holds 30 rounds.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_mag_stanag_fast_7.62x51">
		<text>Fast-loading 7.62x51 STANAG Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_stanag_fast_7.62x51_descr">
		<text>
			Modernized PMAG-style Magazine for 7.62x51 NATO rounds. Used in the HK417, SCAR and SR-25. Holds 20 rounds.
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_stanag_7.62x51_short">
		<text>10-round 7.62x51 STANAG Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_stanag_7.62x51_short_descr">
		<text>
			Compact 10-round STANAG-style Magazine for 7.62x51 NATO rounds. Comes by default with the KAC SR-25, but can fit in the HK417 and SCAR Mk. 17.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_hinge_7.62x51">
		<text>Standard 7.62x51 Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_hinge_7.62x51_descr">
		<text>
		Standard 20-round 7.62x51 magazine used in battle rifles with hinged magazine locking mechanisms. Whatever minor differences in the compatibility between weapons and magazines of this style have been 'worked out' by Zone technicians. Used in the FN FAL, Mk. 14 EBR and G3 rifles.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_hinge_ext_7.62x51">
		<text>Extended 7.62x51 Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_hinge_ext_7.62x51_descr">
		<text>
		Extended 30-round 7.62x51 magazine used in battle rifles with hinged magazine locking mechanisms. Used in the FN FAL, Mk. 14 EBR and G3 rifles.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_mag_l96a1_7.62x51">
		<text>10-round 7.62x51 L96A1 Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_l96a1_7.62x51_descr">
		<text>
		Standard-issue 10-round magazine for the L96A1. The L96 is a favorite of Western mercenaries and Monolith forces. 
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_remington700_7.62x51">
		<text>Standard 7.62x51 Remington 700 Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_remington700_7.62x51_descr">
		<text>
		Standard 5-round Remington 700 Magazine. The Remington 700 is a popular hunting rifle and fares rather well in the Zone's conditions.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_wa2000_7.62x51">
		<text>Standard Walther WA 2000 Magazine calibre 7.62x51</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_wa2000_7.62x51_descr">
		<text>
		Standard Walther WA 2000 Magazine calibre 7.62x51.
		</text>
	</string>


	<string id="st_mag_pkm_pkm">
		<text>100-round 7.62x54 PKM Box</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_pkm_pkm_descr">
		<text>
			Heavy box that holds 100 rounds of 7.62x54R ammunition in a belt, for use with the PKM. It is advised to bring a few of these if you plan on hunting Pseudogiants or Chimeras.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_l96a1_pkm">
		<text>Modified 10-round 7.62x54 L96A1 Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_l96a1_pkm_descr">
		<text>
		Modified L96A1 Magazine calibre 7.62x54.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_mag_sv98_7.62x54">
		<text>Standard 7.62x54 SV98 Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_sv98_7.62x54_descr">
		<text>
			Standard 10-round polymer magazine for the SV-98 sniper rifle. The SV-98 is used primarily by Russian law enforcement; limited numbers have found their way into the hands of the Duty faction through secret channels.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_mag_svd_7.62x54">
		<text>Standard 7.62x54 SVD Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_svd_7.62x54_descr">
		<text>
			Standard 10-round magazine for the SVD and SVU sniper rifle. The SVD is popular with members of all factions, if they can get their hands on such a rifle. 
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_svd_7.62x54_extended">
		<text>20-round 7.62x54 SVD Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_svd_7.62x54_extended_descr">
		<text>
			Extended 20-round magazine for the SVD and SVU sniper rifle. Commonly used with the SVU-A rifle to allow it to temporarily fill the role of LMG in close quarters engagements.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_mag_svt40_7.62x54">
		<text>Standard 7.62x54 SVT-40 Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_svt40_7.62x54_descr">
		<text>
			Standard 10-round magazine used with the SVT-40 rifle. The SVT-40 is a classic Great War rifle that is popular with many stalkers, especially Loners.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_mag_svt40_pkm">
		<text>Standard 7.62x54 SVT-40 Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_svt40_pkm_descr">
		<text>
			Standard 10-round magazine used with the SVT-40 rifle. The SVT-40 is a classic Great War rifle that is popular with many stalkers, especially Loners. This variant has been modified slightly to allow for loading of 7.62x54 machine gun rounds.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_mag_svt40_7.62x39">
		<text>Modified 7.62x39 SVT-40 Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_svt40_7.62x39_descr">
		<text>
			SVT-40 magazine modified to load the intermediate 7.62x39 round.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_mag_trg_magnum_300">
		<text>Standard .338 LM Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_trg_magnum_300_descr">
		<text>
			5-round magazine for the Sako TRG-42, L96 AWM and M24 SWS. This magazine was originally designed for the Sako, however, it has been 'modified' slightly to accommodate different rifles. Works fine in most rifles, as long as you remember to tap the magazine every once in a while.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_l96a1m_magnum_300">
		<text>10-round .338 LM L96A1 Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_l96a1m_magnum_300_descr">
		<text>
			Standard-issue 10-round magazine for the L96A1 that fits the slightly larger and considerably more powerful .338 Lapua Magnum. The L96 is a favorite of Western mercenaries and Monolith forces.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_mag_m98b_magnum_300">
		<text>Standard .338 LM M98B Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_m98b_magnum_300_descr">
		<text>
			10-round magazine compatible with the Barrett M98B.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	
	<string id="st_mag_vssk_12.7x55">
		<text>Standard 12.7x55 VSSK Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_vssk_12.7x55_descr">
		<text>
		Standard 5-round magazine used in the VSSK sniper rifle.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_ash12_12.7x55">
		<text>Standard 12.7x55 ASh-12 Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_ash12_12.7x55_descr">
		<text>
		Standard ASh-12 Magazine with capacity for 10 rounds. It is unlikely more than 10 rounds will ever be needed for human targets.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_ash12_ext_12.7x55">
		<text>Extended 12.7x55 ASh-12 Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_ash12_ext_12.7x55_descr">
		<text>
		Extended ASh-12 Magazine with capacity for 20 rounds. For when you need to bring down giant mutants.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_m82_12.7x55">
		<text>10-round 12.7x55 M82 Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_m82_12.7x55_descr">
		<text>
			10-round magazine for the Barrett M82 rifle, modified to fit 12.7x55 STs rounds. The first stalker to bring such a monster of a weapon discarded it after running out of ammunition; enterprising technicians have retrofitted this weapon to fire more common rounds without needing to replace the very heavy barrel.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	
	<string id="st_mag_saiga12s_12x70">
		<text>Standard 12x70 Saiga-12S Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_saiga12s_12x70_descr">
		<text>
		Standard Saiga-12S magazine with capacity for 8 shotshells. The Saiga is a good quality shotgun that is popular with Dutyers.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_saiga12s_ext_12x70">
		<text>Extended 12x70 Saiga-12S Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_saiga12s_ext_12x70_descr">
		<text>
		Extended Saiga-12S magazine with capacity for 12 shotshells. More shells means more mutants you can kill each each magazine.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_mag_usas12_12x70">
		<text>Standard 12x70 USAS-12 Drum</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_usas12_12x70_descr">
		<text>
		20-shell drum for the USAS-12 automatic shotgun. The firepower offered by the USAS-12 is unrivaled at short range, although the weight and magazine bulk makes it impractical to carry around.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_vepr_12x70">
		<text>Standard 12x70 Vepr-12 Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_vepr_12x70_descr">
		<text>
			Standard 10-shell magazine for the Vepr-12. Despite their similarities, the Vepr cannot share magazines with the Saiga.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_vepr_compact_12x70">
		<text>Compact 12x70 Vepr-12 Magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_vepr_compact_12x70_descr">
		<text>
			A small magazine for the Vepr-12 with only five shell capacity. Don't be fooled - the magazine can fit in your pocket and is extremely easy to load.
		</text>
	</string>

</string_table>
