<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<string_table>

	<!--COMMON-->
	<string id="st_mag_weapon_jammed">
		<text>Weapon jammed</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_eject_magazine">
		<text>eject magazine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_unload_ammo">
		<text>unload ammo</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_loadout_remove">
		<text>remove from loadout</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_loadout_add">
		<text>add to loadout</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_retool">
		<text>retool</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_mag_err_retool">
		<text>Cannot retool loaded magazine! Remove all rounds before retooling.</text>
	</string>
	<!-- MCM -->
	
	<string id="ui_mcm_menu_magazines">
		<text>Magazines</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_menu_magazines_title">
		<text>Anomaly Magazines</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_magazines_title">
		<text>Anomaly Magazines Redux</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_magazines_lootquality">
		<text>Loot quality</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_magazines_lootquality_desc">
		<text>Multiplier on chance to find good ammo in magazines, and improved magazines.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_magazines_ignore_loaddelay">
		<text>Disable per-magazine bullet un/load time</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_magazines_ignore_loaddelay_desc">
		<text>If enabled, use consistent times for loading/unloading ammo from magazines \nThis changes un/load speeds to 1 second per bullet \nFactor sliders below still take effect</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_magazines_mag_loadtime_factor">
		<text>Bullet load time factor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_magazines_mag_loadtime_factor_desc">
		<text>Multiplier for bullet load time \nIf per-magazine bullet un/load time is disabled can be treated as seconds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_magazines_mag_unloadtime_factor">
		<text>Bullet unload time factor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_magazines_mag_unloadtime_factor_desc">
		<text>Multiplier for bullet unload time \nIf per-magazine bullet un/load time is disabled can be treated as seconds</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_magazines_debug">
		<text>Enable Debug Logs</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_magazines_debug_desc">
		<text>Enables debugging logs in console.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_magazines_empty_mags_stack">
		<text>Stack empty magazines in inventory</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_magazines_empty_mags_stack_desc">
		<text>If enabled, empty magazines will stack together in inventory instead of being separate.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_magazines_sort_inv">
		<text>Sort inventory as magazines are updated</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_magazines_sort_inv_desc">
		<text>Uncheck this if you don't like items in your inventory moving around when magazines are updated.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_magazines_highlight_color">
		<text>Highlight Color</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_magazines_highlight_color_desc">
		<text>Highlight color for magazines that are part of your loadout.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ui_mcm_magazines_highlight_clr_a">
		<text>Highlight Opacity</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_magazines_highlight_clr_a_desc">
		<text>How much of the UI background is visible through the highlight. Lower values make the highlight more subtle.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ui_mcm_lst_ram_orange">
		<text>Orange</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_lst_ram_pink">
		<text>Pink</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_lst_ram_blond">
		<text>Blond</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_lst_ram_white">
		<text>White</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_lst_ram_brown">
		<text>Brown</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_lst_ram_blue">
		<text>Blue</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ui_mcm_magazines_show_hud">
		<text>Enable Magazine HUD</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_magazines_show_hud_desc">
		<text>If enabled, you will see magazines currently equipped in your HUD, near your ammo counter.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_magazines_icon_text">
		<text>Enable Ammo Text on Magazine HUD</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_magazines_icon_text_desc">
		<text>If enabled, you will see text on the HUD for the first round in a magazine.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_magazines_ammo_icon">
		<text>Enable Ammo Icons on Magazine HUD</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_magazines_ammo_icon_desc">
		<text>If enabled, you will see small ammo icons on the HUD for the first round in a magazine.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_magazines_retain_round">
		<text>Enable "one in the chamber"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_magazines_retain_round_desc">
		<text>If enabled, weapons retain a round in the chamber when magazines are ejected.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_magazines_fast_loading">
		<text>Enable Fast Loading in Stashes</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_magazines_fast_loading_desc">
		<text>If enabled, loading and unloading rounds in stashes will be instant, like in Escape from Tarkov.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_magazines_ejection">
		<text>Empty mag unload behavior</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_magazines_ejection_desc">
		<text>Controls where empty magazines go. (Throw to ground disabled, pending it ever working right)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_lst_ground">
		<text>Throw on ground</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ui_mcm_lst_ruck">
		<text>Put in backpack</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ui_mcm_lst_loadout">
		<text>Put in loadout</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ui_mcm_magazines_mag_unequip_trs">
		<text>Treat as empty %</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_magazines_mag_unequip_trs_desc">
		<text>Used for "Put in backpack" or "Throw on ground" option \nMagazines below this % will be treated as empty.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_magazines_rant">
	<text>An explanation of how combat reloading (reloading with inventory closed) works:

	\n\nYour load out is a set of pockets/loops on your vest. For this example you have 4 pockets and you have 4 mags in your load out, one in each pocket, and a fifth mag in the gun.
	\nYou go to reload, your gun is in one hand, you grab the magazine in the gun with the other and remove it. You now have a gun in one hand and a magazine in the other. All four pockets have a magazine in them so you can't put the magazine in your hand into a pocket and you can't take a magazine out of a pocket because both of your hands are full. What do you do?
	\nShove the magazine in your hand into your drop-pouch, or backpack since we don’t simulate a drop-pouch.
	\nNow you have a free hand, you take a magazine from a loadout pocket and put it into the gun. leaving you with one empty loadout pocket. Reload complete.
	\nIf you start the process with a free pocket in your loadout the mag from the gun gets put into that pocket. Unless it is empty, then by default it goes into your bag. This can be changed so that empty magazines are placed into loadout slots or dropped to the ground.

	\n\nIf you have the inventory open then it is not a combat reload and an additional attempt to place the magazine into your load out is performed because it is assumed you can set the gun or magazine down. Also the setting to drop magazines on the ground is ignored when inventory is open.
	\nHowever if you think that RavenAscendant is wrong and that during a combat reload your stalker has a magical third hand to hold the magazine that came out of the gun until it can be placed in the freed up loadout slot, or that they would hold it in their teeth/knees/armpit/psionic powers, then there is an option below to enable that behavior.\n\n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ui_mcm_magazines_three_hands">
			<text>Use a third hand to place an ejected magazine back into your loadout after a combat reload.</text>
	</string>


	<string id="ui_mcm_magazines_three_hands_desc">
			<text>Raven still thinks this is wrong.</text>
	</string>


	<!--MAGAZINES-->

	<string id="st_dot">
		<text>•</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_bonus">
		<text>(Outfit:%s + Extra:%s)<!--alt:> (%s + %s)<--></text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_small">
		<text>Small magazines:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_medium">
		<text>Medium magazines:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_large">
		<text>Large magazines:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_base">
		<text>Magazine base</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_base_descr">
		<text>Magazine base.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_mag_size">
		<text>Magazine size:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_size_small">
		<text>small</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_size_medium">
		<text>medium</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_size_large">
		<text>large</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mag_loaded">
		<text>Loaded magazine:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mag_loaded_none">
		<text>WARNING: No magazine loaded</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_mag_ammo_loaded_count">
		<text>Loaded rounds:</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_mags">
		<text>Anomaly Magazines</text>
	</string>
	<string id="article_mags_text">
		<text>
			%c[pda_green]Mags Redux%c[ui_gray_1]\n \n
			\nWelcome to using Mags Redux. This guide will cover most of the features and changes you can expect when using this mod.
			\nFor users of the old Anomaly Magazines (from Wuut) you can expect little difference in gameplay. Most of the functionality is the same.\n \n
			
			%c[pda_green]I. How to load and fire weapons%c[ui_gray_1]\n
			\n• Weapons that would logically use magazines in real life require the usage of magazines.
			\n   • Weapons that do not will behave as in vanilla (shotguns, some bolt rifles, revolvers)
			\n• Ammo must be manually loaded into magazines. The magazine description will indicate what sort of ammo is compatible. To load ammo, drag the ammo item onto the magazine. This will initiate a loading procedure, which will one by one load rounds in.
			\n   • To cancel this procedure, click anywhere.
			\n• To put a magazine into loadout, right click the magazine. There will be an option 'add to loadout'. The magazine background will change color and an icon will be added: this means the magazine has been added to your equipment loadout.
			\n   • From here, if you are holding an eligible weapon, reloading your weapon will utilize the magazine in your loadout.
			\n   • The mod will attempt to automatically select the magazine that a) has the largest size and b) has a top round equal to your ammo type.
			\n• Magazines can also be manually inserted and ejected. Right click a weapon to find the option to eject the magazine. 
			\n• Ammo wheel can be used to swap magazines. Magazines are categorized by the top round.\n \n
			
			%c[pda_green]II. Where to find magazines%c[ui_gray_1]\n
			\n• Vendors that stock guns will stock magazines. Magazines may also be sold to them for a pittance.
			\n• NPCs will have a couple magazines for their weapon, with a little ammo.
			\n   • NPCs, specifically high-rank NPCs, have a small chance of dropping improved magazines. These magazines load faster, have higher capacities, or both.\n\n

			
			%c[pda_green]III. Explanation of MCM options.%c[ui_gray_1]\n
			\n• Loot quality: Affects quantity of dropped mags, fill amount, and chance for improved magazines.
			\n• Load/unload time factor: Multiplier on the bullet load/unload speed in magazines.
			\n• Fast loading: Enables instant un/loading of magazines IN STASH ONLY.
			\n• One in the chamber: Preserves a chambered round when switching mags, just like real life. 
		</text>
	</string>


</string_table>
