<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>

<!-- Lukash (Freedom Leader) -->
	<string id="about_freedom_lider_miklyha_0">
		<text>Are you the stalker who broke through the Brain Scorcher and lived there for half a year?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_freedom_lider_miklyha_1">
		<text>Well, one of them. And it wasn't half a year - more like just over a month. But yeah, name's Lukash. Nice to meet you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_freedom_lider_miklyha_2">
		<text>How was it?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_freedom_lider_miklyha_3">
		<text>Look, buddy. I know that place is interesting and all, but I'd rather not start reminiscing. What matters most is that I got out safe and sound.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_freedom_lider_miklyha_4">
		<text>Got it. Thanks anyway.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="monolith_eidolon_start_0">
		<text>Praise the Monolith, brother.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="find_blackbox_mlr_reward_freedom_0">
		<text>I found a flight recorder.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="find_blackbox_mlr_reward_freedom_1">
		<text>Oh, serious? Bring it here. Let's see what these bozos are planning.</text>
	</string>


	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_3_1_0">
		<text>I'm looking for Leshiy, is he with you?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_3_1_1">
		<text>He sure is. Head down to the first floor, he's at the end of it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_3_1_2">
		<text>Thank you.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="devushka_5_help_0">
		<text>Hey Lukash, a friend of mine wanted to come see you. I think you know her.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="devushka_5_help_1">
		<text>Ah, yes. Come on in! Help yourself to some grass - you might need it for the trip ahead. You made the right choice coming here, you two. Loki's job became a lot harder after the Monolith got a second wind. The medicine you'll bring him will help save many decent people.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="devushka_help1_0">
		<text>Apparently Hip has never been past the Barrier before. Is this true?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="devushka_help1_1">
		<text>Yes. Can't blame her. After you watch some of your friends get zombified before your eyes, makes sense you'd want to get the hell away from the place it happened. Between that, and having to fight Duty...eh. But she seems resolved to make the trip now. The two of you will be going to Yanov station in Jupiter. Drop these meds off with Loki once you arrive.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="devushka_help1_2">
		<text>Alright. The sooner we go, the better.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="devushka_help1_3">
		<text>Hang on Lukash. Just need a minute to get everything together.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_life_ask">
		<text>Hey, Lukash! Care to chat about life in Freedom for a bit?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_life_1">
		<text>Sure! You've heard of Bob Marley, yes? His birthday is a celebrated event around here... *sigh* too bad the lads never seem to remember when it is. It's the sixth of February, in case you care, although good luck getting that into the heads of our seedy new arrivals.\n \nMake no mistake, the celebrations tend to be quite memorable - more ham than one can fit on a spit, and enough vodka to knock a pseudogiant on its ass.\n \nHahaha...yeah, good times. Still, sometimes I regret getting the boys to shack up in this place with me. Not everyone has the willpower to camp next to the Radar for years on end, and you can tell it's taking its toll.\n \nMake no mistake - my boys are badasses. Firm and hard to the core. But I see what they share with each other around the campfires. Reminds me of our days under Chekhov - disgraceful.\n \nBut what else are the lads supposed to do - use those spooky psy-helmets the government scientists conjure up in their bunkers? Nuh-uh. I know some of our more tight-assed boys around here do that, but how do they know those helmets are just there to protect their consciousness? How do they know it won't turn them into a different kind of zombie when the state decides to make its final move?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_life_2">
		<text>A while back, the government developed a specially modified bulletproof vest. It integrated carefully treated artefact fragments that could heal the wearer's wounds before their very eyes. Naturally, only the military got to use them, so we went ahead and changed that, hehe. Once we got hold of a few models, we tried to reverse-engineer the new technology into our own outfits.\n \nIt didn't really go anywhere for us at first, but luckily one of my boys, eh, stumbled upon some research notes. The data was made available to the public immediately.  Just like that, Freedom ensured the government monopoly on personal combat life support systems would be broken forever.\n \nThis is part of what Freedom is all about. We ensure the mice and the rats of this world don't get screwed over by all fat cats sitting at the top.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_life_3">
		<text>Yeah, I've got a minute.\n \nYou know what bullshit really tires me out some days? The idea of Freedom being nothing but a bunch of sexual deviants and druggies looking for their next hit, their next fix.\n \nI've heard many sick rumours from our detractors over the years... but none of them get my hackles up more than their fetishistic stories about us trying to get our peckers into Bloodsuckers. It all started as a vicious rumour by Duty a few years ago. How did this rumour come about, you ask? I warn you, it's not for the faint of heart.\n \nWhat happened was a couple of our brave new boys - about six of them, actually - were hunting for artefacts in the Bloodsucker Village. I was quite proud of them, most people are too afraid to go near that place. It was an ambush. A veteran Duty squad had already been camping in that village, waiting just for them. At the time, we thought those rookies were simply all killed, but no...\n \nWhat happened is Duty overwhelmed and kidnapped our young rooks easily. Duty stripped their armour off, paraded them back to that filthy bloodsport arena in Rostok, and arranged a fight. Off-the-books. They promised my missing boys they'd be let go if they could wrestle down a bloodsucker barehanded and... I'm sure you can guess what they were expected to do next. It makes me sick to recount this, but you need to know the full story.\n \nThey were pitted against two bloodsuckers - one for every three of my lads they had captured.  They were forced to pin the beasts down, and then... No, I can't say. Only that the sick Duty bastards were getting the whole thing on camera.  True to their word, Duty let the survivors go. If you can even call them survivors. After their emancipation, most refused to eat or drink. A few managed to get some nice, thick rope... or placed a gun down their throats and...\n \n...others, well, they died from withdrawal. Our sawbones later found traces of meth, cocaine and Adderal in their blood. We don't give our lads that stuff, so one can only assume Duty forced it down their throats.\n \nAnd what did Duty get? They got some exciting new images to back up their propaganda campaigns. And then I got some of the names of the bastards involved. And then they got stuck and left to die like bleeding pigs. But I'm not done yet.\n \nWe are Freedom fighters, and Duty has yet to pay for all the crimes against liberty that they have committed.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_life_4">
		<text>Alright. Today can be a cautionary tale. Many, many years ago we had a boy among our ranks - Pavlik, his name was. Well-liked, not a bad guy. He seemed open and laid-back, like many of our newer recruits first are. Well, he quickly made new friends, and the lads here at the base trusted him with all sorts of interesting facts, secrets, personal stories... One day, I discovered he was selling these secrets off to the mercs.\n \nPavlik isn't the only one who's done something like this. Freedom has a sad history of dealing with shit like this every year or so. These stories always begin differently, but all turn out the same way - with the damn snitch coughing the blood out his lungs, profoundly regretting his poor life choices.\n \nThere's a lot of love in our community. A lot of trust. I wouldn't want to *ever* be the guy who betrays it. Would you? </text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_life_5">
		<text>Yeah, the state of the Zone has been on my mind for a while. It wouldn't hurt to have someone else stand around and listen to what I'm thinking.\n \nI have to be honest, life isn't easy here. Only the strong, the flexible or the clever can expect to survive long. Those who get too stubborn, too careless, too complacent... they die quickly. The Zone has a way of killing off those who try to threaten or abuse it, while it lifts up those who respect it - those who remember that they're here because they have nowhere else to turn. Those who do not take it for granted.\n \nThis is why Freedom must do all it can to preserve the Zone. Despite its dangers, it's a wondrous place for others. For those who have nothing, those who have lost hope, they get to come here and find new purpose. Even inventors or artists who have lost their inspiration, or don't know how to make their next breakthrough - they can come here and leave with everything they need.\n \nThis is why we fight against the government - who'd shackle this miracle in red tape, cages and categories. It's why we battle with Duty, who'd gladly nuke this place again if it meant an end to the mutants and anomalies here. I want the Zone to be around when the sons and daughters of my nephews and nieces grow up. I want them to come and go from this place as they please, without any weedy officials or slimy organizations telling them that they can't.\n \nThis place was intended for all humanity. Not one human. Not even a group of them. And for this reason, we must make an end to tyrants.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_life_6">
		<text>Sure. I suppose you might have questions about our relations with some of the other groups.\n \nFirstly, as a general rule neutral stalkers off-limits. They represent the common man and are the lifeblood of what Freedom stands for. Of course, that doesn't mean you should blindly trust them, nor should you ever defer to them without good cause - many of them have pro-Duty or even pro-government views. But unless they're causing trouble, live and let live.\n \nSecondly, bandits. Who first called them bandits, anyways? Now, some of them genuinely are sick bastards. Those ones, I'd shoot myself, but most are just neutral stalkers that Duty have targeted and segregated with their propaganda campaigns. As a result, they're much more desperate than most stalkers, but they're just trying to survive here like anyone else.\n \nDushman's mercs? Between you and me, most of them are slimy bastards, but dependable when on a contract. The only thing they care about is money, and right now their money tells them to subvert the local government, much like we do. We get along at an arm's length, and that's all I really have to say about them.\n \nEcologists? If I had my way, I'd have given most of their state-funded asses an eviction notice ages ago. But Skinflint keeps whining about us needing supplies from their bunkers, and Loki is too soft-hearted to support me in this, despite otherwise being a good leader. Overall, Freedom respects their viewpoints enough that we leave the scientists alone. Even if I personally believe their studies are too harsh and invasive on the local wildlife.\n \nDon't even get me started on Duty or Military, or you'll get me ranting for hours.\n \nMonolith focus too much on their precious rock, rather than the Zone as a whole. Not to mention they're truly awful when it comes to sharing. Don't try to reason with them - they'd sooner blow up in your face than sit down for a chat, and would sooner kill you than let you take one step past the Barrier.\n \nAnd other groups? Well, they're around, but Freedom doesn't encounter them enough on a day-to-day basis for me to think much of them. Anyways, that's it for now. I can't spend my whole day discussing this.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_life_7">
		<text>Eh, life is too grave right now. Everyone's sitting at their posts, looking glum. It's ridiculous. Let me share a joke or two with you.\n \nSo, a state-sponsored news reporter successfully arranges an interview with a Freedom member - yeah I know, sounds crazy right there. It gets even better.\n \n"So what do you think of the military forces we have stationed here?" the reporter asks.\n"They are pigs. They are cruel, stupid and blind scum of the earth!" the Freedomer replies, like the good lad he is.\nThe reporter pauses for a bit, then asks her next question.\n"Alright. So what do you think of Duty?"\nThe Freedomer goes silent, as if deep in thought, before finally saying...\n"Actually, the military isn't so bad when you put it like that..."</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_life_8">
		<text>No matter what else you might hear about Freedom, remember this: we happily accept anyone who recognizes that the Zone is a place where the rule of state doesn't apply. It's a place where you can live right and live freely under your own morals and common sense instead... as long as you're willing to live with the consequences, too. This is what Freedom is all about - taking life on our own terms. By banding together, we ensure this ideal is never suppressed.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_life_9">
		<text>Yeah, let me tell you something about our worst enemy.\n \nSo, an experienced Dutyer and a rookie Dutyer are walking in the Zone, when suddenly the older one stops dead in his tracks and whispers to his underling.\n"Shh! Move over to that tree. Carefully."\nThe younger Dutyer starts sweating and begins carefully, very carefully, moving to the tree. He does little zig-zags, even spinning in quick circles to what the danger might be.\nEventually, he reaches the tree. Suddenly, the veteran Dutyer shouts.\n"I KNEW IT! I KNEW THEY WERE LYING WHEN THEY SAID THERE WERE ANOMALIES THERE!" \n \nHeh. Classic campfire joke. What, you were expecting something serious? Things are tense enough around camp as it is. Unless we have any real business to discuss, I'd appreciate you giving me some space for now. I need to concentrate on keeping this base afloat.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_life_end">
		<text>Maybe another time, man? Right now, I need to focus on keeping the boys coordinated, and I know a few of them will want to see me in private soon. </text>
	</string>
	
<!-- (Freedom guide) -->
	<string id="mil_freedom_guid_meet_0">
		<text>Hey, what's up?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_freedom_guid_meet_1">
		<text>Nothing much. I'm Leshiy, nice to meet you. I'm the local guide and scout.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_freedom_guid_meet_2">
		<text>And how's the local intelligence? I presume you've visited many places.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_freedom_guid_meet_3">
		<text>Indeed. I've even been in an anomaly. That was when I was still a mercenary... entered a spatial bubble with my squad. It's a long story. Anyway, I offer guides to the Cordon, Yantar and Yanov station in Jupiter. Forty-five hundred, five thousand, and six thousand roubles respectively.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_freedom_guid_meet_4">
		<text>I'll keep that in mind.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="mil_freedom_guid_go_0">
		<text>Lead me somewhere.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_freedom_guid_go_1">
		<text>Sure, man. Where to?</text>
	</string>
		<string id="mil_freedom_guid_go_2">
			<text>To Jupiter. %c[d_orange][6000 RU]</text>
		</string>
		<string id="mil_freedom_guid_go_5">
			<text>Need the money first, pal.</text>
		</string>
		<string id="mil_freedom_guid_go_8">
			<text>Here, all yours.</text>
		</string>
		<string id="mil_freedom_guid_go_3">
			<text>To the Cordon. %c[d_orange][4500 RU]</text>
		</string>
		<string id="mil_freedom_guid_go_6">
			<text>Got the money?</text>
		</string>
		<string id="mil_freedom_guid_go_9">
			<text>Here, keep it.</text>
		</string>
		<string id="mil_freedom_guid_go_4">
			<text>To Yantar. %c[d_orange][5000 RU]</text>
		</string>
		<string id="mil_freedom_guid_go_7">
			<text>Did you bring the money?</text>
		</string>
		<string id="mil_freedom_guid_go_10">
			<text>Of course. Here.</text>
		</string>
	<string id="mil_freedom_guid_go_11">
		<text>Forgot it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_freedom_guid_go_12">
		<text>I've changed my mind.</text>
	</string>

</string_table>
