<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
	<string id="st_af_surge_up_name">
		<text>Improved surge regenerator</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_surge_up_descr">
		<text>Unique, a device that absorbs electrical energy around itself and partially transforms it into the body, increasing endurance. Excess energy leads to the regeneration of damaged tissues. It mainly serves as an over voltage protection for limited short-circuit shock current, limiting the amount of electricity coming into contact with the body, by closing it to the ground. Represents a rather complex electronic circuit of valuable radio components, which greatly increases the electrical resistance of the body. As a result, the body falls under a lower voltage and is able to withstand discharges of electricity that previously led to death. Thus, it is vitally important to have a current-limiting microreactor when it is necessary to approach electric anomalies or other sources of electricity. Like any electronic object, it can be used as a repair material with appropriate tools and skills.\n \n%c[d_red]\n\n%c[d_red]WARNING:%c[ui_gray_2]\n \n%c[default]It should be noted that such a module will not be able to work properly and provide sufficient protection if your suit does not meet the minimum protection requirements while in an abnormal field.\n \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] effectiveness of mult. units is stackable\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_frames_up_name">
		<text>Improved aluminium frames</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_frames_up_descr">
		<text>Instead of simply carrying a backpack secured by a pair of shoulder straps, one can attach it to the suit by means of aluminium frames, which optimises your carrying capabilities. These improved frames are made of aluminium which is the material of choice due to its light weight, and some external elements are made of plastic in order to attain desired flexibility while sprinting. The whole construction is equipped with a system of straps and webbing to provide a high degree of adjustability. This quality design allows the shoulder straps to be adjusted up or down so as to make wearing a backpack comfortable regardless of one's torso size. Single set of frames replaces only the main framework of your backpack, but it's possible to use more sets to further improve your carrying capabilities. Although the system is built of light aluminium, some parts can still prove useful for minor outfit repairs.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] everyday item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] effectiveness of mult. units is stackable\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_grid_up_name">
		<text>Improved titanium grid</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_grid_up_descr">
		<text>Instead of simply carrying a backpack secured by a pair of shoulder straps, one can attach it to the suit by means of a titanium grid, which optimises your carrying capabilities. The improved grid is made of titanium which is the material of choice due to its light weight and high durability, and some external elements are made of plastic in order to attain desired flexibility while sprinting. The whole construction is equipped with a system of straps and webbing to provide a high degree of adjustability. This quality design allows the shoulder straps to be adjusted up or down so as to make wearing a backpack comfortable regardless of one's torso size. A single grid replaces only the main framework of your backpack, but it's possible to use more grids to further improve your carrying capabilities. Grids are created from very high quality titanium, thus disassembled grid can be used as an effective combat outfit or helmet repair supplement.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] everyday item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] high quality\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] effectiveness of mult. units is stackable\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_freon_up_name">
		<text>Improved freon emission module</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_freon_up_descr">
		<text>The improved freon emission module is designed to maintain a constant temperature around the body at the level of 20 degrees Celsius. It is thus extremely useful in order to minimise the effects of extreme heat in situations requiring additional protection. It emits a thick layer of freon-cooled air particles which produce a miniscule vacuum absorbing any excess heat and slightly decreasing the temperature around the user. Another feature of the freon emission module is its ability to resist electricity to a moderate extent.\n \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] effectiveness of mult. units is stackable\n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_cooler_up_name">
		<text>Improved body cooler</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cooler_up_descr">
		<text>The improved body cooler is an electric module designed to maintain a constant temperature around the body at the level of 14 degrees Celsius. It is thus extremely useful in order to minimise the effects of extreme heat in situations requiring additional protection. It emits quick electrical impulses which produce a miniscule vacuum absorbing any excess heat and slightly decreasing the temperature around the user. It does not require water to function. Another feature of the body cooler is its ability to resist electricity to a moderate extent. In case of disassembly of the unit using a toolkit, the metal casing can be reused as outfit repair material.\n \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] high quality\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] effectiveness of mult. units is stackable\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_kevlar_up_name">
		<text>Improved kevlar plates and attachments</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_kevlar_up_descr">
		<text>Kevlar plates are widely known for their protective capabilities, and are highly valued because of this feature. They perform a wide variety of functions, the most important of which is absorbing the impact of firearm projectiles on the front and the back of the torso. They constitute a lightweight alternative to heavy steel plates. Additionally, any type of armour plating also helps maintain suits in good condition, preventing degradation through wear and tear. Used by military units the world over.\n \n
		%c[d_orange]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_orange] • effectiveness of mult. units is stackable\n
		%c[d_orange] • protection is only applied to arms, legs and torso\n
		%c[d_orange] • +2 BR Class per unit\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_plates_up_name">
		<text>Improved carbon steel plates</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_plates_up_descr">
		<text>These steel plates are specially crafted, heat treated and shaped for ballistic defeating properties, fitting a wide variety of protective applications. They are designed to withstand smaller ballistic impacts on the front and the back of the torso. This protection, however, comes at a price as the thick steel plates are very heavy, thus limiting freedom of movement. Additionally, any type of armour plating also helps maintain suits in good condition, preventing degradation through wear and tear. Used extensively by Spetsnaz forces.\n \n%c[d_red]\n\n%c[d_red]WARNING:%c[ui_gray_2]\n \n%c[default]Steel is a conductor and its proximity to the skin makes the body more vulnerable to electricity. For this reason, it is suggested to proceed with caution when near electrical anomalies or other sources of electricity.\n \n
		%c[d_orange]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_orange] • effectiveness of mult. units is stackable\n
		%c[d_orange] • protection is only applied to arms, legs and torso\n
		%c[d_orange] • +4 BR Class per unit\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_camelbak_up_name">
		<text>Improved camelbak</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_camelbak_up_descr">
		<text>Borrowing its name from the myth that camels store water in their humps, camelbak is a pack worn on the back or around the waist of the user, containing a bladder that is filled with water to keep one hydrated. Flexible tube with a mouthpiece facilitates use even in most pressing situations. This model is camouflaged and integrated in the suit to protect the system from damage from any source, be it combat or anomaly. Because the container is made of a high-quality textile, experienced stalkers sometimes re-use scrapped camelbaks for quality materials to patch their field outfits.\n \n%c[d_red]\n\n%c[d_red]WARNING:%c[ui_gray_2]\n \n%c[default]Although water has low electrical conductivity, its proximity to the body may make you more vulnerable to electrical currents. For this reason, it is recommended to take special notice of your surroundings when in possession of a camelbak.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] military item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] effectiveness of mult. units is stackable\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_surge_name">
		<text>Surge suppressor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_surge_descr">
		<text>A small albeit advanced device that absorbs electrical energy from its closest surroundings. It serves as a protection of sorts as it limits the amount of electricity that comes into direct contact with the body by either blocking it or by shorting it to ground. As it is in fact a very sophisticated resistor circuit, the Surge Suppressor greatly increases electrical resistance of the body. The result is that the user is hit by a significantly lower voltage and is able to survive outbursts which would normally be lethal. It is thus of vital importance to have a surge suppressor on your belt when in proximity of electrical anomalies and other sources of electricity in the Zone. As with all metal objects, it can be used as a source of repair material as long as one has appropriate tools and enough skill.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] effectiveness of mult. units is stackable\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_frames_name">
		<text>Aluminium frames</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_frames_descr">
		<text>Instead of simply carrying a backpack secured by a pair of shoulder straps, one can attach it to the suit by means of aluminium frames, which optimises your carrying capabilities. The frames are made of aluminium which is the material of choice due to its light weight, and some external elements are made of plastic in order to attain desired flexibility while sprinting. The whole construction is equipped with a system of straps and webbing to provide a high degree of adjustability. This quality design allows the shoulder straps to be adjusted up or down so as to make wearing a backpack comfortable regardless of one's torso size. Single set of frames replaces only the main framework of your backpack, but it's possible to use more sets to further improve your carrying capabilities. Although the system is built of light aluminium, some parts can still prove useful for minor outfit repairs.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] everyday item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] effectiveness of mult. units is stackable\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_grid_name">
		<text>Titanium grid</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_grid_descr">
		<text>Instead of simply carrying a backpack secured by a pair of shoulder straps, one can attach it to the suit by means of titanium grid, which optimises your carrying capabilities. The grid is made of titanium which is the material of choice due to its light weight and high durability, and some external elements are made of plastic in order to attain desired flexibility while sprinting. The whole construction is equipped with a system of straps and webbing to provide a high degree of adjustability. This quality design allows the shoulder straps to be adjusted up or down so as to make wearing a backpack comfortable regardless of one's torso size. A single grid replaces only the main framework of your backpack, but it's possible to use more grids to further improve your carrying capabilities. Grids are created from very high quality titanium, thus disassembled grid can be used as an effective combat outfit or helmet repair supplement.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] everyday item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] high quality\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] effectiveness of mult. units is stackable\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_freon_name">
		<text>Freon emission module</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_freon_descr">
		<text>The freon emission module is designed to maintain a constant temperature around the body at the level of 24 degrees Celsius. It is thus extremely useful in order to minimise the effects of extreme heat in situations requiring additional protection. It emits a thick layer of freon-cooled air particles which produce a miniscule vacuum absorbing any excess heat and slightly decreasing the temperature around the user. Another feature of the freon emission module is its ability to resist electricity to a moderate extent.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] effectiveness of mult. units is stackable\n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_cooler_name">
		<text>Body cooler</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cooler_descr">
		<text>The body cooler is an electric module designed to maintain a constant temperature around the body at the level of 18 degrees Celsius. It is thus extremely useful in order to minimise the effects of extreme heat in situations requiring additional protection. It emits quick electrical impulses which produce a miniscule vacuum absorbing any excess heat and slightly decreasing the temperature around the user. It does not require water to function. Another feature of the body cooler is its ability to resist electricity to a moderate extent. In case of disassembly of the unit using a toolkit, the metal casing can be reused as outfit repair material.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] high quality\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] effectiveness of mult. units is stackable\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_kevlar_name">
		<text>Kevlar plates and attachments</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_kevlar_descr">
		<text>Kevlar plates are widely known for their protective capabilities, and are highly valued because of this feature. They perform a wide variety of functions, the most important of which is absorbing the impact of firearm projectiles on the front and the back of the torso. They constitute a lightweight alternative to heavy steel plates. Additionally, any type of armour plating also helps maintain suits in good condition, preventing degradation through wear and tear. Used by military units the world over.\n \n
		%c[d_orange]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_orange] • effectiveness of mult. units is stackable\n
		%c[d_orange] • protection is only applied to arms, legs and torso\n
		%c[d_orange] • +1 BR Class per unit\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_plates_name">
		<text>Carbon steel plates</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_plates_descr">
		<text>These steel plates are specially crafted, heat treated and shaped for ballistic defeating properties, fitting a wide variety of protective applications. They are designed to withstand smaller ballistic impacts on the front and the back of the torso. This protection, however, comes at a price as the thick steel plates are very heavy, thus limiting freedom of movement. Additionally, any type of armour plating also helps maintain suits in good condition, preventing degradation through wear and tear. Used extensively by Spetsnaz forces.\n \n%c[d_red]\n\n%c[d_red]WARNING:%c[ui_gray_2]\n \n%c[default]Steel is a conductor and its proximity to the skin makes the body more vulnerable to electricity. For this reason, it is suggested to proceed with caution when near electrical anomalies or other sources of electricity.\n \n
		%c[d_orange]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_orange] • effectiveness of mult. units is stackable\n
		%c[d_orange] • protection is only applied to arms, legs and torso\n
		%c[d_orange] • +3 BR Class per unit\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_camelbak_name">
		<text>Camelbak</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_camelbak_descr">
		<text>Borrowing its name from the myth that camels store water in their humps, camelbak is a pack worn on the back or around the waist of the user, containing a bladder that is filled with water to keep one hydrated. Flexible tube with a mouthpiece facilitates use even in most pressing situations. This model is camouflaged and integrated in the suit to protect the system from damage from any source, be it combat or anomaly. Because the container is made of a high-quality textile, experienced stalkers sometimes re-use scrapped camelbaks for quality materials to patch their field outfits.\n \n%c[d_red]\n\n%c[d_red]WARNING:%c[ui_gray_2]\n \n%c[default]Although water has low electrical conductivity, its proximity to the body may make you more vulnerable to electrical currents. For this reason, it is recommended to take special notice of your surroundings when in possession of a camelbak.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] military item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] effectiveness of mult. units is stackable\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_iam_name">
		<text>Improvised Application Module (empty)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_iam_descr">
		<text>The Improvised Application Module (IAM) filters a small amount of radiation particles emitted from artefacts. This mechanical metal pouch is the cheapest device that allows the user to harness the power of less potent artefacts. Artefact filter is composed of multiple layers made primarily of lead which shield from radiation. A low-cost alternative to the more reliable AAC and AAM. In case of emergency or if no longer needed, the module can be utilised as a source of quality metal for use in outfit or helmet repairs. Currently unusable. To attach it to the belt, you have to put an artefact inside. The artefact will retain its characteristics with the exception of reduced radiation output. Due to its low quality, the IAM is only able to block beta particles. Formed by all artefacts, beta particles are able to damage skin in a similar way to a burn.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[ui_white] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] valuable\n
		%c[ui_white] • %c[ui_gray_2] artefact storage device\n
		%c[ui_white] • %c[ui_gray_2] maximum capacity:%c[ui_gray_1] 1\n
		%c[ui_white] • %c[ui_gray_2] protects from the following radioactive emissions:\n
		%c[d_blue]   - beta particles\n
		%c[ui_white] • %c[ui_gray_2] state:%c[ui_gray_1] empty\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_aac_name">
		<text>Artefact Application Container (empty)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_aac_descr">
		<text>The Artefact Application Container (AAC) filters a moderate amount of radiation particles emitted from artefacts. This mechanical aluminium container is the most cost-efficient and thus the most popular way of handling artefacts as it allows the user to harness the power of more potent artefacts. Artefact filter is composed of multiple layers made primarily of lead, with one layer of thorium which has strong radiation shielding properties. This device has been manufactured by scientists residing in military bunkers around the Zone. In case of emergency or if no longer needed, the module can be utilised as a source of quality metal for use in outfit or helmet repairs. Currently unusable. To attach it to the belt, you have to put an artefact inside. The artefact will retain its characteristics with the exception of reduced radiation output. Compared to the IAM, the AAC is capable of filtering out gamma rays. Formed by most artefacts, gamma rays are able to penetrate skin, damage DNA, and in high doses, internal organs by breaking the bonds between atoms in a molecule.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] valuable\n
		%c[ui_white] • %c[ui_gray_2] artefact storage device\n
		%c[ui_white] • %c[ui_gray_2] maximum capacity:%c[ui_gray_1] 1\n
		%c[ui_white] • %c[ui_gray_2] protects from the following radioactive emissions:\n
		%c[d_blue]   - beta particles\n
		%c[d_green]   - gamma rays\n
		%c[ui_white] • %c[ui_gray_2] state:%c[ui_gray_1] empty\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_aam_name">
		<text>Artefact Application Module (empty)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_aam_descr">
		<text>The Artefact Application Module (AAM) filters a significant amount of radiation particles emitted from artefacts. This advanced mechanical module is the most effective way of harnessing the power of most potent artefacts. Artefact filter is composed of numerous layers made of nano-carbon. It is hence lightweight and has strongest radiation shielding properties of all devices. Regarded as a symbol of affluence in the Zone. Most commonly used by the scientists to minimise the harmful effects of artefacts. Designed and manufactured in Ukraine by a government institute which provides equipment for the scientists residing in the Zone of Alienation. In case of emergency or if no longer needed, the module can be utilised as a source of quality metal for use in outfit or helmet repairs. Currently unusable. To attach it to the belt, you have to put an artefact inside. The artefact will retain its characteristics with the exception of reduced radiation output. Compared to the AAC, the AAM is capable of filtering out neutrons. Formed by only the most unstable artefacts, neutrons are able to penetrate skin and, in high doses, damage DNA and internal organs by causing instability to a molecule's atomic nuclei, which may then in turn decay to cause further damage. Even if the neutron is 'safely' absorbed, sufficient exposure will lead to deuterium poisoning.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] high quality\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] valuable\n
		%c[ui_white] • %c[ui_gray_2] artefact storage device\n
		%c[ui_white] • %c[ui_gray_2] maximum capacity:%c[ui_gray_1] 1\n
		%c[ui_white] • %c[ui_gray_2] protects from the following radioactive emissions:\n
		%c[d_blue]   - beta particles\n
		%c[d_green]   - gamma rays\n
		%c[d_orange]   - neutrons\n
		%c[ui_white] • %c[ui_gray_2] state:%c[ui_gray_1] empty\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
<!------------------------ Mutant Hide ------------------------>
	<string id="st_hide_flesh_name">
		<text>Flesh hide</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hide_flesh_descr">
		<text>Hide removed from a breed of mutated pigs commonly referred to as fleshes. Its heavy weight (its main drawback) results from a thick layer of fat underneath the relatively soft and shallow skin. It offers low physical protection, but on the other hand considerably reduces the harmful effects of chemical, thermal and electrical anomalies. Can be used only for minor repairs as the layer of fat is useless for the purposes of armour maintenance and must be cut off, leaving only a small patch of shallow skin tissue.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] light mutant pelt\n%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] damage prot. negligible\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] effectiveness of mult. units is stackable\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_hide_boar_name">
		<text>Boar pelt</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hide_boar_descr">
		<text>A hide almost fully covered with a thick layer of fur, removed from one of wild boars found commonly in the Zone. The mutants themselves are quite resistant to damage and can take considerable punishment, and the reason for this is simple: big muscle mass and almost unbreakable bones. The skin, on the other hand, is quite thin (most probably to provide the creature with effective means of thermal regulation), making it a rather poor choice for armour enhancement. The fur in turn makes the hide a relatively potent thermal insulator. Can also be used for light repairs. Unfortunately, wearing the pelt on top of the armour makes the user less resistant to radioactive and toxic damage as heavy particles often accumulate within the fur.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] light mutant pelt \n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] effectiveness of mult. units is stackable\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_hide_bloodsucker_name">
		<text>Bloodsucker skin</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hide_bloodsucker_descr">
		<text>Bloodsuckers as a species evolved from humans and this affinity can still be seen in the texture of their skin. What is most characteristic, the skin is very soft and pleasant in touch, almost like the skin of a child. This applies, however, only to the outer layer - underneath, bloodsuckers boast well-developed muscles which can be utilised to form a coat of sorts with considerable damage reducing potential, especially in regard to melee attacks. This makes bloodsucker skin a popular choice among experienced hunters who also wear it as a sign of their proficiency. The most unique property and at the same time the main drawback of the skin is its very intense reaction to temperature change - although the tissue itself will only burn in very high temperatures, it can get very hot making it increasingly damaging to wearer and equipment underneath it.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] medium mutant pelt\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] valuable \n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] effectiveness of mult. units is stackable\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_hide_psysucker_name">
		<text>Psysucker skin</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hide_psysucker_descr">
		<text>Psysuckers as a species evolved from bloodsuckers and this affinity can still be seen in the texture of their skin. What is most characteristic, the skin is very soft and pleasant in touch, almost like the skin of a child. This applies, however, only to the outer layer - underneath, Psysuckers boast well-developed muscles which can be utilised to form a coat of sorts with considerable damage reducing potential, especially in regard to melee attacks. This makes Psysucker skin a popular choice among experienced hunters who also wear it as a sign of their proficiency. The most unique property and at the same time the main drawback of the skin is its very intense reaction to temperature change - although the tissue itself will only burn in very high temperatures, it can get very hot making it increasingly damaging to wearer and equipment underneath it. Reports indicate that whereas the skin offers relatively low physical protection it can be used to absorb and disperse significant amounts of incoming psy waves when worn over the head.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] medium mutant pelt\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] valuable \n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] effectiveness of mult. units is stackable\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_hide_lurker_name">
		<text>Lurker hide</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hide_lurker_descr">
		<text>A thick hide almost fully covered with a layer of fur, removed from a lurker. The mutants themselves are quite resistant to damage and can take considerable punishment, and the reason for this is simple: big muscle mass and almost unbreakable bones. The skin of lurker is known for being thick and durable, making it a good choice for armour enhancement. The fur in turn makes the hide a relatively potent thermal insulator. Can also be used for light repairs.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] light mutant pelt \n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] effectiveness of mult. units is stackable\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_hide_burer_name">
		<text>Burer skin</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hide_burer_descr">
		<text>Skinning a burer is a lot like skinning a twisted dwarf. Add to it an almost unbearable stench of bad eggs and you get the idea why stalkers consider this quite a feat. Reports indicate that whereas the skin offers relatively low physical protection it can be used to absorb and disperse significant amounts of incoming psy waves when worn over the head. Burer's skin has low electrical resistance, thus the wearer is more susceptible to electrical damage. Furthermore, due to the fact that burers are relatively rarely encountered in the Zone, the skin has significant research potential, making it a valuable trading commodity for the scientists.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] light mutant pelt\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] rare scientific specimen\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] valuable\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] effectiveness of mult. units is stackable\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_hide_chimera_name">
		<text>Chimera hide</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hide_chimera_descr">
		<text>Chimera, being one of the most dangerous mutants in the Zone, is not only a significant threat, but can also be regarded as a viable source of wealth. All parts that can be taken from chimera's corpse can be sold for a large amount of money, but it is the skin that is one of the most valued scientific specimens as well as one of the best armour enhancements available in the Exclusion Zone. It offers very good protection properties and, even more importantly, is relatively light-weight thanks to which it does not limit mobility. However, its most unique feature is that organic fibres found in the skin act as very effective electrical conductors. This fact to a large degree confirms reports of recon units (especially those scouting around the AMK Industrial Complex) concerning sightings of chimeras surrounded in what looked like an electrical anomaly, producing discharges on contact with any hostile living organism. Unfortunately, no unit was able to make it back, so there is no evidence confirming the existence of such a creature.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] heavy mutant pelt\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] very rare scientific specimen\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] extremely valuable\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] effectiveness of mult. units is stackable\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_hide_pseudogiant_name">
		<text>Pseudogiant hide</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hide_pseudogiant_descr">
		<text>The skin of a pseudogiant in many ways resembles the skin of an elephant. It's thick and hard in touch, its texture is very irregular and full of folds which act as the creature's cooling mechanism. The average thickness of pseudogiant's skin is around 2 cm, which makes it very durable and capable of withstanding significant damage. This is, however, at the cost of increased weight. Since pseudogiants are known to often live in areas of high toxicity and radioactivity, the hide naturally adapted to such conditions, which further increases its usefulness. It can also be used to patch even the heaviest of outfits but this process requires the most durable and expensive tools available. It is valued not only for its practical qualities, but can also serve as a prestigious hunting trophy and a rare specimen for the scientists in the Zone.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] very heavy mutant pelt\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] scientific specimen\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] valuable\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] effectiveness of mult. units is stackable\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_hide_controller_name">
		<text>Controller scalp</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hide_controller_descr">
		<text>As is the case with other humanoid mutants, it's quite an emotional challenge to scalp a controller and it proves to be even more difficult as the face of a controller retains certain characteristics of the person it once was. Confidential sources within the military also revealed that fingerprints of the person who turned into a controller can sometimes be found in the database. Recent analysis shows that not only the hand of the controller is capable of producing psy waves - the whole body is the source of emissions. For this reason, the scalp - when prepared properly - has the ability to absorb and filter psy energy, but for this effect to take place it is necessary to cover your head with multiple scalps. The skin is also electrically conductive. As regards its physical properties, it is light and can only be used for minor outfit repairs. As is the case with all humanoid psy creatures, the skin of a controller is electrically conductive.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] light mutant pelt\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] rare scientific specimen\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] very valuable\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] effectiveness of mult. units is stackable\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_hide_pseudodog_name">
		<text>Pseudodog fur</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hide_pseudodog_descr">
		<text>Densely covered with short and stiff fur, the pelt of pseudodog remains one of the most useful, widespread and versatile mutant pelts available in the Zone. It can be easily attached to armour with even lightest of tools, and yet it's quite durable, which makes it suitable for medium-grade outfit repairs. When used as a whole - it can cover significant area of the body with protective layer which increases resistance to both physical damage and heat. The fur also provides effective insulation. However, as is the case with all such pelts, it easily catches radioactive and toxic particles, so it is highly advised to remove it when in radioactive or toxic areas.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] medium mutant pelt\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] effectiveness of mult. units is stackable\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_hide_psy_dog_name">
		<text>Psy-dog fur</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hide_psy_dog_descr">
		<text>The fur of a psy dog is undoubtedly one of the most beautiful and rare clothing materials in the world. Usually snow white or grey, it is in great demand and can be sold for a hefty sum of money. It's probably made its way into fashion industry thanks to smugglers some of whom have recently turned to hunting mutants. For those in the Zone, it can serve as a blanket, especially during cold nights, and offers efficient rupture protection and mild psy influence reduction when head part of the fur is used as a mask or a hood. However, it easily catches radioactive and toxic particles, so it is highly advised to remove it when in radioactive or toxic areas. Hunters wear it with pride, but only if the creature was slain by their own hands.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] medium mutant pelt\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] valuable\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] effectiveness of mult. units is stackable\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_powder_poltergeist">
		<text>'Diamond powder'</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_powder_poltergeist_descr">
		<text>"Diamond powder" is a common name given to crystal-like substance sometimes found in the belly of all species of psy creatures. It is not known what metabolic processes lead to its emergence and for this reason scientists are eager to pay large sums of money to lay their hands on it. Practical use is limited but some stalkers are known to sprinkle their most cherished hunting knives with it as it makes sharpening significantly easier. It also makes blades look shiny and well-kept.\n \n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] psy mutant metabolism product\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] very rare scientific specimen\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] valuable\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
</string_table>
