<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<!--===========================================================
<
< TEXT  STRINGS FOR TASKS ON MILITARY WAREHOUSES MAP
<	CoC 1.4.08 - DoctorX Questlines 1.6
<
<	Modified by: DoctorX
<	Last revised: October 07, 2016
<
<===========================================================-->

<string_table>


	<!-- /////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////
	<!--
	<!-- STORYLINE TASK TEXT  STRINGS
	<!--
	<!--	Modified by DoctorX
	<!--	for DoctorX Questlines 1.6
	<!--	October 07, 2016
	<!--
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Lukash (Freedom Honcho) Default Storyline Task -->

	<string id="drx_sl_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_default_task_name">
		<text>Get Next Task</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_default_task_text">
		<text>I have another job waiting. I should get to it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_default_task_about">
		<text>I want you to meet with someone. He is no friend of mine but he could use your assistance.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_default_task_finish">
		<text>Good luck stalker.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Lukash (Freedom Honcho) Assassination Storyline Task- -->

	<string id="drx_sl_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_1_name">
		<text>Assassination for Lukash</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_1_text">
		<text>Lukash has a target he needs eliminated.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_1_about">
		<text>Hey, I'm glad you came. I have something I need you to do for me. There is a mutual enemy of ours that needs to be eliminated. He is dangerous. Take him down immediately.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_1_finish">
		<text>Awesome bro! Thanks.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Lukash (Freedom Honcho) Freedom Assault on Monolith Storyline Task -->

	<string id="drx_sl_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_2_name">
		<text>Freedom Assault on Monolith</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_2_text">
		<text>Lukash has asked me to lead Freedom in an assault against the Monolith.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_2_about">
		<text>Monolith forces keep breaking through our blockade. I want to take the fight to them for once. I've recruited an assault squad and want you to lead them in an invasion on Monolith territory. Take them out.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_2_finish">
		<text>Man, you've got a set on you. Great job.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Lukash (Freedom Honcho) Search Lab X-8 (Outskirts) Storyline Task -->

	<string id="drx_sl_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_3_name">
		<text>Search Lab X-8</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_3_text">
		<text>Search Lab X-8 in Outskirts for evidence of Clear Sky occupation.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_3_about">
		<text>I have received information that former members of Clear Sky might have occupied Lab X-8 some time ago. I need you to investigate the Lab and see if you can recover any documents they might have left there.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_3_finish">
		<text>Excellent work. You have done well.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- \\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\ -->


	<!-- /////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////
	<!--
	<!-- CHANGE FACTIONS TASK TEXT  STRINGS
	<!--
	<!--	Modified by DoctorX
	<!--	for DoctorX Questlines 1.6
	<!--	December 08, 2016
	<!--
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Пропущенный диалог Лукаша -->

	<string id="drx_sl_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_cf_task_1_name">
		<text>Freedom!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_cf_task_1_text">
		<text>Lukash will introduce me to Freedom's way of life for a token sum of 15,000 RU.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_cf_task_1_about">
		<text>Heh, and I guess you're looking for a sweet taste of Freedom, aren't you? Yeah, I can sort you out. Just ask yourself one thing - "Do I have what it takes to be a badass"? Because you gotta have stones bigger than Death Lamps to roll with us. We have lots of good times here, sure, but when shit hits the fan, you gotta be ready to help defend your brothers against fanatics, fascists, governments...\n \nWe fight for a Free Zone. If you're serious about helping us set up an Anarchist Utopia here, kindly set aside 15,000 RU for the boys, and I'll happily introduce you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_cf_task_1_finish">
		<text>Good work. You're finally free. A word of warning, though - anyone who disrupts the freedom of my boys tends to wind up sleeping in the Bloodsucker Village. Remember to be considerate of others around here.</text>
	</string>
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Lukash (Freedom Honcho) Payoff Change Factions Task -->

	<string id="drx_sl_sl_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_cf_task_1_name">
		<text>Freedom!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_sl_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_cf_task_1_text">
		<text>Lukash will introduce me to Freedom's way of life for a token sum of 15,000 RU.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_sl_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_cf_task_1_about">
		<text>Heh, and I guess you're looking for a sweet taste of Freedom, aren't you? Yeah, I can sort you out. Just ask yourself one thing - "Do I have what it takes to be a badass"? Because you gotta have stones bigger than Death Lamps to roll with us. We have lots of good times here, sure, but when shit hits the fan, you gotta be ready to help defend your brothers against fanatics, fascists, governments...\n \nWe fight for a Free Zone. If you're serious about helping us set up an Anarchist Utopia here, kindly set aside 15,000 RU for the boys, and I'll happily introduce you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_sl_mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_cf_task_1_finish">
		<text>Good work. You're finally free. A word of warning, though - anyone who disrupts the freedom of my boys tends to wind up sleeping in the Bloodsucker Village. Remember to be considerate of others around here.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- \\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\ -->


	<!-- /////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////
	<!--
	<!-- DYNAMIC TASK TEXT  STRINGS
	<!--
	<!--	Modified by DoctorX
	<!--	for DoctorX Questlines 1.6
	<!--	October 07, 2016
	<!--
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Lukash (Freedom Honcho) Stop Enemy Assault Task -->
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_1_name">
		<text>Destroy the Enemy Detachment</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_1_text">
		<text>A detachment of stalkers has been causing problems for Freedom's friends. Lukash is offering a bounty to whoever takes these punks out.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_1_about">
		<text>Do you feel like helping Freedom for a reward? We've got some damn punks who won't settle down, and it's time to teach them a lesson. These rascals have been sneaking into our territory. They have been shooting at our friends. And, to top it all off, they have the gall to gaslight my men! It's time to give them a lethal education on personal space. Can you do it? </text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_1_finish">
		<text>Ah, great! Maybe now we'll get some goddamn peace and quiet around here, eh?</text>
	</string>

	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_2_name">
		<text>Raid the Enemy</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_2_text">
		<text>I have been tasked to raid enemy territory for Freedom. I should report back to Lukash after the job is done.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_2_about">
		<text>I have a dangerous but important mission if you are willing. With Monolith to the north and Duty to the south, things are getting a little claustrophobic for my liking. I need a certified badass to raid an enemy camp and give us more breathing room. Do you dare to be that badass?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_2_finish">
		<text>Ha! You actually did it, you mad man! Here, you've earned this, along with my respect.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_3_name">
		<text>Eliminate the Monolith Convert</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_3_text">
		<text>A Freedom member has converted to the Monolith. Lukash has tasked me with finding and killing him.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_3_about">
		<text>I've got some real heavy news, man. One of our Freedom fighters has fallen under the influence of the Monolith. He was a good man, and I know he wouldn't have wanted to continue living as some alien crystal's brainwashed killer. Please, find him and take him down. Otherwise, his old friends are going to have to do it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_3_finish">
		<text>It's done? Good. I know this was rough. Our brothers at the Barrier will drink to their fallen comrade. As for you, here's your payment.</text>
	</string>


	<!-- ASSASSINATE DUTY FOR FREEDOM TASK -->
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_4_name">
		<text>Deal with the Problematic Stalker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_4_text">
		<text>Lukash will reward me for capping a troublesome stalker.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_4_about">
		<text>There's a fellow who's walking around not far from here. He shot one of ours down once. And something like that cannot be forgiven. Will you take the job to whack him? We'll pay, don't worry.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_4_finish">
		<text>Hell yeah! That'll teach 'em to mess with us. Here's your reward, as I promised. Good job, stalker.</text>
	</string>


	<!-- FIND WEAPON FOR FREEDOM TASK -->
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_5_name">
		<text>Bring Lukash a Reliable %s</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_5_text">
		<text>Lukash has asked me to find a specific firearm in mint condition. I should return to him as soon as I find what he wants.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_5_about">
		<text>While Freedom's benefactors keep the lads supplied with the weaponry they need, I could really do with a new %s for personal reasons. If you happen to find one in excellent condition, I would be willing to give you a substantial payment for it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_5_fetch_about">
		<text>While Freedom's benefactors keep the lads supplied with the weaponry they need, I could really do with a new %s for personal reasons. If you happen to find one in excellent condition, I would be willing to give you a substantial payment for it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_5_fetch_finish">
		<text>Well done. This new shooter will make an enormous difference should the worst come to pass. Here is the payment I promised.</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- Lukash (Freedom Honcho) Decimate the Enemy Task -->
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_6_name">
		<text>Trigger Happy</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_6_text">
		<text>Lukash is promoting aggression against some of Freedom's enemies. I can bring %s to him for a sweet bounty.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_6_about">
		<text>Well, right now, we're stuck in a hammer and anvil situation. Y'know, zealots to the north, extremists to the south, and sprinkle in some military goons for good measure. How about you explain to them what we think of their edicts and commands the old-fashioned way? There'll be a sweet reward at the end for you, don't worry.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_6_fetch_about">
		<text>Well, right now, we're stuck in a hammer and anvil situation. Y'know, zealots to the north, extremists to the south, and sprinkle in some military goons for good measure. How about you explain to them what we think of their edicts and commands the old-fashioned way? After you've finished humiliating them, bring me %ses as trophies. There'll be a sweet reward at the end for you, don't worry.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_6_fetch_finish">
		<text>Hey, nice job, man. Here's your money.</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- Lukash (Freedom Honcho) Mortal Sin Unquenchable Flame Tasks -->
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_7_about">
		<text>Hey man. Here's a thing. Remember those Sin folks? They didn't get the memo the last time you kicked their collective asses, so I think it's high time for an encore. Loki said they've been spotted being unruly in Zaton, especially around the area of abandoned substation workshops. Go put them down.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_7_finish">
		<text>Some of the newer stalkers among Freedom are starting to think you're the Second Coming of Rambo. That you keep coming back alive and well from jobs like this makes me think they may be onto something. So here. A little something for our Rambo.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- Lukash (Freedom Honcho) Rescue the Freedom Agent Task -->
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_8_name">
		<text>Zoneraker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_8_text">
		<text>A Freedom spy needs to be extracted from an enemy faction. I'll need to kill the other members of the squad, then escort him back to the base. The spy has an SVD.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_8_about">
		<text>One of my best men is currently hiding out among the enemy, trying to learn their secrets. He's usually a solid guy, so when he begins missing our contact times, I begin to worry. I have a hunch he's been ratted out, and that the squad he's with is now quietly waiting for the perfect opportunity to silence him permanently. We need to get him home. He left me a location ping, but he's with other stalkers. You need to take care of them and bring my man back in one piece. You will recognize him by his rifle, an SVD. He will have to shoot at you to maintain his deception when you attack the group, but he won't be aiming too well, so don't hold a grudge.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_8_finish">
		<text>Fine work. Time to grease this guy's nuts for his knowledge.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_8_msg_join">
		<text>Hey man, stop! I'm the Freedom spy! Sorry for taking potshots at you. I had to keep my cover just in case...luckily you made it. If you bring me to Army Warehouses safely, Lukash will reward you well. Lead the way, I'll follow!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_8_msg_leave">
		<text>Thanks for pulling my nuts out of the fire, stalker! See you around!</text>
	</string>
	
	
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_9_name">
		<text>Why We Can't Have Nice Things</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_9_text">
		<text>Lukash has asked me to destroy the military vehicles in Cordon before they do any damage in the Zone. I'll need to bring explosives.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_leader_stalker_task_9_about">
		<text>Do you have explosives? If so, I've got a big job for you. Right now, the military is bringing armoured vehicles into the Zone to reinforce their troops. I ask you, is this fair? Look at the rusty, dysfunctional pieces of junk we have rotting in our warehouses! If we can't have tanks that work in the Zone, then neither can the government! My spies say these vehicles are arriving to be stationed at the Cordon checkpoint as we speak. Don't worry, they'll make sure the vehicles are unmanned when you pay your visit, so you can destroy them without being turned into swiss cheese. You want in? Then pack your pineapples and get going!</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Skinflint (Freedom Mechanic) -->
	
	<!-- FIND MUTANT MEAT FOR FREEDOM TASK -->
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_10_freedom_trader_stalker_task_1_name">
		<text>Bring Wild Game for Freedom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_10_freedom_trader_stalker_task_1_text">
		<text>Skinflint said he'd pay me to bring him %s. Time to go hunting.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_10_freedom_trader_stalker_task_1_about">
		<text>I have just the job for you, man, if you are not afraid of a few mutants. Are you interested?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_10_freedom_trader_stalker_task_1_fetch_about">
		<text>So, some of the guys are planning a dinner party to celebrate Bob Marley's birthday. Better late than never, right? Anyways, the more meat we can get for the feast, the better - so if you are out and about, bring me enough %s, and I'll make it worth your while. Jah will never forget you!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_10_freedom_trader_stalker_task_1_fetch_finish">
		<text>Ah, this'll make for a fine meal once the chef gets his hands on it. Here's your payment. Why not buy some vodka and celebrate?</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Skinflint (Freedom Mechanic) Deliver Equipment Dynamic Task -->

	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_10_freedom_trader_stalker_task_2_name">
		<text>Deliver Locked Case to Skinflint</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_10_freedom_trader_stalker_task_2_text">
		<text>Skinflint has a delivery that needs to be picked up.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_10_freedom_trader_stalker_task_2_about">
		<text>One of our couriers was supposed to bring a package through today. Sadly, they had to hide it somewhere safe when a Duty patrol caught wind of them. They sent me the stash coordinates before going invisible on the network, so if you're willing to walk on over and finish the job by fetching the goods, I'll give you a cut of their pay.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_10_freedom_trader_stalker_task_2_finish">
		<text>Let's take a look-see...ah yes. Just what we needed. Thank you stalker, here's your cut of the pay.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Skinflint (Freedom Trader) Night Terror Task -->
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_10_freedom_trader_stalker_task_3_name">
		<text>Phantoms in the Dark</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_10_freedom_trader_stalker_task_3_text">
		<text>Skinflint will pay me to stop a terrible mutant that haunts the Bloodsucker Village. I'll need to keep myself alert.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_10_freedom_trader_stalker_task_3_about">
		<text>Sleep has been a little harder around camp lately. Each night we hear screaming, but before we can do anything about it, yet another one of our men on the road gets swallowed by the darkness. We find their mangled remains strewn about the Bloodsucker Village the next day.\n \nLukash thinks a rare breed of bloodsucker may be in town. A darker, stronger, more vicious motherfucker that only comes out at night. A few of our war-dogs think we should cease night hikes until it migrates and hopefully starts messing up Duty instead, believing it's too risky for us to go after it directly.\n \nWell, I say if you've got the stones to wait for it in the Village after nightfall, I'd be thrilled to shower you in roubles for killing the bastard, and the rest of the lads around here will be grateful to get a good night's sleep again. Or at least as good as sleep gets this close to the Brain Scorcher. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_10_freedom_trader_stalker_task_3_finish">
		<text>Wow, you actually did it! You lunatic. I'll let the camp know the good news. Glad we have a hunter like you around.</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Skinflint (Freedom Trader) Scarce Supplies Task -->
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_10_freedom_trader_stalker_task_4_name">
		<text>Scarce Supplies</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_10_freedom_trader_stalker_task_4_text">
		<text>Skinflint needs %s to help keep Freedom's medic stocked. I've agreed to help him.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_10_freedom_trader_stalker_task_4_about">
		<text>Hey man. Some of our guys can get a bit too adventurous from time to time. We haven't got enough supplies to treat all of 'em.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_10_freedom_trader_stalker_task_4_fetch_about">
		<text>Yeah. You know how rough and tumble life can be in Freedom, right? Dodging bullets and fighting fanatics is just part of the daily life around here. As badass as it makes Freedom's fighters feel, it also means we're getting short on meds. Since Solid is too high off his ass to organize medical supplies, that responsibility now falls to me. If you can help out by bringing in some %s, you'd have Freedom's gratitude. And some of my roubles. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_10_freedom_trader_stalker_task_4_fetch_finish">
		<text>Ah, brilliant. I'll make sure these stay out of Solid's sight until his patients need it. Thanks a lot, stalker.</text>
	</string>
	
	
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_10_freedom_trader_stalker_task_5_name">
		<text>Amass Equipment for Freedom Infiltration</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_10_freedom_trader_stalker_task_5_about">
		<text>Well, there is something important that needs looking at. A special infiltration mission to Rostok is planned, I must keep the details secret sorry. We need some equipment to perfect the disguise of our special operatives in order for them to blend in perfectly. We need 5.45x39 HP rounds, about 10 full boxes, so that they can defend themselves against mutants on the road to Rostok without alerting the checkpoint guards. If things go south our men will need some army grade medical supplies as well, 5 complete army medkits should do. Don't fret, your payment will be adequate. If you go the extra mile and get some cocaine and some porn mags, you'll even get a bonus, this should help our operatives to bribe some Duty members to accomplish their mission. So, you in?</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- \\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\ -->


	<!-- /////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////
	<!--
	<!-- MECHANIC TASK TEXT  STRINGS
	<!--
	<!--	Modified by DoctorX
	<!--	for DoctorX Questlines 1.6
	<!--	October 07, 2016
	<!--
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Screw (Freedom Mechanic) Find Level 1 Toolkit Task -->

	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_mechanic_stalker_task_1_name">
		<text>Find %s for Screw</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_mechanic_stalker_task_1_text">
		<text>%s are required by Screw to install basic equipment upgrades, I should bring them back to him if I find any.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_mechanic_stalker_task_1_about">
		<text>Yo! Some bandits were supposed to give us some new tools from Dark Valley, but they never showed! Eh, they were probably bullshitting anyway, but if you manage to find some bog-standard, entry-level tools, bring them here as quick as you can. You'd be well paid for your help. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_mechanic_stalker_task_1_fetch_about">
		<text>Good! Once you find some %s, I can finally get the ball rolling around here.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_mechanic_stalker_task_1_fetch_finish">
		<text>Thanks, man! I knew there was a reason I asked you. You look like a man who can get shit done.</text>
	</string>



	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_mechanic_stalker_task_2_name">
		<text>Find %s for Screw</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_mechanic_stalker_task_2_text">
		<text>%s are required by Screw to install advanced equipment upgrades, I should bring them back to him if I find any.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_mechanic_stalker_task_2_about">
		<text>Yeah, you know what isn't right? We're sitting right in the middle of one of the government's old armouries - it was a real storehouse for their special forces, back in the day. Yet half the amazing gear they left behind has just been lying around, rusting to shit because we don't have the proper tools to maintain everything.\n \nWe should change that. Bring me another toolkit - something more advanced this time. It's time to show the Man we can run His war machines better than He can!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_mechanic_stalker_task_2_fetch_about">
		<text>Thanks. If you manage to come through for me on this, I'll be able to perform more intricate upgrades on your equipment in future, too.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_mechanic_stalker_task_2_fetch_finish">
		<text>You keep this shit up, everyone around here is going to love you. Thanks again, man.</text>
	</string>


	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_mechanic_stalker_task_3_name">
		<text>Find %s for Screw</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_mechanic_stalker_task_3_text">
		<text>%s are required by Screw to install expert equipment upgrades, I should bring them back to him if I find any.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_mechanic_stalker_task_3_about">
		<text>Well, the bad news is most of the big guns stashed in the armoury really can't be saved at this point. The good news is this - I could do some real nice calibrations on the equipment we do have working, even our exoskeletons. What I'll need, though, is a more precise set of tools.\n \nCare to help Freedom tech up one more time?  The reward will be even better than last time, and I'll throw in some field maintenance lessons for good measure!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_mechanic_stalker_task_3_fetch_about">
		<text>Ha! You absolute mad lad! Well, go on then. Once you're back with some expert tools, I will show you what a talented mechanic can do.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_smart_terrain_7_7_freedom_mechanic_stalker_task_3_fetch_finish">
		<text>Man, Freedom's gonna love this. Shotguns with parachutes! Armoured SMGs! I'll make it happen! Here's your cash, for a job well done.</text>
	</string>
	
	
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Defend the barrier -->
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<string id="barrier_defense_monolith_announce">
		<text>To every friendly Stalker reading this, a large group of Monolith soldiers is approaching the Barrier, any help will be appreciated and rewarded.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barrier_defense_monolith_title">
		<text>Defend the Barrier</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barrier_defense_monolith_descr">
		<text>Freedom is asking for help to repel a Monolith attack.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="barrier_defense_monolith_chatter_1">
		<text>Monolith? I'll pass...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barrier_defense_monolith_chatter_2">
		<text>Whoa, free money. Here I come!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barrier_defense_monolith_chatter_3">
		<text>I wasn't planning to go to the Army Warehouses any time soon anyway.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barrier_defense_monolith_chatter_4">
		<text>Rewarded how? Cash, artefacts, guns? I'm not going to drag my ass there for just some vodka.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barrier_defense_monolith_chatter_5">
		<text>Damn! I'm too far, I'd get there when it's all over already. Wanted to test my new rifle.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barrier_defense_monolith_chatter_6">
		<text>Killing Monolith? I'll do it for free, damn fuckers.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barrier_defense_monolith_chatter_7">
		<text>Can I keep what I find on the bodies?</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="barrier_defense_monolith_intro_1">
		<text>I've heard your transmission, I have come to help defend the Barrier.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barrier_defense_monolith_intro_2">
		<text>Excellent, the scouts reported several Monolith squads approaching and any extra gun is welcome. Get in position and wait for the fanatics to show up, simple right? If you feel it's becoming too much and decide to run we won't hold it on you but of course you can forget the reward.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="barrier_defense_monolith_outro_1">
		<text>The Barrier is safe.. for now at least.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barrier_defense_monolith_outro_2">
		<text>Good shooting stalker, this should cover some of the lead you put in those bastards. And a little extra to relax. Glad we had you around!</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="barrier_defense_monolith_start_announce">
		<text>The scouts say they're on the move right now, everybody get in position!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barrier_defense_monolith_midchatter">
		<text>Oh damn, watch out! They got an RPG!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barrier_defense_monolith_run_announce">
		<text>This ain't summer camp stalker. Be thankful there's people with more balls than you to keep your lot safe.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barrier_defense_monolith_end_announce">
		<text>Good job brothers, and thanks to all the volunteers that didn't run away. Come back to me for your reward.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="barrier_defense_zombie_announce">
		<text>To every friendly Stalker reading this, a large group of zombies is approaching the Barrier, any help will be appreciated and rewarded.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barrier_defense_zombie_title">
		<text>Defend the Barrier</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barrier_defense_zombie_descr">
		<text>Freedom is asking for help to repel a zombie attack.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="barrier_defense_zombie_chatter_1">
		<text>Poor things...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barrier_defense_zombie_chatter_2">
		<text>I'll pass, just doesn't feel right.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barrier_defense_zombie_chatter_3">
		<text>Well, at least it isn't Monolith.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barrier_defense_zombie_chatter_4">
		<text>This better be worth it, last time I spent more bullets than what I got in return.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barrier_defense_zombie_chatter_5">
		<text>Damn! I'm too far, I'd get there when it's all over already. Wanted to test my new rifle.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barrier_defense_zombie_chatter_6">
		<text>Zombies from the Radar? Damn... my friend went there just a few days ago.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barrier_defense_zombie_chatter_7">
		<text>Can I keep what I find on the bodies?</text>
	</string>
	
	
	<string id="barrier_defense_zombie_intro_1">
		<text>I've heard your transmission, I have come to help fighting the zombies.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barrier_defense_zombie_intro_2">
		<text>Very well, usually they dont put up much of a fight but we are short on manpower thanks to Monolith and those pretend soldiers, it should be as easy as shooting at the range.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="barrier_defense_zombie_start_announce">
		<text>The horde is breaking through, everybody get in position!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barrier_defense_zombie_midchatter">
		<text>Don't they ever end?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barrier_defense_zombie_run_announce">
		<text>What is it, scared of things that can barely shoot back?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barrier_defense_zombie_end_announce">
		<text>Good job brothers, finally they can rest in peace. Volunteers, come back to me for your reward.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="barrier_defense_zombie_outro_1">
		<text>They're all dead, for real now.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barrier_defense_zombie_outro_2">
		<text>Very well, hope you didn't recognize anyone in there. Sometimes people come back from the Barrier more shaken up than when fighting Monolith. Let's have a drink at those poor souls, and something to help you not end up like them.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="barrier_defense_reinforcements_1">
		<text>Hold on guys, we're coming to help!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barrier_defense_reinforcements_2">
		<text>We just departed from the base, we'll be there soon.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barrier_defense_reinforcements_3">
		<text>Is it that bad over there? I though you were enough!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barrier_defense_reinforcements_4">
		<text>It has already begun! Come on guys move your ass or we'll miss all the action!</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- Solid (Freedom Medic) -->
	<string id="mil_freedom_medic_task_1_name">
		<text>Find %s for Solid</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_freedom_medic_task_1_text">
		<text>A %s is required by Solid for his work on medical supplies. I should bring it back to him if I find one.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_freedom_medic_task_1_about">
		<text>Maintaining what's left from medical supplies storage with this number of injuries I have to treat on daily basis is worrying. I'm gonna run out of bandages and medkits soon or later. I need you to find me one of those old drug-making kits. They will come in handy for sure.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_freedom_medic_task_1_fetch_about">
		<text>You bet your sweet ass there is. I've been looking all over for a %s. It should contain just the right cocktail of ingredients I need to make all sorts of drugs. For medicinal use, of course. I know the things some of the lads around here say about me. Don't listen to that bullshit. All I need is some decent kit, and I'll be able to get my little clinic into decent shape again.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_freedom_medic_task_1_fetch_finish">
		<text>Great job! I owe you big time.</text>
	</string>

</string_table>
