<string_table>

	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_5_name">
		<text>Clear Lab X16 Research Field for Ecologists</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_5_text">
		<text>Pr. Sakharov needs the Lab X16 to be cleaned from mutants so his teams can perform some research in the lab.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_5_about">
		<text>Dear stalker, I have a mission for you if you are up to the task. My assistants and research teams need to check some anomalies in the Lab X16, also called the Brain Lab, or the Miracle Machine. According to recent researchs, such laboratories can apparently encompass very rare artefacts. The main issue is that ever since the machine has been turned off, the lab has become the new home of many mutants. This hinders my research and I need the Lab X16 to be purged from the mutants presence. Could you help me?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_5_finish">
		<text>Wonderful news, I am dispatching my research teams and assistants as soon as possible. Here is your reward. Until next time stalker.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_6_name">
		<text>Clear Agroprom Underground Research Field for Ecologists</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_6_text">
		<text>Pr. Sakharov needs the Agroprom Underground lab to be cleaned from mutants so his teams can perform some research.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_6_about">
		<text>Dear stalker, I have a mission for you if you are up to the task. My assistants and research teams need to check some anomalies in Agroprom Underground. According to recent researchs, this place contains rare artefacts. However this installation is full of mutants and is very unsecure. If my research teams know it has been recently cleaned by an experienced stalker, I think they will have enough courage to perform some research in these underground tunnels. Could you help me?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_6_finish">
		<text>Wonderful news, I am dispatching my research teams and assistants as soon as possible. Here is your reward. Until next time stalker.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_fanat_task_3_name">
		<text>Clean Mutants in Meadow</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_fanat_task_3_text">
		<text>Fanatic needs Meadow to be cleaned from mutants so that loners can establish a base there in the near future.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_fanat_task_3_fetch_about">
		<text>Listen up bratan: we have more and more loners in Cordon and we want to expand the base towards Meadow. It's a cosy and strategic place, however it is filled with dangerous mutants. We need a kind a soul that would be able to clear the various mutant nests from Meadow. Are you in? You will of course be rewarded considering how dangerous that place is.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_2_12_stalker_fanat_task_3_fetch_finish">
		<text>Oh, you've cleared the mutants from Meadow? That's some seriously awesome news, to be honest I didn't think you would be able to make it. This will for sure make the next expeditions towards Meadow easier. Who knows, maybe we will be able to start building an outpost over there. Here is your reward.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="mechanic_explanation">
		<text>Bratan, does it look like I have time to spare to repair your equipment? "Do it yourself", do you know it? I heard it's trending on the social networks. Anyway, you can use the workbench that is around, for free. You can distinguish it thanks to the lit lamp. Everyone is using it, and yet nobody is turning the lights off. I guess that saving the planet isn't the top concern of most stalkers. \n\n
		Alright no need to be grumpy, let me tell you few tips and tricks.\n
		First, Keep in mind that guns parts can be swapped without a workbench nor any repair kit, except for the barrel. Repair kits however allow you to replace any part of the guns with a brand new one. Meanwhile, cleaning kits allow you to clean dirty parts that are within your gun directly, including the barrel.\n
		Now, back on the workbench, you can repair guns and armors with the appropriate repair kits overthere.  You can also upgrade your equipment and craft some new gear as well. To give you ideas about how to craft new stuff, I have some blueprints for sell if you want. 
		</text>
	</string>



</string_table>