<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
	
    <string id="ui_mcm_npe_module_gamma_tutorial_ammo_ammo">
        <text>Damage System Tutorial</text>
    </string>

    <string id="ui_mcm_npe_module_gamma_tutorial_ammo_title">
        <text>G.A.M.M.A. Tutorials</text>
    </string>

    <string id="ui_mcm_npe_module_gamma_tutorial_ammo_desc">
        <text>Damage System</text>
    </string>
	
    <!-- MCM -->
    <!-- Name of the toggle that sets if tutorial has been completed-->
    <string id="ui_mcm_npe_module_gamma_tutorial_ammo">
        <text>G.A.M.M.A. Ammo</text>
    </string>
    <!-- MCM -->

    <!-- Title of the whole tutorial -->
    <string id="ui_mcm_npe_module_gamma_tutorial_ammo_title">
        <text>Damage System Tutorial</text>
    </string>

    <!-- Cards -->
    <!-- 1 -->
    <string id="ui_gamma_tutorial_ammo_card_01_title">
        <text>Using the right tool for the right job
		</text>
    </string>

    <string id="ui_gamma_tutorial_ammo_card_01_description">
        <text>
			• Your survival will depend on using the correct ammunition type and caliber depending on the enemies that you are facing.\n \n
			
			• Ammunition are generally belonging to one of the 3 following types:\n
				 | - Full Metal Jacket (FMJ): cheap ammunition with a good compromise between armor penetration and damage.\n
				 | - Hollow Point (HP): more expensive ammunition designed to deal more damages to soft targets, like flesh.\n
				 | - Armor Penetrative (AP): even more expensive ammunition designed to pierce stalker’s armors.\n \n

			• You can press the Y key (by default) to quickly select the different ammo type for your currently active gun.\n \n

			• Certain calibers do not have access to all three ammunition type (9x21, 7.62x39, 7.62x54r, 7.62x51...).\n \n

			• You can check ammunition properties by hovering your mouse over ammo boxes in your inventory. You will find precious information this way:\n
				 | - Ammunition Armor Penetration Power value (AP).\n
				 | - Ammunition Stopping Power (DMG).\n \n

			• Certain guns can have slight damage boosts compared to other guns in a given caliber, thus increasing the ammunition Nominal Power.\n \n
		</text>
    </string>
    <!-- 1 -->

    <!-- 2 -->
    <string id="ui_gamma_tutorial_ammo_card_02_title">
        <text>Armor Penetration
		</text>
    </string>

    <string id="ui_gamma_tutorial_ammo_card_02_description">
        <text>• Stalkers wear armors that can withstand several bullets that do not have enough armor penetration. \n \n

• Stalkers have armor values split following three areas: legs, upper body, head. Each limb group has its own armor value depending on the armor the stalker wears. Shooting in the same limb group consistently will help defeating opponents armor faster than spraying and praying.\n \n

• Using low armor penetration ammunition against heavily armored enemies can kill them, especially if aiming in the legs that are less armoured that the body and the head. It will however require a lot more ammunition than AP ammo in the head.\n \n

		</text>
    </string>
    <!-- 2 -->
    
    <!-- 3 -->
    <string id="ui_gamma_tutorial_ammo_card_03_title">
        <text>Flesh Damage
		</text>
    </string>

    <string id="ui_gamma_tutorial_ammo_card_03_description">
        <text>• Mutants are considered soft targets and are easier to defeat using high damage rounds. \n \n

• Armor Penetration hardly matters when hunting mutants.\n \n

• Keep in mind that dealing damage, and defeating armors, is all about big numbers, but a high rate of fire and a low recoil can achieve better results than a bigger, slower, less controllable gun.\n \n

• You can see this tutorial again by going in Mod Config Menu > NPE Modules > G.A.M.M.A. and by unticking the tutorial. \n \n
</text>
    </string>
    <!-- 3 -->
</string_table>