<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
	
    <string id="ui_mcm_npe_module_gamma_tutorial_artefact_artefact">
        <text>Artefacts Tutorial</text>
    </string>

    <string id="ui_mcm_npe_module_gamma_tutorial_artefact_title">
        <text>G.A.M.M.A. Tutorials</text>
    </string>

    <string id="ui_mcm_npe_module_gamma_tutorial_artefact_desc">
        <text>Artefacts</text>
    </string>
	
    <!-- MCM -->
    <!-- Name of the toggle that sets if tutorial has been completed-->
    <string id="ui_mcm_npe_module_gamma_tutorial_artefact">
        <text>G.A.M.M.A. Artefacts</text>
    </string>
    <!-- MCM -->

    <!-- Title of the whole tutorial -->
    <string id="ui_mcm_npe_module_gamma_tutorial_artefact_title">
        <text>Artefacts Tutorial</text>
    </string>

    <!-- Cards -->
    <!-- 1 -->
    <string id="ui_gamma_tutorial_artefact_card_01_title">
        <text>Using an Artefact Detector
		</text>
    </string>

    <string id="ui_gamma_tutorial_artefact_card_01_description">
        <text>%c[ui_white]
		• You just equipped an Artefact Detector. These can be used using the "6" key (by default). Beware that detectors need batteries to work.\n \n
		
		• Each detector can detect different tiers of artefacts: \n
		  | - Echo Detector: up to T1 artefacts. \n
		  | - Bear Detector: up to T2 artefacts. \n
		  | - Grizzly Detector and more: up to T4 artefacts. \n \n

		• Detectors passively detect surrounding artefacts: when an artefact is available, a small artefact icon marked with a "?" will blink in the bottom left corner of the screen. The detection range is however reduced compared to having a detector in your hands. \n \n

		• Anomalous fields in which artefacts are found usually have elemental anomalies, radiations and more: be sure to be adequately equipped before diving in such dangerous locations. Your inventory has a convenient UI displaying all your resistances (20% means 20% damage reduction). \n \n
		</text>
    </string>
    <!-- 1 -->

    <!-- 2 -->
    <string id="ui_gamma_tutorial_artefact_card_02_title">
        <text>Artefacts Types
		</text>
    </string>

    <string id="ui_gamma_tutorial_artefact_card_02_description">
        <text>%c[ui_white]
				• There are two types of artefacts: %c[d_orange]Perktifacts%c[ui_white] and %c[pda_blue]Defensive Artefacts%c[ui_white].\n \n
		
				• %c[d_orange]Perktifacts%c[ui_white] always spawn at 100% efficiency. However their efficiency decreases overtime when they are equipped. %c[d_orange]Perktifacts%c[ui_white] provide extremely diverse and situational buffs and capacities. These effects are often increased depending on the number of the same Perktifact that you have equipped on your belt.\n \n

				• %c[pda_blue]Defensive Artefacts%c[ui_white] spawn at random low efficiency, but their efficiency remains the same overtime. The higher the %c[pda_blue]Defensive Artefacts%c[ui_white] efficiency, the stronger the effects. %c[pda_blue]Defensive Artefacts%c[ui_white] provide damage resistances. However, they often provide maluses to certain resistances as well. Higher tier %c[pda_blue]Defensive Artefacts%c[ui_white] (indicated by chevrons on the artefact icon) provide stronger resistances increase (... and malus).\n \n
		</text>
    </string>
    <!-- 2 -->
    
    <!-- 3 -->
    <string id="ui_gamma_tutorial_artefact_card_03_title">
        <text>Empowering Artefacts
		</text>
    </string>

    <string id="ui_gamma_tutorial_artefact_card_03_description">
        <text>%c[ui_white]
				• Two %c[pda_blue]Defensive Artefacts%c[ui_white] of the same kind can be combined to cumulate their efficiencies through the "Artefact Empowering" process (22% Wrenched + 32% Wrenched = 54% Wrenched).\n \n
				
				• This process requires the Artefact Melter, a tool that can be found (in white stashes, rarely) or bought (from Ecologists).\n \n

				• To Empower a %c[pda_blue]Defensive Artefacts%c[ui_white], right-click the Artefact Melter tool, select "empower", select the artefact you want to empower and select the second artefact of the same kind. This will consume one charge of the Artefact Melter.\n \n	

				• Artefact Melter charges can be regenarated by destroying artefacts by holding the Left Alt key and drag and dropping the Artefact Melter onto a given artefact in your inventory. The number of charges regenerated depend on the artefact tier. \n \n		
		</text>
    </string>
    <!-- 3 -->
	
    <!-- 4 -->
    <string id="ui_gamma_tutorial_artefact_card_04_title">
        <text>Crafting Artefacts
		</text>
    </string>

    <string id="ui_gamma_tutorial_artefact_card_04_description">
        <text>%c[ui_white]
				• %c[pda_blue]Defensive Artefacts%c[ui_white] can be crafted using the Artefact Melter.\n \n
				
				• Right-click the Artefact Melter, select "fusion", and craft artefacts following the recipes requirements (alternatively, you can access the menu through the workbench UI).\n \n				

				• New recipes can be bought from Ecologists traders. The highest tier of artefacts can only be crafted through a set of recipes found on high rank stalkers.\n \n		
				
				• The crafted %c[pda_blue]Defensive Artefacts%c[ui_white] will have an efficiency inherited from the artefact(s) used in the recipe (average of all artefacts efficiencies).\n \n		
		</text>
    </string>
    <!-- 4 -->
	
    <!-- 5 -->
    <string id="ui_gamma_tutorial_artefact_card_05_title">
        <text>Other Belt Items
		</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_gamma_tutorial_artefact_card_05_description">
        <text>%c[ui_white]
				• There are other type of belt items: Pelts and Tech Items.\n \n
				
				• Pelts are obtained from skinning mutants. The better the knife, the better the condition of the Pelts. Only one Pelt can be equipped at a time, but they only provide bonuses.\n \n

				• Tech Items can be bought from traders or crafted. Upgraded versions of the Tech Items can only be obtained through upgrading the base Tech Items from the crafting UI.\n \n		

				• %c[d_orange]Combining the effects of Artefacts, Pelts and Tech Items is of paramount importance to overcome the challenges of the Zone.\n \n \n

			%c[yellow]You can see this tutorial again by going into Mod Config Menu (MCM) > NPE Modules > G.A.M.M.A. and unticking the tutorial.\n \n</text>				
		</text>
    </string>
    <!-- 5 -->
</string_table>