<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
    <!-- SERIOUS: If anybody wants to edit this please make sure that you save it in `windows-1251` encoding. Otherwise the dots for card 5 get fcked up.-->

    <!-- MCM -->
    <!-- Name of the toggle that sets if tutorial has been completed-->
    <string id="ui_mcm_npe_module_gamma_tutorial_repair_armor">
        <text>Armor Maintenance</text>
    </string>
    <!-- MCM -->

    <!-- Title of the whole tutorial -->
    <string id="ui_mcm_npe_module_gamma_tutorial_repair_armor_title">
        <text>Armor maintenance</text>
    </string>

    <!-- Cards -->
    <!-- 1 -->
    <string id="ui_gamma_tutorial_repair_armor_card_01_title">
        <text>Armor repair tutorial</text>
    </string>

    <string id="ui_gamma_tutorial_repair_armor_card_01_description">
        <text>You just looted your first armor, congratulations. However it might not be readily useable. Let's learn how to repair it.\n \nEach armor belongs to an armor class. Each class has a corresponding armor repair kit:\n
            • Light\n
            • Medium\n
            • Heavy\n
            • Exo\n \nAll of these (except exo repair kits) can be looted, or crafted with the appropriate toolkits and components.\nTo be able to craft an exo repair kit you need to find the crafting recipe for it first.
        </text>
    </string>
    <!-- 1 -->

    <!-- 2 -->
    <string id="ui_gamma_tutorial_repair_armor_card_02_title">
        <text>The anatomy of armors</text>
    </string>

    <string id="ui_gamma_tutorial_repair_armor_card_02_description">
        <text>Armor related items can be broken down into 4 categories:\n
                • Repair kits\n
                • Repair items\n
                • Support items\n
                • Components\n \nRepair kits\nYou need one to be able to swap components.\n \nRepair items\nThese are used for field reparis. The numbers indicate the minimum overall armor condition required to use it.\n \nSupport items\nDuring a repair these items can be added to boost the base condition gain from a repair. Some repair items can also be support items.\n \nComponents\nThese items are what armors are comprised of. These can only be swapped at a workbench. The armors overall condition is determined by the condition of it's components.
        </text>
    </string>
    <!-- 2 -->
    
    <!-- 3 -->
    <string id="ui_gamma_tutorial_repair_armor_card_03_title">
        <text>Field repairs</text>
    </string>

    <string id="ui_gamma_tutorial_repair_armor_card_03_description">
        <text>If you have a repair item that can repair the armor at it's current overall condition all you have to do is right click the repair item and click use (or double click) then select the support material (if you want to use one) and click repair.\n \nBelow a certain condition (dictated by the armor class' repair kit) you can no longer field repair an armor and have to swap parts at a workbench.</text>
    </string>
    <!-- 3 -->
    <!-- Cards -->
</string_table>