<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<!--
	Weapons
-->

<string_table>
	
	<string id="st_not_in_use">
        <text>ѕредмет не используетс€/The Item is not in use</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_not_in_use_descr">
        <text>ѕредмет не используетс€/The Item is not in use </text>
    </string>

	<string id="st_knifebf4">
        <text>The ЂOTs-04ї Combat knife</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_knifebf4_descr">
        <text> The OTs-04 knife was developed at the Tula Central Design Research Bureau (TsKIB) in the late 80s - early 90s and was intended for special forces of the Interior Ministry troops. </text>
    </string>
	
	<string id="st_kukri">
        <text>Kukri</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_kukri_descr">
        <text>This is a special blade made of high-carbon spring-spring steel of the bus, which for many years stood in an anomal field, and therefore has excellent cutting and chopping properties. Ideal for cutting mutants of all stripes, and for protection against them. </text>
		</string>
		
	<string id="st_wpn_ak12_custom">
        <text>AK-12 Monolith</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_ak12_custom_descr">
        <text>A rare stuff. Modified version of AK-12 2012. Mainly used by the Monolith faction. Has several modes of firing: automatic, single and, three rounds.\n \n
		%c[0,140,140,140]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[0,93,0,116] Х %c[0,140,140,140] The weapon can be upgraded using tactical kit\n
		%c[0,93,0,116] Х %c[0,140,140,140] Scopes: All scopes for picatinny\n
		%c[0,93,0,116] Х %c[0,140,140,140] Silencer: 5.45/7.62 Hexagon Sound Suppressor\n</text>
    </string>

    <string id="st_wpn_ak12_mono_kit">
		<text>AK12 Monolith Upgraded</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_ak12_mono_kit_descr">
		<text>A rare stuff. Modified version of AK-12 Monolith. Mainly used by the Monolith faction. Has several modes of firing: automatic, single and, three rounds. Thanks to the new trigger group, it is a more advanced and powerful weapon than the original. Increased rate of fire and improved balancing. 
 This is irreversible upgrade.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[0,93,0,116] Х %c[0,140,140,140] The weapon was upgraded using "Monolith" Tactical Kit\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: Trijicon Acog and AN/PEQ-16 LAM (integrated).\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] "Guard" Grenade Launcher.\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: Hexagon 5.45/7.62 Sound Suppressor.\n </text>
    </string>
				
	<string id="st_wpn_ak12_m1">
        <text>ј -12 (2016)</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_ak12_m1_descr">
        <text>The version of the AK-12 presented to the public in 2016. It differs quite significantly in appearance and in the design of a number of important units from the previous version of the AK-12 shown in 2015. The design of the machine was revised both to eliminate a number of identified shortcomings and problems, and in the direction of improving manufacturability, taking into account the wishes of the military.\n 
		%c[0,140,140,140]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[0,93,0,116] Х %c[0,140,140,140] Scopes: All scopes for picatinny\n
		%c[0,93,0,116] Х %c[0,140,140,140] GP-25 grenade launcher\n
		%c[0,93,0,116] Х %c[0,140,140,140] Silencer: 5.45/7.62 Hexagon Sound Suppressor\n</text>
    </string>
		
		<string id="st_wpn_usp_tac">
        <text>HK USP Match Tactical</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_usp_tac_descr">
        <text>This is modification of the HK USP Match specially developed for scientists by the personal order of Professor Sakhorov, designed for use in the "Specialist-Scientist" kit. The operation of the system of mechanisms is improved with the help of artefacts. The difference from the standard USP Match is the ability to install a silencer. The gun is equipped with an enlarged magazine for 22 rounds of 9mm caliber. (The Specialist-Scientist kit includes: BCC Savant, HK USP Match Tactical, Monolith Blade).\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] The kit includes Laser Aiming Module and Red Dot Sights mount.\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: Docter Sight, Aimpoint T1 (low mount), Trijicon RMR, Leupold DeltaPoint PRO.\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: AAC Black Box\n </text>
    </string>
	
	
	
	<string id="st_wpn_vintorez_m1">
		<text>VSS "Savant"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vintorez_m1_descr">
		<text>This is early prototype of VSS Savant. This build is more popular between pro-stalkers because of lower price than final version. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All except of EOTS-62 and Tactical Kits (two scopes)\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] supressor VSS (integrated)\n </text>
	</string>
	
	
	<string id="st_wpn_vintorez_m2">
		<text>VSS "Merc"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vintorez_m2_descr">
		<text>At the request of the Syndicate of Mercenaries, a team of enthusiastic scientists led by Professor Sakhorov was engaged in finalizing the prototype. To develop and conduct field trials, it took about 20 artefacts from gravitational anomalies. As a result, this allowed the Picatini bar to be installed on the receiver without loss of accuracy, as well as improved mechanics, which led to higher reliability indicators..\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ATPIAL (Advanced Target Pointer Illuminator Aiming Laser) AN/PEQ-15 produced by L3 Insight Technologies. Tactical device that combines laser designators in both visible and IR band with IR searchlight. \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All except of 1P59 Giperon\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Fab Defense stock and foregrip are installed\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] supressor VSS (integrated)\n </text>
	</string>
	
	
	<string id="st_tactical_knife">
		<text>Monolith's Blade</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_tactical_knife_descr">
		<text>[RUSSIAN ACCENT "ON"] It is rumoured, these blades are produced in very a few by masters from a groupment Monolith. Threw composition of alloy not known - it is talked to extract him it is possible only in the heart of sarcophagus.[RUSSIAN ACCENT "OFF"]</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_saiga12s_m1">
		<text>Saiga-12 "Nerd"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_saiga12s_m1_descr">
		<text>Nerd - is the evidence of the professorТs concern for his wards. This Saiga version was purchased specifically for personnel. Used in "negotiations" with especially dangerous mutants about the transfer of their organs as a gift to science .. Experienced hunters look with considerable envy at the "nerds" armed with this model.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All Red Dot scopes for Dovetail mount.\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: Hexagon 12K\n </text>
	</string>
	
	
	<string id="st_wpn_m4_ru556">
		<text>Ruger SR-556</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m4_ru556_descr">
		<text>Several of these rifles entered the Zone through scientists. According to legend, Professor Sakharov received 6 small conteiners with these guns from foreign sponsors, 
but 5 of them were lost during transportation. 
Ruger SR-556 is an American self-loading carbine manufactured by the arms company Sturm, 
Ruger & Company, Inc. became the first Ruger of the AR-10 family. Ruger SR-762 chambered for .308. 
Belongs to a few samples of AR-15 rifles using the removal of powder gases. 
Production ceased in January 2016 after the introduction of the Keymod Lightweight option.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Universal mount by NcStar with Trijicon RMR red dot sight installed on it. \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes:  All for picatinny/weaver (except of Red Dot Sights with low mount: Trijicon RMR, Leupold DeltaPoint PRO, Aimpoint T1 (low mount), Docter Sight, 1P76 Rakurs (low mount).\\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Suppressor: NATO\n </text>
	</string>
	
	
	<string id="st_wpn_saiga12s_m2">
		<text>Dushman's Saiga</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_saiga12s_m2_descr">
		<text>Saiga modified by mercs request. Picatinny rail and a massive muzzle brake compensator installed, significantly reducing recoil.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All Red Dot scopes for picatinny/weaver and for Dovetail mount except of OKP-7, Kobra EKP-1S-03, Kobra EKP-8-02.\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: SilencerCo SalvoЃ 12\n </text>
	</string>
	
	
	
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74m_beard">
		<text>AK-74M Beard</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74m_beard_descr">
		<text> This AK, a kind of beard venom (not to be confused with his tea). Lightweight and tailored to the harsh conditions of the Zone. Does not provide for mounting a grenade launcher. It is made at Skadovsk and Yanov Station, from where it disperses throughout the Zone.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: all scopes for Dovetail mount (except of 1p59 Giperon and PSO scopes with an eyecup) and all red dot sights (except of Aimpoint PRO and Aimpoint T1 with high mount and Barska 11090). The use of PSO scopes with an eyecup on this weapon is highly not recomended.\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: TGP-A. No Grenade Launcher available for this model\n </text>
	</string>
	
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak105_sp">
		<text>AK-105 Specialist</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak105_sp_descr">
		<text> The modification was based on the usual AK-105, which, as a result, (thanks to mercenaries craftsmen) for a long time turned into a favorite burrel of these guys.A very balanced weapon with low recoil, good accuracy and high wear resistance.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Leupold Deltapoint Pro Red Dot sight preinstalled on NcStar 45 mount\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All scopes for dowetail mount except of PSO scopes with an eyecup, 1P59 Giperon and red dot sights.\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: TGP-A.\n </text>
	</string>



		<string id="st_wpn_akm_isg">
		<text>Rifle Dynamics RD-47 ISG</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_akm_isg_descr">
		<text> A custom model developed on the basis of AKM by the American company Rifle Dynamics. It is one of the most high-tech weapons in the Zone. Used by ISG special units.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ATPIAL (Advanced Target Pointer Illuminator Aiming Laser) AN/PEQ-15 produced by L3 Insight Technologies. Tactical device that combines laser designators in both visible and IR band with IR searchlight. \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All scopes for picatinny/weaver\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: Rifle Dynamics ISG Sound Suppressor\n </text>
	</string>
	
	
		<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_isg">
		<text>Rifle Dynamics RD-74U ISG</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_isg_descr">
		<text> A custom model developed on the basis of AKSU by the American company Rifle Dynamics. It is one of the most high-tech weapons in the Zone. Used by ISG special units.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All scopes for picatinny/weaver\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: Rifle Dynamics ISG Sound Suppressor\n </text>
	</string>

		<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_m1_isg">
		<text>Rifle Dynamics RD-74U ISG Tactic</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_m1_isg_descr">
		<text> Modification RD-74U ISG, developed by the American company Rifle Dynamics. It is one of the most high-tech weapons in the Zone. Used by ISG special units.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ATPIAL (Advanced Target Pointer Illuminator Aiming Laser) AN/PEQ-15 produced by L3 Insight Technologies. Tactical device that combines laser designators in both visible and IR band with IR searchlight. \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All scopes for picatinny/weaver\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: Rifle Dynamics ISG Sound Suppressor\n </text>
	</string>
	
	
		<string id="st_wpn_ak74_isg">
		<text>Rifle Dynamics RD-74M ISG</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74_isg_descr">
		<text>An advanced version of the AK-74M developed by the American company Rifle Dynamics. It is one of the most high-tech weapons in the Zone. Used by ISG special units.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ATPIAL (Advanced Target Pointer Illuminator Aiming Laser) AN/PEQ-15 produced by L3 Insight Technologies. Tactical device that combines laser designators in both visible and IR band with IR searchlight. \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Universal mount by NcStar with Trijicon RMR red dot sight installed on it. \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All scopes for picatinny/weaver.\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: Rifle Dynamics ISG Sound Suppressor\n </text>
	</string>
	
	
		<string id="st_wpn_vintorez_isg">
		<text>Rifle Dynamics RD-9x39 ISG</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vintorez_isg_descr">
		<text>The brainchild of the founder of Rifle Dynamics, Jim Fuller. The model is developed on the basis of the well-known and well-established VSS Vintorez. One of the main differences from the original is the presence of a special mechanism that allows you to fire with a misfire of two bullets and a picatinny rail installed along the entire length of the weapon. Used by ISG special units.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ATPIAL (Advanced Target Pointer Illuminator Aiming Laser) AN/PEQ-15 produced by L3 Insight Technologies. Tactical device that combines laser designators in both visible and IR band with IR searchlight. \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Universal mount by NcStar with Trijicon RMR red dot sight installed on it. \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All scopes for picatinny/weaver and dawtail except of red dot sights and 1P78 Kashtan.\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Some rumors say that this gun can be used with underbarrel grenade launcher) \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: Integrated \n </text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_sks_tac">
		<text>SKS Tactical</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sks_tac_descr">
		<text>Molot OP-SKS Carbine is designed for loading with 7.62x39 - the very popular ammunition in Zone. The weight and dimensions make the carbine ergonomic for shooters of any age and height. The tactical option differs from the original in the presence of a mount for installing sights in the fore-end area and also the possibility of installing a silence. Also new light trigger was installed on this model that significantly increased the rate of fire\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] SKS SOCOM Rail: Integrated \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: all scopes for Dovetail mount and all red dot sights (except of Aimpoint PRO and Aimpoint T1 with high mount)\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: Hexagon SKS 7.62x39 sound suppressor \n</text>
	</string>


		<string id="st_wpn_sks_molot">
		<text>SKS Molot</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sks_molot_descr">
		<text>Molot OP-SKS Carbine is designed for loading with 7.62x39 - the very popular ammunition in Zone. The weight and dimensions make the carbine ergonomic for shooters of any age and height.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: all scopes for Dovetail mount\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: None \n</text>
	</string>
	
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ks23">
		<text>KS-23</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ks23_descr">
		<text>Special carbine, 23 mm - Soviet multifunctional police pump-action shotgun, designed to suppress riots, selective force, mental and chemical effects on offenders. Interestingly, having a caliber of more than 20 mm and a rifled barrel, the KS-23 should not be classified as small arms, but as small-caliber artillery.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: The long 700mm barrel can be replaced by short 510mm one to decrease the wheight of the weapon.\n</text>
	</string>


	<string id="st_wpn_ks23_kaban">
		<text>KS-23M Drozd</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ks23_kaban_descr">
		<text>Shortened version of KS-23 with removable metal stock. 23 mm - Soviet multifunctional police pump-action shotgun, designed to suppress riots, selective force, mental and chemical effects on offenders. Interestingly, having a caliber of more than 20 mm and a rifled barrel, the KS-23 should not be classified as small arms, but as small-caliber artillery.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: Boar Tactical Kit for KS-23M Drozd.\n</text>
	</string>	
	
	
		<string id="st_tomahawk">
		<text>Gerber Downrange Tomahawk</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_tomahawk_descr">
		<text>Tactical tomahawk, multitool and breaching tool, all-in-one solution.</text>
	</string>
	
	
		<string id="st_wpn_dvl10_m1">
		<text>DVL-10 Saboteur</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_dvl10_m1_descr">
		<text>DVL-10 is a lightweight, compact, and silenced rifle in proprietary and current military subsonic calibers and has been developed for special service and combat missions where exceptional accuracy and range are needed.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All scopes for picatinny/weaver except of red dot sights.\n 
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: Integrated \n</text>
	</string>	
	
	
		<string id="st_wpn_dvl10">
		<text>DVL-10 Urbana</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_dvl10_descr">
		<text>DVL-10 is a lightweight and compact sniper rifle in proprietary and current military subsonic calibers has been developed for special service and combat missions where exceptional accuracy and range are needed.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All scopes for picatinny/weaver except of red dot sights.\n 
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: None \n</text>
	</string>	
	

		<string id="st_wpn_saiga12s_isg">
		<text>Kalashnikov USA Saiga-12 ISG</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_saiga12s_isg_descr">
		<text>A model developed by Kalashnikov USA on the basis of the Komrad 12 semi-automatic rifle for hunting and protecting members of ISG research teams from mutants. The weapon has both a dovetail mount and a picatinny bar for use with various types of sights. This model has a new type of trigger mechanism , which allows you to two rounds burst.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All Red Dot scopes for picatinny/weaver. \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: SilencerCo SalvoЃ 12 \n</text>
	</string>


		<string id="st_wpn_ak74_pmc">
		<text>AK-74 PMC</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74_pmc_descr">
		<text>A modification of the Kalashnikov assault rifle, developed in 1970 for the 5.45x39 cartridge.
 It differs from the standard version by the installed body kit, which includes a tactical grip, a forend with picatinny rails and a folding telescopic buttstock, which significantly improves ergonomics of the gun. The kit also includes a laser targeting device, a tactical flashlight and an adapter mount for sighting devices.
 In the Zone similar models are usually used by mercenaries, Ukrainian special forces, various PMCs and other power structures for conducting special operations.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ATPIAL (Advanced Target Pointer Illuminator Aiming Laser) AN/PEQ-15 produced by L3 Insight Technologies. Tactical device that combines laser designators in both visible and IR band with IR searchlight. \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All scopes for picatinny/weaver and for Dovetail mount except of PSO scopes with eyecup, EOTS-62 and 1P59 Giperon. \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: ATG \n</text>
	</string>


		<string id="st_wpn_svds_pmc">
		<text>SVDS PMC</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_svds_pmc_descr">
		<text>Dragunov sniper rifle with folding stock - the SVDS variant. Was specially designed for Russian paratroopers and special forces units. In the Zone similar models are usually used by mercenaries, Ukrainian special forces, various PMCs and other power structures for conducting special operations.\n 
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All scopes for picatinny/weaver except of red dot sights. \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: Rotor 43 \n
		%c[ui_gray_2] The kit includes:\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Rotor 43 thread adapter for SVD-S,  \n
        %c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] SAG MK1 Freefloat Chassis for SVD, \n
        %c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Zenit foregrip RK-5 (short) for very good recoil control\n
        %c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Custom SVDS dust cover,\n
        %c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Zenit RK3 pistol grip, \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Universal mount by NcStar that allows installing the auxiliary sight at 45 degrees angle with Trijicon RMR red dot sight installed on it. \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_val_tac">
		<text>AS Val Tactic</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_val_tac_descr">
		<text>The AS Val is widely used by Russian Army recon units, as well as by MVD (Internal Affairs Ministry) and FSB (Federal Security Bureau) Special Forces. The AS-VAL is a gas operated, integrally suppressed weapon. The receiver is machined from steel forging for improved strength. It has a standard side-mounted rail for optical, night vision or red dot scopes but has no provision for mounting a bayonet or a grenade launcher. The integral suppressor could be easily detached for maintenance, repair, or compact storage, but the rifle should not be fired with the suppressor removed due to safety and reliability issues.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All scopes for dovetail mount\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] VSS suppressor (integrated)\n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_vintorez_n1">
		<text>VSS Vintorez</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vintorez_n1_descr">
		<text>Designed at TsNIITochMash by Peter Serdyukov and his team, the new rifle was intended for various Spetsnaz troops of the Soviet Army, KGB and MVD. The VSS is quite popular among its users for its stealthy capabilities and the great lethality of the heavy 9x39mm bullets. The effective range of the VSS is limited to 300-400 metres. Standard sighting equipment consists of side rail on the receiver, which usually accommodates the 4x  PSO-1M2-1 scope. Any other scope or night vision sight can be mounted on the appropriate mount. Backup iron sights consist of tangent rear and blade front. The rear sight is graduated for up to 400 metres.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All scopes for dovetail mount\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] VSS suppressor (integrated)\n </text>
	</string>	

	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_n1">
		<text>AKS-74U</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_n1_descr">
		<text>The AKS-74U was intended for use mainly by Spetsnaz units, airborne infantry, rear-echelon support units and armoured vehicle crews, who require a compact but relatively powerful individual automatic weapon. The AKS-74U is significantly more manoeuvrable in tight quarters than the AKS-74, but a significant decline in muzzle velocity resulted in a decrease in effective range.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All scopes for dovetail mount (except of PSO scopes with eye cup and 1P59 Giperon). The use of PSO scopes with an eyecup on this weapon is highly not recomended.\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: PBS-4 suppressor\n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_tac">
		<text>AKS-74U Tactical</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_tac_descr">
		<text>The AKS-74U was intended for use mainly by Spetsnaz units, airborne infantry, rear-echelon support units and armoured vehicle crews, who require a compact but relatively powerful individual automatic weapon. The AKS-74U is significantly more manoeuvrable in tight quarters than the AKS-74, but a significant decline in muzzle velocity resulted in a decrease in effective range. This special variant has a 45 round RPK magazine.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All scopes for dovetail mount (except of PSO scopes with eye cup and 1P59 Giperon) and all Red Dot Sights except of Aimpoint PRO and Aimpoint T1 with high mount.\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: PBS-4 suppressor\n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_m4_tac">
		<text>M4 Tactical</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m4_tac_descr">
		<text>Colt M4A1 - an assault rifle (carbine), designed in the USA on the basis of AR-15 platform for 5.56x45 NATO cartridge. It was developed primarily for use by vehicle operators and fireteams, who required a more compact and lighter weapon than a standard full-length rifle, but using the same ordnance. However, US SOCOM (United States Special Operations Command) was soon to adopt the M4A1 for all subordinate units, followed by general introduction of M4A1 into service in the US Army and Marine Corps.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes:  All for picatinny/weaver (except of Red Dot Sights with low mount: Trijicon RMR, Leupold DeltaPoint PRO, Aimpoint T1 (low mount), Docter Sight, 1P76 Rakurs (low mount).\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: Surefire SOCOM556-MONSTER\n </text>
	</string>	

	<string id="st_wpn_m4_butcher">
		<text>ћ4 Butcher</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m4_butcher_descr">
		<text>Modernized model Colt M4A1 Commando (CQBR) is an assault rifle, designed in the USA on the basis of AR-15 platform for 5.56x45 NATO cartridge. It was developed primarily for use by vehicle operators and fireteams, who required a more compact and lighter weapon than a standard full-length rifle, but using the same ordnance. However, US SOCOM (United States Special Operations Command) was soon to adopt the M4A1 for all subordinate units, followed by general introduction of M4A1 into service in the US Army and Marine Corps.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes:  All for picatinny/weaver (except of Red Dot Sights with low mount: Trijicon RMR, Leupold DeltaPoint PRO, Aimpoint T1 (low mount), Docter Sight, 1P76 Rakurs (low mount) and OKP-7.\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: NATO\n </text>
	</string>

    <string id="st_wpn_mp153_m1">
        <text>Carabineer</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_mp153_m1_descr">
		<text>A customized version of the MP-153 shotgun. Capable of semi-automatic fire like its predecessor, but provides better recoil compensation thanks to the quite effective muzzle brake. It also has Picatinny rail which allows to use reflex and holographic sights and ability to use sound supressor.\n
	    %c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: Due to the position of the stock, it is possible to install sights only with a very low mount: Barska AC10632, C-More, Docter Sight, Aimpoint T1, Trijicon RMR, Leupold DeltaPoint PRO, OKP-7, 1P76 Rakurs. \n \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: SilencerCo SalvoЃ 12 \n</text>
    </string>

    <string id="st_wpn_fal_sa58_osw">
		<text>DS ARMS SA-58</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_fal_sa58_osw_descr">
		<text>SA-58 OSW (Operations Specialist Weapon) manufactured by American company DSA (David Selvaggio Arms) is a legal copy of the FAL, its made with the same Steyr-Daimler-Puch production line equipment as the StG-58. It may come with a different barrel length, an aluminum-alloy lower receiver, and improved Glass-filled Nylon furniture. Civilian models are semi-automatic, but military and Law Enforcement clients can procure select-fire models that have a fully automatic cyclic rate of 750 rounds/minute. The DSA-58 can use any metric-measurement FAL magazines.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All scopes for picatinny/weaver\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: AAC 7.62 SDN-6\n </text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="st_wpn_toz106_m1">
        <text>TOZ-106</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_toz106_m1_descr">
		<text>Single-barreled 20ga hunting shotgun with sliding breech bolt. Widely known by it vernacular name, the Death of the Chairman, for its compact size.\n
	    %c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: Due to the position of the stock, it is possible to install sights only with a very low mount: Barska AC10632, C-More, Docter Sight, Aimpoint T1, Trijicon RMR, Leupold DeltaPoint PRO, OKP-7, 1P76 Rakurs. \n \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: None \n</text>
    </string>

    <string id="st_wpn_toz106">
        <text>TOZ-106 (Folding Stock)</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_toz106_descr">
		<text>Single-barreled 20ga hunting shotgun with sliding breech bolt. Widely known by it vernacular name, the Death of the Chairman, for its compact size.\n
	    %c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: None \n \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: None \n</text>
    </string>

    <string id="st_wpn_fal_aus">
        <text>DS ARMS SA-58 AUS "Austrian Style"</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_fal_aus_descr">
		<text>SA-58 manufactured by american company DSA (David Selveggio Arms) is a legal copy of the FAL, it's made with the same Steyr-Daimler-Puch production line equipment as the StG-58. This modelel comes with 21" barrel length, and other "Austrian Style" stuff like original Austrian foregrip for a FAL, aluminum-alloy lower receiver, and improved Glass-filled Nylon furniture. This model used by military and Law Enforcement and can run a fully automatic. The DSA-58 can use any metric-measurement FAL magazines.\n
	    %c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: None \n \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Can be upgraded using Tactical Kits \n \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: AAC 7.62 SDN-6\n</text>
    </string>	

		<string id="st_wpn_glock17">
		<text>Glock 17</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_glock17_descr">
		<text>The Glock 17 is a polymer-framed, short recoil-operated, locked-breech semi-automatic pistol designed and produced by Austrian manufacturer Glock Ges.m.b.H.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: None\n 
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: None \n</text>
	</string>

		<string id="st_wpn_glock17_m1">
		<text>Glock 17 Tactical</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_glock17_m1_descr">
		<text>The Glock 17 is a polymer-framed, short recoil-operated, locked-breech semi-automatic pistol designed and produced by Austrian manufacturer Glock Ges.m.b.H. The tactical variant of Glock 17 has some additional futures: integrated Aimtech glock base for Red Dot sights, installed Pachmayr tactical rubber grip and threaded barrel manufactured by Double Diamond.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: Docter Sight, Aimpoint T1 (low mount only), Trijicon RMR, Leupold Deltapoint PRO\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: Osprey 9mm \n</text>
	</string>	

	<string id="st_wpn_pm_bas_actor">
		<text>Unic Makarov PM</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pm_bas_actor_descr">
		<text>A semi-mythical PM with extended barrel and suppressor mount threading. Some claim it was a limited series manufactured in Bulgaria, others insist on DDR, and some are even prone to think of it as a handcrafted upgrade. How did it end up in the Zone, no living soul can tell...\n
				%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
   %c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: Silencer 9mm\n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_pm_bas_custom">
		<text>PM (custom)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pm_bas_custom_descr">
	<text>Customized version of Makarov PM with longer threaded barrel for use with PMM silencer. This Soviet legacy is the most common pistol in the Zone and is one of the best compact self-defence handguns available. It is small, highly reliable, easy to use and maintain in working order. It also suffers from several drawbacks, including short range, low firing accuracy and poor stopping power, while also losing out to modern pistols in its class in terms of weight and magazine size. In 1951, the Pistol Makarova was selected because of its simplicity, easy manufacturing, accuracy, and reasonable stopping power.\n
				%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
   %c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: Silencer PMM\n</text>
	</string>
		
	<string id="st_wpn_pm_bas">
	      <text>PM</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pm_bas_descr">
		<text>This Soviet legacy is the most common pistol in the Zone and is one of the best compact self-defence handguns available. It is small, highly reliable, easy to use and maintain in working order. It also suffers from several drawbacks, including short range, low firing accuracy and poor stopping power, while also losing out to modern pistols in its class in terms of weight and magazine size. In 1951, the Pistol Makarova was selected because of its simplicity, easy manufacturing, accuracy, and reasonable stopping power.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_pmm_bas">
		<text>PMM</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pmm_bas_descr">
		<text>The most widely known variant, the Makarov PMM was a redesign of the original gun. In 1990 a group of engineers reworked the original Makarov, primarily by increasing the load for the cartridge. The result is 25% more gas pressure increasing in muzzle velocity. The PMM magazine holds 12 rounds, compared to the PM's 8 rounds.\n
				%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
   %c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: Silencer PMM\n</text>
	</string>

		<string id="st_wpn_fal_aus_kit_aus_tri">
		<text>DS Arms SA-58 AUS "Scout"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fal_aus_kit_aus_tri_descr">
		<text>FAL SA58 AUS modernised using DS Arms tactical kit. After the modification this weapon can be used very effectively at long and medium distances. SA-58 manufactured by american company DSA (David Selveggio Arms) is a legal copy of the FAL, it's made with the same Steyr-Daimler-Puch production line equipment as the StG-58. This modelel comes with 21" barrel length, and other "Austrian Style" stuff like original Austrian foregrip for a FAL, aluminum-alloy lower receiver, and improved Glass-filled Nylon furniture. This model used by military and Law Enforcement and can run a fully automatic. The DSA-58 can use any metric-measurement FAL magazines.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: Trijicon Acog and Aimpoint T1 (integrated)\n \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: AAC 7.62 SDN-6\n</text>
	</string>

		<string id="st_wpn_fal_aus_kit_sa5x_spec">
		<text>DS Arms SA-58 AUS "Defender"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fal_aus_kit_sa5x_spec_descr">
		<text>FAL SA58 AUS modernised using DS Arms tactical kit. After the modification this weapon can be used very effectively at long and medium distances. SA-58 manufactured by american company DSA (David Selveggio Arms) is a legal copy of the FAL, it's made with the same Steyr-Daimler-Puch production line equipment as the StG-58. This modelel comes with 21" barrel length, and other "Austrian Style" stuff like original Austrian foregrip for a FAL, aluminum-alloy lower receiver, and improved Glass-filled Nylon furniture. This model used by military and Law Enforcement and can run a fully automatic. The DSA-58 can use any metric-measurement FAL magazines.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: ELCAN SpecterDr and Aimpoint T1 (integrated)\n \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: AAC 7.62 SDN-6\n</text>
	</string>

		<string id="st_wpn_fal_aus_kit_fal_leup">
		<text>DS Arms SA-58 AUS "Marauder"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fal_aus_kit_fal_leup_descr">
		<text>FAL SA58 AUS modernised using DS Arms tactical kit. After the modification this weapon can be used very effectively at long and medium distances. SA-58 manufactured by american company DSA (David Selveggio Arms) is a legal copy of the FAL, it's made with the same Steyr-Daimler-Puch production line equipment as the StG-58. This modelel comes with 21" barrel length, and other "Austrian Style" stuff like original Austrian foregrip for a FAL, aluminum-alloy lower receiver, and improved Glass-filled Nylon furniture. This model used by military and Law Enforcement and can run a fully automatic. The DSA-58 can use any metric-measurement FAL magazines.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: Leupold Mark 8 and Aimpoint T1 (integrated)\n \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: AAC 7.62 SDN-6\n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak12">
		<text>AK-12 (2012)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak12_descr">
		<text>The Kalashnikov AK-12 assault rifle is the newest creation of the IZMASH factory. It is intended to replace older Kalashnikov AK-74M and AK-100 series rifles for domestic use, as well as for export. The rifle is a gas operated, selective fire rifle using traditional "Kalashnikov type" action with long stroke gas piston and rotary bolt locking. The bolt group is noticeably lightened to decrease recoil and improve accuracy in automatic fire.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] All scopes for picatinny/weaver\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 grenade launcher\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] 5.45/7.62x39 Hexagon Sound Suppressor\n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak104_alfa">
    	<text>AK-104 Alpha</text>
  	</string>
  	<string id="st_wpn_ak104_alfa_descr">
		<text>Customized version of the 7.62 mm AK-104 assault rifle. Looks like a finger tip of some Mid-Eastern operators... Comes with Sig Bravo 4 scope and Trijicon RMR mounted on it.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] All scopes for picatinny/weaver\n		
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: 5.45/7.62x39 Hexagon Sound Suppressor\n </text>
  	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak74_n">
		<text>AK-74</text>
	</string>
    <string id="st_wpn_ak74_n_descr">
		<text>The AK-74 is a 5.45x45mm assault rifle developed in the early 1970s by Mikhail Kalashnikov to replace the earlier AKM. It was introduced in 1974 and first saw service with Soviet forces engaged in the Afghanistan Conflict. The AKM rifle was adapted to fire smaller 5.45x45mm cartridge and fitted with a large muzzle brake.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 grenade launcher (after modification)\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] All dovetail mount scopes except of PSO scopes with eye cup due to the inconvenience of using these scopes on AK type of rifles and 1P59 Giperon. \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ATG suppressor\n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_svd_m1">
		<text>SVD</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_svd_m1_descr">
		<text>Originally intended for designated marksmen in every basic Soviet infantry unit, the Dragunov SVD was not designed for specialised sniper teams. Relatively light for a sniper rifle but well-balanced and having semiautomatic fire, its precision is good but not exceptional. It has an effective range of up to 800 metres.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes:  All dovetail mount scopes except of except of red dot sights.\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: KZRZP suppressor (after modification)\n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_svds">
		<text>SVDS</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_svds_descr">
		<text>Dragunov sniper rifle with folding stock - the SVDS variant. Was specially designed for Russian paratroopers and special forces units.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All dovetail mount scopes except of except of red dot sights.\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: TGP-V Suppressor\n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_rpg7">
		<text>RPG-7</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_rpg7_descr">
		<text>The RPG-7 is a further development of the previous RPG-2 anti-tank grenade launcher. The RPG-7, in its first version, known as RPG-7V, has been adopted by the Soviet army in 1961, and is still fielded in Russia and at least 50 more countries. By far, RPG-7 can be considered as one of the most successful anti-tank grenade launchers ever made. Initially thought of as an anti-armour weapon, it was later adopted for other fire support missions with the introduction of other types of grenades, such as anti-infantry HE-FRAG and multi-purpose Thermobaric/FAE. The RPG-7 is a shoulder fired, single shot, smoothbore recoilless launcher, grenades are loaded from the front, and the rear of the barrel is fitted with venturi nozzle. Due to the recoilless design, the backblast is dangerous. The RPG-7 is usually issued with 2.7X fixed magnification optical sight, designated PGO-7. It is a simple and inexpensive, but possess a high threat to modern tanks and can also serve in a number of other roles, making it a flexible weapon.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: PGO-7V Sight\n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak74m_n">
		<text>ј -74ћ</text>
	</string>
    <string id="st_wpn_ak74m_n_descr">
		<text>In 1991, the Izhmash factory began production of an improved AK-74 - the AK-74M assault rifle. Apart from several minor production improvements, the rifle also features a new foldable synthetic stock made from a black, glass-filled polyamide. The AK-74M also uses a reinforced muzzle device and dust cover. Each AK-74M is fitted with a side-rail bracket for mounting optics. The AK-74M has been accepted as the new service rifle of the Russian Federation\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 grenade launcher (after modification)\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] All dovetail mount scopes except of PSO scopes with eye cup due to the inconvenience of using these scopes on AK type of rifles and 1P59 Giperon.\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: TGP-A Suppressor\n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_n">
		<text>Colt M1911</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_n_descr">
		<text>An improved version of a classic semi-automatic pistol, which passed all the major armed conflicts of the 20th century with flying colours and entered the new millennium with confidence. Produced by dozens if not hundreds of arms manufacturers around the world in both standard and modified configurations. The weapon's only drawback, its mediocre magazine capacity, is largely compensated by the hard-hitting ammo it uses.\n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_sig226">
		<text>Sig Sauer P226R</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig226_descr">
		<text>The SIG Sauer P226R is a full-sized, service-type pistol made by SIG Sauer, a standard service weapon of Navy SEALs. Chambered for the 9x19mm Parabellum, features a Picatinny rail mount on the underside of a frame.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Can be upgraded using Tactical Kit.\n 
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: none\n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_sig220_n">
		<text>Sig Sauer P220</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig220_n_descr">
		<text>The SIG-Sauer P220, manufactured in the late 1970s by J.P. Sauer &amp; Son Company, is often considered the best out of the box .45 calibre double action pistol. An instant success, the P220 was adopted by the Swiss and Japanese SDF and by many European police organisations. This pistol also found its way into the US, first through the Browning Arms Company of Utah and since the 1980s, through the SIGARMS Company of New Hampshire.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Can be upgraded using Tactical Kit.\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: none\n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_walther_p99">
		<text>Walther P99</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_walther_p99_descr">
		<text>Ergonomics being a key focus in its design, the Walther P99 is a recoil-operated pistol with a fibreglass polymer frame. Developed for law enforcement and the civilian shooting market, it's employed by police units in a number of countries.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Can be upgraded using Tactical Kit.\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: none\n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_sig226_226sig_kit">
		<text>Sig Sauer P226R Custom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig226_226sig_kit_descr">
		<text>The SIG Sauer P226R is a full-sized, service-type pistol made by SIG Sauer, a standard service weapon of Navy SEALs. Chambered for the 9x19mm Parabellum, features a Picatinny rail mount on the underside of a frame.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Installed Tactical Kit: Threaded barrel for using with suppressor, ergonomic gripp plates and Trijicon RMR Red Dot sight with mounting plate. This upgrade is irreversible.\n 
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: Osprey 9mm\n\n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_sig220_n_upg220">
		<text>Sig Sauer P220 Custom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig220_n_upg220_descr">
		<text>The SIG-Sauer P220, manufactured in the late 1970s by J.P. Sauer &amp; Son Company, is often considered the best out of the box .45 calibre double action pistol. An instant success, the P220 was adopted by the Swiss and Japanese SDF and by many European police organisations. This pistol also found its way into the US, first through the Browning Arms Company of Utah and since the 1980s, through the SIGARMS Company of New Hampshire.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Installed Tactical Kit: Threaded barrel for using with suppressor, Tritium sights and Viridian X5L laser sight and high capacity magazine for 12 rounds. This upgrade is irreversible.\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: BLACK BOX .45\n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_walther_p99_mod9">
		<text>Walther P99 Custom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_walther_p99_mod9_descr">
		<text>Ergonomics being a key focus in its design, the Walther P99 is a recoil-operated pistol with a fibreglass polymer frame. Developed for law enforcement and the civilian shooting market, it's employed by police units in a number of countries.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Installed Tactical Kit: Threaded barrel for using with suppressor, Tritium sights and Viridian X5L laser sight. This upgrade is irreversible.\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: Gemtech\n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_rpk74_16">
		<text>RPK-16 5.45x39 light machine gun</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_rpk74_16_descr">
		<text>Newest Russian light machine gun - RPK-16 chambered in 5.45x39mm rounds. Key features of this kind of weapon are - quick detachable barrels, enhanced ergonomics, weaver rails on a handguard and dust cover.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] All scopes for picatinny/weaver\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] 5.45/7.62x39 Hexagon Sound Suppressor\n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_fn57">
		<text>FN Five-seveN</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fn57_descr">
		<text>The Five-seveN is a delayed blowback operated, semi-automatic firearm. The Five-seveN pistol was designed by FN Herstal as a complimentary sidearm for the P90 submachine gun. The P90 and Five-seveN share the same ammunition, the 5.7x28mm SS190 cartridge. The idea behind the ammunition and weapon is to provide good penetration against targets protected by body armour, while keeping the weapon's weight, dimensions and recoil at reasonable levels.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] The kit includes Laser Aiming Module and Red Dot Sights mount\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: Docter Sight, Aimpoint T1 (low mount), Trijicon RMR, Leupold DeltaPoint PRO.\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: 5.7x28 suppressor\n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_abakan_n">
		<text>AN-94 Abakan</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_abakan_n_descr">
		<text>A key improvement of the AN-94 over the AK-74 is the introduction of the additional 2-rounds burst mode. Nikonov design delays the force of recoil until the fired rounds have left the barrel, which along with a unique 1800 rpm two-shot burst function increases body armour piercing capabilities of this firearm. Used by Spetsnaz operators as well as Duty members to take out armoured targets at relatively long ranges.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 grenade launcher (after modification)\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All dovetail mount scopes except of PSO scopes with eye cup due to the inconvenience of using these scopes on AK type of rifles and 1P59 Giperon.\n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ks23_kaban_kab_up">
		<text>KS-23 Boar</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ks23_kaban_kab_up_descr">
		<text>Shortened version with mounted Trijicon RMR reflex sight. 23 mm - Soviet multifunctional police pump-action shotgun, designed to suppress riots, selective force, mental and chemical effects on offenders. Interestingly, having a caliber of more than 20 mm and a rifled barrel, the KS-23 should not be classified as small arms, but as small-caliber artillery. Also this version has thread for sound supressor that can be found somewere at south locations of Zone.\n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ks23_23_up">
		<text>KS-23 Short Barrel</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ks23_23_up_descr">
		<text>Special carbine, 23 mm - Soviet multifunctional police pump-action shotgun, designed to suppress riots, selective force, mental and chemical effects on offenders. Interestingly, having a caliber of more than 20 mm and a rifled barrel, the KS-23 should not be classified as small arms, but as small-caliber artillery. This modification of KS-23 has short 510mm barrel installed on it instead of standard long 700mm one.\n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_remington700">
		<text>Remington 700</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_remington700_descr">
		<text>The Remington Model 700 is a series of bolt-action centerfire rifles manufactured by Remington Arms since 1962.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Can be upgraded using: MOD X Gen.3 chassis, Magpul "PRO 700", Promag Archangel polymer stock and The Deer Hunter .338 kit\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Daniel Defence Wave QD suppressor \n </text>
	</string>
	
		<string id="st_wpn_remington700_archangel">
		<text>Remington 700 Archangel</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_remington700_archangel_descr">
		<text>The Remington Model 700 is a series of bolt-action centerfire rifles manufactured by Remington Arms since 1962. This model has Promag Archangel polymer stock installed on it.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Installed Promag Archangel polymer stock\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Daniel Defence Wave QD suppressor \n </text>
	</string>

		<string id="st_wpn_remington700_magpul_pro">
		<text>Remington 700 Magpul PRO</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_remington700_magpul_pro_descr">
		<text>The Remington Model 700 is a series of bolt-action centerfire rifles manufactured by Remington Arms since 1962. This model has Magpul PRO 700 chassis and additional Trijicon RMR Red Dot Sight installed on it.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Installed Magpul "PRO 700" chassis\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Daniel Defence Wave QD suppressor \n </text>
	</string>

		<string id="st_wpn_remington700_mod_x_gen3">
		<text>Remington 700 Modular Rifle System</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_remington700_mod_x_gen3_descr">
		<text>The Remington Model 700 is a series of bolt-action centerfire rifles manufactured by Remington Arms since 1962. This model has MOD X GEN III Modular Rifle System and additional Leupold DeltaPoint PRO Red Dot Sight installed on it.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Installed MOD X Gen.3 chassis\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Daniel Defence Wave QD suppressor \n </text>
	</string>

		<string id="st_wpn_sr1m">
		<text>9x21 Serdyukov SR1MP Gyurza</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sr1m_descr">
		<text>The Serdyukov semi-automatic pistol - also known as SPS and Gyurza (УViperФ), GRAU Index 6P53. Pistol designed for the Russian Federation special forces purposes by P. Serdyukov and I. Belyaev, for 9x21 mm cartridge.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Can be upgraded using Tactical Kit.\n 
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: None \n</text>
	</string>
	
			<string id="st_wpn_sr1m_sr1upgr1">
		<text>9x21 Serdyukov SR1MP Gyurza</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sr1m_sr1upgr1_descr">
		<text>The Serdyukov semi-automatic pistol - also known as SPS and Gyurza (УViperФ), GRAU Index 6P53. Pistol designed for the Russian Federation special forces purposes by P. Serdyukov and I. Belyaev, for 9x21 mm cartridge.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] The pistol was upgraded using tactical kit.\n 
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: SR1MP silencer 9x21 \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_k98_mod">
		<text>Mauser 98k Forester</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_k98_mod_descr">
		<text>A modified version of the WWII German sniper rifle Mauser Karabiner 98k. The wooden stock was replaced with a more organomic polymer one. The rifle is equipped with an excellent sniper scope manufactured by March, Japan. In the Zone, a rifle is used mainly for hunting mutants at long and over-long distances.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: March (integrated)\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: K98 Forester. (Barrel adapter needed to mount a silencer) \n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_k98_mod_silen98">
		<text>Mauser 98k Forester (with silencer adapter)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_k98_mod_silen98_descr">
		<text>A modified version of the WWII German sniper rifle Mauser Karabiner 98k. The wooden stock was replaced with a more organomic polymer one. The rifle is equipped with an excellent sniper scope manufactured by March, Japan. In the Zone, a rifle is used mainly for hunting mutants at long and over-long distances.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: March (integrated)\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: K98 Forester.\n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ks23_ecolog">
		<text> —-23 Ecolog</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ks23_ecolog_descr">
		<text> Modification of KS-23, developed for the needs of the scientific staff located in the Zone.\n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak105">
		<text>AK-105</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak105_descr">
		<text>The AK-105 is a 5.45x39mm carbine version of the AK-74M rifle. The AK-105 is supplementing AKS-74U carbines in Russian Army service. Ideal for CQC (close quarters combat), it's not intended for long range combat. The rifle's reiver is made of stamped steel; the magazine is made out of reinforced fibreglass and the stock is made of hollow plastic, making it lighter, more durable, and allowing a field kit to be stored inside of it.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: all scopes for Dovetail mount except of PSO scopes with eye cup due to the inconvenience of using these scopes on AK type of rifles and 1P59 Giperon.\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Can be upgraded using Tactical Kit.\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: TGP-A suppressor\n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak105_swamp">
		<text>AK-105 Swamp Thing</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak105_swamp_descr">
		<text>The AK-105 is a 5.45x39mm carbine version of the AK-74M rifle. The AK-105 is supplementing AKS-74U carbines in Russian Army service. A very rare variant of the AK-105. It is found mainly among the veterans of the Clear Sky group. Due to the presence of several sighting devices, it is ideal for combat both at close and medium-long distances.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] The weapon was upgraded using "Swamp Thing" Tactical Kit\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: Elcan SpecterDr, Trijicon RMR and AN/PEQ-15 LAM (integrated)\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: 5.45/7.62x39 Hexagon Sound Suppressor\n </text>
	</string>

		<string id="st_wpn_remington700_lapua700">
		<text>M700 The Deer Hunter</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_remington700_lapua700_descr">
		<text>The Deer Hunter is modification of Remington Model 700 for precise shooting on very long distances. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] The weapon was upgraded using The Deer Hunter .338 kit\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: M700 .338LM \n </text>
	</string>

		<string id="st_wpn_pl15">
		<text>Lebedev PL-15 Pistol</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pl15_descr">
		<text>Russian self-loading pistol PL-15-01 chambered for 9x19 mm Parabellum. The difference between the pistol and its analogues is its ergonomics and balance, which correspond to the current ideas about human biomechanics. The automation calculation methods used during its creation contribute to a large shooting resource, and in combination with the applied ergonomics solutions, make the pistol comfortable in terms of recoil, toss after a shot and quick return to the aiming line. All this contributes to a quick re-shot and fast transfer of fire, and an ergonomic handle with a large angle of inclination makes it easier to shoot "offhand".\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] The weapon can be upgraded using kit: "Tactic".\n 
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] The LAM for PL-15 can be installed\n 
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: PL-15 Sound Suppressor \n</text>
	</string>

		<string id="st_wpn_pl15_pl15_scolaz">
		<text>Lebedev PL-15 "Tactic"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pl15_pl15_scolaz_descr">
		<text>Russian self-loading pistol PL-15-01 chambered for 9x19 mm Parabellum. The difference between the pistol and its analogues is its ergonomics and balance, which correspond to the current ideas about human biomechanics. The automation calculation methods used during its creation contribute to a large shooting resource, and in combination with the applied ergonomics solutions, make the pistol comfortable in terms of recoil, toss after a shot and quick return to the aiming line. All this contributes to a quick re-shot and fast transfer of fire, and an ergonomic handle with a large angle of inclination makes it easier to shoot "offhand".\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] The weapon was upgraded using: "Tactic" kit (LAM, Aimpoint T1 scope).\n 
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: PL-15 Sound Suppressor\n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak105_shakal">
		<text>AK-105 Shakal</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak105_shakal_descr">
		<text>The AK-105 is a 5.45x39mm carbine version of the AK-74M rifle. The AK-105 is supplementing AKS-74U carbines in Russian Army service. A very rare variant of the AK-105. It is found mainly among the veterans of the Duty group. Due to the presence of several sighting devices, it is ideal for combat both at close and medium-long distances.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] The weapon was upgraded using "Shakal" Tactical Kit\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: Trijicon Acog, Trijicon RMR and AN/PEQ-15 LAM (integrated)\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: 5.45/7.62x39 Hexagon Sound Suppressor\n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_sig220_n_u2p2g0r">
		<text>Sig Sauer P220 Custom Nine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig220_n_u2p2g0r_descr">
		<text>The SIG-Sauer P220, manufactured in the late 1970s by J.P. Sauer & Son Company, is often considered the best out of the box .45 calibre double action pistol. An instant success, the P220 was adopted by the Swiss and Japanese SDF and by many European police organisations. This pistol also found its way into the US, first through the Browning Arms Company of Utah and since the 1980s, through the SIGARMS Company of New Hampshire.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Installed Tactical Kit: Threaded 9x19 barrel for using with standard Black Box .45 suppressor, Tritium sights and Viridian X5L laser sight and high capacity 19 rounds magazine. This upgrade is irreversible.\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: BLACK BOX .45\n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_aps_bas">
		<text>APS</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aps_bas_descr">
		<text>The Stechkin APS is a Russian selective fire machine pistol, bearing the name of its designer Igor Stechkin. The Stechkin automatic pistol was originally chambered for 7.62x25mm Tokarev but was changed to the 9x18mm calibre used in the new Makarov pistol, as it became clear that this cartridge was set to become the new service ammunition for handguns in the Soviet Army. In 1951, both the Makarov and Stechkin were introduced into the Soviet military arsenal, replacing the ageing TT-33.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Can be upgraded using Tactical Kit.\n 
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: None \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_aps_bas_apsabigo">
		<text>APS Upgraded</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aps_bas_apsabigo_descr">
		<text>The Stechkin APS is a Russian selective fire machine pistol, bearing the name of its designer Igor Stechkin. The Stechkin automatic pistol was originally chambered for 7.62x25mm Tokarev but was changed to the 9x18mm calibre used in the new Makarov pistol, as it became clear that this cartridge was set to become the new service ammunition for handguns in the Soviet Army. In 1951, both the Makarov and Stechkin were introduced into the Soviet military arsenal, replacing the ageing TT-33.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Installed Tactical Kit: Threaded barrel for using with APB sound suppressor, Tritium sights and ergonomic pistol grip rubber.\n 
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: APB \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_mp133_bas">
		<text>MP-133</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp133_bas_descr">
		<text>The MP-133 is a product of the Izhevsk Mechanical Plant. This shotgun is an evolution of the earlier IZh-81 pump action shotgun, and is intended for civilian and security markets. It is produced in two basic versions: standard MP-133 with tubular magazine and MP-133K with detachable box magazine, both versions can be in various barrel lengths and styles, wood or polymer furniture, fixed or side folding polymer stock or pistol grip only. The MP-133 shotgun uses traditional pump action with sliding forend that has dual action bars. Locking is achieved by a tilting locking piece, installed in the bolt and engages the notch in the barrel extension when in battery. Feed is from tubular underbarrel magazine that holds 4 rounds, though capacity can be enhanced by installing magazine extension tubes.\n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_mp153_bas">
		<text>MP-153</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp153_bas_descr">
		<text>The MP-153 self-loading shotgun was the first semi-automatic shotgun designed and manufactured by Izhevsk Mechanical Plant. It was developed along with the pump action MP-133 shotgun and shares many parts and assemblies with it. The MP-153 is one of the most popular semi-automatic shotguns of Russian origin, and is widely used to hunt various games in Russia. It is also sold for export, it is known as Remington "Spartan" SPR-453 autoloader in US. MP-153 shotguns are known for solid but somewhat heavy construction and reliability.\n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_gauss_bas">
		<text>Gauss rifle</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_gauss_bas_descr">
		<text>A highly experimental, artefact-powered, super-accurate weapon made by an unknown party in the Zone. Its gunshot is nearly inaudible, because instead of gunpowder, it uses magnets to accelerate its bullet to incredible speeds. Despite the gauss rifle's tremendous firepower, the recoil is insignificant. The accuracy and power of this gun exceeds those of all other small arms.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Enhanced computer EOTS-62 scope (integrated)</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_umirotvoritel_bas">
		<text>Unidentified weapon</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_umirotvoritel_bas_descr">
		<text>An unknown weapon, the firing mechanism of which has not been established. The weapon appears faulty - squeezing the trigger doesn't do anything. It's very heavy and definitely high-tech. Of note is that it appears not to fire bullets based on ignition. Most probably, the rounds are propelled by electro-magnetic forces. One can only suspect what kind of destructive potential it possesses.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_pb_bas">
		<text>PB</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pb_bas_custom">
		<text>PB (modern)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pb_bas_descr">
		<text>The PB (Pistolet Besshumnyj or Silent Pistol), also known in the Soviet army as 6P9, has been developed in 1967 for Spetsnaz units of the Soviet Army, as well as for KGB operatives. The pistol is based on a modified Makarov PM pistol and features an unique integral two part suppressor. Issued into service in 1967, the PB (GRAU index 6P9) is a Soviet silenced pistol based on the Makarov PM. It was intended for use by the KGB and army reconnaissance groups. The front part of the suppressor is detachable, so that the pistol can be broken down into two parts for convenient carry. The PB's integral suppressor also reduces the bullet velocity to below subsonic levels.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] 6P9 suppressor (integrated)</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_akm_alfa">
    	<text>CAA AK-Alfa</text>
  	</string>
  	<string id="st_wpn_akm_alfa_descr">
		<text> Developed in Israel by Command Arms &amp; Acessories (CAA), the AK-Alfa assault rifle was first presented to the public in 2016. This weapon is marketed under two brands - "Kalashnikov USA" and "Kalashnikov Israel". Apparently, this weapon got into the Zone with the the ISG faction. The AK-Alpha assault rifle is an attempt to improve the ergonomics of the AK rifle while maintaining its main advantages - high reliability and ease of maintenance.
               The base for the AK-Alpha is the receiver, the barrel with the gas tube, the bolt group and the main components of the trigger of the Russian-made Saiga carbine.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All for picatinny/weaver except of scopes with very low mounting: Trijicon RMR, Leupold DeltaPoint PRO, Aimpoint T1 (low mount), Docter Sight.\n		
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: 5.45/7.62x39 Hexagon Sound Suppressor\n </text>
  	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_sr2_veresk">
    	<text>SR-2M Veresk</text>
  	</string>
  	<string id="st_wpn_sr2_veresk_descr">
		<text> SR-2M "Veresk" is a Russian submachine gun (manufactured by TsNIITOCHMASH), designed to engage enemy personnel in close combat (at a distance of up to 200 m) using individual body armor. The main advantage of the SR-2 is its high firepower, high accuracy of fire and the destructive effect of a bullet at close range. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: KP SR-2 Reflex Sight\n	
        %c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Can be upgraded using Tactical Kit.\n 		
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: GZV-SR2\n </text>
  	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_sr2_veresk_sr2_upkit">
    	<text>SR-2M Veresk (Upgraded)</text>
  	</string>
  	<string id="st_wpn_sr2_veresk_sr2_upkit_descr">
		<text> SR-2M "Veresk" is a Russian submachine gun (manufactured by TsNIITOCHMASH), designed to engage enemy personnel in close combat (at a distance of up to 200 m) using individual body armor. The main advantage of the SR-2 is its high firepower, high accuracy of fire and the destructive effect of a bullet at close range. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n		
        %c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] The weapon was upgraded using tactical upgrade kit. (Irreversible upgrade) \n	
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: GZV-SR2\n </text>
  	</string>	

	<string id="st_wpn_sr2_m1">
    	<text>SR-2M Veresk (Modernized)</text>
  	</string>
  	<string id="st_wpn_sr2_m1_descr">
		<text> SR-2M "Veresk" is a Russian submachine gun (manufactured by TsNIITOCHMASH), designed to engage enemy personnel in close combat (at a distance of up to 200 m) using individual body armor. The main advantage of the SR-2 is its high firepower, high accuracy of fire and the destructive effect of a bullet at close range. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n		
        %c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] All Red Dot sights for picatinny/weaver, and two scopes with magnification: PN-23 and Leupold Mark 8 CQBSS 1.1-8x24 . \n	
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: GZV-SR2\n </text>
  	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_aug_a1_bas">
		<text>Steyr AUG A1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aug_a1_bas_descr">
		<text>Steyr AUG A1 in standard rifle configuration (military green colour). The AUG is an Austrian bullpup 5.56mm assault rifle, designed in the 1960s by Steyr Mannlicher GmbH &amp; Co KG (formerly Steyr-Daimler-Puch). The AUG (Armee-Universal-Gewehr "universal army rifle") was adopted by the Austrian Army as the StG 77 (Sturmgewehr 77) in 1978, where it replaced the 7.62mm StG 58 automatic rifle (a licence-built FN FAL). In production since 1978, it is the standard small arm of the Austrian Bundesheer and various national police units.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] 1.5x scope (integrated).\n 
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Suppressor: Steyr UMS \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_aug_a3_bas">
		<text>Steyr AUG A3</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aug_a3_bas_descr">
		<text>Steyr AUG (Armee Universal Gewehr - Army Universal Rifle) is an Austrian 5.56x45mm NATO bullpup assault rifle, designed in the 1960s by Steyr-Daimler-Puch and now manufactured by Steyr Mannlicher GmbH & Co KG. The Steyr AUG A3 differs from the base model in the presence of four Picatinny slats: the top one is used for attaching sights, a grenade launcher or a vertical front handle can be attached to the bottom, and a laser pointer or other necessary additional equipment is attached to the side.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All for picatinny/weaver except of scopes with very low mounting: Trijicon RMR, Leupold DeltaPoint PRO, Aimpoint T1 (low mount), Docter Sight.\n 
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Suppressor: Steyr UMS \n</text>
	</string>	

	<string id="st_wpn_aug_a1_custom_bas">
		<text>Steyr AUG A1 CQB</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aug_a1_custom_bas_descr">
		<text>Steyr AUG A1 in standard rifle configuration (military green colour). The AUG is an Austrian bullpup 5.56mm assault rifle, designed in the 1960s by Steyr Mannlicher GmbH&Co KG (formerly Steyr-Daimler-Puch). The AUG (Armee-Universal-Gewehr "universal army rifle") was adopted by the Austrian Army as the StG 77 (Sturmgewehr 77) in 1978, where it replaced the 7.62mm StG 58 automatic rifle (a licence-built FN FAL). In production since 1978, it is the standard small arm of the Austrian Bundesheer and various national police units. CQB - has less weight and increased rate of fire compared to the original.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] 1.5x scope (integrated).\n 
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Suppressor: Steyr UMS \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_aug_a3_custom_bas">
		<text>Steyr AUG A3 Commando</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aug_a3_custom_bas_descr">
		<text>Steyr AUG (Armee Universal Gewehr - Army Universal Rifle) is an Austrian 5.56x45mm NATO bullpup assault rifle, designed in the 1960s by Steyr-Daimler-Puch and now manufactured by Steyr Mannlicher GmbH & Co KG. The Steyr AUG A3 differs from the base model in the presence of four Picatinny slats: the top one is used for attaching sights, a grenade launcher or a vertical front handle can be attached to the bottom, and a laser pointer or other necessary additional equipment is attached to the side.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Installed Trijicon Acog (x4) and PEQ LA5 LAM.\n 
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Suppressor:  Steyr UMS \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak5c_bas">
		<text>AK 5C</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak5c_bas_descr">
		<text>The Ak 5 or Automatkarbin 5 ("automatic carbine 5", "automatic carbine" being the Swedish term for assault rifle) is the Swedish version of the FN FNC assault rifle with certain modifications, mostly to adapt the weapon to the partially subarctic Swedish climate. The Ak 5 is the service rifle of the Swedish Armed Forces. The Bofors Ak 5C is the modernized version of the original Ak 5, following the trend of modular weapons. One of the most significant improvements is the MIL-STD-1913 rail system to which a variety of different optics, lights and sights can be mounted, such as telescopic sights and image intensifiers. The double gas position, iron sights and bolt catch of the original Ak 5 rifle family were discarded.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Can be upgraded using Tactical Kit.\n 
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All for picatinny/weaver.\n 
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Suppressor:  NATO \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak5c_bas_5c_tik">
		<text>AK 5C ISG Special</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak5c_bas_5c_tik_descr">
		<text>The Ak 5 or Automatkarbin 5 ("automatic carbine 5", "automatic carbine" being the Swedish term for assault rifle) is the Swedish version of the FN FNC assault rifle with certain modifications, mostly to adapt the weapon to the partially subarctic Swedish climate. The Ak 5 is the service rifle of the Swedish Armed Forces. The Bofors Ak 5C is the modernized version of the original Ak 5, following the trend of modular weapons. One of the most significant improvements is the MIL-STD-1913 rail system to which a variety of different optics, lights and sights can be mounted, such as telescopic sights and image intensifiers. The double gas position, iron sights and bolt catch of the original Ak 5 rifle family were discarded.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] The weapon was upgraded with tactical kit. The parts in the kit: low profile foregrip, LA5 LAM, Leupold LCO+D'evo scopes and short barrel. (Irreversible upgrade).\n 
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes installed: Leupold (LCO), Leupold D'evo x6 and LA5 Laser Aim Module.\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Suppressor:  Rifle Dynamics ISG Sound Suppressor \n		</text>
	</string>	

	<string id="st_wpn_ak5c_isg">
		<text>AK 5C ISG</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak5c_isg_descr">
		<text>The ISG modification of Swedish AK5C. Rare weapon in Zone. Rarely used by some ISG squads. The Ak 5 or Automatkarbin 5 ("automatic carbine 5", "automatic carbine" being the Swedish term for assault rifle) is the Swedish version of the FN FNC assault rifle with certain modifications, mostly to adapt the weapon to the partially subarctic Swedish climate. The Ak 5 is the service rifle of the Swedish Armed Forces. The Bofors Ak 5C is the modernized version of the original Ak 5, following the trend of modular weapons. One of the most significant improvements is the MIL-STD-1913 rail system to which a variety of different optics, lights and sights can be mounted, such as telescopic sights and image intensifiers. The double gas position, iron sights and bolt catch of the original Ak 5 rifle family were discarded.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All for picatinny/weaver. LA5 LAM (installed).\n 
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Suppressor:  Rifle Dynamics ISG Sound Suppressor \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_m4a1_siber">
		<text>M4A1 RAS</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m4a1_siber_descr">
		<text>The M4 Carbine descends from a family of firearms tracing its lineage back to earlier carbine versions of the M16, all based on the original AR-15 made by ArmaLite. It is a shorter and lighter version of the M16 assault rifle, sharing 80% of its parts. The M4 fires 5.56x45mm NATO ammunition and are gas operated, air cooled, magazine fed, selective fire firearms with a 4 position telescoping stock. As with many carbines, the M4 is handy and more convenient to carry than a full length rifle. It has been adopted by United States Special Operations Command (USSOCOM) and is the preferred weapon of the U.S. Army Special Forces and Navy SEALs.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes:All for picatinny/weaver (except of Red Dot Sights with low mount: Trijicon RMR, Leupold DeltaPoint PRO, Aimpoint T1 (low mount), Docter Sight, 1P76 Rakurs (low mount) and OKP-7.\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Suppressor: ADVANCED ARMAMENT (AAC) M4-2000 \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] M203 grenade launcher\n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_akm_bas">
		<text>AKM</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_akm_bas_descr">
		<text>The AKM is a 7.62x39mm assault rifle designed by Mikhail Kalashnikov. It is an improved version of the AK-47 rifle and was developed in the 1950's. Introduced to the Red Army in 1959, the AKM is the most ubiquitous variant of the AK series of firearms and it has found widespread use with the former Warsaw Pact states and its many African and Asian allies. The production of AKM rifles was carried out at the Tula Arsenal and Izhevsk Mechanical Works.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: None\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Suppressor: PBS-1\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 grenade launcher (after modification)\n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_akms_bas">
		<text>AKMS</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_akms_bas_descr">
		<text>A variant of the AKM, equipped with an under-folding metal shoulder stock in place of the fixed wooden stock. The metal stock of the AKMS is somewhat different from the folding stock of the previous AK-47 model as it has a modified locking mechanism, which locks both support arms of the AKMS stock instead of just one.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n		
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: None\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] PBS-1 suppressor\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] GP-25 grenade launcher (after modification)\n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_sks_b">
		<text>SKS</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sks_b_descr">
		<text>The SKS is one of the first weapons chambered for the 7.62x39mm round. Replaced in Soviet front-line service by the AK-47 in the early 1950s, it remained in second-line service for decades and is still used as a ceremonial arm today.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n%c[d_purple]Х %c[ui_gray_2] none\n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_l85_m1">
		<text>L85 A2</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_l85_m1_descr">
		<text>The development of the SA80 system, which included two weapons - the SA80 IW assault rifle and SA80 LSW light machine gun, began in the late 1960s when the British Army decided to develop a new rifle, to replace the ageing 7.62x51mm L1 SLR British made FN FAL. The standard individual weapon for the British armed forces, the L85 (in its original A1 version) had numerous performance issues. The A2 variant came to be as the result of a significant upgrade in the early 2000s by Heckler & Koch and remains in service as of 2020. L85A2 is extremely reliable over a range of climates for various operational scenarios. The current L85A2 rifles are recognised as reliable and accurate, especially when using standard issue SUSAT telescope sights.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n		
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: Susat with L85 native mount\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Suppressor: ADVANCED ARMAMENT (AAC) M4-2000\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Grenade Launcher: none\n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_l85_m2">
		<text>L85 A2 Modernized</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_l85_m2_descr">
		<text>The development of the SA80 system, which included two weapons - the SA80 IW assault rifle and SA80 LSW light machine gun, began in the late 1960s when the British Army decided to develop a new rifle, to replace the ageing 7.62x51mm L1 SLR British made FN FAL. The standard individual weapon for the British armed forces, the L85 (in its original A1 version) had numerous performance issues. The A2 variant came to be as the result of a significant upgrade in the early 2000s by Heckler & Koch and remains in service as of 2020. L85A2 is extremely reliable over a range of climates for various operational scenarios. The current L85A2 rifles are recognised as reliable and accurate, especially when using standard issue SUSAT telescope sights.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
        %c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Upgraded: Picatinny rail installed on top of the native dovetail mount\n		
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All for picatinny/weaver (except of Red Dot Sights with low mount: Trijicon RMR, Leupold DeltaPoint PRO, Aimpoint T1 (low mount), Docter Sight, 1P76 Rakurs (low mount).\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Suppressor: ADVANCED ARMAMENT (AAC) M4-2000\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Grenade Launcher: none\n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_l85_m3">
		<text>L85 A2 Tactic</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_l85_m3_descr">
		<text>The development of the SA80 system, which included two weapons - the SA80 IW assault rifle and SA80 LSW light machine gun, began in the late 1960s when the British Army decided to develop a new rifle, to replace the ageing 7.62x51mm L1 SLR British made FN FAL. The standard individual weapon for the British armed forces, the L85 (in its original A1 version) had numerous performance issues. The A2 variant came to be as the result of a significant upgrade in the early 2000s by Heckler & Koch and remains in service as of 2020. L85A2 is extremely reliable over a range of climates for various operational scenarios. The current L85A2 rifles are recognised as reliable and accurate, especially when using standard issue SUSAT telescope sights.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
        %c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Upgraded: Picatinny rail installed on top of the native dovetail mount, quadrail fore-end, foregrip and B.E. MEYERS MAWL-C1 tactical green laser aim modul.\n		
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All for picatinny/weaver (except of Red Dot Sights with low mount: Trijicon RMR, Leupold DeltaPoint PRO, Aimpoint T1 (low mount), Docter Sight, 1P76 Rakurs (low mount).\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Suppressor: ADVANCED ARMAMENT (AAC) M4-2000\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Grenade Launcher: Heckler&Koch M320\n</text>
	</string>	

	<string id="st_wpn_scar_siber">
		<text>FN SCAR-H</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_scar_siber_descr">
		<text>The Special Operations Forces Combat Assault Rifle (SCAR) is a modular rifle made by FN Herstal for SOCOM to satisfy the requirements of the SCAR competition. This family of rifle consist of two types, the SCAR-H and SCAR-L. The SCAR-H (Heavy) is chambered in 7.62x51mm NATO cartridge.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All for picatinny/weaver (except of Red Dot Sights with low mount: Trijicon RMR, Leupold DeltaPoint PRO, Aimpoint T1 (low mount), Docter Sight, 1P76 Rakurs (low mount).\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Suppressor: AAC 7.62 SDN-6\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Grenade Launcher: FN HERSTAL FN40GL Mk2\n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_scar_siber_black">
		<text>FN SCAR-H (Black)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_scar_siber_black_descr">
		<text>The Special Operations Forces Combat Assault Rifle (SCAR) is a modular rifle made by FN Herstal for SOCOM to satisfy the requirements of the SCAR competition. This family of rifle consist of two types, the SCAR-H and SCAR-L. The SCAR-H (Heavy) is chambered in 7.62x51mm NATO cartridge.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All for picatinny/weaver (except of Red Dot Sights with low mount: Trijicon RMR, Leupold DeltaPoint PRO, Aimpoint T1 (low mount), Docter Sight, 1P76 Rakurs (low mount).\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Suppressor: AAC 7.62 SDN-6\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Grenade Launcher: FN HERSTAL FN40GL Mk2\n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_scar_siber_m1">
		<text>FN SCAR-H Tactical</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_scar_siber_m1_descr">
		<text>The Special Operations Forces Combat Assault Rifle (SCAR) is a modular rifle made by FN Herstal for SOCOM to satisfy the requirements of the SCAR competition. This family of rifle consist of two types, the SCAR-H and SCAR-L. The SCAR-H (Heavy) is chambered in 7.62x51mm NATO cartridge.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Installed Upgrades: Tactical Magpull foregrip, Tritium Sights\n		
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All for picatinny/weaver (except of Red Dot Sights with low mount: Trijicon RMR, Leupold DeltaPoint PRO, Aimpoint T1 (low mount), Docter Sight, 1P76 Rakurs (low mount).\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Suppressor: AAC 7.62 SDN-6\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Grenade Launcher: none\n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_scar_siber_m1_black">
		<text>FN SCAR-H Tactical Black</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_scar_siber_m1_black_descr">
		<text>The Special Operations Forces Combat Assault Rifle (SCAR) is a modular rifle made by FN Herstal for SOCOM to satisfy the requirements of the SCAR competition. This family of rifle consist of two types, the SCAR-H and SCAR-L. The SCAR-H (Heavy) is chambered in 7.62x51mm NATO cartridge.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Installed Upgrades: Tactical Magpull foregrip, Tritium Sights\n	
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All for picatinny/weaver (except of Red Dot Sights with low mount: Trijicon RMR, Leupold DeltaPoint PRO, Aimpoint T1 (low mount), Docter Sight, 1P76 Rakurs (low mount).\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Suppressor: AAC 7.62 SDN-6\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Grenade Launcher: none\n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_scar_siber_m2">
		<text>FN SCAR-H Expert Operator</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_scar_siber_m2_descr">
		<text>The Special Operations Forces Combat Assault Rifle (SCAR) is a modular rifle made by FN Herstal for SOCOM to satisfy the requirements of the SCAR competition. This family of rifle consist of two types, the SCAR-H and SCAR-L. The SCAR-H (Heavy) is chambered in 7.62x51mm NATO cartridge.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Installed Upgrades: Tactical Magpull foregrip, Tritium Sights, B.E. MEYERS MAWL-C1 tactical green laser aim modul\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: All for picatinny/weaver (except of Red Dot Sights with low mount: Trijicon RMR, Leupold DeltaPoint PRO, Aimpoint T1 (low mount), Docter Sight, 1P76 Rakurs (low mount).\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Suppressor: AAC 7.62 SDN-6\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Grenade Launcher: none\n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_scar_siber_m2_custom">
		<text>FN SCAR-H Specialist Operator</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_scar_siber_m2_custom_descr">
		<text>The Special Operations Forces Combat Assault Rifle (SCAR) is a modular rifle made by FN Herstal for SOCOM to satisfy the requirements of the SCAR competition. This family of rifle consist of two types, the SCAR-H and SCAR-L. The SCAR-H (Heavy) is chambered in 7.62x51mm NATO cartridge.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Installed Upgrades: B.E. MEYERS MAWL-C1 tactical green laser aim modul\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes installed: Vortex RAZOR UH-1 и EOTech G33.STS magnifier.\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Suppressor: AAC 7.62 SDN-6\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Grenade Launcher: none\n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_korth">
		<text>Korth 4" Barrel</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_korth_descr">
		<text>Korth is a high-end firearms manufacturer based in Lollar, Germany. For some gun aficionados, nothing more needs to be said. Builders in the tradition of ultimate European luxury brands, Korth are perhaps best known for revolvers with price tags that most people would find easier to associate with German cars than German guns. But that out-of-this-world pricing reputation which is the stuff of gun counter lore world wide is derived from their full custom stuff; the entry point is far more accessible. The starting point for a Korth is around the starting point for a Rolex: five thousand dollars will put some of that European goodness in your hands, and it will sure be memorable. Korth guns are legendary.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n		
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: none\n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_korth_custom">
		<text>Korth 6" Barrel</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_korth_custom_descr">
		<text>Korth is a high-end firearms manufacturer based in Lollar, Germany. For some gun aficionados, nothing more needs to be said. Builders in the tradition of ultimate European luxury brands, Korth are perhaps best known for revolvers with price tags that most people would find easier to associate with German cars than German guns. But that out-of-this-world pricing reputation which is the stuff of gun counter lore world wide is derived from their full custom stuff; the entry point is far more accessible. The starting point for a Korth is around the starting point for a Rolex: five thousand dollars will put some of that European goodness in your hands, and it will sure be memorable. Korth guns are legendary.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Installed long 6 inch threaded barrel.\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes: Docter Sight\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: BLACK BOX .45\n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_grenade_launcher">
		<text>GP-25 "Kostyor" grenade launcher</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_grenade_launcher_descr">
		<text>A single shot, front loaded, rifled underbarrel grenade launcher for assault rifles made in Warsaw Pact countries. Designed to greatly expand fire-power of a basic infantry squad. The firing mechanism is self-cocking, with a manual safety catch and automatic shot prevention if incorrectly installed onto a rifle.\n \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] muzzle velocity: %c[ui_gray_1]~76 m / sec\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] fire range: %c[ui_gray_1]~300 m\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] reload time: %c[ui_gray_1]slow\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ammunition: %c[ui_gray_1]VOG-25 40mm grenade</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_grenade_launcher_m203">
		<text>M203 grenade launcher</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_grenade_launcher_m203_descr">
		<text>A modified M203 grenade launcher whose length has been decreased by three inches, and which can be attached to weapons by means of a Picatinny rail. Thanks to a changed mount, this grenade launcher is widely used around the world and can be installed on most currently produced rifles. Although of more modern design, it has almost the same properties as its Soviet counterpart - the GP-25 grenade launcher.\n \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] muzzle velocity: %c[ui_gray_1]~76 m / sec\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] fire range: %c[ui_gray_1]~300 m\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] reload time: %c[ui_gray_1]slow\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] ammunition: %c[ui_gray_1]M203 40mm grenade</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_howa20">
		<text>Howa Type 20</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_howa20_descr">
		<text>The assault rifle was officially unveiled to the public in May 2020. This weapon is intended to replace the Type 89 assault rifle, which has been in service for about 30 years. The new rifle of the Japanese Self-Defense Forces, like the previous one, was developed by Howa Machinery Co, and uses 5.56 mm ammunition. The development of a new rifle to replace the Type 89 began at the request of the Japanese Armed Forces in 2014. Externally and structurally, the new Type 20 rifle is a kind of arithmetic mean of many modern rifles, such as the HK433 or CZ BREN II, and, apparently, does not have any original features. However, there is nothing wrong with this, since it is not the originality of the design that is required from the army weapon, but reliability, low price and compliance with the customer's requirements. It remains a mystery how and in what quantity this rifle came to the participants of a scientific expedition to the Zone.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Includes: MARCH Shorty scope and AN/PEQ-15A DBAL-A2 Laser Device\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: KAC QDSS NT-4 5.56х45\n </text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ar15_freedom">
		<text>AR-15 HERA</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ar15_freedom_descr">
		<text>A deeply modernized AR15 rifle, usually in service with the veterans of the Freedom. The body kit installed on the weapon allows you to feel confident at any firing range, but at the same time, the weapon is distinguished by a high price due to the use of very expensive components in the kit.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Scopes:  All for picatinny/weaver (except of Red Dot Sights with low mount: Trijicon RMR, Leupold DeltaPoint PRO, Aimpoint T1 (low mount), Docter Sight and 1P76 Rakurs (picatinny).\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Installed Upgrades: B.E. MEYERS MAWL-C1 tactical green laser aim modul and Here Arms foregrip (helps in recoil control) and stock.\n
		%c[d_purple] Х %c[ui_gray_2] Silencer: Surefire SOCOM556-MONSTER\n </text>
	</string>
	
</string_table>
