<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<!--
	Weapons
-->

<string_table>
	
		
	<string id="st_wpn_aa12">
		<text>AA-12</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aa12_descr">
		<text>The AA-12 is an automatic shotgun developed in 1972 by Maxwell Atchisson. The most famous feature is the reduced recoil. The current 2005 version was developed over 18 years and the original design is the base of several other weapons, including the USAS-12. This version is a custom-made version with the bolt on the gun?s side unlike previous versions.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Aimpoint H1, EOTech 553, Mepro 21, Trijicon RMR\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	

	<string id="st_wpn_vhs2">
		<text>VHS-K2</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vhs2_descr">
		<text>VHS-2 is a fully ambidextrous 5.56 NATO caliber assault rifle. Designed on bullpup modular platform it maintain all the ballistic benefits of a longer barrel in a shorter package without sacrificing overall length, accuracy and muzzle velocity. Only a few of these were found being used by high ranked stalkers in the Zone.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45 compatible suppressor\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Comp M4S, EOTech 553\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_p320">
		<text>SIG P320</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_p320_descr">
		<text>With its unmatched modularity, unprecedented accuracy, and uncompromising reliability, the state-of-the-art SIG SAUER P320 has quickly become one of the most sought after firearms on the market today. Chosen by all branches of the U.S. military, as well as law enforcement agencies across the country and around the world, the P320 redefines the modern handgun.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] GemTech suppressor\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] SIG Sauer Romeo 1 Pro (integrated)\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_maxim">
		<text>Maxim 9</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_maxim_descr">
		<text>Crazy ass pistol envisioned by Nignog Hip.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Maybe\n \n
		</text>
	</string>


	<string id="st_wpn_volt_gun">
		<text>Volt Cannon</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_volt_gun_descr">
		<text>
		Hand-crafted weapon, rarely found in use. The radius of destruction give a chance use it for destruction of fortified enemy groups. The created electric "bullet" can't penetrate heavy armor from the first hit, but a couple of shots can cover a huge area within a short timespan. It uses charged up shards of electro artifacts as ammunition.Used for eliminating enemies behind cover.
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2]Damage radius: 14m
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2]Fire distance: 120m		
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_m134">
		<text>M134 Minigun</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m134_descr">
		<text>
		The M134 Minigun is an American 7.62?51mm NATO six-barrel rotary machine gun with a high rate of fire. It features a Gatling-style rotating barrel assembly with an external power source, normally an electric motor It?s terrible idea to go against someone wielding this weapon.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_flaregun">
		<text>FlareGun</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_flaregun_descr">
		<text>
		Single shot flare gun, used to fire signal rockets in the sky. Can?t harm or attract monsters.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_akelysium">
		<text>AK-Elysium</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_akelysium_descr">
		<text>
		This gun fires an incredible and powerful round but while the original ammo, Air Burst Ammo, only the gun made it to the zone. The gun is equipped with a precise laser and helps hip fire. Maybe it?s possible to use artifacts to replace it?
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_raptr">
		<text>Raptr Shotgun</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_raptr_descr">
		<text>
		The Raptr shotgun is the peak in shotgun badassery. If there was a Doomslayer in the Zone, he would definitely use it.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Leupold M40, Eotech XPS3, Aimpoint CompM4s, Aimpoint H1H, Firefield MG Kemper XL, Vortex Razor AMG UH-1\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_pl14">
		<text>PL-14 Lebedev pistol</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pl14_descr">
		<text>
		The Lebedev pistol is a Russian semi-automatic pistol, which produced under Kalashnikov Concern and designed by Dmitry Lebedev. It was introduced in 2015 as PL-14 and later changed it designation as PL-15 in the year 2016.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9mm silencer\n 
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Docter Sight\n 
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_mk18">
		<text>MK 18</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mk18_descr">
		<text>
		The Mk18 is a carbine. It has a 30 round magazine, medium recoil, and select full-automatic fire mode. It?s compact size allows it to have the close-range versatility of a sub-machine gun, while retaining the firepower of a carbine.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45 compatible suppressor\n 
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Aimpoint CompM4S, EOTech 553, S.U.P \n 
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="kriss_vector">
		<text>Kriss Vector .45</text>
	</string>
	<string id="kriss_vector_descr">
		<text>The KRISS Vector is a series of weapons based upon the parent submachine gun design developed by the American company KRISS USA, formerly Transformational Defense Industries. They use an unconventional delayed blowback system combined with in-line design to reduce perceived recoil and muzzle climb.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] .45 suppressor\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Aimpoint CompM4S, EOTech 553, Aimpoint H1H, Trijicon RMR, Leupold D-EVO, Vortex Razor G2 \n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="sa58u">
		<text>DSA SA-58U OSW</text>
	</string>
	<string id="sa58u_descr">
		<text>SA-58U OSW (Operations Specialist Weapon) it's an improved variant, using better parts than it?s counterpart SA58. It's made with the same Steyr-Daimler-Puch production line equipment as the StG-58. It may come with a different barrel length, an aluminum-alloy lower receiver, and improved Glass-filled Nylon furniture.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45 compatible suppressor\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] CompM4S, EOTech 553,Aimpoint H1H, S.U.P.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_detonator">
		<text>Tactical Strike Detonator</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_detonator_descr">
		<text>A relic from the past. This is the most powerful weapon that anyone can find inside or outside the Zone. Without the launch codes however, it is just paper weight. It will order a series of tactical bombing at the target and at the end, a small, low-powered tactical nuke will obliterate whatever is left alive !!!WARNING - Use it very far from your target or you will join them in the afterlife. - WARNING!!! \n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_mini14">
		<text>Ruger Mini-14</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mini14_descr">
		<text>
		The Mini-14 is a lightweight semiautomatic rifle manufactured by Sturm, Ruger & Co. used by military personnel, law-enforcement personnel, and civilians. It is a decent option for stalkers that desire to start their careers with a decent gun.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.56x45 compatible suppressor\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Leupold M40\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_flamer">
		<text>Flamethrower</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_flamer_descr">
		<text>This thing was made by local crafters during the X-Mas holidays, after which the schematics spread all over the Zone.</text>
	</string>
	
	
	<string id="st_wpn_nvss">
		<text>Rubrakul's VSS Vintorez</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_nvss_descr">
		<text>
		The VSS Vintorez is a marksman rifle featuring an integral suppressor originating from the Soviet Union. The Vintorez was developed alongside the AS Val to replace modified general-purpose firearms, for clandestine operations.\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Kobra, Krechet, Okp-7, Pso1, S.U.P.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_amb17">
		<text>AMB-17</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_amb17_descr">
		<text>
		The AMB-17, is an integrally suppressed assault rifle that uses a heavy subsonic 9?39mm SP5 cartridge and armor-piercing SP6 cartridge. It was developed and manufactured in the late 2010s by Kalashnikov Concern. It made it?s way to the Zone through Mercernaries and high ranking military officers that like to sport the lastest in weaponry technology. \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] Kobra, Krechet, Okp-7, Pso1, S.U.P.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
</string_table>
