<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>

<!-- Miscellaneous gear -->
	<string id="st_psy_helmet_name">
		<text>Scientific psy-helmet (calibrated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_psy_helmet_desc">
		<text>A psy-helmet designed to fit under regular headgear. It was developed under the leadership of Sakharov at the research station near Yantar. The unique layout of the helmet, consisting of electrical artefacts together with the device’s mounted antennas operate on the principle of the shield. When activated, the helmet projects an invisible dome near the carrier, acting on the energised particles released by the Shell artefact, thanks to which most of the radiation is extinguished, then the remnants are reflected by the protection system built directly into the helmet’s body. The uniqueness of this Psy-helmet lies in its ability to withstand the unusual mind-altering psy-frequencies of the various DUGA emitters within the Chernobyl Exclusion Zone.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_bad_psy_helmet_name">
		<text>Scientific psy-helmet (uncalibrated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bad_psy_helmet_desc">
		<text>An uncalibrated psy-helmet designed to fit under regular headgear. It was developed under the leadership of Sakharov at the research station near Yantar. The unique layout of the helmet, consisting of electrical artefacts together with the device’s mounted antennas operate on the principle of the shield. When activated, the helmet projects an invisible dome near the carrier, acting on the energised particles released by the Shell artefact, thanks to which most of the radiation is extinguished, then the remnants are reflected by the protection system built directly into the helmet’s body. The uniqueness of this Psy-helmet lies in its ability to withstand the unusual mind-altering psy-frequencies of the various DUGA emitters within the Chernobyl Exclusion Zone.</text>
	</string>
	

<!-- Headgear -->
	<string id="st_helm_exo_name">
		<text>Exohelm</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_exo_descr">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]The Exohelm, named due to its common appearance alongside exoskeleton armors, is a thick steel helmet produced in the same Ukrainian factories as the exoskeleton armors. The accompanying gas mask is a British SF10, which is easily found on the surplus markets after they were replaced for the General Service Respirator (GSR). Though the gas mask is somewhat dated, the heavy steel helmet provides good protection from shrapnel and small-caliber rounds.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_battle">
		<text>Sphere M12 helmet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_battle_dolg">
		<text>Duty Sphere M12 helmet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_battle_freedom">
		<text>Freedom Sphere M12 helmet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_battle_descr">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]An aluminium/titanium helmet with a cloth exterior for camouflage. Comes with pockets that can be filled with additional armour pieces.  This helmet is in common use among Military Stalkers and Spetsnaz, who typically use it in tandem with PSZ-series body armour. Overall, the M12 Sphere Helmet provides some of the best combat-oriented protection in the Zone, and is in demand among any wealthy stalker who expects to get caught in a serious battle.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_hardhat">
		<text>Surplus steel helmet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_hardhat_descr">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A desperately outdated steel army helmet with a retractable visor for the eyes and not much else. Provides negligible protection against anomalies or radiation, but can deflect bullets. This helmet was never particularly popular in the Zone, except for use in brief armed conflicts between factions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_protective">
		<text>SSP-99 screen helmet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_protective_descr">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A high quality curtain helmet made by the same Defense Research Institute as the SSP-99 and SEVA bodysuits, and intended to be used along with both as standard. Has a hermetic design, and allows for complete isolation from the conditions of an anomalous environment. A closed-cycle air filtering system supplies the wearer with consistently cool, clean air, making it more comfortable than typical gas masks.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_respirator">
		<text>Refitted PBF gas mask kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_respirator_freedom">
		<text>Freedom PBF gas mask kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_respirator_dolg">
		<text>Duty PBF gas mask kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_respirator_descr">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A ShMB gas mask refitted with external 40mm filters for greater functionality. Because the process of conversion from the old internal "porkchop" filters was never standardized, however, there is some slight variance in weight and radiological protection between individual masks. As a general rule, masks like this offer respectable protection in areas of increased radioactive activity, but suffer from a high failure rate in toxic environments and have negligible protection against physical impacts, rapidly breaking when placed under such conditions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_resp">
		<text>Respirator</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_resp_descr">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A basic plastic and rubber respirator, used to protect the wearer from inhaling harmful dusts, fumes, vapours or gases. Widely used by rookies and even some veterans from all factions due to its light weight and economical environmental protection. However, it provides negligible physical protection and is practically guaranteed to fail in more heavily irradiated areas.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_respirator_gp5">
		<text>GP-5 gas mask</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_respirator_gp5_descr">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]Originally manufactured from 1962 to 1989, the GP-5 gas mask was built with the intention to protect the Soviet people from radioactive fallout. It is a helmet-mask made of white and black rubber, with the lenses held in place by a crimping rim. The filters, however, have been restored or replaced with a great deal of care. Compared to gas mask kits of similar price and availability, such as the PBF, this reconditioned respiratory device boasts greater protection against radiation, but an even greater failure rate in toxic environments. \n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_bandana">
		<text>Bandana</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_bandana_descr">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]An ordinary fabric bandana worn by conscripts, support corps and rear-echelon troops in the Military. Normally worn on the head, soldiers will often drape it around their mouth and nose instead to avoid breathing in toxic or radioactive particles. While better than nothing, this obviously isn't very effective, and bandanas used this way need frequent replacement.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_rp_bala">
		<text>Balaclava</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_rp_bala_descr">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A regular black fabric balaclava. It'll help keep your face warm in Eastern Europe's frigid winters, if nothing else. While the cloth of the mask does help filter some toxic and radioactive particles from the air you breathe, this protection is unreliable at best, and balaclavas used this way will soon need to be replaced.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_cloth_mask">
		<text>Cloth mask</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_cloth_mask_descr">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A simple piece of cloth, folded into a mask. It is often used by stalkers to prevent dangerous particles from entering the body, as a precautionary measure. However, with prolonged use, it can accumulate toxins, so it is always desirable to have a spare for a quick replacement.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_m40">
		<text>M40 gas mask</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_m40_descr">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]This M40 is equipped with a multilayered 40-millimetre breathing filter placed on the left. This mask provides respectable radiation and chemical protection for extended periods, even after suffering damage. This gas mask is mass-produced for the US Armed Forces, and finds great use among Mercenaries.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_metro">
		<text>Apocalypse helm</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_metro_descr">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]Believed to have first been created by a faction known as "Final Day", this helm resembles a Czech M10 Gas Mask with heavy armour plating modifications. While it is uncomfortably heavy for most, it still boasts good protective characteristics versus chemical, radioactive and physical threats. When Final Day's leaders were assassinated and the faction dissolved by a stalker named Ghost, these helmets gradually entered into circulation among well-heeled stalkers, particularly those who intended to raid the myriad underground labs across the Zone.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_tactic">
		<text>Sphere-08 helmet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_tactic_descr">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A modern, high quality helmet with a built-in air filtration system, with features based on Western models. The design consists of several layers of Kevlar to protect the wearer from severe physical harm. The helmet is also made of composite dielectric materials, thereby granting the wearer greater insulation from shock than most similar models. Most commonly used by the Zone's Spetsnaz operators, especially in conjunction with the PS5 body armour series.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="helm_spartan">
		<text>Cz-M10 Spartan helmet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_spartan_descr">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A helmet commissioned by extremely influential stalkers, based off the Apocalypse helm designs formerly used by "Final Day". Compared to the Apocalypse, however, this helmet is not only lighter, but more protective across the board. It compares highly favourably to modern combat helmets such as the "sphere" series in addition to boasting amazing protection against anomalies. A popular choice among stalkers who can get hold of it.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="helm_dolg_battle">
		<text>Duty Sphere M12</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_dolg_battle_descr">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1] REMOVED FROM GAME. One of two versions of Sphere M12 used by Duty. This one is more commonly used and improves upon original M12 in terms of physical and psy protection, at cost of slightly increased weight and worse resistance to elements. It is supposed to be worn with PSZ-9d armoured suit, same as original M12 is worn with the Bulat.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="helm_dolg_battle_redline">
		<text>Duty Sphere M12 "Red Line"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_dolg_battle_redline_descr">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1] REMOVED FROM GAME. Of two versions of Duty's Sphere M12, this one is more technologically advanced, and therefore both more protective and lighter. Same as the PSZ-9d "Red Line", this tactical headset is only given to most well-known soldiers of Duty, who achieved great things for their faction. This helmet is not only a masterpiece of combat design, but also a sign of great honour and high position within Duty's ranks. \n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="helm_dolg_vintage">
		<text>PSM-4 combat helmet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_dolg_vintage_descr">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1] REMOVED FROM GAME. PSM-4 is a heavy and bulky, but very durable combat helmet. It has an integrated, tough gas mask reinforced with a number of metal parts and fit for popular EO-19 filters. It also has a class IIIA anti-ballistic visor. The helmet is very heavy due to its mostly metal construction and very slight use of modern synthetic materials. It is very uncomfortable, but thanks to its thickness it is not only very physically resistant, but also capable of shielding the wearer from a considerable amount of external psy influence. It should be noted, that this thickness, compared with mostly metal build, make the inside of helmet heat up really quickly, possibly posing a threat to the wearer. It is therefore highly advised to take the helmet off when in proximity of thermal anomalies. Even though the PSM-4 cannot be count among more optimal helmets, it is still used by some Duty soldiers who require solid protection, but lack the money to afford high-end gear. There also are some old military equipment enthusiasts, who wear the PSM-4 just for its characteristic, vintage look. \n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="helm_ach7">
		<text>ACH-7 headgear set</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_ach7_descr">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]The ACH-7 (Advanced Compound Headgear, 7 Parts) is a more modern version of the surplus steel helmet. It is marginally better at stopping shrapnel. Its main draw, however, is its surprising resistance to psychic attacks, along with its unexpectedly low cost. That said, its lack of a respiratory device makes it an extremely poor choice for the Zone's conditions overall, and is typically only purchased by rookies brave enough to investigate psy-anomalies so early in their stalking careers.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="helm_ach7ex">
		<text>ACH-7EX headgear set</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_ach7ex_descr">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]The ACH-7EX is an "Extended" version of the original ACH-7 headgear set. The inclusion of a respiratory system alone makes this model a major improvement over its predecessor. Boasting chemical and radiological protection somewhere between that of a GP-5 and a PBF kit, along with respectable physical protection makes this headgear an appealing choice for many stalkers who are looking for a good but economical balance between anomalous and combat protection.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="helm_eo21">
		<text>EO-21 PBFM gas mask</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_eo21_descr">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1] REMOVED FROM GAME. Even further modernized version of EO-20 PBF gas mask, designed by Stalker craftsmen. It is both more protective and resistant, and it uses filters that are slightly lighter and guarantee a bit better protection from irradiated particles and toxins. Its visor is wider and more impact-resistant; the apparatus was also made less susceptible to any sources of physical damage.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="helm_dolg_eo21_red">
		<text>EO-21 PBFM Krasnyy</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_dolg_eo21_red_descr">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1] REMOVED FROM GAME. EO-21 PBFM gas mask modified by Duty for enhanced physical protection. It is at the point of highest, most optimal and budget-friendly defence/weight ratio. This is the Krasnyy series model, designed for use with the modified PS5-2M; regular version of this mask used by Duty is simply an original EO-21 with red filters.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="helm_eo21sawnoff">
		<text>EO-21 PBFL gas mask</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_eo21sawnoff_descr">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1] REMOVED FROM GAME. The most compact, the lightest gas mask in the Zone. It is commonly known as the "sawn-off EO-21", as it looks like if someone took the original mask and cut off its upper half. In truth, this mask was designed this way and is meant for use in less contaminated areas. Its main goal, aside of protection of course, is to make using it as comfortable as possible. It can be used both by itself or with an oxygen tank, which can be attached by a pipe to a socket present on the left side of the mask, just above one of its filters. It uses the exact same filter type as full sized EO-21.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="helm_dolg_eo21sawnoff">
		<text>Duty EO-21 PBFL</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_dolg_eo21sawnoff_descr">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1] REMOVED FROM GAME. Compact version of EO-21 gas mask used by low-ranking Duty members in the least contaminated areas of the Zone. Compared to its original version, the mask was made just slightly more resistant, optimizing it for combat performance to minimize the risk of any heavy damage. Even though it still doesn't stand much of a chance against pistol bullets, it won't crack after receiving a strong punch, and will save the wearer's teeth as well.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="helm_gp5">
		<text>GP-5 gas mask</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_gp5_descr">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1] DUPLICATE. REMOVED FROM GAME. Originally manufactured from 1962 to 1989, the GP-5 gas mask was built with the intention to protect the Soviet people from radioactive fallout. It is a helmet-mask made of white and black rubber, with the lenses held in place by a crimping rim. The filters, however, have been restored or replaced with a great deal of care. Compared to gas mask kits of similar price and availability, such as the PBF, this reconditioned respiratory device boasts greater protection against radiation, but an even greater failure rate in toxic environments.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="helm_ppm88">
		<text>PPM-88 gas mask</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_ppm88_descr">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A Russian gas mask well suited for CBRN ecological hazards. In the Zone, it can be considered a functional and spiritual successor to the GP-5, possessing comparable overall characteristics alongside significant improvements in protection versus chemical and radiological threats. A good option that most stalkers can use throughout their careers, provided they don't see too much combat or do anything similarly foolish.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="helm_m50">
		<text>M50z gas mask</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_m50_descr">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]An M50 gas mask tweaked for better functionality in the Zone. Although some of its protective characteristics are actually slightly worse as a result, it makes up for this in a much-needed boost to protection from both psychic and radioactive phenomena. Overall, this mask is considered an improvement over the M40. Unlike the M40, however, this mask is bought directly by private military companies for the express purpose of supplying the Zone's Mercenaries. \n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="helm_ranger">
		<text>GP-10z ranger gas mask</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_ranger_descr">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]Using the GP-10 as its model, this gas mask was designed primarily to protect the wearer from controllers and poltergeists. The success rate is somewhat mixed, but this model remains an excellent option for those who need protection from psychic, thermal, and shrapnel attacks.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="helm_dolg_tactic_red">
		<text>Duty Sphere 08 Krasnyy</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_dolg_tactic_red_descr">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1] REMOVED FROM GAME. Sphere 08 headgear set modified and used by Duty, usually paired with their version of Berill armoured suit. Same as the rest of Duty's Krasnyy series gear, this helmet is supposed to serve as a combat gear protecting from both human and mutant threat; it is therefore even more vulnerable to environmental threats than the original, but in turn provides more physical and psy protection. \n \n
		</text>
	</string>


<!-- Novice outfits -->
	<string id="novice_outfit_name">
		<text>Leather jacket</text>
	</string>
	<string id="novice_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A warm leather anorak worn over a cosy turtleneck sweater, tucked into sturdy jeans and hiking boots. The outfit of choice among naive or inexperienced stalkers, veterans consider it barely a step above walking around the Zone in your underwear.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="novice_outfit_camo_name">
		<text>Firearm enthusiast's jacket</text>
	</string>
	<string id="novice_outfit_camo_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A warm leather anorak worn over a cosy turtleneck sweater, tucked into sturdy jeans and hiking boots. Formerly owned by a typical firearm enthusiast, it sports several advantages over an ordinary jacket - namely a camouflage pattern and a higher quality material choice alongside a more educated weight distribution system. Still utterly inadequate for the Zone's harsh conditions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="novice_outfit_tourist_name">
		<text>Tourist’s jacket</text>
	</string>
	<string id="novice_outfit_tourist_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A warm leather anorak with an integrated backpack, worn over a cosy turtleneck sweater, tucked into sturdy jeans and hiking boots. It seems the previous owner was a real lover for hikes. The educated choice of materials and weight management system makes this more useful than most leather jackets, but is still unsuitable for anything more than quiet walks along the Zone's borders.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="csky_novice_outfit_name">
		<text>Clear Sky leather jacket</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_novice_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A soft blue leather anorak worn over a cosy turtleneck sweater, tucked into sturdy jeans and hiking boots. These simple suits are assembled in large quantities by Clear Sky's tailors for use within the faction. Not recommended for use outside the southernmost parts of the Zone.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="dolg_novice_outfit_name">
		<text>Duty leather jacket</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_novice_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A dark leather anorak worn over a cosy turtleneck sweater, tucked into sturdy jeans and combat boots. Formerly used only as relaxed wear for off-duty Dutyers, these simple suits were never intended for use by those on active service. Desperate times, however, occasionally call for desperate measures.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="bandit_novice_outfit_name">
		<text>Black leather jacket</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_novice_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A black leather jacket commonly associated with the Zone's bandits and crooks. Mostly worn to intimidate rookies from other factions, it provides very little protection against anything more than a stiff breeze or the occasional flying vodka bottle.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="bandit_novice_alt_outfit_name">
		<text>Armoured leather jacket</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_novice_alt_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]Jackets like this first entered circulation among Bandits thanks to Quartermaster Morgan, a corrupt supplier who formerly belonged to the Duty faction. Offers protection comparable to a standard Military service outfit. Still not great protection in the Zone, especially not when fighting against enraged or vengeful Dutyers.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="redline_novice_outfit_name">
		<text>Redline leather jacket</text>
	</string>
	<string id="redline_novice_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A snazzy bright red leather anorak worn over a cosy turtleneck sweater, tucked into sturdy jeans and hiking boots. The colour alone should be reason enough to avoid use in the Zone.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="svoboda_novice_outfit_name">
		<text>Freedom leather jacket</text>
	</string>
	<string id="svoboda_novice_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A camouflaged leather anorak worn over a cosy turtleneck sweater, tucked into sturdy jeans and combat boots. Such attire is typically only worn by Freedomers when they feel absolutely safe - in other words, almost never.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>


<!-- Overcoats -->
	<string id="monolith_trenchcoat_outfit_name">
		<text>Monolith overcoat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trenchcoat_freedom_brown_outfit_name">
		<text>Heavy Freedom overcoat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trenchcoat_dolg_brown_outfit_name">
		<text>Heavy Duty overcoat</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="trenchcoat_outfit_name">
		<text>Overcoat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trenchcoat_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A long, thick overcoat. The protection offered by this apparel can vary tremendously depending on the tailor, but as a general rule is only slightly less useless than the leather jacket. Still, many newer stalkers will swear by it simply because it looks so damn cool.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="trenchcoat_brown_outfit_name">
		<text>Heavy brown overcoat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trenchcoat_brown_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A long, thick overcoat worn over a butchered scientist suit. Although the closed cycle system and several other features seem to have been stripped off for whatever reason, the end result still compares favourably to many basic stalker suits.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="trenchcoat_green_outfit_name">
		<text>Heavy green overcoat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trenchcoat_green_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A long, thick green overcoat worn over a butchered scientist suit. Although the closed cycle system and several other features seem to have been stripped off for whatever reason, the end result still compares favourably to many basic stalker suits.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="greh_trenchcoat_outfit_name">
		<text>Sin heavy overcoat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_trenchcoat_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A long, thick, bloodstained overcoat worn over a butchered scientist suit. Although the closed cycle system and several other features seem to have been stripped off for whatever reason, the end result still compares favourably to many basic stalker suits.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	

<!-- Exploration -->
	<string id="travel_outfit_name">
		<text>"Voyager" stalker suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A Zone-assembled suit that has been handmade by local craftsmen as a matter of survival. This particular outfit is of high quality and intended for extended exploration - it boasts a surprisingly sophisticated weight distribution system along with more than ample protection against the Zone's environmental factors, particularly radiological and chemical threats. A suit of choice for many artefact hunters and even some mutant hunters, its most notable downside - aside from its high price compared to other stalker suits - is its sheer hopelessness in a firefight. It's unlikely its previous owner parted with it willingly. \n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="nomad_outfit_name">
		<text>"Nomad" stalker suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="nomad_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A Zone-assembled suit that has been handmade by local craftsmen as a matter of survival. This particular outfit is of high quality and feels exceptionally light and comfortable to wear, despite being much more protective overall when compared to other stalker suits. It is clear that whoever assembled this armour was highly familiar with the Zone's nature, and evidently put a great deal of pride and care into their work - something that might not have been true of its previous owner. Either way, its quality is matched only by its price.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="antirad_outfit_name">
		<text>GP-5MvC Antirad bodysuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="antirad_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]GP-5 Antirad suit was designed even before the discovery of the Brainscorcher, and was actually worn by the very Stalkers who first brought news about unusually strong psy waves north of Army Warehouses. The suit was developed by some frequent visitors of the 100 Rads and the Barkeep himself, who supported the project financially, and later made a lot of money selling sets of the suit. Since then the suit was upgraded multiple times, but the base design (based on Sunrise suit) remained the same. In its current, modernized version (GP-5M) its main components are the Sunrise suit with specially treated fabrics and more rubberized parts, as well as with a larger number of pockets. A common and old but still reliable GP-5 gas mask is integrated with lightweight oxygen tanks carried on the back. The main goal of this outfit was to provide much more radiation protection than the regular Sunrise, making journeys to the north not as dangerous. Even though it is often called a budget SEVA suit, it doesn't even come close to its level of anomalous protection. The suit is meant to be worn in highly irradiated areas, but it doesn't stand much of a chance against stronger anomaly fields. Version C of the outfit additionally bears a camouflage pattern of different shades of green, enabling the wearer to easily hide in dense foliage. \n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="hybrid_outfit_name">
		<text>Hybrid armoured suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="hybrid_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A bit of an awkward duckling, this outfit was created by one of Kiev's defence research institutes for the purpose of guarding researchers in the Zone. It is clear the suit was created on a budget, however, as the ballistic armour woven into the outfit simultaneously makes it weaker against anomalous phenomena, while still providing less protection in a firefight than a Beryllium vest. As such, none of these suits were ever officially commissioned by the Ukrainian government, although a few nonetheless managed to find their way into the Zone through shady means. A popular choice for stalkers who want decent general protection yet cannot spring for something better.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="wastelander_outfit_name">
		<text>"Wastelander" stalker suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="wastelander_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A Zone-assembled suit that has been handmade by local craftsmen as a matter of survival. This particular outfit is unusually light compared to average Stalker suits, but possesses a spacious Class IIIA vest and lightweight inserts. It's essentially a more nimble Stalker-made Berill-5M suit.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

<!-- CS outfits -->
	<string id="csky_light_novice_outfit_name">
		<text>CS-1 body armour</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_light_novice_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A light suit worn by Clear Sky's novice researchers. It provides more than adequate protection from the anomalous phenomena in the Swamps, but does little to protect from physical threats or radiological phenomena.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="csky_light_outfit_name">
		<text>CS-2a body armour</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_light_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A blue bodysuit intended for conducting rapid search operations in areas of low risk - anomalous or otherwise. Not intended for pitched battle or intense firefights, although it'd likely still fare better than the CS-1 in such scenarios.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="csky_medium_outfit_name">
		<text>CS-3a body armour</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_medium_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A heavier but still comfortable outfit worn by members of Clear Sky that provides more than adequate general protection, especially in combat. However, the armour is also highly conductive and susceptible to corrosion.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="csky_heavy_outfit_name">
		<text>CS-3b body armour</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_heavy_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]Formerly the standard outfit issued to Clear Sky assault squads, after the faction’s infamous failure against the NPP in 2011 this armour serves as a reminder that even an excellent protective bodysuit cannot guarantee safety on the wrong side of the perimeter. The armour is capable of stopping a pistol bullet, while the wearer is also reasonably protected from anomalies.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	

<!-- NBC outfits -->
	<string id="nbc_outfit_name">
		<text>Tactical Stalker suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="nbc_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A 'Sunrise' Stalker suit whose vest has been switched out with a special pocketed load-bearing vest. Though its ballistic and anomaly protection are both low, it's a solid suit for a scavenger on a budget.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="monolith_nbc_outfit_name">
		<text>Tactical Monolith suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_nbc_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A Monolith suit whose vest has been switched out with a special pocketed load-bearing vest. Though its ballistic and anomaly protection are both low, it's a solid suit for a scavenger on a budget.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="cs_nbc_outfit_name">
		<text>CS-2t suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cs_nbc_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A CS-2b stalker suit whose vest has been switched out with a special pocketed load-bearing vest. Though its ballistic and anomaly protection are both low, it's a solid suit for a scavenger on a budget.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="nbc_merc_outfit_name">
		<text>Load-bearing 'Twilight' tactical suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="nbc_merc_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A Mercenary 'Twilight' suit whose vest has been switched out with a special pocketed load-bearing vest. Though its ballistic and anomaly protection are both low, it's a solid suit for a scavenger on a budget.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="nbc_freedom_outfit_name">
		<text>Keeper of Freedom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="nbc_freedom_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A Sentinel of Freedom suit whose vest has been switched out with a special pocketed load-bearing vest. Though its ballistic and anomaly protection are both low, it's a solid suit for a scavenger on a budget.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="nbc_dolg_outfit_name">
		<text>PS5-Mt suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="nbc_dolg_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A PS5-M suit whose vest has been switched out with a special pocketed load-bearing vest. Though its anomaly protection is both low, it's a solid suit for a scavenger on a budget.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="bandit_nbc_outfit_name">
		<text>Load-bearing 'Sunset' tactical suit </text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_nbc_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A 'Sunset' bandit suit whose vest has been switched out with a special pocketed load-bearing vest. Though its ballistic and anomaly protection are both low, it's a solid suit for a scavenger on a budget.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	
<!-- Assault vest -->
	<string id="light_loner_outfit_name">
		<text>Interceptor body armour</text>
	</string>
	<string id="light_loner_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]An old IBA suit imported from the West and modified for the Zone's conditions. It's a little heavy, but provides fair anomaly protection along with good anti-ballistic characteristics. Sometimes worn by stalkers hired as auxiliaries to help fight wars between factions, this suit significantly improves one's chance of surviving a skirmish compared to regular stalker gear.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="light_freedom_outfit_name">
		<text>Defender of Freedom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="light_freedom_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]Rumoured to be supplied to the Freedom faction directly from an unknown source, this suit is based on the somewhat outdated IBA system, but modified for greater comfort when operating in the Zone's conditions. A respectable suit of body armour, its intended use in the Zone may well be to properly protect skirmish forces expected to assault lightly entrenched enemy positions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="light_voen_outfit_name">
		<text>Military stalker IBAz suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="light_voen_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]An Interceptor Anomalous Body Armour System that used to belong to a Military Stalker. Compared to the standard model, this suit is more comfortable to wear and features overall superior anomaly protection. Not normally issued to conscripts or Spetsnaz operators, Military Stalkers who wish to use this suit generally have to order it themselves.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="light_monolit_outfit_name">
		<text>Monolith IBAz assault suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="light_monolit_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]An Interceptor Anomalous Body Armour System that has somehow ended up in the hands of the Monolith. Compared to the standard model, this suit is slightly more ergonomic and boasts greater protection against psychic interference. These vests usually enter the faction by way of hapless stalkers getting stuck trying to cross the Barrier. More often than not, the next time they're seen by the Zone at large is during the Monolith's next invasion into the Warehouses.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="light_dolg_outfit_name">
		<text>IBAz universal protection</text>
	</string>
	<string id="light_dolg_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]An old IBA suit imported from the West and modified for the Zone's conditions. Uncomfortably heavy both to wear and to carry, the Duty variant seems to have received extensive upgrades for protection against chemical weapons. It is unlikely that Duty order these suits from the outside world themselves, however. Rather, it is widely believed that they are simply refurbished and restored after being salvaged off the bodies of vanquished anarchists.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="light_merc_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary IBAz suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="light_merc_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A well-kept Interceptor Anomalous Body Armour System sold directly to the Mercenaries from various Western sources. This suit, while a little uncomfortable, is overall better than the standard model circulating around the Zone. It's intended to allow Mercenaries to fulfill contracts that call for light assaults on fortified enemy positions within the Zone. \n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="light_isg_outfit_name">
		<text>UNISG IBAz suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="light_isg_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A strong but somewhat outdated combat suit modified to additionally give adequate anomalous protection to the wearer. This suit is the bare minimum that one should wear in situations where conflict with armed SSU forces seems inevitable. Also not a bad choice for UN scouts who intend to conduct light raids into the Zone's myriad laboratories.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>


<!-- Sunrise suits -->
	<string id="stalker_outfit_name">
		<text>"Sunrise" stalker suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A Zone-assembled suit that has been handmade by local craftsmen as a matter of survival. Made of twin-layered rubberised cloth with plexiglass lining and integrated body armour, the Sunrise is one of the oldest stalker suits in existence. It is also widely considered the BARE MINIMUM protection a stalker should have for serious trips into the Zone. Despite this, it enjoys immense popularity among rookies and veteran stalkers alike thanks to its economical use and great modification potential.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="stalker_outfit_camo_name">
		<text>"Chameleon" stalker suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_outfit_camo_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]NOT IN GAME. Camouflaged during assembly, this DIY stalker bodysuit is a combination of twin-layered rubberised cloth with Plexiglas lining and built-in body armour. Despite the fact that the body armour is often strained by anything beyond even pistol bullets, the suit enjoys great popularity due to its low cost and modification potential.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="stalker_outfit_alt_name">
		<text>"Hipster" stalker suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_outfit_alt_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]NOT IN GAME. This DIY stalker bodysuit is a combination of twin-layered rubberised cloth with Plexiglas lining and built-in body armour. Despite the fact that the body armour is often strained by anything beyond even pistol bullets, the suit enjoys great popularity due to its low cost and modification potential.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="stalker_drought_outfit_name">
		<text>"Drought" stalker suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_drought_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A Zone-assembled suit that has been handmade by local craftsmen as a matter of survival. For a stalker suit, the Drought possesses marginally better ballistic protection than average, but is also considerably less comfortable to wear. On the plus side, it comes with several belt slots. While intended for artefacts, these slots are most often filled with camelbacks to offset the extra weight of the suit, which is partially what earned it the ironic nickname of "Drought". Like the Sunrise, it is hugely popular for its relatively low cost and great modification potential.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="stalker_predator_outfit_name">
		<text>"Predator" stalker suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_predator_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A Zone-assembled suit that has been handmade by local craftsmen as a matter of survival. An overall upgrade over the "Drought" suit, the "Predator" features similar protection in a gunfight while also being significantly more comfortable to wear. For this reason, it can be a favoured choice among any stalker who needs a little more protection and a lot more mobility than what the average stalker suit can afford. Like most stalker suits, it enjoys popularity among greenhorns and experts alike thanks to its low maintenance costs and great modification potential. \n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="stalker_autumn_outfit_name">
		<text>"Autumn" stalker suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_autumn_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A Zone-assembled suit that has been handmade by local craftsmen as a matter of survival. This suit is a favourite among newer artefact hunters and creative hitmen, as it allows one to either traverse - or hide within - chemical anomaly fields with much greater ease than a stalker suit would normally allow. It is also slightly more comfortable to wear than the average stalker suit, despite further featuring enhanced ballistic protecion. As it is only slightly more expensive than the Sunrise suit, it's a good choice for stalkers willing to spring that little bit further with their Rubles.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="stalker_vineleaf_outfit_name">
		<text>"Vineleaf" stalker suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_vineleaf_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]NOT IN GAME. A higher quality version of the regular Sunrise bodysuit, made of more resistant and expensive materials. The main build of the suit is pretty much the same as that of basic Sunrise, but the use of higher quality materials lead to increased protective qualities without a significant increase in weight. The suit is also more durable and has a potential for more advanced modifications. The "Vineleaf" version is mainly focused of increasing the wearer's mobility and comfort without reducing its protective qualities. It achieves this goal by the use of a more flexible, thermoactive fabric; the outfit slightly shrinks when exposed to a high heat. Stalkers who just bought the outfit make their way to the nearest thermal anomaly and stand next to it for a while - the outfit then shrinks and fits their body perfectly as a result. Even though it sounds dangerous, nobody ever reported the suit disturbing their blood flow. This fabric also seems to be a bit more difficult to cut, therefore making the suit grant more protection from attacks of weaker mutants. One last quality of this suit is that its inner layer is treated with a compound which slightly cools the body, increasing comfort. As its name suggests, "Vineleaf" bears a camouflage in colours similar to that of a vine or ivy leaves. The pattern consists of large, irregularly shaped spots of lighter and darker shades of the colour.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="stalker_bear_outfit_name">
		<text>"Bear" stalker suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_bear_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A Zone-assembled suit, handmade by local craftsmen as a matter of survival. Slightly heavier than other stalker suits, some still take it along due to its improved protection against ballistics and potent insulation against thermal threats. Sadly this insulation is achieved not through conventional fabrics, but rather through an unnamed home-made anomalous compound created through trial and error. The side effect of this is that the wearer's body is much more likely to be overloaded by electrical shocks. Most often used by stalkers working in the Burner anomalies near Yantar.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="stalker_salamander_outfit_name">
		<text>"Salamander" stalker suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_salamander_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A Zone-assembled suit that has been handmade by local craftsmen as a matter of survival. This suit was designed for stalkers who place value on observation and exploration - it has about average protection for a stalker suit in combat (which can be avoided) or against anomalies (which can be spotted), but grants exceptional defence against radiation. A good choice for those who are highly aware of their surroundings and simply need something to stave off the Invisible Killer. Ironically, for something dubbed the "Salamander", it demonstrates a poor ability to safely channel heat. Like all stalker suits, however, it is an economical choice with great upgrade potential.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="stalker_graphite_outfit_name">
		<text>"Graphite" stalker suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_graphite_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A Zone-assembled suit that has been handmade by local craftsmen as a matter of survival. It was independently designed by a few optimistic stalkers who were expecting to take measurements of psy-storms out in the open. Naturally, this endeavour failed, but their designs were later recovered and used to produce a stalker suit, able to shelter the wearer's nervous system. Somewhat prone to overheating and not too good against chemical spills. An infrequent, and somewhat outdated, joke among modern stalkers is to throw the suit on the floor and then pretend it isn't there.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="stalker_tigerstripe_outfit_name">
		<text>"Tigerstripe" stalker suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_tigerstripe_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A Zone-assembled suit that has been handmade by local craftsmen as a matter of survival. One of the heavier stalker suits available, this outfit was designed for those who prefer to make their money as hired killers or fighters instead of looting artefacts or skinning mutants. Compared to the average stalker suit, it provides marginally better protection against ballistics and a genuine improvement in defence against shrapnel, cuts and blunt impacts. Compared to many other combat suits, however, this apparel's main draw lies simply in how cheap it is to maintain.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ecologist_guard_outfit_name">
		<text>ISRIT guard jumpsuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecologist_guard_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A basic suit originally intended as spare equipment for Professor Hermann's "Iskra Scientific Research and Investigation Team", it has since become a relatively cheap protective bodysuit for Ecologist guards working all over the Zone. Boasts more than adequate anomaly protection for its price, but will generally struggle to stop more than a pistol bullet. Most guards will spring for a SEVA or SSP-99M when they can. Those who expect to take part in serious combat actions will rather stick to proper Military combat suits.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="cs_stalker_outfit_name">
		<text>CS-2b body armour</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cs_stalker_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]Unlike other suits in the CS-1, 2 and 3 series, this body armour was only created after the faction's massive losses at the Chernobyl NPP. It is widely considered to be the first proper successor to the CS-1 suit as it focuses on keeping the wearer safe from anomalous environments over armouring them for battle. Provides adequate physical protection and good environmental resistances.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>


<!-- STS (Special Tactical Suits) -->
	<string id="svoboda_light_outfit_name">
		<text>Wind of Freedom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="svoboda_light_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]This comfortable stalker bodysuit is made by Freedom craftsmen. The suit’s fabric is treated with Horizon, a special solution developed by the faction by trial and error, to increase resistance to chemical anomalies. One can only guess what the side effects might be.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="monolith_outfit_name">
		<text>Monolith X-18 suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A mysterious outfit associated with the Monolith faction. It consists of an environmental bodysuit that provides more than adequate chemical and radiological protection, underneath a ballistic vest capable of stopping weak pistol rounds. Its anomaly protection, however, is subpar. Previously of unknown origin, scores of these suits were found in containers and lockers underneath the X18 facility in Dark Valley. Although the stalkers who found this cache have since all mysteriously disappeared, this discovery has nonetheless launched thousands of conspiracy theories among stalkers of other factions, the premise of many claiming that these suits predate the creation of the Zone itself.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="bandit_sun_outfit_name">
		<text>"Sunset" tactical suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_sun_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A Zone-assembled suit, made by local craftsmen as a matter of survival. Its design seems to be modelled on that of a Special Tactical Suit, but bears an especially disturbing resemblance to a Monolith X-18 suit that has had its conventional NBC features stripped down in favour of greater insulation from thermal and electrical threats. Mostly used by Bandits in Dark Valley to clear out the poltergeists that occasionally escape from the local lab.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="merc_sun_outfit_name">
		<text>"Twilight" tactical suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_sun_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A Zone-assembled suit, made by local craftsmen as a matter of survival. Clearly, the resident Mercenaries have taken a leaf out of the Free Stalkers' book, and have begun to locally produce some of their own outfits. Shows signs of inspiration from the Monolith X-18 suit - an outfit the Mercs no doubt try to salvage from their costly skirmishes in Limansk. Overall of good quality, most Mercenaries find it more than adequate for mid-level operations south of Radar.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="merc_nighthunter_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary STS-N body armour</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_nighthunter_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]Sometimes nicknamed the "Nighthunter", this outfit is a slightly heavy special tactical suit, used by Mercenaries in both nocturnal and urban combat scenarios. In terms of design and performance, it strikes a good balance between typical Spetsnaz armour and a common stalker suit. It possesses more than adequate protection for skirmishes, but is generally considered mediocre by those who prefer artefact hunting contracts over fulfilling hit jobs. \n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="merc_wolven_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary STS-W body armour</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_wolven_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]Sometimes nicknamed the "Wolven", this outfit is a comfortable special tactical suit, used by Mercenaries in both exploratory expeditions and stealth operations. This suit possesses good anomaly protection for its class, allowing the wearer to move through - or hide in - dangerous anomalous fields in relative safety. Naturally useful for artefact hunting, this protection also allows large teams of Mercenaries to set up ambushes in unexpected locations, allowing them to take down targets considered too tough for more orthodox methods.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="isg_outfit_name">
		<text>UNISG Mk 1 tactical body armour</text>
	</string>
	<string id="isg_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]Based on a fairly standard suit design used by Western special forces, outfits like this are common to many militaries throughout the world. This is the bare minimum a UNISG operative can expect to be fitted with. Compared to even a basic Mercenary LC suit, this body armour is both heavier and less protective and as such can be considered barely adequate for the Zone's conditions. Still, it is a massive step up from the army uniforms found on Ukrainian conscripts.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="isg_merc_outfit_name">
		<text>UNISG Mk 2 tactical body armour</text>
	</string>
	<string id="isg_merc_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]An improvement over the original Mk-1 design, this outfit is much better suited for the Zone's conditions. Its overall protection against anomalies is more than adequate, and particularly great protection is afforded against chemical, toxic or thermal hazards. These improvements were commissioned by UNISG based on the limited data that could be recovered from their less fortunate predecessors. Still, wearers are encouraged to avoid contact with local stalkers as often as possible.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	
<!-- LCS (Light Combat Suit) -->
	<string id="merc_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary LC suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]The "Light Combat Suit" is one of the most common outfits used by the Zone's Mercenaries. Its design is based on the suit used by the special forces of Western armies. Due to a special treatment of the fabric, the armour has a strengthened stability during the physical movement of its plates. Adequate for basic operations, but quite poor in quality compared to standard Spetsnaz gear, and was quite obviously not designed with the existence of anomalies in mind.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="merc_fighter_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary LC-F suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_fighter_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]Sometimes bitterly referred to as the "Fighter" by sarcastic Mercenaries, this suit is a variation of the standard LC outfit that has sacrificed a great deal of protection for increased mobility, better thermal protection and a belt slot for artefacts. It can perform surprisingly well in operations where stealth and speed are imperative, and thus finds limited used among Merc scouts and hitmen who operate in the less irradiated parts of the Zone.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="banditmerc_outfit_name">
		<text>Fenced LC suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="banditmerc_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A light combat suit obtained through shady means to help armour local Bandit gangs. Its design is based on the suit used by the special forces of Western armies. In a twist of dramatic irony, however, it appears whoever supplied these suits was ripping his customers off. This outfit's overall protection is extremely poor for the Zone's conditions and is significantly worse than the Light Combat suits used by the Zone's Mercenaries. Still, it is at least comfortable to wear, and arguably better than what Ukraine's conscripts get. Arguably.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="renegademerc_outfit_name">
		<text>Renegade LC suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="renegademerc_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A light combat suit obtained through shady means to help armour local groups of Renegades. Its design is based on the suit used by the special forces of Western armies. Surprisingly pleasant to wear, this outfit provides more than adequate protection from small arms, lacerations and errant shrapnel. Still, it is not really intended for use in areas of high radiological or anomalous activity, and as such few wearers will be found deep in the Zone with any regularity.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="merc_sunset_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary LCz suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_sunset_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A Mercenary Light Combat Suit modified for better use in the Zone. Possessing overall improvements over the standard LC suit across the board, it is generally considered more than adequate for light combat engagements, but a little uncomfortable to use in anomalous areas. Still, this suit is a genuine improvement all around for most newer Mercenaries, and - for general use - is not a bad alternative to the faction's special tactical suits.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="merc_scout_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary LC-S suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_scout_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]Nicknamed the "Scout", this outfit is, essentially, an LC-F suit modified to fill a more specialized niche. While a little heavier and less protective in combat than an LC-F, it is still a very comfortable suit. A cheap source of environmental protection, this suit's modifications make it a good choice for Mercenaries who want to explore the Zone's anomalies on a budget.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="merc_jackal_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary LTS-J body suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_jackal_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A light tactical suit, nicknamed "Jackal" after the now dead Merc leader who was assigned to crack open a laboratory named X-8 over six years ago. This outfit provides more-or-less adequate protection from the Zone's dangers, but what sets it apart is how marvellously comfortable it is on top of possessing a fairly sophisticated weight distribution system. This, on top of a relatively affordable price, makes it a favourite among slightly more experienced Mercenaries.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="merc_coyote_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary MTS-C body suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_coyote_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A medium tactical suit, nicknamed the "Coyote". Widely considered the successor of the LTS-J body suit, this outfit boasts better physical protection on top of an even better weight distribution system. Naturally, its price is higher than that of its predecessor, but this won't stop most Mercs from springing for it when they are able.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="greh_armored_outfit_name">
		<text>Irij flak armour</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_armored_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A comfortable and ergonomic arming suit used to outfit Sin's followers en masse. It consists of a ballistic vest over an environmental bodysuit. Providing passable protection from anomalies and good protection from gunfire, these suits do a good job fortifying the already durable warriors of Sin.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="greh_armored_camo_outfit_name">
		<text>Vyriy flak armour</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_armored_camo_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A more advanced variant of regular Sin flak armour, typically gifted to the faction's more loyal and devout members. Compared to its more standard counterpart, this suit provides increased protection from anomalies in addition to fortifying the wearer's strength beyond its often already considerable limits.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="dolg_voin_outfit_name">
		<text>PS6-V warrior suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_voin_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A modern, updated variant of the original PS5-M universal protection bodysuit. Is more than adequate for all of the Zone's conditions as well as being markedly comfortable for a Duty suit. Originally intended to replace its predecessor entirely, its higher production cost put this goal on hold in the face of Duty's multitude of recent losses.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="isg_lcs_outfit_name">
		<text>UNISG LC suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="isg_lcs_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A "Light Combat Suit" model adapted for use by UNISG troops. Its design is based on the one used by the special forces of Western armies. Compared to the Mercenary variant, it has better anomaly protection and worse combat protection. Comes with built-in body armour and armour attachment modules, but is mediocre overall outside the most basic of operations within the Zone.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="isg_lcs_camo_outfit_name">
		<text>UNISG LC-C suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="isg_lcs_camo_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A modified "Light Combat Suit" model adapted for use in the Zone by UNISG troops. Its design is based on the suit used by the special forces of Western armies. Despite its light weight and general comfort, this outfit demonstrates more than adequate protection against anomalies and during gunfights against lightly armed opponents. Sadly, it is not of much help against shrapnel, bludgeoning or stab wounds.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="isg_lcs_urban_outfit_name">
		<text>UNISG LC-UC suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="isg_lcs_urban_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A modified "Light Combat Suit" model adapted for use in battle by UNISG troops. Its design is based on the suit used by the special forces of Western armies. Compares favourably in combat compared to many other outfits in its class, but still falls short of what a Spetsnaz operator would be wearing. Not recommended for use in areas of high anomalous or radiological activity.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>


<!-- Berill-5M Armoured Suits -->
	<string id="army_outfit_name">
		<text>Military service outfit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="army_outfit_description">
		<text>A poor protective outfit contracted by government bureaucrats outsourcing to the lowest bidder. Typically issued to helicopter pilots, tank drivers, rear-echelon personnel, conscripts and enlisted servicemen. Provides adequate protection from small mutants. Although its overall combat protection is better than the leather jackets commonly found on the rookies of other factions, that really isn't saying much.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="specops_outfit_name">
		<text>Berill-5M armoured suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="specops_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]This item comprises military PS5 series body armour with beryllium sputter modified for use in the Zone. Designed for intense rapid-insertion assault operations, this outfit is standard issue for most Spetsnaz operators in the Zone, but requires a high quality respirator to counteract its weaknesses against radiation and anomalies. Occasionally, this suit will be sold to ordinary stalkers in exchange for various "favours".\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="specops_dolg_outfit_name">
		<text>PS5-B battle armour</text>
	</string>
	<string id="specops_dolg_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]This item comprises military PS5 series body armour with beryllium sputter modified for use in the Zone. Compared to a standard PS5-M universal protection suit, this outfit is more ergonomic and protective overall, but is slightly less insulated and provides much less defence against heavy impacts, like a poltergeist's telekinetic attack.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="specops_merc_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary B-5M armoured suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="specops_merc_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]Spetsnaz body armour "acquired" and repurposed by the Zone's Mercenaries. Provides good physical protection while also being remarkably comfortable to wear, although its weaknesses against environmental hazards demand it be used alongside a high quality gas mask and helmet. Often worn by Mercenaries who used to work for the SSU.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="specops_bandit_outfit_name">
		<text>Deserter's B-5M armoured suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="specops_bandit_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A set of PS5 series body armour with beryllium sputter, acquired through shady means by the Zone's Bandits. Although the suit shows visible signs of irreparable wear and tear, it's still an excellent choice for battle when both protection and mobility is needed. Not really recommended for use near anomalies, however.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="svoboda_heavy_outfit_name">
		<text>Guardian of Freedom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="svoboda_heavy_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A set of Spetsnaz body armour that has been "liberated" for use in the Freedom faction. This suit has been treated with "Sovereign", an anomalous compound invented by the faction through trial and error. As such, it provides reasonable protection against the Zone's hazards on top of being a good combat suit. Any Freedomer expected to help defend the Barrier will do their best to get their hands on this suit, or at least something like it.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="dolg_specops_red_outfit_name">
		<text>PS5-B2 veteran battlesuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_specops_red_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]This suit is a set of former Spetsnaz body armour, bolstered with more substantial protection for one's vital organs. An excellent combat bodysuit, although it has an infamous failure rate in areas of extreme anomalous activity. Despite this, Duty's veterans do not shun this suit, claiming you don't need much protection from anomalies once you know how to spot them.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>


<!-- PS5-M Universal protection suit -->
	<string id="dolg_outfit_name">
		<text>PS5-M universal protection</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]This old version of the Duty bodysuit is better suited for recruits who may prefer the familiarity of stalker suits over frontline battle armour. Unlike the PSZ series, the suit provides reasonable protection against anomalies while also being capable of stopping a pistol bullet.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="dolg_scout_outfit_name">
		<text>PS5-R scout vest</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_scout_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]An old Duty suit that was developed alongside the PS5-M universal protection outfit. This armour was intended to protect Duty scouts in the early days of the Zone's existence. These days, however, the only parts of the Zone left to be explored are far too dangerous for a light bodysuit like this. As such, these suits are mostly retired now, kept in reserve only to outfit Duty recruits in desperate circumstances.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="dolg_red_outfit_name">
		<text>PS5-M hunter suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_red_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A somewhat heavier variant of the PS5-M universal protection suit, specifically designed for Dutyers intending to hunt mutants. A small amount of ballistic protection is sacrificed in favour of much better protection against common mutant attacks, along with greater protection from the environments such mutants are likely to be found in. Compares well even to modern Duty suits.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="svoboda_heavy_outfit_2_name">
		<text>Sentinel of Freedom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="svoboda_heavy_outfit_2_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]An aged, slightly heavier stalker bodysuit made long ago by Freedom craftsmen. Although the suit has obviously acquired some wear and tear in places, it's roughly on par with most other basic stalker suits even today. Found semi-regularly on Freedom veterans. That said, younger Freedomers will pay through the nose to acquire one of these outfits, simply because of the amazing stories these venerable suits have acquired over the years.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="bandit_ps5_outfit_name">
		<text>Fenced PS5-M universal protection</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_ps5_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]Armour like this first entered circulation among Bandits thanks to Quartermaster Morgan, a corrupt supplier who formerly belonged to the Duty faction. Gives up some of its physical protection for greater comfort and defence against anomalies. These suits are a major sore point for the Duty faction, and getting them out of the hands of anarchists, criminals and murderers is an unspoken priority.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="greh_ps5_outfit_name">
		<text>Volos flak armour</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_ps5_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]This outfit's design is based on the PS5-M universal protection suit. It is unknown how this armour has come into the possession of Sin. Nevertheless, Duty would not be happy to know their armour designs are being appropriated by Zone-worshipping fanatics, and would likely make the recovery of these suits an unspoken priority. The suit itself is of good quality, and more than adequate for the Zone's conditions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	
<!-- Skat-9 Military Armoured Suits -->
	<string id="military_outfit_name">
		<text>Skat-9 armoured suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="military_merc_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary Skat-9 armoured suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="military_monolit_outfit_name">
		<text>Monolith Skat-9 armoured suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="military_freedom_outfit_name">
		<text>Liberated Skat-9 armoured suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="military_sky_outfit_name">
		<text>CS-4b armoured suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="military_bandit_outfit_name">
		<text>Looted Skat-9 armoured suit</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="military_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]An excellent protective suit for the Zone. This heavy military-grade armour is designed for major battle operations in anomalous areas. Comprises a PSZ-12p heavy military armoured suit, built-in compensation suit, and an anomalous protection bodysuit. The armour provides excellent protection against bullet and fragmentation damage, without greatly reducing the wearer’s mobility. Although originally intended for the sole use of Military stalkers and experienced Spetsnaz operators, this armour occasionally finds its way into factions outside of the Military through unknown means.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="dolg_heavy_outfit_name">
		<text>PSZ-9d body armour</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_heavy_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]Developed by defence research institutes in Kiev, the first iteration of this Duty bodysuit began as a simple old set of Spetsnaz PSZ-9 body armour, modified for the Zone. Its design has since been continuously improved over the years, yet curiously never took on a new designation. These days, this armour's latest design is capable of stopping a rifle bullet, and boasts great protection against the Zone's myriad horrors in general. The main drawbacks are - naturally - both its bulkiness and its price. It is uncommon for armour as prized as this to be issued to any Dutyer who hasn't proven themselves in some significant manner. \n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="dolg_pantsir_outfit_name">
		<text>PSZ-7p shell armour</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_pantsir_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]An "in-between" suit that is more protective than Duty's regular PS5 universal protection suit, yet cheaper and easier to produce than a proper set of PSZ-9d body armour. Ideal for skirmishes, it retains the ballistic and thermal protection of a full PSZ suit, but is otherwise inferior under most other circumstances. Still, its relative ease of maintenance and repair is a great boon to Dutyers far away from friendly territory, such as the investigators who venture up into Yanov or beyond. A great suit overall, although it has displayed a high failure rate against electrical accidents, thunderstorms, and poltergeist attacks.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="dolg_heavy_redline_outfit_name">
		<text>PSZ-9kl command armour</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_heavy_redline_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A variant of the PSZ armour series that sacrifices some anomaly protection for greatly increased safety against explosions and extreme blunt impacts. This suit was a favourite of the late Lieutenant Colonel Shulga, who rarely ventured outside his operational base in Yanov, yet constantly feared assassination at the hands of Freedom. Thus, heavy protection like this fitted his needs perfectly. As fate would have it, he'd instead later be presumed dead after leading a mass assault into Pripyat with his contingent of troops, never to be seen again. It's not uncommon for Duty sympathizers to claim his sacrifice bought the Zone precious time by slowing the Monolith's sudden resurgence, and veteran Dutyers will occasionally wear suits like this to battle in his honour.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>


<!-- Scientific outfits -->
	<string id="scientific_outfit_name">
		<text>SEVA bodysuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]This suit was designed and produced by one of Kiev's defence research institutes and represents an excellent alternative to hand-made stalker suits. It combines a CBRN jumpsuit with a specially-treated class II kevlar vest. Due to the quality materials used, this bodysuit sports good durability within ambient anomalous fields. Still, it is expensive, and not as effective as more modern armor or CBRN systems.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="svoboda_scientific_outfit_name">
		<text>Watchman of Freedom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="svoboda_scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]Produced by Freedom craftsmen especially for observing anomalous phenomena in the Zone. The specially-treated materials provide good protection and suit durability during prolongued exploration of anomalous fields. However, the built-in "Sentinel" body armour is ineffective at stopping medium to high-power cartridges.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="monolith_scientific_outfit_name">
		<text>Monolith scientific suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]The Monolith scientific suit includes a flak vest of unknown origin and also features unique modifications for greater resistance to radiation at the cost of being more vulnerable to psy-fields. The anomaly protection and suit durability otherwise match the standard SEVA bodysuit. Curiously, according to some legends, these suits are most often worn by the soldiers who defend the Brain Scorcher in Radar, although no one outside the Monolith faction can easily confirm.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="cs_scientific_outfit_name">
		<text>CS-4a SEVA suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cs_scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]An unofficial version of the SEVA scientific suit, fresh off the smuggling route. Typically used by exploratory groups of the Clear Sky faction. Offers good protection from radiation, but is otherwise of mediocre quality for a SEVA suit.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="cs_scientific_outfit_good_name">
		<text>CS-4a Pathfinder</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cs_scientific_outfit_good_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]An unofficial version of the SEVA scientific suit that has been extensively improved by Novikov, Clear Sky's resident technician. Aside from having great protection and durability within anomaly fields, it's also extremely comfortable to move around in. These qualities have made it a high-demand suit among Clear Sky and other factions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="bandit_scientific_outfit_name">
		<text>Looted SEVA suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]Bandits have never been terribly interested in the science and research of anomalous fields, but, nevertheless, they use protective suits such as these to organise ambushes and attacks on stalkers where they are not expected at all: in anomalous fields and radiation pockets. The suit has an external insulation coating, which provides good protection against all kinds of anomalous effects. Due to a lack of any protection from physical impacts, the suit is ideally used to ambush unsuspecting victims.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="isg_scientific_outfit_name">
		<text>UNISG SEVA suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="isg_scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]Originally commissioned by the first iteration of UNISG from one of Kiev's defence research institutes for research in the Zone. The special treatment materials provide enhanced protection and durability against radiation and anomalous effects. However, the built-in body armour is easily defeated by most bullet types.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="merc_scientific_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary SEVA suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A variant of the SEVA bodysuit that was commissioned by Mercenaries. Used by veteran Mercs on artefact-hunting contracts, this suit provides good anomaly protection for a SEVA. However, it lacks some of the more recent anti-psy-field upgrades.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="merc_combat_scientific_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary Pathfinder</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_combat_scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]As a token of goodwill (and to help cover their research costs), Clear Sky occasionally makes coveted "Pathfinder" suits on commission for use among the Zone's Mercenaries. Compared to the stock SEVA suit, this model is superior across the board. Compared to the original CS-4a Pathfinder, this suit sacrifices protection against chemical anomalies and radiation in exchange for a Class IIIA ballistic vest.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="dolg_scientific_outfit_name">
		<text>PS5-9Md universal scientific suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]The Duty faction version of the standard SEVA suit. Like the standard suit variant, it consists of a durable anomaly-resistant CBRN jumpsuit and a specially-treated Class II kevlar vest. A solid suit for extended dives into anomaly fields. \n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="dolg_scientific_red_outfit_name">
		<text>PS5-9Md light scientific suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_scientific_red_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A lighter variant of the Duty scientific suit that has shed almost half its weight at the cost of slightly decreased protection. The ballistic armor has been replaced by a class IIA vest with numerous pockets.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="dolg_scientific_wood_outfit_name">
		<text>PS5-9Md light Pathfinder</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_scientific_wood_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]As a token of goodwill (and to help cover their research costs), Clear Sky occasionally makes coveted "Pathfinder" suits on commission for use among the Duty faction. Altered according to Duty's needs, this suit has a few differences compared to the CS-4a pathfinder. Namely, its weight has been reduced by almost half at the expense of some of its protection. Despite this, it's an excellent and comfortable outfit for Duty's more curious members.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="bandit_scientific_dark_outfit_name">
		<text>Patchwork anomaly suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_scientific_dark_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A SEVA-like suit made virtually from scratch by one of the Bandits' gifted craftsmen. Compared to the looted SEVAs that are brought in and restored, this patchwork outfit boasts average protection against anomalies while retaining a surprisingly low weight. Additionally, it's rather stylish and comfy, which has allowed it to become a hit among the smooth criminals who can afford it.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="renegade_scientific_outfit_name">
		<text>Renegade SEVA suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="renegade_scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]This comfortable bodysuit, originally intended for research in the Zone, makes for a great alternative to the various Light Combat or hand-made suits one might have access to. Compared to a standard SEVA suit, it provides improved protection against thermal hazards and blunt trauma. However, its other protective qualities are inferior to the original SEVA.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="merc_scientific_armored_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary SEVA body armour</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_scientific_armored_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A variant of the SEVA bodysuit that was commissioned by Mercenaries. Some of its environmental protection systems were stripped down to accommodate Class IIIA plates. Used by veteran mercenaries who are expected to guide researchers and artefact hunters in the more dangerous parts of the Zone.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="monolith_scientific_light_outfit_name">
		<text>Monolith patchwork science suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_scientific_light_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A SEVA-like suit made virtually from scratch by an unknown craftsman. Compared to an ordinary Monolith scientific suit, this outfit is lighter and provides better protection from both chemical burns and radiation. However, its other qualities have suffered. It is unknown what role this suit fills within the Monolith faction as a whole, although it's been speculated that it's purpose is largely ceremonial.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ace_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary ACE scientific suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ace_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]One of the most technologically advanced bodysuits in the Zone. The ACE armor system incorporates a next-generation CBRN and a pocketed kevlar vest with Class III plate inserts. Using state of the art materials such as selectively-permeable coatings, this suit manages both maximal anomaly protection and wearer comfort. The suit is only used by the most wealthy and explorative Mercenaries, due to the comparatively low ballistic protection provided at its price point.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>


<!-- SSP-99 -->
	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_orange_name">
		<text>SSP-99 bodysuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_orange_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]The SSP-99 is a current-generation CBRN suit specially designed for the Zone conditions. It is used by scientific expeditions for extended forays into anomalous fields. When combined with the SSP-99 screen helmet, it includes an integrated air-filtering and air-conditioning system. The suit itself is thermally and electrically resistant and provides good protection from radiation and biological anomalies. Its design is specifically tailored for maximum durability in thermal, chemical, and electrical fields. However, it provides neither bullet nor splinter protection.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_grn_name">
		<text>SSP-99M bodysuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_grn_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]High quality modified SSP-99 suit. A kevlar underlayer has been added to the suit to reduce the risk of suit puncture from hostile mutants. It provides improved protection from biological anomalies compared to the SSP-99.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_white_name">
		<text>SSP-99 Diamond</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_white_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]The SSP-99 is a current-generation CBRN suit specially designed for the Zone conditions. It is used by scientific expeditions for extended forays into anomalous fields. When combined with the accompanying SSP-99 helmet, it includes an integrated air-filtering and air-conditioning system. The Diamond variant gives superior protection from electricity.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_blue_name">
		<text>SSP-99M Sapphire</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_blue_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]High quality modified SSP-99 suit. A kevlar underlayer has been added to the suit to reduce the risk of suit puncture from hostile mutants. The Sapphire model provides excellent protection against short-range psi-emissions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_red_name">
		<text>SSP-99Ì Ruby</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_red_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]High quality modified SSP-99 suit. A kevlar underlayer has been added to the suit to reduce the risk of suit puncture from hostile mutants. The ‘Ruby’ model provides improved protection against melee attacks, and includes an integrated wound healing system.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_yello_name">
		<text>SSP-99 Topaz</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_yello_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]The SSP-99 is a current-generation CBRN suit specially designed for the Zone conditions. It is used by scientific expeditions for extended forays into anomalous fields. When combined with the accompanying SSP-99 helmet, it includes an integrated air-filtering and air-conditioning system. The Topaz variant provides increased protection from radiation.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>


<!-- Heavy combat suits -->
	<string id="exolight_outfit_name">
		<text>Exosuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="exolight_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel. It also includes many of the attach points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. Additionally, it is only useful in melee and ranged fights, since it offers no anomaly protection whatsoever.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="dolg_exolight_outfit_name">
		<text>PSZ-10d Duty battlesuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_exolight_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel. It also includes many of the attach points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. Additionally, it is only useful in melee and ranged fights, since it offers no anomaly protection whatsoever. This suit is typically found in the hands of elite Duty warriors, especially those assigned to guard VIPs or launch exceedingly dangerous raids on enemy STALKERs.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="svoboda_exolight_outfit_name">
		<text>Warrior of Freedom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="svoboda_exolight_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel. It also includes many of the attach points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. Additionally, it is only useful in melee and ranged fights, since it offers no anomaly protection whatsoever. Only the most respected members of Freedom will ever be found wearing a suit like this, and even then only when attacking enemy personnel.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="merc_exolight_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary exosuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_exolight_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel. It also includes many of the attach points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. Additionally, it is only useful in melee and ranged fights, since it offers no anomaly protection whatsoever. An outfit of choice for the captains and bodyguards of Mercenary companies requiring top of the line ballistic protection.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="bandit_exolight_outfit_name">
		<text>Looted exosuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_exolight_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel. It also includes many of the attach points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. Additionally, it is only useful in melee and ranged fights, since it offers no anomaly protection whatsoever. This makes it a wonderful suit for conducting raids on other STALKERs. Both imposing and highly intimidating in appearance, this outfit is a favourite among the Zone's most powerful outlaws.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="monolith_exolight_outfit_name">
		<text>Monolith exosuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_exolight_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel. It also includes many of the attach points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. Additionally, it is only useful in melee and ranged fights, since it offers no anomaly protection whatsoever. A favourite among the Monolith's battle preachers and tactical masters, who claim the confines of the suit to be as comforting as the Sarcophagus itself.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="military_exolight_outfit_name">
		<text>Military stalker exosuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="military_exolight_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel. It also includes many of the attach points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. Additionally, it is only useful in melee and ranged fights, since it offers no anomaly protection whatsoever. Considered too cumbersome by the Ukrainian government, these suits are never issued to any unit or individual. Thus soldiers - most often Military stalkers and the occasional old veterans - must always find and pay for it through their own means.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="cs_exolight_outfit_name">
		<text>CS-5 exosuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cs_exolight_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel. It also includes many of the attach points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. Additionally, it is only useful in melee and ranged fights, since it offers no anomaly protection whatsoever. These outfits are smuggled in from Ukrainian factories near the borders of the Zone.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="isg_exolight_outfit_name">
		<text>UNISG exosuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="isg_exolight_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel. It also includes many of the attach points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. Additionally, it is only useful in melee and ranged fights, since it offers no anomaly protection whatsoever. A rare sight, since most ISG operatives prefer increased mobility over raw protective power.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="exo_wood_outfit_name">
		<text>Woodland exosuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="exo_wood_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel. It also includes many of the attach points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. This model includes an early-generation CBRN jumpsuit lined with kevlar.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="bandit_exo_earth_outfit_name">
		<text>Fenced exosuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_exo_earth_outfit_description">
		<text>NOT IN GAME. The "underwear" of an exoskeleton, sometimes mistakenly known as the "Radsuit". This outfit provides almost all the protection one can expect from a full exoskeleton, but due to being stripped of its servos and batteries, it provides none of the strength enhancement. On the positive side, this means the suit is now easier to maintain and, unlike a full exoskeleton, does not prevent the wearer from sprinting. Consists of an integrated tactical helmet, a heavy armoured vest and a reinforced environmental jumpsuit.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="freedom_exo_vineleaf_outfit_name">
		<text>Hero of Freedom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_exo_vineleaf_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel. It also includes many of the attach points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. This variant includes an old CBRN jumpsuit lined with kevlar and an additional attachment slot.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="exo_dolg_outfit_name">
		<text>PSZ-10d Duty battlesuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="exo_dolg_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel. It also includes many of the attach points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. Additionally, it is only useful in melee and ranged fights, since it offers no anomaly protection whatsoever. This suit is typically found in the hands of elite Duty warriors, especially those assigned to guard VIPs or launch exceedingly dangerous raids.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="exo_dolg_red_outfit_name">
		<text>PSZ-10d Venator battlesuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="exo_dolg_red_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel. It also includes many of the attach points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. Additionally, it is only useful in melee and ranged fights, since it offers no anomaly protection whatsoever. This particular variant is typically found in the hands of elite Duty huntsmen, where its greater defense against mutants is utilized.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="exo_dolg_wood_outfit_name">
		<text>PSZ-10l forest battlesuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="exo_dolg_wood_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel. It also includes many of the attach points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. This variant includes an older CBRN jumpsuit with kevlar weave and additional steel reinforcement. Typically found with elite Duty members, particularly those conducting short operations in northern reaches of the Zone.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="exo_dolg_urban_outfit_name">
		<text>PSZ-10g urban battlesuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="exo_dolg_urban_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel. It also includes many of the attach points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. Additionally, it is only useful in melee and ranged fights, since it offers no anomaly protection whatsoever. Old and exceedingly heavy, it's possible that suits like this were used by the Duty faction to raid Pripyat and clash with Freedom back in 2012.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="exo_merc_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary heavy armour TB-1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="exo_merc_outfit_description">
		<text>NOT IN GAME. This heavy armoured suit, known as the TB-1, possesses a high physical protection comparing to the original heavy armours. For all other parameters it’s identical to exoskeleton, except for a slightly less ballistic and rupture protection. Composed of three elements; a tactical helmet, a heavy armoured vest and reinforced jumpsuit. Used by expert Mercenaries on missions in the north, for taking down elite squads of the Monolith. It bears a standard merc dark blue camouflage pattern, suitable for operations in urban environment (or anywhere else, but only at nighttime). \n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="exo_merc_urban_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary urban exosuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="exo_merc_urban_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel. It also includes many of the attach points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. Additionally, it is only useful in melee and ranged fights, since it offers no anomaly protection whatsoever. An outfit of choice for the captains and bodyguards of Mercenary companies operating in areas like Limansk or Pripyat.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="exo_merc_wood_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary woodland exosuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="exo_merc_wood_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel. It also includes many of the attach points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. This variant includes an old CBRN that, unfortunately, has not been modified for the Zone.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="exo_merc_grass_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary grassland exosuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="exo_merc_grass_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel. It also includes many of the attach points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. This variant includes an asbestos-weave jumpsuit, which the wearer dons at their own risk.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>


<!-- Proptotype Exoskeleton -->
	<string id="stalker_proto_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>"Sunrise" proto-exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_proto_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A stalker bodysuit, specially designed to be fitted with the servos and batteries of an exoskeleton, allowing the wearer to carry significantly more equipment than they could under any other circumstances, but lacking the armour of a proper exosuit. Compared to a full exoskeleton, it provides less protection, but is also considerably lighter.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="svoboda_light_proto_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>Wind of Freedom proto-exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="svoboda_light_proto_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A Wind of Freedom suit that has been specially modified to fit with the servos and batteries of an exoskeleton, allowing the wearer to carry significantly more equipment than they could under any other circumstances, but lacking the armour of a proper exosuit. Compared to a full exoskeleton, it provides less protection, but is also considerably lighter.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="dolg_proto_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>PS5-M proto-exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_proto_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A PS5-M universal protection suit that has been specially modified to fit with the servos and batteries of an exoskeleton, allowing the wearer to carry significantly more equipment than they could under any other circumstances, but lacking the armour of a proper exosuit. Compared to a full exoskeleton, it provides less protection, but is also considerably lighter.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="dolg_heavy_proto_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>PSZ-9d proto-exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_heavy_proto_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A PSZ-9d armoured suit that has been specially modified to fit with the servos and batteries of an exoskeleton, allowing the wearer to carry significantly more equipment than they could under any other circumstances. Compared to a full exoskeleton, it sacrifices raw ballistic protection for greater functionality in anomaly fields.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="military_proto_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>Skat-9 proto-exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="military_proto_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]The very first iteration of the military exoskeleton was this Skat-9 armoured suit modified to fit with the servos and batteries of an exoskeleton. Compared to a third-generation exoskeleton, it sacrifices raw ballistic protection for greater functionality in anomaly fields.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="monolith_proto_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>X-18 proto-exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_proto_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]An armour made by either Monolithians or an unknown manufacturer. It has been specially modified to fit with the servos and batteries of an exoskeleton, allowing the wearer to carry significantly more equipment than they could under any other circumstances, but lacking the armour of a proper exosuit. Compared to a full exoskeleton, it provides less protection, but is also considerably lighter.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="cs_stalker_proto_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>CS-2b proto-exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cs_stalker_proto_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A set of CS-2b body armour that has been specially modified to fit with the servos and batteries of an exoskeleton, allowing the wearer to carry significantly more equipment than they could under any other circumstances, but lacking the armour of a proper exosuit. Compared to a full exoskeleton, it provides less protection, but is also considerably lighter.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ecolog_proto_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>SSP-99M proto-exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecolog_proto_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A unique armor system composed of an exoskeleton-powered SSP-99M jumpsuit with an anomaly-resistant Class IIA kevlar vest placed on top. The durable exo-frames are capable of providing mechanical support for carrying heavy loads even through anomaly fields, making it ideal for aiding researchers during deep incursions into the Zone.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="isg_proto_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>UNISG tactical proto-exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="isg_proto_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A UN-branded special tactical suit that has been specially modified to fit with the servos and batteries of an exoskeleton, allowing the wearer to carry significantly more equipment than they could under any other circumstances, but lacking the armour of a proper exosuit. Compared to a full exoskeleton, it provides less protection, but is also considerably lighter.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	
<!-- Exoskeletons -->
	<string id="exo_outfit_name">
		<text>Exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="exo_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]An experimental sample of a military exoskeleton. Was never mass-produced due to extraordinary cost and some design flaws. Despite this, it is in demand due to its ability to take on the weight of all carried equipment, and therefore small batches are made in underground facilities outside Ukraine. Consists of a steel-reinforced kevlar jumpsuit and a tactical vest with Class IV inserts, all carried by powered limbs and servomotors.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="dolg_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>PSZ-10d exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]Excellent high-tech armor. Domestically developed by one of the research institutes, specifically for the Duty faction. That said, this armour is slowly being phased out in favour of cheaper, more practical suits, and the few exosuits in active service tend to be in the hands of Duty's oldest veterans. Consists of a steel-reinforced kevlar jumpsuit and a tactical vest with Class IV inserts, all carried by powered limbs and servomotors.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="svoboda_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>Paragon of Freedom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="svoboda_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]Produced by Freedom’s finest artisans. Experimenting with different modifications, after numerous attempts they managed to create a really successful design. While not always the most practical suit to maintain, it is undeniably powerful, and as such is entrusted only to Freedom's finest warriors and guardsmen. Consists of a steel-reinforced kevlar jumpsuit and a tactical vest with Class IV inserts, all carried by powered limbs and servomotors.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="merc_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]An experimental sample of a military exoskeleton of western production for equipping Mercenaries and other armed groups. While not always the most practical suit to maintain in the Zone, it simultaneously allows the wearer to be both heavily armed and extremely well armoured, with enough strength to carry weeks worth of supplies. Most often worn as a morale booster and highly protective utility suit by veteran Mercenary captains expected to lead their men through hellish conditions. Consists of a steel-reinforced kevlar jumpsuit and a tactical vest with Class IV inserts, all carried by powered limbs and servomotors.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="monolith_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>Monolith exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]High-tech armor, made on the basis of a military exoskeleton. However, study samples have revealed that its servos are made of alloys and materials unknown to any field of science in any other part of the world. Consists of a steel-reinforced kevlar jumpsuit and a tactical vest with Class IV inserts, all carried by powered limbs and servomotors. Wearing this suit feels like being buried under the concrete of the Sarcophagus itself - terrifyingly claustrophobic for most stalkers, but eerily comforting for true servants of the Monolith. \n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="bandit_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>Heisted exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A stolen military exoskeleton customised by outlaws to attack well-guarded facilities and to plunder well-armed stalkers. More martially inclined aspiring Bandit Lords tend to favour this armour, using it as a stark and unquestionable symbol of their strength and authority over lesser criminals. After all, for one to keep wearing such a coveted suit among murderers and thieves, one must by necessity possess great strength and cunning.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="military_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>Military stalker exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="military_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]The official version of a military exoskeleton. Released in limited quantities by special order to the Military Stalkers, who must pay for it themselves. Designed to carry heavy weapons like grenade launchers and machine guns, along with enough ammunition, food and meds to keep the unit supplied for long periods of time. Occasionally fielded in lieu of light vehicles.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="cs_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>CS-5 exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cs_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]An experimental version of the army exoskeleton smuggled into the Zone from Ukrainian factories before being refurbished by Clear Sky technicians. Generally, suits like these are held in reserve, to be deployed only in times of true crisis. That said, especially trusted comrades and associates of the faction may eventually receive permission to acquire such a suit for their own personal uses, although  not without great cost.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ecolog_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>Scientific exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecolog_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]An official version of the military exoskeleton, intended for use by the Ecologists' guards. The suit feels almost impervious to small arms, and its advanced servomotors make it an excellent choice for those in entrenched defensive positions, as it greatly aids in the use of heavy defensive weaponry. When out in the field, wearers of this suit are more commonly used to carrying the ludicrous amount of batteries, LLMCs, AAMs and other supplies an accompanying scientist might need when exploring the Zone.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="renegade_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>Renegade exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="renegade_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]One of a few exoskeletons assembled by the Renegades back in 2011 to help secure their final push into Clear Sky's base. Unfortunately, they were virtually wiped out before their final victory ever came, thanks to the interference of a Mercenary with a trenchcoat and a marksman rifle. Modern Renegades who wear this armour always go into battle like a man possessed, eager to mete vengeance upon their most hated foes. That is to say, almost everyone else.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="isg_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>UNISG exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="isg_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]The official version of the UNISG exoskeleton. Released in limited quantities by special order of the United Nations. While it still possesses many of the design flaws of other exoskeletons, it's nonetheless seen as a great alternative to light command and scout vehicles, which would have great trouble navigating the Zone anyways, and thus is deployed in their stead.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="greh_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>Vyraj power armour</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]High-tech armor, based on the original experimental military designs. However, as far as anyone can see, its servos are made of alloys and materials unknown to any field of science in any other part of the world. Consists of a steel-reinforced kevlar jumpsuit and a tactical vest with Class IV inserts, all carried by powered limbs and servomotors. Wearing this suit creates an unnatural feeling of bliss and calm within the wearer, although whether this sense of security is genuine or not remains to be seen.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>


<!-- Nosorog exskeletal armour -->
	<string id="dolg_nosorog_outfit_name">
		<text>PSZ-10d Nosorog</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_nosorog_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary Nosorog</text>
	</string>
	<string id="army_nosorog_outfit_name">
		<text>Military stalker Nosorog</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_nosorog_outfit_name">
		<text>Monolith Nosorog</text>
	</string>
	<string id="isg_nosorog_outfit_name">
		<text>UNISG Nosorog</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="nosorog_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A next generation exoskeleton, consisting of a doubly reinforced exosuit. Rumoured to have been the brainchild of a now deceased stalker named "Fang", whose designs were later claimed by all sorts of powerful factions across the Zone. If regular exoskeletons allow stalkers to feel like a light vehicle, the Nosorog almost makes them believe they're a main battle tank, able to withstand incredible punishment while carrying tremendous ordnance. Typically only available to a faction's most valuable members, and even then only during exceptionally dangerous missions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="freedom_nosorog_outfit_name">
		<text>Champion of Freedom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_nosorog_outfit_desc">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]A next generation exoskeleton, consisting of a doubly reinforced exosuit. Rumoured to have been the brainchild of a now deceased stalker named "Fang", whose designs were later claimed by all sorts of powerful factions across the Zone. If regular exoskeletons allow stalkers to feel like a light vehicle, the Champion of Freedom almost makes them believe they're a main battle tank, able to withstand incredible punishment while carrying tremendous ordnance. Typically only available to a faction's most valuable members, and even then only during exceptionally dangerous missions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>


<!-- No group -->	
	<string id="ghillie_outfit_name">
		<text>Ghillie suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ghillie_outfit_description">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]This suit is designed to simulate a ‘heap of foliage.’ Usually this type of suit is worn by snipers and hunters to blend in with the environment and hide themselves from enemies. Ghillie suits are commercially produced, but usually both military personnel and civilians customise and improve them to suit their needs. Despite its high efficiency, it can be very impractical: even in a temperate climate, it becomes hot over time and is very heavy.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

</string_table>
