<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<!--
	Repair Kits
-->

<string_table>
	<string id="st_cleaning_kit_p_new">
		<text>Type A Weapon Cleaning Kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_cleaning_kit_p_new_descr">
		<text>A set of specialized brushes which can be used to clean the barrel and other parts of a firearm from dirt, sand, moisture, lubricant residues and other foreign materials that have accumulated during use. Such sets are quite commonly used in the Zone in order to keep firearms in a good shape at all times. It is possible to utilize common tools to have a better access to inner mechanisms of a gun or alcohol to more easily dissolve oil residue. Can also be used to better spread gun oil, however a more cost-efficient method used by most experienced stalkers entails the application of animal fat on the brushes as an alternative lubricant. This particular set fits typical handgun calibers.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_orange] • Can be used to clean dirty parts within guns. (above 60 condition)\n
		Right-click a gun > maintain parts > clean part.\n
		%c[0,255,255,255]COMPATIBILITY:\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] Mainly for small caliber weapons\n
		</text>
	</string>
    
	<string id="st_cleaning_kit_s_new">
		<text>Type B Weapon Cleaning Kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_cleaning_kit_s_new_descr">
		<text>A set of specialized brushes which can be used to clean the barrel and other parts of a firearm from dirt, sand, moisture, lubricant residues and other foreign materials that have accumulated during use. It is possible to utilize common tools to have a better access to inner mechanisms of a gun or alcohol to more easily dissolve oil residue. This particular set is suitable for use in hunting weapons and historic weapons, like bolt-action rifles and most manually operated shotguns. "Aurora" kit comes with three specialized brush types, one for respectively after-fire cleaning, lubricant spreading and rust removal. Keeps your favorite shooter in a good shape at all times.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_orange] • Can be used to clean dirty parts within guns. (above 60 condition)\n
		Right-click a gun > maintain parts > clean part.\n
		%c[0,255,255,255]COMPATIBILITY:\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] Mainly for simple medium caliber and shotgun weapons\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_cleaning_kit_r5_new">
		<text>Type C Weapon Cleaning Kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_cleaning_kit_r5_new_descr">
		<text>A set of specialized brushes which can be used to clean the barrel and other parts of a firearm from dirt, sand, moisture, lubricant residues and other foreign materials that have accumulated during use. Such sets are quite commonly used in the Zone in order to keep firearms in a good shape at all times. It is possible to utilize common tools to have a better access to inner mechanisms of a gun or alcohol to more easily dissolve oil residue. Can also be used to better spread gun oil, however a more cost-efficient method used by most experienced stalkers entails the application of animal fat on the brushes as an alternative lubricant. This particular pack is standard issue with the Ukrainian Armed Forces and comes in a hard plastic reusable container.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] Can be used to clean dirty parts (above 60 condition) within guns. Right-click a gun > maintain parts > clean the desired part.\n
		%c[0,255,255,255]COMPATIBILITY:\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] Mainly for standard issue military weapons\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_cleaning_kit_r7_new">
		<text>Type D Weapon Cleaning Kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_cleaning_kit_r7_new_descr">
		<text>A set of specialized brushes which can be used to clean the barrel and other parts of a firearm from dirt, sand, moisture, lubricant residues and other foreign materials that have accumulated during use. Such sets are quite commonly used in the Zone in order to keep firearms in a good shape at all times. It is possible to utilize common tools to have a better access to inner mechanisms of a gun or alcohol to more easily dissolve oil residue. Can also be used to better spread gun oil, however a more cost-efficient method used by most experienced stalkers entails the application of animal fat on the brushes as an alternative lubricant. This particular set has certain deep-penetrating solvents and specially shaped brushes that allow a user to clean very internally complicated weapons, as well as clean precision rifles without affecting their accuracy. Manufacturer unknown, but its simple design and construction as well as very high quality materials used suggest a military, presumably special forces origin.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] Can be used to clean dirty parts (above 60 condition) within guns. Right-click a gun > maintain parts > clean the desired part.\n
		%c[0,255,255,255]COMPATIBILITY:\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] Mainly for large caliber and/or complex weapons\n
		</text>
	</string>

    <string id="st_toolkit_p_new">
        <text>Type A Weapon Repair Kit</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_toolkit_p_new_descr">
        <text>This kit contains oils, solvents, basic cleaning equipment and specialized tools used for disassembly and maintenance of mechanisms of weapons. It also by standard comes with set of elementary firearm spare parts. The kit is quite heavy, but is irreplaceable when venturing deep into the Zone as it can be used in life-or-death situations to make a firearm usable again. Due to differences in weapon construction this particular set can only be used for disassembly and repair of weapons with handgun calibers. It's also possible to additionally increase the effectiveness of the kit by borrowing certain materials from or combining with other kits during a single maintenance session.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] Can be used to replace parts within a gun. Right-click a gun > maintain parts > replace the desired part.\n
        %c[0,255,255,255]COMPATIBILITY:\n
        %c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] Mainly for small caliber weapons\n
        </text>
    </string>

    <string id="st_toolkit_s_new">
        <text>Type B Weapon Repair Kit</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_toolkit_s_new_descr">
        <text>This kit contains oils, solvents, basic cleaning equipment and specialized tools used for disassembly and maintenance of mechanisms of weapons. It also by standard comes with set of elementary firearm spare parts. The kit is quite heavy, but is irreplaceable when venturing deep into the Zone as it can be used in life-or-death situations to make a firearm usable again. This is a fairly common kit with tools and components suitable for most shotguns and historic Great War weaponry. These types of kits can be commonly found in hunters and gunsmiths who come to the Zone to ply their trade. It's also possible to additionally increase the effectiveness of the kit by borrowing certain materials from or combining with other kits during single maintenance session.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] Can be used to replace parts within a gun. Right-click a gun > maintain parts > replace the desired part.\n
        %c[0,255,255,255]COMPATIBILITY:\n
        %c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] Mainly for simple medium caliber and shotgun weapons\n
        </text>
    </string>

    <string id="st_toolkit_r5_new">
        <text>Type C Weapon Repair Kit</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_toolkit_r5_new_descr">
        <text>This kit contains oils, solvents, basic cleaning equipment and specialized tools used for disassembly and maintenance of mechanisms of weapons. It also by standard comes with set of elementary firearm spare parts. The kit is quite heavy, but is irreplaceable when venturing deep into the Zone as it can be used in life-or-death situations to make a firearm usable again. These are standard Ukrainian army quartermaster repair kits used to maintain their standard-issue weapons - Duty maintains a trade deal with the military for these kits, but usually an unscrupulous soldier here and there is willing to trade one of these for an artifact or a case of vodka. It's also possible to additionally increase the effectiveness of the kit by borrowing certain materials from or combining with other kits during single maintenance session.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] Can be used to replace parts within a gun. Right-click a gun > maintain parts > replace the desired part.\n
		%c[0,255,255,255]COMPATIBILITY:\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] Mainly for standard issue military weapons\n
        </text>
    </string>

    <string id="st_toolkit_r7_new">
        <text>Type D Weapon Repair Kit</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_toolkit_r7_new_descr">
        <text>This kit contains oils, solvents, basic cleaning equipment and specialized tools used for disassembly and maintenance of mechanisms of weapons. It also by standard comes with set of elementary firearm spare parts. The kit is quite heavy, but is irreplaceable when venturing deep into the Zone as it can be used in life-or-death situations to make a firearm usable again. This is a specialized set used to maintain high-precision weapons like sniper rifles and battle rifles, as well as some weapons with complex internal mechanisms like light machine guns and some assault rifles. Such kits are quite rare, and are usually found in limited supply among even the most well-armed factions of the Zone. It's also possible to additionally increase the effectiveness of the kit by borrowing certain materials from or combining with other kits during single maintenance session.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] Can be used to replace parts within a gun.\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] Right-click a gun > maintain parts > replace the desired part.\n
		%c[0,255,255,255]COMPATIBILITY:\n
        %c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] Mainly for large caliber and/or complex weapons\n
        </text>
    </string>
</string_table>