<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<!--
	Weapons
-->

<string_table>

	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_classic">
		<text>Colt M1911 "Classic"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_classic_s">
		<text>Colt M1911</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_classic_descr">
		<text>This is the original Colt 1911, made by John Moses Browning in 1910 and patented the next year, hence the 1911 designation. Coming to service in 1913, this is considered to be the very first self-loading handgun that is vastly successful, being able to use the .45 ACP and shoot at least 1000 rounds flawlessly. You can tell it's a classic 1911 and not an 1911A1 by the fact it has a smaller ejection port, longer trigger and especially the diamond-shaped grip, also its only magazine of 7, keep it with you. Thanks to the black market going on in The Zone, this true classic has been acquired, though it might have been modified a bit, good luck figuring that out. If you want accuracy using a strong caliber without too much recoil, this might be for you, but it's best used as a backup gun if anything, since it has no way to have a suppressor.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911a1">
		<text>Colt M1911A1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911a1_descr">
		<text>An improvement of the 1911, after criticism from World War I and outside of it too, reissued to the U.S. Military in 1924. One major issue that the 1911 had was the hammer, since the guard was made too small, there was a high chance of getting a "hammer bite". For that, a longer "beaver tail" has been made. Also, the safety grip has been changed to be more ergonomic, it has a cutout near the frame to help with different hand shapes, a smaller trigger for less force application, wider ironsights and simplified checkered grips. All these changes, some are controversial like the new safety grip and the trigger, but the hammer guard and ironsights are a big improvement. You simply can't go wrong with this pistol, though some still prefer the original 1911 and find their own ways to avoid the flaws on those, such as gripping it one-handed to avoid hammer bites.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_tokarev">
		<text>Russian Contract Colt M1911</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_tokarev_descr">
		<text>A "Russian version" of the 1911. The only difference here would be that it has different markings, but this seems to be an old variant where it has no Cyrillic stamp indicating it's the version ordered from USA to Russia. It is identical to the 1911, but one key and important difference is the fact the magazine and barrel is slightly modified, which in turn can be further modified easily by any technician to change the caliber from .45 ACP to 7.62x25mm Tokarev.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_up_add_colttokarev_name">
		<text>Change of calibre to 7.62x25</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_up_add_colt695_name">
		<text>Change of calibre to 9x19</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_sw645">
		<text>Smith &amp; Wesson 645</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sw645_descr">
		<text>The Smith &amp; Wesson Model 645 is a .45 ACP compact pistol manufactured in 1985 and discontinued in 1988, despite so, a lot of folks from the black market are able to obtain it, let alone even make some illegaly even. The S&amp;W 645 is constructed almost entirely from stainless steel and is thus extremely resistant to harsh weather conditions. Since it's very easy to do so, any technician can change the caliber to 9x19, turning it into a S&amp;W Model 659. Overall, good backup pistol if you need less weight and better close quarter combat. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] .45 ACP suppressor</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_m45">
		<text>Colt M45</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m45_descr">
		<text>A modern variant of the M1911, this is the standard-issue side arm for the Force Recon Element of the United States Marine Corps' Marine Expeditionary Units since 1985. This idea of a better 1911 came in the late 1980s, from the USMC Colonel, Robert Young. It is pretty much an M1911A1 assembled by many manufacturers, since it has the slide from Springfield Armory, Mag Extract &amp; Release from Wilson Combat and everything else from Nowlin Manufacturing. The results, while sounding like "Frankenstein Monster" of a description, actually does make a pretty pistol that is better than the 1911. The Mercenaries favour it much so for the fact it's heavily customizable, the betterments are just bonuses.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] .45 ACP suppressor</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_m45a1">
		<text>Colt M45A1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m45a1_descr">
		<text>A modern variant of the M1911 and an improvement of the M45, this is the standard-issue side arm for the Force Recon Element of the United States Marine Corps' Marine Expeditionary Units since 1985. Compared to the M45, the improvements the M45A1 has is the dual recoil spring system that spreads out the recoil force of the .45 ACP round by lowering the peak force of the recoil pulse, the 3-dot red tritium night sights, a 5-inch national match barrel, ambidextrous safety, picatinny rail for the frame and a desert tan Cerakote finish. You wonder how the desert tan Ceratoke finish even fits in The Zone, but it might be a Mercenary's pride. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] .45 ACP suppressor</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_svi">
		<text>Strayer Voigt Infinity</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_svi_s">
		<text>SVI 2011</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_svi_descr">
		<text>Strayer-Voigt Inc. is a manufacturer of M1911-styled modular pistols, this especially includes the Strayer-Voigt Infinity itself, SVI for short. It is a pistol marketed for competition, so it is rather expensive and rare as it's not available for any army or average arms-bearing citizen. How did this even get in The Zone? No doubt from those flamboyant American mercenaries. The pistol itself has the massive benefit of having its own trademark Strayer-Voigt magazine, which holds 15 rounds. It has also been modified in-house to shoot in 3-burst at a fast rate. Oh and, if none of that makes you happy, the tritium optic fiber will, since it's blue. However, don't expect the same good ol' reliability as the classic 1911. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] .45 ACP suppressor</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_coonan357">
		<text>Coonan .357 Magnum Compact</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_coonan357_s">
		<text>Coonan .357</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_coonan357_descr">
		<text>The Coonan .357 Magnum is a peculiar semi-auto gun that uses .357 Magnum done through the chassis of a Colt 1911. This is done by changing the barrel, slide, handle and magazine to accommodate the caliber change. By the looks of it, this came through the Zone thanks to...Some sinister group, how they have acquired it is a mystery, but by the looks of how unkempt, contrasted and slightly broken the gun looks, it could even be an illegal clone of the original Coonan. Sadly, the weapon isn't exactly the best when it comes to accuracy, but the recoil is tolerable (as long as you don't rapid-fire) and the handling is great, one main benefit of using this instead of some other .357 pistols like the Desert Eagle is the conceal carry, weight and better Close Quarters Combat.</text>
	</string>

</string_table>
