<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<!--
	Weapons
-->

<string_table>

	<string id="st_wpn_streetsweeper">
		<text>Armsel Protecta</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_streetsweeper_aim">
		<text>Armsel Protecta</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_streetsweeper_nimble">
		<text>Armsel Protecta Custom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_streetsweeper_descr">
		<text>The unique rotating cylinder-fed 12-gauge shotgun, developed for riot control and combat, is a force to be reckoned with in close-quarters mayhem. With its distinctive drum magazine, rapid-fire capabilities, and devastating spread, it's the go-to choice for those who prefer swift and powerful confrontations on the urban battlefield.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_streetsweeper_aim_descr">
		<text>The unique rotating cylinder-fed 12-gauge shotgun, developed for riot control and combat, is a force to be reckoned with in close-quarters mayhem. With its distinctive drum magazine, rapid-fire capabilities, and devastating spread, it's the go-to choice for those who prefer swift and powerful confrontations on the urban battlefield. This variant is highly modernised, details inside are tightly fit to each other, muzzle energy is increased significantly thanks to higher pressure in the gun barrel. Sacrificing rate of fire, stopping power is increased. This model has Aimpoint AB collimator sight made by Swedish company.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]ATTACHMENTS: \n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] "Aimpoint" sight (integrated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_streetsweeper_nimble_descr">
		<text>The unique rotating cylinder-fed 12-gauge shotgun, developed for riot control and combat, is a force to be reckoned with in close-quarters mayhem. With its distinctive drum magazine, rapid-fire capabilities, and devastating spread, it's the go-to choice for those who prefer swift and powerful confrontations on the urban battlefield. According to certain sources, this model once belonged to Tank, but little is known about him.</text>
	</string>


</string_table>