<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>

<string_table>

	<string id="encyclopedia_gamma">
		<text>G.A.M.M.A. Manual</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_gamma_text">
		<text>%c[pda_blue]G.A.M.M.A. Manual.%c[ui_gray_1]</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_gamma_aaintro">
		<text>--- Welcome to G.A.M.M.A. ---</text>
	</string>
	<string id="article_gamma_aaintro_text">
		<text>
			%c[pda_white]Welcome to G.A.M.M.A \n \n %c[ui_gray_1]

			\n%c[pda_blue]G.A.M.M.A. stands for Grok's Automated Modular Modpack for Anomaly.%c[ui_gray_1]
			\n
			\n \n%c[pda_green]This modpack also features its own new modular set of add-ons including:%c[ui_gray_1]
			\n  A new UI
			\n - A rebalanced survival experience focused on crafting, repairing and cooking.
			\n - A sense of progression during your playthrough thanks to small and global changes of most systems and gameplay loops.
			\n - Rebalanced damages systems for the player and NPCs.
			\n - Rebalanced guns ballistics and melee system damages.
			\n - Overhauled radiations effects and dynamic radiation areas.
			\n - Many fixes for some major addons including the Boomsticks and Sharpsticks gunpack.
			\n - A new economy where traders will only sell you supplies, and where good ammunition will only be available to trustful stalkers.
			\n - New starting loadouts focused on providing pistols, SMGs or WW2 guns to have a smoother start with calibers for which you can buy ammo. It also gives you the basic tools to wander the Zone, which is nice for Ironman runs.
			\n - And so much more!

		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_gamma_progress">
		<text>Progression</text>
	</string>
	<string id="article_gamma_progress_text">
		<text>
			%c[pda_white]How To Progress \n \n %c[ui_gray_1]
			\n In summary, the basics of G.A.M.M.A. progression are as follows:
			\n - Perform tasks, kill mutants, collect their parts, keep these parts to accomplish stalkers tasks. 
			\n - Collect stashes coordinates, visit those stashes (white or green icons on the PDA map), to get nice loot and toolkits.
			\n - Use the acquired toolkits to craft repair kits for guns and armors you found to improve your gear and chance of survival.
			\n -  By completing tasks, earn goodwill for different factions to buy better supplies, including better ammo for your shiny new guns.
		</text>
	</string>



	<string id="article_gamma_healing">
		<text>Healing and Medicines</text>
	</string>
	<string id="article_gamma_healing_text">
		<text>
			%c[pda_white]Healing and Medicines \n \n %c[ui_gray_1]
			\n -  Use basic healing items like medkits or bandages to heal your main health; This heals your limbs temporarily (yellow HP).
			\n -  To convert the temporary HP (yellow) to permanent HP (white) for your limbs, use post heal items such as Ibuprofen, Fentanyl, Antidot or Yadulin.
			\n -  Any medicines with white dots in their description will heal the temporary HP for that limb or area. Such healing items have a white heart icon.
			\n -  Post-healing will give you side effects such as extreme hunger or dizziness. Dizziness can be cured using stamina boosting medicine or water.
			\n -  Keep in mind that damage resistance injectors work (indicated by a shield icon).
			\n - 	You don't need every medical item to heal your body. Mark the most important ones as favorite for an easy access.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_gamma_crafting">
		<text>Crafting</text>
	</string>
	<string id="article_gamma_crafting_text">
		<text>
			%c[pda_white]Crafting \n \n %c[ui_gray_1]
			\n -  Crafting is based on toolkits that you will find in marked stashes.
			\n -  Right click any toolkit to open a portable workbench to start crafting and repairing or upgrading your gear.
			\n -  There are 6 types of toolkits: Basic, Advanced, Expert, Medical, Gunsmith and the Artefact Melter.
			\n -  Almost all recipes are available from the start, including cooking recipes. 
			\n -  Some recipes are locked, these are mainly advanced exos PSUs recipes. You can get them from  
			\n Lv5 supply Mercenary and Ecologist traders.
			\n -  "Junk" items that are necessary for crafting recipes are indicated by a hammer and pincer icon. Keep those.
			\n -  Disassemble the gear you find will allow you to retrieve crafting parts. Some of these items are valuable, 
			\n like broken detectors, so be sure to keep those if you need extra cash.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_gamma_cooking">
		<text>Cooking</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_gamma_cooking_text">
		<text>
			%c[pda_white]Cooking \n \n %c[ui_gray_1]
			\n -  All cooking recipes are available from the start.
			\n -  Cooking is essential, it will provide high calorie food for cheap.
			\n -  Using the basic cooking kit near bonfires will allow you to cook without the need for charcoal.
			\n -  The advanced cooking kit needs liquid fuel to work. However, it is able to cook high tier meals which provide useful long lasting buffs.	
		</text>
	</string>




	<string id="article_gamma_radiation">
		<text>Radiations</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_gamma_radiation_text">
		<text>
			%c[pda_white]Radiation \n \n %c[ui_gray_1]
			\n -  GAMMA features dynamic radiation and a revamped radiation damage system.
			\n -  New random radiation patches are spawned when starting a new game.
			\n -  Radiation will slowly reduce your health (much slower than Vanilla) and will reduce your max stamina. 
			\n -  The more irradiated you are, the more likely critical organs will be damaged. This results in the 
			\n player character coughing and losing a significant amount of health.
			\n -  The radiation meter can be found at the bottom left corner of the screen. If it starts being filled, you just hit 
			\n a radiation patch, try to back track to avoid traversing it. Radiation can also come from artefacts that are not in a container.
			\n -  Use anti-rad drugs, cigarettes, tobacco, water, or alcohol to cure radiation. Using rad protecting drugs is also a good way to avoid radiation.
			\n -  The more to the north you go, the more dangerous the radiations will be. Be sure to have a good gas mask before going 
			\n into northern areas. Entering the Army Warehouses or areas further North without a gas mask or proper anti-radiation medication can kill you if 
			\n you hit just one bad radiation patch. Keep in mind that running into a strong radiation area will likely make you unable to move, trapping you.
		</text>
	</string>







	<string id="article_gamma_stashes">
		<text>Stashes</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_gamma_stashes_text">
		<text>
			%c[pda_white]Stashes \n \n %c[ui_gray_1]
			\n -  Stashes are the main source of toolkits, which are the most critical items you need to progress.
			\n -  Unmarked stashes are almost always empty.
			\n -  Stashes must be marked to contain anything of value, especially toolkits.
			\n -  Stash content is tied to the map they spawn in.
			\n -  The more to the north a stash is in the Zone, the better the loot.
			\n -  Expert toolkits can only be found in the Red Forest or further North.
			\n -  Storing stuff in stashes is safe: it won't be looted by NPCs.
			\n -  Even if the stash is marked at some point, content will spawn in the stash on top of what you previously stored. 
		</text>
	</string>


	<string id="article_gamma_disguise">
		<text>Disguise</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_gamma_disguise_text">
		<text>
			%c[pda_white]Disguise \n \n %c[ui_gray_1]
			\n -  You can wear other faction's armor and be considered a member of that faction if the factions patch is attached.
			\n -  If you tear off the patch, you'll be considered as a member of your characters faction.
			\n -  When attaching the patch, you need to be out of the field of view of other stalkers so your disguise doesn't blow up.
			\n -  This feature is especially powerful with ecologist armor, but they are very hard to get your hands on in GAMMA.
			\n -  The condition of the armor impacts how easy you will be spotted. 
			\n -  High ranked stalkers will see through your tricks more easily than lower ranked ones.
		</text>
	</string>



	<string id="article_gamma_inventory">
		<text>Inventory</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_gamma_inventory_text">
		<text>
			%c[pda_white]Inventory \n \n %c[ui_gray_1]
			\n -  Inventory management is easy, just clean your inventory from unnecessary mess by storing items in a stash of choice.
			\n -  Holding Shift while moving your cursor in your inventory will transfer the whole stack of items you are pointing on. 
			\n - 	Pressing Shift+T performs a "Take All", good for looting quickly.
			\n -  Water bottles are better weight-wise than cantines to quench thirst. Keep the cantines in your main stash to cook with.
			\n
			\n -  Mutant parts and meat don't weight much. Keeping some in your inventory will allow you to complete tasks.
			\n 
			\n -  Crafting tools don't weight much and you can right click them to "open workbench" and start crafting on-the-go.
			\n 
			\n -  Ammunition can be quite heavy, but disassembled ammo parts are very lightweight. Keep these parts and craft ammo with

			\n your gunsmith toolkit on-the-go. Be sure to disassemble all unnecessary ammo.
			\n
			\n -  You can right click and mark some items as "Favorite" and others as "Junk". This will give you an easy access to the
			\n important items that will always be on the top of every inventory containers. It's the opposite for junk: it will always be at
			\n the bottom of inventories.
		</text>
	</string>


	<string id="article_gamma_lore">
		<text>Lore</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_gamma_lore_text">
		<text>
			%c[pda_white]Lore \n \n %c[ui_gray_1]
			\n After the fall of the Monolith thanks to Strelok, the Zone became a place of science and discoveries.
			\n The zone wasn't a secret place anymore and the UN began to ban the sale of firearms in the Zone to make it more
			\n peaceful, with paid PMCs ensuring the security of scientists and limiting fights between factions.
			\n Indeed, the EU and UN decided to put a stop to the bloodshed in the Zone as well as gun smuggling
			\n from the Zone to nearby countries by limiting gun traffic. No faction wanted to give the UN
			\n and EU any more reasons to contract more private military companies. PMCs were already crawling
			\n throughout the Zone.
			\n
			\n During that period of peace, new discoveries were made, such as artefact melting, fusion, and empowering thanks to the work of Prof. Sakharov.
			\n
			\n This "Golden Age" of science in the Zone however made the existing factions weaker since the Monolith was not a priority anymore.
			\n Deep in the heart of the Zone and CNPP, the Monolith was secretly getting stronger, and a new group of fanatics began to emerge, even crazier than the Monolith if the rumors are to be believed.

			\n Fast forward to 2018, the Golden Age of the Zone is over, the Monolith has returned. They have reactivated the miracle machine and the brain
			\n scorcher, and it's 2012 all over again. The weakened factions have grown even softer, no longer the hardened Monolith killers they were back in the old days.
			\n The only hope of most stalkers? Finding Strelok. Some say he's still alive, and Doc, one of his old friends, might have some leads regarding his location.
			\n
			\n You arrive in the Zone in the middle of this mess. You are tasked with finding Strelok and helping clean the Zone from the Monolith scourge.
		</text>
	</string>




	<string id="article_gamma_money">
		<text>Money</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_gamma_money_text">
		<text>
			%c[pda_white]Money \n \n %c[ui_gray_1]
			\n In GAMMA money is of the essence, especially in the beginning.
			\n There are fast ways to make cash, namely doing tasks without picking fights, selling mutant parts or selling
			\n artefacts to the ecologists.
			\n
			\n You'll find yourself often spending money on healing items and that's intended. The more you play, the better
			\n the toolkits you'll have and the easier it will be to repair good gear and craft items, which will save money
			\n and make fights easier, thus helping you saving even more money.
			\n
			\n In the mid game, you'll inevitably get loads of money. This can be used to upgrade your equipment, or invest in
			\n expensive AP ammo.
			\n
			\n You can also buy detectors and NVGs at traders... Or craft them and save some money.
			\n Maintaining an exoskeleton armor will also be a money sink since you often need to buy expensive exo batteries.
			\n
			\n Better healing items are also a must to have easier fights, using stimpacks will greatly help you in tense fights.
		</text>
	</string>









	<string id="article_gamma_plates">
		<text>Protection Plates</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_gamma_plates_text">
		<text>
			%c[pda_white]Protection Plates \n \n %c[ui_gray_1]

			\n Armor plates belt attachments are on par with artefacts protection, reaching about 15% ballistic and explosive protection.
			\n They do not have electric res penalties anymore. They do not protect you from mutants anymore.
			\n Plates can't be bought at merchants anymore.
			\n Basic Kevlar armor plates are obtained via questlines (basic tier 1 plate) or crafted from scratch using armor parts.
			\n
			\n Armor plates can be upgraded via the crafting system:
			\n -       The tier 1 Kevlar plate can be upgraded to tier 2 Kevlar plate with lots of armor parts.
			\n -       The tier 2 Kevlar plate can be upgraded to tier 3 metallic plate with lots of armor parts.
			\n -       The tier 3 metallic plate can be upgraded to tier 4 metallic plate with lots of armor parts.
			\n
			\n This system should push the player to scavenge armor parts for longer.
			\n Armor parts used in this system are conveniently marked with a hammer and pincer icon for easy sorting and looting.
			\n This should prevent players that don't want to engage in artefacts hunting to not die miserably once they fight monolith
			\n and sin in the north, which are exclusively using AP ammo.
		</text>
	</string>



	<string id="article_gamma_arty">
		<text>Artefacts Reinvention</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_gamma_arty_text">
		<text>
			%c[pda_white]Artefacts Reinvention \n \n %c[ui_gray_1]

			\n -  New Grizzly Detector to find all artefacts even with NVGs on. Craftable with an advanced toolkit.
			\n
			\n -  New artefact spawning system: artefacts spawn randomly in the current map of the player in anomalous fields so be
			\n sure to check them whenever you move around them!
			\n -  Rare artefacts also respawn in the labs after emissions.
			\n

			\n -  New artefacts quality system: artefacts spawn with a random low condition (or "quality") to mimic that every artefact 

			\n is different. With the new Artefacts Melter, you can combine artefacts to make them stronger and increase their quality.
			\n
			\n%c[pda_yellow]New toolkit, the Artefacts Melter:%c[ui_gray_1]

			\n -  Buy it at Sakharov or Herman for about 30k RU.
			\n -  You can craft stronger artefacts (right click > Fuse Artefacts) or empower them (right click > Empower artefacts). 
			\n -  Every action you take with the artefacts melter will consume some charges. 
			\n -  You can refill the melter by holding Left Alt key and dragging it on top of any artefact.
			\n -  Keeping an empty melter on you is a good way to replenish it on your way through the zone with unwanted artefacts.
			\n 
			\n%c[pda_yellow]Artefact Empowering:%c[ui_gray_1]
			\n -  Combine two exactly similar artefacts to sum their condition / quality. 
			\n -  You can combine any junk artefact with any other junk artefact at a reduced rate.

			\n%c[pda_yellow]Artefact Crafting:%c[ui_gray_1]
			\n -  Access the craft menu as usual. There will be a new crafting subsection: Artefacts. 
			\n -  This will allow you to convert multiple artefacts of a given tier to the tier above:
			\n -  Junk > Tier 1 (7mS).
			\n -  Tier 1 > Tier 2 (12mS).
			\n -  Tier 2 > Tier 3 (23mS).
			\n -  Tier 3 > Special.
		</text>
	</string>






	<string id="article_gamma_energy">
		<text>Energy</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_gamma_energy_text">
		<text>
			%c[pda_white]Energy Management \n \n %c[ui_gray_1]

			\n Energy in GAMMA is a balancing act between travel, food, drinks, medicine and sleep.
			\n
			\n You character will be tired at the end of the day. You have to sleep to replenish your energy.
			\n You can only sleep if you are tired enough. Using sleeping pills will allow you to forcefully
			\n sleep.
			\n
			\n Depending on how the day was, you'll get tired faster or not. Eating copious meals and taking
			\n sleep inducing drugs will make you to feel tired and get rest at the end of the day.
			\n
			\n However, if you are eating small meals, and use energy drinks or caffeine tablets often,
			\n you'll have a hard time being tired enough to sleep at the end of the day.
			\n
			\n You'll have a chance to wake up early. Be sure to try to sleep more than what you intend to
			\n sleep the correct amount of time, or use better sleeping gear (matress and sleeping bag).
			\n
			\n Vodka and Beer can help you sleep as well.
		</text>
	</string>



	<string id="article_gamma_traders">
		<text>Traders</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_gamma_traders_text">
		<text>
			%c[pda_white]Traders Progression \n \n %c[ui_gray_1]


			\n -  Traders will mostly sell supplies and some accessories.
			\n -  You won't be able to buy or sell armors and guns at traders.
			\n -  You can increase traders supply level by doing tasks for the trader's faction.
			\n The goodwill thresholds are: 
			\n 500, 1000, 1500 and 2000 goodwill. 

			\n
			\n This is a reliable way to secure a steady income of quality ammunitions.
			\n
			\n Traders are either of the WP (Warsaw Pact) or NATO type. This will influence the kind of supplies they sell
			\n (ammo and attachments mostly).
			\n
			\n NATO factions: Mercenaries, Clear Sky, Freedom, UNISG.
			\n WP factions: Military, Loner, Duty, Bandits, Renegades, Monolith.
			\n
			\n This also influences NPCs loadouts of factions, ie: Monolith NPCs have about 50% chance to have a NATO or WP gun.
			\n
			\n Some traders sell very specific items, like Prof. Sakharov and Hermann sell the Artefacts Melter,
			\n a GAMMA specific toolkit that let's you empower and craft artefacts (and you can break artefacts with
			\n it to replenish the melter's power). They also sell exoskeletons' PSU recipes at Supplies Lv 5.
		</text>
	</string>


	<string id="article_gamma_story">
		<text>Storylines</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_gamma_story_text">
		<text>
			%c[pda_white]Storylines & Missions \n \n %c[ui_gray_1]


			\n%c[pda_yellow]Lost to the Zone:%c[ui_gray_1]
			\n Available at your faction leader in your starting base with these factions:
			\n - Loner
			\n - Clear Sky
			\n - Duty
			\n - Freedom
			\n - Mercenary
			\n - Ecologist
			\n
			\n%c[pda_yellow]Mission Afterglow:%c[ui_gray_1]
			\n Available at the start of the UNISG playthrough (type isg in char creation to unlock faction)
			\n
			\n%c[pda_yellow]Artefact Hunters:%c[ui_gray_1]
			\n To start this plot, talk to any NPC among the "Artefact Hunters", ie; Kovalev in church in the swamps or their representative,
			\n named Sarik the Twilight in the Cordon Village.
			\n Available to Ecologist Allies:
			\n - Loner
			\n - Clear Sky
			\n - Duty
			\n - Freedom
			\n - Military
			\n - Mercenary
			\n - Ecologist
			\n
			\n%c[pda_yellow]Last Dawn:%c[ui_gray_1]
			\n Talk to Spire in the Swamps Clear Sky base. Available to Clear Sky Allies:
			\n - Loner
			\n - Clear Sky
			\n - Duty
			\n - Freedom
			\n - Mercenary
			\n - Ecologist
			\n
			\n%c[pda_yellow]Operation Monolith Retribution:%c[ui_gray_1]
			\n Available from Colonel Kuzentsov and help the Military take control of the centre of the Zone. Available to Military Allies:
			\n - Military
			\n - Ecologist
			\n
			\n%c[pda_yellow]Dr.X Questline:%c[ui_gray_1]
			\n Available to all factions, not really story oriented.
		</text>
	</string>






	<string id="article_gamma_repgun">
		<text>Repairs: Guns</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_gamma_repgun_text">
		<text>
			%c[pda_white]Repairs for Guns \n \n %c[ui_gray_1]

			\n Guns must be repaired to progress since you can't buy them from traders with GAMMA Economy.
			\n
			\n You can loot guns from stashes or dead stalkers though, and that's how you will make it to the North in one piece.
			\n Most guns will be destroyed and you'll need to fix them or they will jam very often.
			\n Keep in mind that gun's condition is separated from parts conditions. Gun condition represents how clean a gun is
			\n and will change parts degradation and promote jamming. Jams are coming from the actual gun parts. Repairing the gun
			\n condition will not repair the gun's parts. Each part must be repaired individually. Each part affects the gun jamming
			\n frequency. The barrel changes the damage the gun deals and the strength of ammo penetration.
			\n
			\n%c[pda_yellow]A gun with a very bad barrel condition will deal almost no damage, don't do that.%c[ui_gray_1]
			\n
			\n To repair guns you have two ways:
			\n
			\n - You can get the appropriate repair kit, right click the gun and "maintain parts" it will allow you to replace
			\n the guns parts for 100% condition parts automatically, but will consume a repair kit use. It can even replace barrels. These
			\n kits can be crafted or bought from mechanics once you have the appropriate toolkit (basic, advanced or expert). Replacing parts
			\n that way will improve the gun condition.
			\n - You can however still repair guns without the proper repair kits:
			\n Collect parts above 60% condition and repair them with the appropriate tool to 100% condition
			\n (Ramrod, Multitool, or File). Then simply drag and drop the repaired parts on the gun.
			\n Moving parts in and out of the gun will make it less clean. Barrels can't be replaced that way.
			\n
			\n - If a gun has a barrel with a condition above 60% condition, you can buy a cleaning kit from mechanics and right click the
			\n gun > clean barrel. Same for other parts. It's an easy way to get good guns early since you can buy cleaning kit without any
			\n toolkits unlocked.
			\n
			\n
			\n You must also clean the gun using cleaning equipment or pay a mechanic to do it. Cleaning a gun will not repair its parts
			\n but will prevent parts from degrading while shooting.
		</text>
	</string>




	<string id="article_gamma_reparm">
		<text>Repairs: Armor</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_gamma_reparm_text">
		<text>
			%c[pda_white]Repairs for Armor \n \n %c[ui_gray_1]

			\n Armors repair follow a similar pattern to guns. Find them in stashes or on dead stalkers.
			\n
			\n Collect parts above 50% condition and repair them to 100% condition.
			\n To replace armor parts you'll need the appropriate repair kit in your inventory.
			\n Replace the armor parts using a workbench or right clicking any toolkit to open the workbench and open the repair menu.
			\n Replacing parts will not consume repair kits uses. From 50% and above, armors can be repaired directly using repair kits.
			\n Below that you'll need to change the parts. Be sure to maintain your armor condition often with repair items.
			\n
			\n In GAMMA, mechanics cannot repair armor.
		</text>
	</string>



	<string id="article_gamma_rfpacks">
		<text>Packages</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_gamma_rfpacks_text">
		<text>
			%c[pda_white]Hidden Radio Emitting Packages \n \n %c[ui_gray_1]

			\n You'll get random messages that are telling you to find some packages in certain maps.
			\n
			\n To find them, equip your RF Receiver and press the detector key. Put your weapon away and change the
			\n frequency of your RF Receiver to match the one from the message (check keymap for more details).
			\n
			\n Follow the strong beeps, the faster they are the closer you are to the package.
			\n You can hold the Use button (F) to display the package text and more easily find and grab it.
			\n It's actually an item laying on the ground or hidden in barrels etc. It is NOT a stash you have to interact with.
			\n You can then right click the package in your inventory and open it to get its contents.
			\n
			\n Packages range from random stuff to artefacts or toolkits.
		</text>
	</string>


	<string id="article_gamma_ballistics">
		<text>Ballistics</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_gamma_ballistics_text">
		<text>
			%c[pda_white]Ballistics System \n \n %c[ui_gray_1]

			\n GAMMA uses Grok's Balanced Overhaul Of Ballistic System.
			\n Notably, it changes the bullets and armor penetration from PLAYER to NPCs (not the other way around) using EFT's ammunition
			\n system as an inspiration. The goal is to have a more realistic ballistic system where you must take into account the armor
			\n of your enemy and the ammo type you are using.
			\n
			\n Ammo Armor Penetration (AP) power is compared to the limb armor of the opponent.
			\n If the AP power > limb armor, damage is applied. If AP power is less than limb armor, no damage is applied and limb armor is reduced based on AP power.
			\n Ammo with low AP power thus need to break an opponents limb armor before starting doing damage. AP ammo is thus required to kill heavily armored targets.
			\n FMJ and HP ammo will still work, but the enemy armor must be destroyed by many of these bullets to start doing damage.
			\n Leg and face armor are reduced.
			\n
			\n%c[pda_yellow]AP ammo (Armor Penetrating): %c[ui_gray_1]

			\n -  Expensive but will defeat any endgame heavily armored target. 
			\n -  They are end game ammo, don't use them against lightly armored targets or you will waste money.
			\n
			\n%c[pda_yellow]FMJ ammo (Full Metal Jacket):%c[ui_gray_1] 
			\n -  Cheap and should be used to kill lightly armored targets or as a cheaper and less effective replacement for AP ammo against armored targets.

			\n
			\n%c[pda_yellow]HP ammo (Hollow-Point): %c[ui_gray_1]
			\n -  A bit more expensive than FMJ and should be used to kill mutants since it has even less AP power than FMJ ammo.
			\n
			\n Sniper ammo is actually very powerful, but also very expensive.
			\n .338 Lapua will one shot most enemies with a hit to the chest if you can afford it.
			\n Buckshot will work as inexpensive, early game ammo against stalkers. Forget about it mid and late game: Good for mutants, bad for exos.
			\n Slugs are good to kill mutants and stalkers alike. AP Slugs are best against stalkers.
			\n
			\n Some ammo is much more useful against mutants: HP ammo, .357 magnum, .45 Hydrashock, buckshots, slugs, 7.62x25 Pst.
			\n
			\n Bullets have an armor penetration value in their description. It's based on the Russian BR classification for ammo penetration:

			\n -  BR1 - BR2 = penetrate light armors
			\n -  BR3 - BR4 = penetrate middle-class armors
			\n -  BR5 = penetrate heavy armors
			\n -  BR6 = penetrate exo armors. 

			\n
			\n%c[pda_yellow]Some factions have specific characteristics:
			\n -  Monolith is only using AP ammo.
			\n -  Sin is only using AP ammo, mainly using heavy machine guns, and much more resistant than a normal human being.
			\n -  ISG members have very good gear, only use AP ammo and have a higher ammo penetration resistance.
			\n -  Most Master and Legend stalkers use AP ammo.
			\n -  Factions use guns according to their trader type (WP or NATO).
		</text>
	</string>
</string_table>