<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<!--
	Repair Kits
-->

<string_table>

	<string id="st_sharpening_stones">
		<text>Three-piece sharpening stone set</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sharpening_stones_descr">
		<text>\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] suited for knives and blades\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_1]Blunt knives and tools? It doesn't have to be that way. Super-practical 3 piece grindstone set for everyone, packed in a nice polyester bag. No more loose grindstone, sliding about in drawers, scratching everything - no, everything is now in its place. For perfect sharpening, three important grains for pre-grinding, sharpening and for the subsequent stripping of the blade are integrated in the set, so you can achieve a razor-sharp cutting edge.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] toolkit\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] high quality\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] usable for repairing equipment\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_gun_oil">
		<text>"Brunox Gun Care" spray lubricant</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_gun_oil_descr">
		<text>\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] suited for all weapons\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_1]Spray can containing oil intended for lubricating and protecting firearms. Frequent application will prevent guns from malfunctioning and corroding, especially after prolonged use in combat situations. Prior to lubrication process, it is advisable to properly clean the firearm to remove any foreign material that has accumulated on or inside it. One can also make use of basic tools in order to access the inner parts of a gun so as to maximize the effectiveness of maintenance. A special tuboline increases gliding quality of all movable parts making the oil even better suited for repeaters and automatic weapons. This allows guns to function even at temperatures of up to -55 •C. It has a flash point of 78 •C.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] fast usage (spray lubricant)\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] high quality\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] usable for repairing equipment\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_gun_oil_ru_d">
		<text>"Dvojka" gun oil and cleaning solvent</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_gun_oil_ru_d_descr">
		<text>\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] suited for all weapons\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_1]Iconic Red Army oil that has been in service for almost 70 years. The metal bottle is divided into two separate compartments, one for oil and the other one for the cleaning solvent. In the beginning, the solvent was based on an alkaline solution for effective clean-up of preservation salts in which ammunition was commonly shipped and stored. Since then, the composition of liquids has been modernized many times, but the simple yet ingenious 'double' bottle design remained unchanged. "Dvojka" is very popular in the Exclusion Zone due to its versatility. Bear in mind, however, that the oil requires adequate tools to be spread properly and so that it can reach deep into weapon's inner mechanisms. "Dvojka" should thus be regarded as more of an add-on than a stand-alone maintenance item.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] liquid gun oil and cleaning solvent\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] usable for repairing equipment\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_gun_oil_ru">
		<text>"Rusak" gun oil</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_gun_oil_ru_descr">
		<text>\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] suited for all weapons\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_1]Plastic bottle containing a budget Russian mineral gun oil. Despite its low price, it can prove useful in keeping a firearm in a good condition if applied frequently. It should be used alongside brushes for increased effect. According to the manufacturer, "Rusak" is especially effective for automatic and repeatable weapons due to low friction coefficient. It also contains various anti-corrosion and metal-preserving additives.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] liquid gun oil\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] usable for repairing equipment\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_solvent">
		<text>Hoppe's "No. 9" cleaning solvent</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_solvent_descr">
		<text>\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] suited for all weapons\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_1]Western-made, high-quality firearm cleaning solvent, especially adapted for use in harsh environmental conditions, the Hoppe's No. 9 Bore Cleaning remains perhaps the most commonly used solution. Like all cleaning solvents, it is designed for preventing rust and removing powder, lead and metal fouling, but its unique property is that it makes heavy particles less likely to stick to mechanical parts of a firearm. This proves especially useful in the irradiated Zone. Substance acts quickly, is super-efficient, safe and easy to use. Although it flows freely and penetrates rapidly, it is still advisable to use tools or fabrics to increase spread.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] liquid gun cleaning solvent\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] high quality\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] valuable\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] usable for repairing equipment\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_cleaning_kit_p">
		<text>"Progress" handgun cleaning kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_cleaning_kit_p_descr">
		<text>\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9mm, .45 and .357 caliber weapons\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_1]A set of specialized brushes which can be used to clean the barrel and other parts of a firearm from dirt, sand, moisture, lubricant residues and other foreign materials that have accumulated during use. Such sets are quite commonly used in the Zone in order to keep firearms in a good shape at all times. It is possible to utilize common tools to have a better access to inner mechanisms of a gun or alcohol to more easily dissolve oil residue. Can also be used to better spread gun oil, however a more cost-efficient method used by most experienced stalkers entails the application of animal fat on the brushes as an alternative lubricant. This particular set fits typical handgun calibers.\n \n
		%c[d_orange]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_orange] • Can be used to clean dirty parts (above 60 condition) within guns. Right-click a gun > maintain parts > clean part. \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_cleaning_kit_s">
		<text>"Aurora A108/12" 12ga cleaning kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_cleaning_kit_s_descr">
		<text>\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] 12ga weapons\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_1]A set of specialized brushes which can be used to clean the barrel and other parts of a firearm from dirt, sand, moisture, lubricant residues and other foreign materials that have accumulated during use. It is possible to utilize common tools to have a better access to inner mechanisms of a gun or alcohol to more easily dissolve oil residue. This particular set fits 12ga shotguns. "Aurora" kit comes with three specialized brush types, one for respectively after-fire cleaning, lubricant spreading and rust removal. Keeps your favorite shotgun in a good shape at all times.\n \n
		%c[d_orange]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_orange] • Can be used to clean dirty parts (above 60 condition) within guns. Right-click a gun > maintain parts > clean the desired part. \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_cleaning_kit_r5">
		<text>"ValuPro III" smallbore rifle cleaning kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_cleaning_kit_r5_descr">
		<text>\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.45 and 5.56 caliber weapons\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_1]A set of specialized brushes which can be used to clean the barrel and other parts of a firearm from dirt, sand, moisture, lubricant residues and other foreign materials that have accumulated during use. Such sets are quite commonly used in the Zone in order to keep firearms in a good shape at all times. It is possible to utilize common tools to have a better access to inner mechanisms of a gun or alcohol to more easily dissolve oil residue. Can also be used to better spread gun oil, however a more cost-efficient method used by most experienced stalkers entails the application of animal fat on the brushes as an alternative lubricant. This particular pack fits medium-caliber rifles with long barrels and comes in a hard plastic reusable container.\n \n
		%c[d_orange]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_orange] • Can be used to clean dirty parts (above 60 condition) within guns. Right-click a gun > maintain parts > clean the desired part. \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_cleaning_kit_r7">
		<text>Medium and large caliber rifle cleaning kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_cleaning_kit_r7_descr">
		<text>\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] 7.62, 7.92, 9x39 and .338 caliber weapons\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_1]A set of specialized brushes which can be used to clean the barrel and other parts of a firearm from dirt, sand, moisture, lubricant residues and other foreign materials that have accumulated during use. Such sets are quite commonly used in the Zone in order to keep firearms in a good shape at all times. It is possible to utilize common tools to have a better access to inner mechanisms of a gun or alcohol to more easily dissolve oil residue. Can also be used to better spread gun oil, however a more cost-efficient method used by most experienced stalkers entails the application of animal fat on the brushes as an alternative lubricant. This particular set fits large-caliber rifles and very long barrels. Manufacturer unknown, but its simple design and construction as well as very high quality materials used suggest a military, presumably special forces origin.\n \n
		%c[d_orange]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_orange] • Can be used to clean dirty parts (above 60 condition) within guns. Right-click a gun > maintain parts > clean the desired part. \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_cleaning_kit_u">
		<text>Universal weapon cleaning kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_cleaning_kit_u_descr">
		<text>\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] all weapons\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_1]Advanced gun cleaning kit fitting all common weapon calibers. Besides cleaning and maintenance, it can also be used as an effective repair tool. The set comprises a small portion of efficient lubricant and cleaning solvent as well as some light tools to facilitate access to inner mechanisms of a firearm. In order to maximize effectiveness, combine with additional materials or specialized repair sets.\n \n
		%c[d_orange]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_red] • Cannot be used to clean weapon parts inside guns. \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_repair_kit_p">
		<text>Handgun repair kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_repair_kit_p_descr">
		<text>\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] 9mm, .45 and .357 caliber weapons\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_1]This kit contains oils, solvents, basic cleaning equipment and specialized tools used for disassembly and maintenance of mechanisms of weapons. It also by standard comes with set of elementary firearm spare parts. The kit is quite heavy, but is irreplaceable when venturing deep into the Zone as it can be used in life-or-death situations to make a firearm usable again. Due to differences in weapon construction this particular set can only be used for disassembly and repair of weapons with handgun calibers. It's also possible to additionally increase the effectiveness of the kit by borrowing certain materials from or combining with other kits during a single maintenance session.\n \n
		%c[d_orange]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_orange] • Can be used to replace any parts within guns. Right-click a gun > maintain parts > replace the desired part. \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_repair_kit_s">
		<text>Shotgun repair kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_repair_kit_s_descr">
		<text>\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] 12ga weapons\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_1]This kit contains oils, solvents, basic cleaning equipment and specialized tools used for disassembly and maintenance of mechanisms of weapons. It also by standard comes with set of elementary firearm spare parts. The kit is quite heavy, but is irreplaceable when venturing deep into the Zone as it can be used in life-or-death situations to make a firearm usable again. Due to differences in weapon construction this particular set can only be used for disassembly and repair of weapons with 12ga shotgun caliber. It's also possible to additionally increase the effectiveness of the kit by borrowing certain materials from or combining with other kits during single maintenance session.\n \n
		%c[d_orange]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_orange] • Can be used to replace any parts within guns. Right-click a gun > maintain parts > replace the desired part. \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_repair_kit_r5">
		<text>Smallbore rifle repair kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_repair_kit_r5_descr">
		<text>\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] 5.45 and 5.56 caliber weapons\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_1]This kit contains oils, solvents, basic cleaning equipment and specialized tools used for disassembly and maintenance of mechanisms of weapons. It also by standard comes with set of elementary firearm spare parts. The kit is quite heavy, but is irreplaceable when venturing deep into the Zone as it can be used in life-or-death situations to make a firearm usable again. Due to differences in weapon construction this particular set can only be used for disassembly and repair of medium-caliber rifles. It's also possible to additionally increase the effectiveness of the kit by borrowing certain materials from or combining with other kits during single maintenance session.\n \n
		%c[d_orange]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_orange] • Can be used to replace any parts within guns. Right-click a gun > maintain parts > replace the desired part. \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_repair_kit_r7">
		<text>Medium and large caliber rifle fixing kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_repair_kit_r7_descr">
		<text>\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] 7.62, 7.92, 9x39 and .338 caliber weapons\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_1]This kit contains oils, solvents, basic cleaning equipment and specialized tools used for disassembly and maintenance of mechanisms of weapons. It also by standard comes with set of elementary firearm spare parts. The kit is quite heavy, but is irreplaceable when venturing deep into the Zone as it can be used in life-or-death situations to make a firearm usable again. Due to differences in weapon construction this particular set can only be used for disassembly and repair of large-caliber rifles. It's also possible to additionally increase the effectiveness of the kit by borrowing certain materials from or combining with other kits during single maintenance session.\n \n
		%c[d_orange]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_orange] • Can be used to replace any parts within guns. Right-click a gun > maintain parts > replace the desired part. \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_repair_kit_p_empty">
		<text>Handgun repair kit (empty box)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_repair_kit_p_empty_descr">
		<text>Empty metal box which previously contained tools and spare parts usable for maintaining 9mm, .45 and .357 caliber firearms. Even in its current state it can prove useful in repairing metal parts of outfits. A low-value trading commodity.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_repair_kit_s_empty">
		<text>Shotgun repair kit (empty box)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_repair_kit_s_empty_descr">
		<text>Empty metal box which previously contained tools and spare parts usable for maintaining 12ga caliber firearms. Even in its current state it can prove useful in repairing metal parts of outfits. A low-value trading commodity.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_repair_kit_r5_empty">
		<text>Smallbore rifle repair kit (empty box)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_repair_kit_r5_empty_descr">
		<text>Empty metal box which previously contained tools and spare parts usable for maintaining 5.45 and 5.56 caliber firearms. Even in its current state it can prove useful in repairing metal parts of outfits. A low-value trading commodity.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_repair_kit_r7_empty">
		<text>Medium and large caliber rifle fixing kit (empty box)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_repair_kit_r7_empty_descr">
		<text>Empty metal box which previously contained tools and spare parts usable for maintaining large caliber firearms. Even in its current state it can prove useful in repairing metal parts of outfits. A low-value trading commodity.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_sewing_kit_b">
		<text>Basic sewing kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sewing_kit_b_descr">
		<text>\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] all outfits and light headgear sets\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_1]A light sewing kit consisting of a cloth reel, several steel needles and a pair of scissors. It can be used to sew up bullet holes or ruptures in soft fabrics of outfits. Its practical applications are limited due to the short length of the thread and subpar durability of needles, so the kit will be useless in case of more serious damage. For the same reason, it's compatible with only a handful of materials. Nonetheless, it is strongly advised to always use whatever is available to make the kit more effective.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] usable for repairing equipment\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_sewing_kit_a">
		<text>Advanced sewing kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sewing_kit_a_descr">
		<text>\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] all outfits and light headgear sets\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_1]This advanced set contains more and better sewing accessories than its basic counterpart. Double reels of nylon thread and a large selection of higher-quality needles make it suitable for working on thicker and harder materials, including lighter mutant skins and artificial fibers. It is also capable of repairing more damaged outfits.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] usable for repairing equipment\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_sewing_kit_h">
		<text>Heavy sewing kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sewing_kit_h_descr">
		<text>\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] all outfits and light headgear sets\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_1]This military-grade, heavy sewing kit is designed to handle fractures in protective plates of modern combat armors. It contains enough metallic thread to put together outfits that have literally been torn apart. Capable of sewing on even hardest of mutant hides to your armor of choice. Another advantage of the kit are the basic mechanical tools that can be used to disassemble outfits and headgear in order to salvage repair materials. It's the highest quality sewing kit available in the Zone.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] high quality\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] valuable\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] usable for repairing equipment\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_glue_b">
		<text>"Zviezda" glue tube</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_glue_b_descr">
		<text>\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] all outfits and light headgear sets\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_1]Cheapest of the synthetic adhesives available in the Zone, this epoxy-based solution may be used to put together slightly torn pieces of fabric or to patch up a small hole in your helmet, but it will be useless in case of any serious damage. On the other hand, "Zviezda" has a great value for price, and if used on a regular basis it's able to keep your outfit in a good shape at all times. It is advised to use any type of commonly found materials to greatly increase effectiveness of repair. The glue, however, won't support mutant skins. Can also be used to facilitate sewing.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] usable for repairing equipment\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_glue_a">
		<text>"Tur" glue tube</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_glue_a_descr">
		<text>\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] all outfits and headgear sets\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_1]Advanced glue produced by the Ukrainian chemical industry, modified epoxy-based adhesive "Tur" is able to quickly bind most solid materials. Versatility and ease of use are the two reasons why "Tur" is kept in such a high regard among stalkers, especially since spare materials are scarce. The glue binds both textile fabrics and lighter protective materials like kevlar, but is useless when it comes to metals.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] usable for repairing equipment\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_glue_e">
		<text>"M17" glue tube</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_glue_e_descr">
		<text>\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] all outfits and headgear sets\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_1]M17 is a result of a Soviet military-industrial research project intended to devise an extremely potent, single-ingredient adhesive which could be used in any situation regardless of purpose and materials involved. It was decided to use a highly potent methacrylate which is most often optimized for reacting with either plastic or metal. In case of M17, however, this limitation has been bypassed, making the substance equally effective in both areas. In addition, the adhesive received a significant boost to versatility thanks to its hydrate form: it can be diluted with water and used in any concentration depending on the intended result. There is almost no damage that the glue, combined with appropriate materials, won't be able to repair. Can be used with all materials available in the Zone.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] high quality\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] valuable\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] usable for repairing equipment\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_armor_repair_fa">
		<text>Emergency armor repair set</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_armor_repair_fa_descr">
		<text>\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] all outfits and light headgear sets\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_1]A repair set allowing the user to perform emergency repairs of outfits. Includes military grade ducktape and ready-to-use sheets of thick textile in a variety of shapes and sizes which make it possible to quickly patch up any outfit damage. This is especially useful to prevent further structural damage of already damaged suits. Due to a relatively low durability of provided materials, the kit can be used only for minor repairs and is ineffective in case of harder materials like kevlar or metal. For this reason, the kit has a very limited use in headgear maintenance.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] fast usage (adhesive tape)\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] usable for repairing equipment\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_helmet_repair_kit">
		<text>Headgear repair kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helmet_repair_kit_descr">
		<text>\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] medium and heavy headgear sets\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_1]This kit contains everything that is needed to perform effective repair of modern combat helmets. It features heavy tools that will allow you to work on hard materials such as kevlar, steel or titanium, as well as a very strong, methacrylate-based adhesive. As the kit does not contain any sewing equipment, it cannot be effectively utilized for reparation of flexible materials of armors, but it can be used to disassemble headgear sets to greatly improve the effectiveness of repair.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] high quality\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] valuable\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] usable for repairing equipment\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_repair_kit">
		<text>Heavy outfit repair kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_repair_kit_descr">
		<text>\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] all outfits and headgear sets\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_1]This complex and heavy set includes everything necessary - from ultra-durable threads and needles to polymer-based patches - to conduct a complete repair of any armor or headgear. Can be used regardless of materials involved, be it heavy cloth, military-grade kevlar sheets, or heavy mutant pelts. Additional tools and kits increase effectiveness of repairs.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] high quality\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] valuable\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] usable for repairing equipment\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_light_repair_kit">
		<text>Light armor repair kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_light_repair_kit_descr">
		<text>\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] very light and light armors\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_1]This complex and heavy set includes everything necessary - from ultra-durable threads and needles to polymer-based patches - to conduct a complete repair of any light armor. Can be used regardless of materials involved, be it heavy cloth or military-grade kevlar sheets. Additional tools and kits increase effectiveness of repairs.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] high quality\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] valuable\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] used for repairing light armor\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_medium_repair_kit">
		<text>Medium armor repair kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_medium_repair_kit_descr">
		<text>\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] medium armors\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_1]This complex and heavy set includes everything necessary - from ultra-durable threads and needles to polymer-based patches - to conduct a complete repair of any medium armor. Can be used regardless of materials involved, be it heavy cloth or military-grade kevlar sheets. Additional tools and kits increase effectiveness of repairs.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] high quality\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] valuable\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] used for repairing medium armor\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_exolight_repair_kit">
		<text>Heavy armor repair kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_exolight_repair_kit_descr">
		<text>\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] heavy armours\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_1]This complex and heavy set includes everything necessary - from ultra-durable threads and needles to polymer-based patches - to conduct a complete repair of any heavy armor. Can be used regardless of materials involved, be it heavy cloth or military-grade kevlar sheets. Additional tools and kits increase effectiveness of repairs.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] high quality\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] valuable\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_exo_repair_kit">
		<text>Exoskeleton repair kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_exo_repair_kit_descr">
		<text>\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] any exoskeleton\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_1]This complex and heavy set includes everything necessary - from ultra-durable threads and needles to polymer-based patches - to conduct a complete repair of any hi-tech armor. Can be used regardless of materials involved, be it heavy cloth or military-grade kevlar sheets. Additional tools and kits increase effectiveness of repairs.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] high quality\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] valuable\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] usable for repairing equipment\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	
	<string id="st_leatherman_tool">
		<text>Multitool</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_leatherman_tool_descr">
		<text>A worn but functional multitool, used to disassemble weapons and armour on parts and to maintain worn and rusty trigger mechanisms.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_purple] • %c[ui_gray_2] disassembling tool\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] toolkit\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] high quality\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] usable for weapon parts maintenance\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_rasp_tool">
		<text>File</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_rasp_tool_descr">
		<text>A file, used to restore weapon parts such as a worn or rusty barrel or breech head.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] toolkit\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] high quality\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] usable for weapon parts maintenance\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_ramrod_tool">
		<text>Ramrod</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ramrod_tool_descr">
		<text>An old ramrod consisting of three composite wooden parts, used to restore parts such as worn or rusty barrels and gas tubes.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] toolkit\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] high quality\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] usable for weapon parts maintenance\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_sewing_thread">
		<text>Basic sewing thread</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sewing_thread_descr">
		<text>This sewing thread is made out of many different materials including cotton, linen, nylon, and silk. Every stalker knows it's not easy to avoid cloth tearig every while and then due to the harsh environment inside the Zone. Saving a couple of sewing threads for long trips is a wise idea.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] everyday item\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] usable for outfit parts maintenance\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_heavy_sewing_thread">
		<text>Field armour toolkit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_heavy_sewing_thread_descr">
		<text>An advanced toolkit for sewing and sealing retardants. Including kevlar thread, one of the strongest and most heat resistant commercially available threads. It is about 2.5 times stronger than nylon and polyester, has very little stretch, does not melt, and decomposes at 800F. This makes it a great choice for high stress applications including sewing seams on heavy duty clothing.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] toolkit\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] high quality\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[ui_gray_2] usable for outfit parts maintenance\n
		</text>
	</string>
</string_table>
