<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>

<!-- [ Mercenary Guide) at the merc base -->
<!-- [ Mercenary Trader) at the merc base -->
	<string id="meet_zaton_killer_guide_station_0">
		<text>Who are you?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="meet_zaton_killer_guide_station_1">
		<text>I could ask you a reasonable question in return: what's your damn business? But that's probably not what you wanna hear, is it? I work as a trader, as well as a guide between here and our main outpost in Dead City.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="meet_zaton_killer_guide_station_list_0">
		<text>Could you remind me which routes you do?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="meet_zaton_killer_guide_station_list_1">
		<text>Did you walk through the Scorcher on your way here? There's only one route. To the Dead City, and it's eight grand.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="travel_zaton_killer_guide_station_base_0">
		<text>I want to get to the Dead City.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_zaton_killer_guide_station_base_1">
		<text>Great. Prepare for a nice long sewer trip. Maybe one day I'll save up enough cash for a decent respirator. You ready?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_zaton_killer_guide_station_base_2">
		<text>I'm ready. %c[d_orange][8000 RU]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_zaton_killer_guide_station_base_3">
		<text>I've changed my mind.</text>
	</string>

	
<!-- Pilot [ Loner Guide) -->
	<string id="meet_guid_zat_0">
		<text>You look like an interesting character.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="meet_guid_zat_1">
		<text>Pathfinder Pilot at your service. There aren't many places I can take you, but it'll definitely be much faster and safer. I offer services to Pripyat as well as its outskirts via fellow guide Garry, though I can take you to Jupiter myself.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="meet_guid_zat_list_0">
		<text>Give me your travel list again.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="meet_guid_zat_list_1">
		<text>I can talk to Garry about leading you to Pripyat for four thousand, as well as the outskirts for five thousand. I can lead you to Yanov station in Jupiter by myself, for two thousand.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="travel_guid_zat_0">
		<text>Take me places.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_zat_1">
		<text>Where to?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_zat_2">
		<text>To Pripyat. %c[d_orange][4000 RU]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_zat_3">
		<text>To the Outskirts. %c[d_orange][5000 RU]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_zat_4">
		<text>To Jupiter. %c[d_orange][2000 RU]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_guid_zat_5">
		<text>I've changed my mind.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="stalker_guide_about_himself_0">
		<text>Tell me about yourself.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_guide_about_himself_1">
		<text>My name is Pilot for a reason. I only use safe routes. I don't have what it takes to collect artefacts or fight bandits, so... Everyone should use their talents and let others benefit from them. Every talent has its price, of course.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="stalker_guide_about_anomalies_1116">
		<text>Okay, forget about it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_guide_about_anomalies_1111">
		<text>Tell me about heat anomalies.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_guide_about_anomalies_11111">
		<text>If you see a sort of glimmering, like air steaming over pavement on a hot summer day - that's a heat anomaly. When something gets in it, that spot bursts into an extremely hot flame. At first they thought those were jets of natural gas, but that theory has since fallen into obscurity.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_guide_about_anomalies_1112">
		<text>Tell me about gas anomalies.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_guide_about_anomalies_11121">
		<text>This type of anomaly is dubbed such for its strange, never-ending chemical processes. They produce acid that eats your skin in a matter of seconds, as well as toxic gases that eat your lungs just as fast... Thankfully, gas anomalies are easy to spot out in the open. When you walk into one in a dark tunnel - now that's bad.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_guide_about_anomalies_1113">
		<text>Tell me about electrical anomalies.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_guide_about_anomalies_11131">
		<text>A very interesting type of anomaly which accumulates a substantial amount of static electricity. Stalkers usually take advantage of the fact that an electrical anomaly can be discharged with any metallic item. They throw a bolt in and dash right through before it charges up again. I prefer to go around - the recharge phase is just too quick.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_guide_about_anomalies_1114">
		<text>Tell me about gravitational anomalies.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_guide_about_anomalies_11141">
		<text>They are typically stationary. When you look at a particular spot and notice that objects are distorted behind it - you've got one. And you better keep your distance. All three known varieties react instantly, the moment something touches them. Springboard hurls everything from under it - often at a great distance. Vortex does the opposite: it sucks an object in, crushes it with terrible pressure, only to send the bits flying seconds after. Whirligig lifts its victim in the air, spins and tears him to shreds... An unpleasant end, whichever way you go.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_guide_about_anomalies_1">
		<text>As you approach an anomaly, keep in mind that it's going to be either very hot, or the air will be full of toxic gases, or it will be a radiation hot-spot. There can also be psy-disruptions, but I won't go into those right now. It depends on the nature of the anomaly - be it heat, gas or electricity... or gravity, but I hope you won't have to deal with those. There are also moving anomalies, but that's a different kettle of fish altogether.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_guide_about_anomalies_0">
		<text>Tell me about anomalies.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_guide_about_anomalies_1115">
		<text>Tell me about moving anomalies.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_guide_about_anomalies_11151">
		<text>Personally I've only come across a Comet and a Tesla. The former is a fireball about three feet in diameter. But I assure you, you'll feel the heat from a much greater distance... The latter is, for lack of a better description, a ball of lightning. It's definitely a ball and it's definitely electrical in nature. Both anomalies always keep moving, but usually in closed-loop paths. A careful stalker should be able to easily go around them... Just don't lose your focus.</text>
	</string>
	
<!-- Gonta -->
	<string id="gonta_about_himself_0">
		<text>Tell me about yourself.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gonta_about_himself_1">
		<text>I'm Gonta, leader of the hunting crew. We destroy mutants for cash. We can also capture them alive - for scientific experiments or if anyone needs an exotic pet... As Trapper used to say, "To each animal its own bullet..."</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="gonta_about_mutants_0">
		<text>Tell me about hunting mutants.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gonta_about_mutants_1">
		<text>Well, I'm not the most seasoned of hunters, but I can tell you a good bit about animals than run in packs. Flesh, boars, blind dogs, pseudodogs, snorks, hamsters... I even know a thing or two about bloodsuckers.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gonta_about_mutants_1111">
		<text>Tell me about boars and flesh.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gonta_about_mutants_11111">
		<text>Okay, flesh are the most harmless of mutants. They try to stay away from stalkers, but they'll fight back if you attack 'em. Now, if there's a boar among those fleshes, that spells trouble. Three hundred kilos of rage is nothing to toy with. Try not to stand in its path as it charges at you... Use its momentum against it. A heavy bulk like that won't be able to turn on the dime, will it? Dodge to the side, then plug it full of shot.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gonta_about_mutants_1112">
		<text>Tell me about blind dogs and pseudodogs.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gonta_about_mutants_11121">
		<text>Lone canines aren't that dangerous, but packs of them are a real pain in the ass. They only attack if they're hungry... the bad thing is, they're almost always hungry. If you're up against a whole pack, try to pick them off from a high spot, else they'll just run you over. Especially if there are mature pseudodogs among 'em. They ain't much tougher than blind ones, but much more cunning and dangerous... If one suddenly turns into a whole pack, then remember: you’re being attacked by phantoms. The real pseudodog will hang back and only try to bite you now and again... Try to identify it. As soon as the real dog is dead, the phantoms will simply disappear.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gonta_about_mutants_1113">
		<text>Tell me about snorks.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gonta_about_mutants_11131">
		<text>Remnants of humans... A lone snork isn't much of a problem for an experienced hunter. You wait for him to jump on you and pump him full of shot in the air. Now, when there's a few of 'em... You've gotta just shoot at them as fast as you can while dodging their jumps. They know this and usually try to attack together.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gonta_about_mutants_1114">
		<text>Tell me about tushkanos.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gonta_about_mutants_11141">
		<text>A hunter's nightmare... The worst thing you can do is underestimate them because of their small size. They're incredibly fast, agile and always run in packs. When you feel dozens of small fangs tearing into you - that's when you stop underestimatin' and start shootin'... And that's the scariest part: they're extremely hard to hit. That's why I always tell stalkers to carry a loaded shotgun.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gonta_about_mutants_1115">
		<text>Tell me about bloodsuckers.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gonta_about_mutants_11151">
		<text>They're expert hunters themselves, with excellent disguise. When they're camouflaged you can barely see them. If you're hunting a bloodsucker, try to startle it. You can see it better when it's on the move... Remember, a bloodsucker will try to sneak up behind you and weave its feelers around your neck. That's some creepy shit, man... If you are unlucky enough to run into a few bloodsuckers, always watch your back.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="gonta_about_mutants_1116">
		<text>Okay, forget about it.</text>
	</string>

	
<!-- Owl [ Loner Trader) -->
	<string id="owl_story_0">
		<text>Tell me about this quiet harbor.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="owl_story_1">
		<text>And who the hell are you to demand information from me, eh? I'll just tell you what everyone else around here already knows. There was this strange stalker, turned out to be a major of the SSU. He was a good help, and he also dealt with quite a few dangers. It's only recently that everything went downhill... The Yantar psy-emitter and Brain Scorcher were turned on again. There are clearly activities going on at the Chernobyl NPP, and it's within reach. A squad of experienced stalkers went MIA, and after that another squad stumbled upon some Monolith near the sawmill, from what I heard. After that rumble, people left, and the mutants have been using that to their advantage, breeding unchecked. This is no place for rookies, I can tell you that.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="owl_story_2">
		<text>Yet I see not all is lost here. Is there anything else to keep in mind?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="owl_story_3">
		<text>Yes. I'm an information broker. You see, some hotshots, they come up here looking to exit the rat race and strike it rich. But up here, there's many dangers - cultists, mutants, zombies, you name it. It's very easy for a stalker to die in these marshes. So if you happen to, uh, 'find' any of them dead...I'll pay for their PDAs, no questions asked. Capisce?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="owl_story_4">
		<text>Yeah, I catch your drift.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="information_about_stash_owl_zat_0">
		<text>You got any info on stashes?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="information_about_stash_owl_zat_1">
		<text>I've got everything and more - if you've got the cash, that is. Got plenty of spare info from various sources. Eight thousand for this one, no less.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="information_about_stash_owl_zat1_0">
		<text>Here. %c[d_orange][8000 RU]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="information_about_stash_owl_zat1_1">
		<text>Right. Here are your coordinates.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="find_blackbox_mlr_reward_owl_0">
		<text>Are you interested in data from a flight recorder?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="find_blackbox_mlr_reward_owl_1">
		<text>Wha-of course! Give it here.</text>
	</string>

	
<!-- Beard [ Loner Barman) -->
	<string id="boroda_story_0">
		<text>You must be Beard.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="boroda_story_1">
		<text>That's right. I haven't seen you around before - welcome to the Skadovsk.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="boroda_story_2">
		<text>What can I do here?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="boroda_story_3">
		<text>Whatever you prefer doing. Ever since the departure of Sultan, the hunt for artefacts around here has been more of a breeze than ever. If you plan on going south in the direction of the substation workshops and the waste processing station, be careful. The Syndicate holds those territories, and they pose quite a threat. If you happen to find any artefacts, feel free to bring them here - I'll be more than happy to offer you a decent price. Stay safe around these parts, stalker.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="boroda_story_4">
		<text>Thank you.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="devushka_boroda_help_0">
		<text>Hey Beard! We're still on time, right? We've got a present for you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="devushka_boroda_help_1">
		<text>Just in time, in fact. Here, both of you, a reward for your troubles.</text>
	</string>

	
<!-- Noah [ Loner Honcho) Character Description -->
	<string id="noah_start_dialog_0">
		<text>Man, what the hell were you shooting for? You almost killed me!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="noah_start_dialog_1">
		<text>And what are you here for? No bullshitting - don't waste my time.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="noah_start_dialog_2">
		<text>Okay, easy. Just passing by. Need any help? Can you answer a few questions?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="noah_start_dialog_3">
		<text>I'll answer, but don't screw around.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="noah_start_dialog1_0">
		<text>I have a couple of questions.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="noah_start_dialog1_1">
		<text>...</text>
	</string>
		<string id="noah_start_dialog1_2">
			<text>Where did you get this dog?</text>
		</string>
		<string id="noah_start_dialog1_7">
			<text>That's Lassie. A sweet little bitch... If not for her, I'd have been devoured in my sleep long ago. Cursed mutants... I hate them! Soon as you close your eyes, they start reaching for you with their nasty claws, fangs and feelers...</text>
		</string>
		<string id="noah_start_dialog1_8">
			<text>I see.</text>
		</string>
		<string id="noah_start_dialog1_9">
			<text>And those puppies - where did they come from if Lassie spends all her time with you? Hehe.</text>
		</string>
		<string id="noah_start_dialog1_3">
			<text>Why do you live on this garbage can?</text>
		</string>
		<string id="noah_start_dialog1_10">
			<text>It's an ark! Remember that... you will, if you want to live! When a Wave starts, stay close. Here you'll have a chance to survive. No mutant will ever break in here.</text>
		</string>
		<string id="noah_start_dialog1_11">
			<text>What "Wave"? What are you talking about?</text>
		</string>
		<string id="noah_start_dialog1_12">
			<text>The creatures are watching me day and night. You do not understand... those snorks from the southern plateau have followed me right up to the Ark! I'm an experienced hunter and I know that they would not have chased the victim for so fucking long. Something isn't clear... they must have a collective mind of sorts. My thoughts have been confirmed by the recent attacks on the barge by those horrors.</text>
		</string>
		<string id="noah_start_dialog1_13">
			<text>I guess anything can happen in the Zone, but if your estimates are correct, we're in some deep trouble.</text>
		</string>
		<string id="noah_start_dialog1_4">
			<text>Why do you not trust people?</text>
		</string>
		<string id="noah_start_dialog1_14">
			<text>In time, you'll find the answer yourself.</text>
		</string>
	<string id="noah_start_dialog1_5">
		<text>I think I'll go.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="tasks_noah_dialog_0">
		<text>Need any help?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tasks_noah_dialog_1">
		<text>Well... I do have a couple favors you could do for me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="tasks_noah_dialog_2">
		<text>Find a new shotgun</text>
	</string>
		<string id="tasks_noah_dialog_5">
			<text>My current shooter is crap. If you could bring me something better, like a Saiga... Well, I'm not sure getting a weapon like that in the Zone is possible. I have seen a few bandits with Armsel Protectas, though. You can bring me one of those.</text>
		</string>
	<string id="tasks_noah_dialog_3">
		<text>Deal with the snorks at the southern plateau</text>
	</string>
		<string id="tasks_noah_dialog_6">
			<text>It's time to put an end to those horrid creatures. Every night, I hear them creeping around the barge, waiting, breathing and sniffing. To get to the southern plateau, you'll have to use a teleporter. I've marked it on your map - it's not far from the burnt farmstead.</text>
		</string>
	<string id="tasks_noah_dialog_4">
		<text>I've changed my mind.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="task_1_noah_done_0">
		<text>Here's an Armsel Protecta.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="task_1_noah_done_1">
		<text>...Impressive. Thanks for the help. Now those beasts will think three times before snooping around here.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="task_2_noah_done_0">
		<text>I got those snorks, there were quite a few of them. What were they hunting you for?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="task_2_noah_done_1">
		<text>I'm not sure. I used to head over there once in a while to clean them up, but I don't have any more time for that... have to keep an eye on the puppies. So, thank you for your help.</text>
	</string>

	

	<string id="zat_a2_stalker_barmen_actor_info_0">
		<text>Tell me what life is like here.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_a2_stalker_barmen_actor_info_1">
		<text>That's a broad topic. Try asking some specific questions and I'll do my best to answer them.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_a2_stalker_barmen_actor_info_1111">
		<text>What do stalkers do here?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_a2_stalker_barmen_actor_info_11111">
		<text>Ask yourself that, pal. They step ashore from Skadovsk to explore the terrain and search for artefacts, shooting back at everything and everyone who comes rushing at them. They come back on Skadovsk to get drunk and talk trash... enjoy some R&amp;R before the next raid... though, when an emission hits, it's quite a different scene. That's when we all sit tight and remember those who didn't make it to a cover in time...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_a2_stalker_barmen_actor_info_1112">
		<text>What drove stalkers to the center of the Zone?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_a2_stalker_barmen_actor_info_11121">
		<text>A funny question. Some were out to discover the next artefact goldmine. Some were driven here by the Oasis rumours. Others sought the Wish Granter. And then there are the base human desires: greed and curiosity... Everyone's got their reasons. I'm sure you have yours, too.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_a2_stalker_barmen_actor_info_1113">
		<text>How did you end up here?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_a2_stalker_barmen_actor_info_11131">
		<text>I came here with Grouse after the Scorcher was disabled. But I'm sure that's not what you really wanna know, am I right? I deal mainly in artefacts. The outside is full of trinkets already, so valuable customers want the rare stuff. That's why I decided to set up a stalker camp, where real high-value articles can still be found. I mean, when a stalker comes back with his loot, what does he really need? A cold one in his hand and good ol' human contact, that's what. And that's what the Skadovsk is all about.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_a2_stalker_barmen_actor_info_1114">
		<text>What do you think about bandits?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_a2_stalker_barmen_actor_info_11141">
		<text>Well, it's like this: I got nothing against 'em on board the Skadovsk, so long as they act decent. After all, you don't meet total douche bags all that often. Some of them are actually former stalkers. Who knows, one of them poor bastards might actually decide to give up the crook business before he catches a bullet... Life is full of surprises.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_a2_stalker_barmen_actor_info_1115">
		<text>Nah, that's okay. Forget about it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_a2_stalker_barmen_actor_info_11151">
		<text>If you say so.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="zat_b7_stalkers_victims_dialog_11">
		<text>Howdy, stalker. I'm busy right now. Let's talk later, okay?</text>
	</string>

	<string id="zat_b22_stalker_medic_start_1">
		<text>What brings you here?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_b22_stalker_medic_dialog_start_21">
		<text>I'm listening.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_b22_stalker_medic_dialog_start_22">
		<text>Hi, do you need help?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_b22_stalker_medic_dialog_start_23">
		<text>Hello.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_b22_stalker_medic_need_health_care_0">
		<text>I need medical assistance.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_b22_stalker_medic_need_health_care_1">
		<text>I'll see what I can do.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_b22_stalker_medic_need_health_care_2">
		<text>I'll take a look... Hmm... You look fine to me. You don't have any wounds or show signs of radiation sickness. You should be good to go.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_b22_stalker_medic_need_health_care_111">
		<text>I'll be honest with you - of course, you can use a medical kit or two and everything will be fine. I can solve most of your problems for say 1,850 RU. I have a very good serum that will put you back on your feet in no time. But all these glowing radioactive particles will still be flowing around in your body. No, that the serum cannot fix. But for another 1,480 RU on top, I'll get all this shit out of you. So, what have you decided?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_b22_stalker_medic_need_health_care_11">
		<text>What? Is everything so bad?</text>
	</string>

	<string id="zat_b22_stalker_medic_need_health_care_1111">
		<text>Well, take your money and get to work. Health is more important than money.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_b22_stalker_medic_need_health_care_1112">
		<text>Okay, fix only the radiation. The wounds I can bandage myself.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_b22_stalker_medic_need_health_care_1113">
		<text>You know what, Doc? Fix yourself!</text>
	</string>

	<string id="zat_b22_stalker_medic_need_health_care_11111">
		<text>One moment, please... Yes, everything should be fine now. You can go.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="zat_b22_stalker_medic_need_health_care_11112">
		<text>Well, you won't die from weak radiation. For now at least. But I won't take any responsibility if you bleed to death. Good luck, buddy!</text>
	</string>

	<string id="zat_b22_stalker_medic_need_health_care_11113">
		<text>As you wish, comrade. Don't blame me if you suddenly cease to live.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="zat_b18_noah_start_11">
		<text>Who are you?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_b18_noah_start_111">
		<text>A stalker. We've met before.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_b18_noah_start_1111">
		<text>I don't recall... Anyway, what do you need?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_b18_noah_start_112">
		<text>A stalker. Just a stalker.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_b18_noah_start_1121">
		<text>I see. Looking for refuge in the Ark? Feel yourself at home.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_b18_noah_start_113">
		<text>None of your business.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_b18_noah_start_21">
		<text>Ah, it's you. What do you want?</text>
	</string>

	<string id="zat_b3_stalker_tech_start_15">
		<text>A wise choice, my friend. Gotta keep your gun in mint condition... And if you got a bottle or two on you, I can make it upgrade galore in here. Want a parachute sewn to your shotgun? I can do that, hehe.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_b3_stalker_tech_drink_1_0">
		<text>Got some booze. Want a shot?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_b3_stalker_tech_drink_1_2">
		<text>Nah, I'm off the bottle, man. When I saw item 62, I thought, 'That's it, I'm having the jumps...' See, booze just screws you up. Not a part of a healthy diet. And if I'm gone, who's gonna hammer out ammo for your Gauss rifle?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_b3_stalker_tech_drink_2_0">
		<text>Here's another bottle for you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="zat_b3_stalker_tech_drink_3_0">
		<text>I've got a third one, if you need more.</text>
	</string>

<!-- Nimble -->
	<string id="player_inquiry">
		<text>I'd like to upgrade a gun.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="nimble_response">
		<text>Okay, what kind of gun do you want upgraded? And by the way, don't even think of giving me a trashed gun to work with. Every part and the gun itself has to be at least at 90% condition if you want any work to take place.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="option_pistol_0">
		<text>A pistol.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="option_cqc_0">
		<text>A CQC gun.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="option_rifle_0">
		<text>A rifle.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="option_sniper_0">
		<text>A sniper.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="option_pistol_1">
		<text>What kind of pistol?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="option_cqc_1">
		<text>What kind of CQC gun?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="option_rifle_1">
		<text>What kind of rifle?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="option_sniper_1">
		<text>What kind of sniper?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="option_pistol_2_1">
		<text>A 1911 upgraded to make it hit harder [ 50 000 RU ].</text>
	</string>
	<string id="option_pistol_2_2">
		<text>A 1911 upgraded to make it shoot faster [ 70 000 RU ].</text>
	</string>
	<string id="option_pistol_2_3">
		<text>A deagle [ 50 000 RU ].</text>
	</string>
	<string id="option_pistol_2_4">
		<text>A USP [ 30 000 RU ].</text>
	</string>
	<string id="option_cqc_2_1">
		<text>A protecta [ 30 000 RU ].</text>
	</string>
	<string id="option_cqc_2_2">
		<text>A SPAS-12 [ 30 000 RU ].</text>
	</string>
	<string id="option_cqc_2_3">
		<text>A TOZ-34 [ 45 000 RU ].</text>
	</string>
	<string id="option_cqc_2_4">
		<text>An MP5 [ 65 000 RU ].</text>
	</string>
	<string id="option_rifle_2_1">
		<text>A G36 [ 45 000 RU ].</text>
	</string>
	<string id="option_rifle_2_2">
		<text>A groza [ 45 000 RU ].</text>
	</string>
	<string id="option_rifle_2_3">
		<text>A PKM [ 45 000 RU ].</text>
	</string>
	<string id="option_sniper_2_1">
		<text>A DVL-10 Urbana [ 45 000 RU ].</text>
	</string>
	<string id="option_sniper_2_2">
		<text>A DVL-10 Saboteur [ 45 000 RU ].</text>
	</string>
	<string id="option_sniper_2_3">
		<text>An SVU [ 45 000 RU ].</text>
	</string>
	<string id="convo_exit">
		<text>Actually nevermind.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="convo_back">
		<text>What types of weapons can you upgrade again?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="nimble_rant_missing_gun_and_money">
		<text>If you seriously came here to ask me to upgrade a gun you didn't bring, for money you don't have, then I must be Lukashenko, and I'll have you arrested.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="nimble_rant_missing_gun">
		<text>Do you think I grow them in my backyard? Come back when you actually have the gun.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="nimble_rant_missing_money">
		<text>How the hell am I supposed to afford parts if you don't give me any money? Come back with the money and then we'll talk.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="player_acknowledge">
		<text>Okay.</text>
	</string>
</string_table>