<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
	<string id="st_af_ah_o1">
		<text>"Magnet"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ah_o1_descr">
		<text>An almost fully formed artifact composed of an alloy mainly consisting of iron, bismuth, cadmium, and nickel. Forms in fiery anomalies. It has no useful properties, and most stalkers consider it ordinary junk. The only notable feature of this item is its very peculiar torus shape. Due to traces of radiation, it is unsuitable as a souvenir outside the Zone and has little value.</text>
	</string>	

	<string id="st_af_ah_o2">
		<text>"Magnet"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ah_o2_descr">
		<text>An almost fully formed artifact composed of an alloy mainly consisting of iron, bismuth, cadmium, and nickel. Forms in fiery anomalies. It has no useful properties, and most stalkers consider it ordinary junk. The only notable feature of this item is its very peculiar torus shape. Due to traces of radiation, it is unsuitable as a souvenir outside the Zone and has little value.</text>
	</string>	

	<string id="st_af_ah_h1">
		<text>"Sponge"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ah_h1_descr">
		<text>A pale green substance with no definite shape or useful properties. This artifact randomly shifts from solid to semi-liquid state, making it difficult to process and store. Unlike similar artifacts such as "Soul", the slime secreted by this artifact has neither positive nor negative effects on the human body.</text>
	</string>	

	<string id="st_af_ah_h2">
		<text>"Sponge"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ah_h2_descr">
		<text>A pale green substance with no definite shape or useful properties. This artifact randomly shifts from solid to semi-liquid state, making it difficult to process and store. Unlike similar artifacts such as "Soul", the slime secreted by this artifact has neither positive nor negative effects on the human body, aside from a small amount of radiation contained within it.</text>
	</string>	

	<string id="st_af_ah_g1">
		<text>"Lung"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ah_g1_descr">
		<text>A lump of wrinkled clay and organic remains. Separating individual pieces of material seems impossible due to the presence of some unknown and incredibly strong binding agent. Some scientists suggest the artifact is held together by gravitational anomalies contained within, though this remains unproven. A Geiger counter produces almost no sound when brought close to this strange artifact.</text>
	</string>	

	<string id="st_af_ah_g2">
		<text>"Lung"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ah_g2_descr">
		<text>A lump of wrinkled clay and organic remains. Separating individual pieces of material seems impossible due to the presence of some unknown and incredibly strong binding agent. Some scientists suggest the artifact is held together by gravitational anomalies contained within, though this remains unproven. A Geiger counter produces almost no sound when brought close to this strange artifact.</text>
	</string>	

	<string id="st_af_ah_e1">
		<text>"Souvenir"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ah_e1_descr">
		<text>A quartz shard with remarkable purity ranging from 99.5% to 99.9%, formed exclusively in electrical anomalies. Due to the lack of useful properties, this beautiful artifact is not worth much in the Zone. However, collectors and scientists alike will pay a high price for this unique trinket.</text>
	</string>	

	<string id="st_af_ah_e2">
		<text>"Souvenir"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ah_e2_descr">
		<text>A quartz shard with remarkable purity ranging from 99.5% to 99.9%, formed exclusively in electrical anomalies. Due to the lack of useful properties, this beautiful artifact is not worth much in the Zone. However, collectors and scientists alike will pay a high price for this unique trinket.</text>
	</string>	

	<string id="st_af_ah_s1">
		<text>"Arot-8"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ah_s1_descr">
		<text>An experimental and unstable artifact created artificially. Where and under what circumstances it formed is unknown. It appears to enhance the body's natural healing process, but at the same time emits strong bursts of radiation. Prolonged exposure in close proximity to this artifact is not recommended.</text>
	</string>	

	<string id="st_af_ah_f1">
		<text>"Talking Stone"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ah_f1_descr">
		<text>An unprecedented artifact with remarkable properties. It appears to be of organic origin and is highly symmetrical—an unusual trait for artifacts found in the Zone. It increases the structural strength and elasticity of any material it comes into contact with, and if held to the ear, one could swear they hear indistinct whispering voices.</text>
	</string>	

	<string id="st_af_ah_r1">
		<text>"Mycelium"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ah_r1_descr">
		<text>An artifact found only in the Dead Forest south of Laboratory X-9, composed primarily of plant matter. It is believed that strong psi-fields it was exposed to during formation significantly affected its shape and properties. Because of this, it provides a unique opportunity to study the influence of these still poorly understood phenomena.</text>
	</string>	

	<string id="st_af_ah_r2">
		<text>"Mycelium"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ah_r2_descr">
		<text>An artifact found only in the Dead Forest south of Laboratory X-9, composed primarily of plant matter. It is believed that strong psi-fields it was exposed to during formation significantly affected its shape and properties. Because of this, it provides a unique opportunity to study the influence of these still poorly understood phenomena.</text>
	</string>	

	<string id="st_af_ah_r3">
		<text>"Mycelium"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ah_r3_descr">
		<text>An artifact found only in the Dead Forest south of Laboratory X-9, composed primarily of plant matter. It is believed that strong psi-fields it was exposed to during formation significantly affected its shape and properties. Because of this, it provides a unique opportunity to study the influence of these still poorly understood phenomena.</text>
	</string>	

	<string id="st_af_ah_r4">
		<text>"Mycelium"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ah_r4_descr">
		<text>An artifact found only in the Dead Forest south of Laboratory X-9, composed primarily of plant matter. It is believed that strong psi-fields it was exposed to during formation significantly affected its shape and properties. Because of this, it provides a unique opportunity to study the influence of these still poorly understood phenomena.</text>
	</string>	

	<string id="st_af_ah_r5">
		<text>"Mycelium"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ah_r5_descr">
		<text>An artifact found only in the Dead Forest south of Laboratory X-9, composed primarily of plant matter. It is believed that strong psi-fields it was exposed to during formation significantly affected its shape and properties. Because of this, it provides a unique opportunity to study the influence of these still poorly understood phenomena.</text>
	</string>	

	<string id="st_kovalev_pda_name">
		<text>Kovalev's Laptop</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_kovalev_pda_descr">
		<text>The laptop contains data from the latest field study of anomalous zones around the Agroprom Research Institute conducted by Kovalev. Among the files is a map with the exact locations of anomalous zones that I need to investigate.</text>
	</string>	

	<string id="st_pirogov_pda_name">
		<text>Assistant's PDA</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_pirogov_pda_descr">
		<text>PDA of a deceased stalker who helped Candidate Pirogov place prototypes in anomalies in the Garbage area. It contains all the remaining locations I need to scan.</text>
	</string>		

	<string id="st_strelok_pda_name">
		<text>PDA of a deceased stalker</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_strelok_pda_descr">
		<text>PDA of a deceased stalker who successfully marked anomalous zones in the Red Forest but was intercepted by a Monolith squad on the way back. The screen is covered with dried blood, and some buttons do not work.</text>
	</string>		

	<string id="st_chernov_pda_name">
		<text>Operation "Rainbow" Report No. 9: "On the Nature of Artifact Formation"</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_chernov_pda_descr">
		<text>A stack of papers from Laboratory X-19. Most pages are damp and unreadable. However, surviving fragments of images and diagrams contain information about how some artifacts form "on trees" in the forest south of the X-19 laboratory complex.</text>
	</string>		

	<string id="st_vorobushkin_pda_name">
		<text>Memory Module from VNZ "Krug"</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_vorobushkin_pda_descr">
		<text>A module removed from the equipment of the return-tilt sounding station "Krug". Restored by Professor Vorobushkin. Contains a spectrogram of anomalous emissions around the station, as well as a map of their formations.</text>
	</string>	

	<string id="ah_gramota_info">
		<text>Letter of Recommendation</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ah_gramota_desc">
		<text>A personalized letter of appreciation recognizing your contributions to science, personally signed by Academician Skabinsky. Also includes a recommendation to accept the bearer of this document as a candidate at the Chernobyl Zonal Institute.</text>
	</string>	
</string_table>