<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
    <string id="ah_ecolog">
        <text>Researchers</text>
    </string>

    <string id="Quest1_desc">
        <text>Quest description</text>
    </string>
    <string id="Quest1_title">
        <text>First quest title</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="ah_redirect_to_kovalev_quest_title">
        <text>Researchers: Find Professor Kovalev in the Great Swamps</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_redirect_to_kovalev_quest_desc">
        <text>I managed to find out that Professor Kovalev is in the swamps looking for assistants to conduct research. He can be found near the old church in the southern part of the swamps.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="ah_redirect_to_markov_quest_title">
        <text>Researchers: Find Docent Markov</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_redirect_to_markov_quest_desc">
        <text>Docent Markov needs my help. He is located near the ecologists' bunker in Yantar.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="ah_redirect_to_pirogov_quest_title">
        <text>Researchers: Find Candidate Pirogov</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_redirect_to_pirogov_quest_desc">
        <text>Candidate of Sciences Pirogov needs my help finding artifacts. He is currently in the Dark Valley. I hope he's still alive.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="ah_redirect_to_chernov_quest_title">
        <text>Researchers: Find Staff Member Chernov</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_redirect_to_chernov_quest_desc">
        <text>Find Senior Researcher Chernov, who is located in one of the abandoned houses near the Army Warehouses.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="ah_redirect_to_juk_quest_title">
        <text>Researchers: Find Professor Zhuk</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_redirect_to_juk_quest_desc">
        <text>Professor Vladislav Zhuk needs my help. I can find him somewhere near the Yanov railway station, in Jupiter.</text>
    </string>	

    <string id="ah_redirect_to_vorobushkin_quest_title">
        <text>Researchers: Find Docent Vorobushkin</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_redirect_to_vorobushkin_quest_desc">
        <text>Docent Vorobushkin is somewhere in Zaton. I need to find him to continue helping the research group.</text>
    </string>	

    <string id="ah_redirect_to_skabinsky_quest_title">
        <text>Researchers: Find Academician Skabinsky</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_redirect_to_skabinsky_quest_desc">
        <text>Docent Vorobushkin informed me that the head of the research group, Professor Skabinsky, has already moved on and is currently somewhere in the northern part of the Exclusion Zone. I have no idea how he managed to get there, but I need to find him quickly.</text>
    </string>		

    <string id="ah_fail_skabinsky_quest_title">
        <text>Researchers: Find Academician Skabinsky</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_fail_skabinsky_quest_desc">
        <text>Vorobushkin's calculations aren't entirely accurate, but it's worth a shot. Skabinsky thinks their results led to the "Ash Heap" anomaly. I need to find Skabinsky, who has gone ahead and is waiting for me there.</text>
    </string>	
	
    <string id="ah_kovalev_quest1_title">
        <text>Researchers: Bring Kovalev three anomalous samples</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_kovalev_quest1_desc">
        <text>A research group is searching for anomalous formations in the swamps. Assistant Kovalev asked me to find three samples.</text>
    </string>	
    <string id="ah_bol_o1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Lower Ash Heap" anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_bol_o1_desc">
        <text>One of the samples is located in the "Lower Ash Heap" anomaly.</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="ah_bol_o2_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Swamp Hollow" anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_bol_o2_desc">
        <text>One of the samples is located in the "Swamp Hollow" anomaly.</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="ah_bol_g1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Western Swamp" anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_bol_g1_desc">
        <text>One of the samples is located in the "Western Swamp" anomaly.</text>
    </string>		
	
	<string id="ah_bol_e1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Sparker" anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_bol_e1_desc">
        <text>One of the samples is located in the "Sparker" anomaly.</text>
    </string>	

    <string id="ah_kovalev_quest2_title">
        <text>Researchers: Bring Kovalev a laptop and three artifacts</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_kovalev_quest2_desc">
        <text>Assistant Kovalev was taking measurements in Agroprom when an unexpected bandit attack caught him off guard. He dropped his laptop, which contains the data needed to find the artifacts, at the stalker base. I need to return his laptop to him, as well as find three artifacts.</text>
    </string>	
    <string id="ah_agr_pda_title">
        <text>Find Kovalev's laptop</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_agr_pda_desc">
        <text>Find Kovalev's abandoned laptop. Apparently, it is located in an EMP zone on the second floor of a building, and getting it will require passing through electrical anomalies and a small area of psy-influence.</text>
    </string>	
	<string id="ah_agr_none_title">
        <text>Find the artifact. Location unknown.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_agr_none_desc">
        <text>I need to find an artifact in Agroprom. The exact location can be found by recovering Kovalev's laptop.</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="ah_agr_g1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Old Claws" anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_agr_g1_desc">
        <text>The artifact is located in the "Old Claws" anomaly.</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="ah_agr_g2_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Anomalous Hollow"</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_agr_g2_desc">
        <text>The artifact is located in the "Anomalous Hollow".</text>
    </string>	
	<string id="ah_agr_h1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Bird Carousel" anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_agr_h1_desc">
        <text>The artifact is located in the "Bird Carousel" anomaly.</text>
    </string>	

    <string id="ah_markov_quest1_title">
        <text>Researchers: Bring Markov three samples from Yantar</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_markov_quest1_desc">
        <text>Docent Markov works separately from the group of scientists in Yantar. He asked me to find anomalous samples that I can track down using my detector.</text>
    </string>	
    <string id="ah_yan_o1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Grabbing Hands" anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_yan_o1_desc">
        <text>One of the samples is located in the "Grabbing Hands" anomaly.</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="ah_yan_h1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Poisoned Lake" anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_yan_h1_desc">
        <text>One of the samples is located in the "Poisoned Lake" anomaly.</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="ah_yan_h2_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Concrete Dump" anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_yan_h2_desc">
        <text>One of the samples is located in the "Concrete Dump" anomaly. You will need psy-protection to reach it.</text>
    </string>		
	
    <string id="ah_markov_quest2_title">
        <text>Researchers: Bring Markov three artifacts from the Wild Territory</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_markov_quest2_desc">
        <text>Professor Markov reported that we need to expand the search area. The Wild Territory is located near Yantar. There are anomalous formations there too, at three different points of interest.</text>
    </string>	
    <string id="ah_dt_o1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Radioactive Workshop"</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_dt_o1_desc">
        <text>This anomaly is not marked on the map. The workshop itself can be found near the checkpoint to Rostok, and the area is highly radioactive.</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="ah_dt_e1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Electra" anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_dt_e1_desc">
        <text>The target is located somewhere around the Electra anomaly. You should grab more bolts or empty casings.</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="ah_dt_e2_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Sparkling Dusk" anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_dt_e2_desc">
        <text>An anomaly in the tunnel under Rostok, also known as "Sparkling Dusk". It seems there should be a safe passage...</text>
    </string>	

    <string id="ah_markov_quest3_title">
        <text>Researchers: Bring Markov three artifacts from the area near X-16</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_markov_quest3_desc">
        <text>I need to find three artifacts near the old X-16 laboratory complex. Because of the "Brain Scorcher", this will be impossible without proper psy-protection. Professor Sakharov should be able to help me with this problem.</text>
    </string>	
    <string id="ah_yan_e1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "St. Elmo's Fire" anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_yan_e1_desc">
        <text>The object is located in the "St. Elmo's Fire" anomaly. It's electrical, you'll need bolts.</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="ah_yan_e2_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Wandering Lights" anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_yan_e2_desc">
        <text>The object is located in the "Wandering Lights" anomaly.</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="ah_yan_g1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact somewhere on the factory grounds</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_yan_g1_desc">
        <text>None of the researchers have gone this far. But a perfectly clear anomalous signal is coming from somewhere among the buildings on the Yantar factory grounds. I need to be careful.</text>
    </string>	

    <string id="ah_pirogov_quest1_title">
        <text>Researchers: Bring Candidate Pirogov three samples from the Dark Valley</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_pirogov_quest1_desc">
        <text>The Dark Valley is dangerous for a quiet artifact hunt. Mutants and bandits could be lurking around any corner. Nevertheless, I need to bring three anomalous samples from there for Professor Pirogov.</text>
    </string>	
    <string id="ah_td_o1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Comet" anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_td_o1_desc">
        <text>A fascinating anomaly that few have explored. It's located at the end of a long corridor where the "Comet" travels. The entrance is near the bandit base in the north.</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="ah_td_o2_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Dark Rift" anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_td_o2_desc">
        <text>The anomalous sample is located somewhere in the "Dark Rift" anomaly.</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="ah_td_e1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Deadly Cloud" anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_td_e1_desc">
        <text>The "Deadly Cloud" anomaly is located on the territory of the bandit base, so if you don't fight your way in, you'll have to sneak in.</text>
    </string>		
	
    <string id="ah_pirogov_quest2_title">
        <text>Researchers: Bring Candidate Pirogov three samples from the Truck Cemetery</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_pirogov_quest2_desc">
        <text>Moving further, deep into the Zone. Our interest is now drawn to the Truck Cemetery. It doesn't differ much from the Dark Valley in the abundance of sudden mutants and bandits.</text>
    </string>	
    <string id="ah_kt_g1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Ravine" anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_kt_g1_desc">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Ravine" anomaly.</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="ah_kt_o1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Roadside Picnic" anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_kt_o1_desc">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Roadside Picnic" anomaly, just make sure you don't become the picnic yourself.</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="ah_kt_h1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Badlands" anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_kt_h1_desc">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Badlands" anomaly.</text>
    </string>	

    <string id="ah_pirogov_quest3_title">
        <text>Researchers: Bring Candidate Pirogov a PDA and two experimental samples</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_pirogov_quest3_desc">
        <text>The stalker-assistant who was studying anomalies on Pirogov's behalf before me has gone missing. Valuable information about the studied anomalies has disappeared with him. I need to find the assistant and his PDA, retrieve the data on the anomalies, and then extract the objects from the anomalies for study.</text>
    </string>	
    <string id="ah_sv_pda_title">
        <text>Find the missing stalker's PDA</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_sv_pda_desc">
        <text>Most likely, the stalker got caught by bandits. But our primary concern is the important information on his PDA. It seems his signal was coming from somewhere near the Flea Market close to the checkpoint; I should start looking there.</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="ah_sv_g1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Witches' Ring" anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_sv_g1_desc">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Witches' Ring" anomaly. It's toxic and large, it won't be an easy task.</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="ah_sv_h1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Soda" anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_sv_h1_desc">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Soda" anomaly.</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="ah_sv_none_title">
        <text>Find the artifact using coordinates from the missing stalker's PDA</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_sv_none_desc">
        <text>The location of the desired sample is unknown. First, you must find the PDA of the stalker who was working for Pirogov before me.</text>
    </string>		
	
    <string id="ah_chernov_quest1_title">
        <text>Researchers: Bring Chernov three artifacts from the Army Warehouses territory</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_chernov_quest1_desc">
        <text>You need to find three different artifacts and bring them to Professor Chernov. This will be a real test, the Army Warehouses is quite a dangerous place.</text>
    </string>	
    <string id="ah_mil_h1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Acid Swamp" anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_mil_h1_desc">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Acid Swamp" anomaly.</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="ah_mil_g1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Carousel" anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_mil_g1_desc">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Carousel" anomaly.</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="ah_mil_o1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Steamer" anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_mil_o1_desc">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Steamer" anomaly. A harsh anomaly radiating extreme heat from burning mines. You shouldn't linger there.</text>
    </string>	
	
    <string id="ah_chernov_quest3_title">
        <text>Researchers: Bring Chernov a stalker's PDA and two artifacts from the Red Forest</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_chernov_quest3_desc">
        <text>Professor Chernov tasked some stalker with creating maps of anomalous zones in the Red Forest. The work was finished, but the stalker had to flee the territory before he could transmit the data. I need to find his PDA, which he dropped somewhere in the tunnels to Limansk, near the bridge.</text>
    </string>	
    <string id="ah_les_pda_title">
        <text>Find the missing stalker's PDA in the western tunnels</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_les_pda_desc">
        <text>While running from Monolith fanatics, the stalker dropped his PDA with research data somewhere in the western tunnels. I need to find it to figure out which anomalous zones I have to explore.</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="ah_les_o1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Symbiont" anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_les_o1_desc">
        <text>After analyzing the map in the stalker's PDA, I managed to identify the "Symbiont" anomaly as one that requires investigation.</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="ah_les_e1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Underground Thunderstorm" anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_les_e1_desc">
        <text>After analyzing the map in the stalker's PDA, I managed to identify the "Underground Thunderstorm" anomaly as one that requires investigation. It is located underground, in the northwestern mines.</text>
    </string>	
	<string id="ah_les_none_title">
        <text>Find the artifact somewhere in the Red Forest</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_les_none_desc">
        <text>The Red Forest is dangerous and treacherous. Fortunately, the lost stalker's PDA has a map with the anomalies we need. To find the artifacts, you first need to find this PDA somewhere in the western tunnels.</text>
    </string>		
	
    <string id="ah_chernov_quest4_title">
        <text>Researchers: Find an artificial artifact</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_chernov_quest4_desc">
        <text>According to Chernov, artifacts can be created artificially. It's worth searching the house of a scientist who might have been doing this even before the catastrophe. Apparently, his house was located near the place where the Generators anomaly is now designated. Perhaps this is no coincidence.</text>
    </string>	
	
    <string id="ah_chernov_quest5_title">
        <text>Researchers: Visit the X-19 complex</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_chernov_quest5_desc">
        <text>Laboratory X-19, known as the "Bunker", apparently engaged in the creation of artificial artifacts. Now this laboratory is destroyed, but documents of interest to us could have survived. We need to find them. Perhaps they will tell us where we can find an "artifact farm".</text>
    </string>	
    <string id="ah_rad_pda_title">
        <text>Search the entrance to X-19</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_rad_pda_desc">
        <text>Perhaps this is where something pointing to the famous "artifact beds" was left behind. I need to check the entrance to the laboratory for documents.</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="ah_rad_r_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the Dead Forest</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_rad_r_desc">
        <text>According to the documents, the artifacts were grown in the forest south of the complex. There are only very rough, blurry coordinates of the trees that should be examined for anomalous objects, so I'll probably have to comb the entire forest.</text>
    </string>		

    <string id="ah_chernov_quest6_title">
        <text>Researchers: Find two artifacts in the Dead City</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_chernov_quest6_desc">
        <text>For a complete matrix of the Zone, scientists need to cover all territories. Now our goal is the Dead City, which they still haven't explored. Professor Chernov gave me approximate coordinates for two anomalies he is interested in.</text>
    </string>	
    <string id="ah_mg_o1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the administrative building</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="ah_mg_o1_desc">
        <text>Find the artifact in the City Committee building. The scanner should help.</text>
    </string>
	<string id="ah_mg_g1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the Palace of Culture</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_mg_g1_desc">
        <text>Find the artifact in the Palace of Culture.</text>
    </string>		

    <string id="ah_juk_quest1_title">
        <text>Researchers: Find three anomalous samples in the vicinity of Jupiter</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_juk_quest1_desc">
        <text>Professor Zhuk is compiling a spectrogram of samples from different anomalous zones in Jupiter. He asked me to find these samples.</text>
    </string>	
    <string id="ah_up_g1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Bitumen" anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_up_g1_desc">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Bitumen" anomaly. It's a hot place; without thermal protection it will be difficult.</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="ah_up_h1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Concrete Bath" anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_up_h1_desc">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Concrete Bath" anomaly. It seems experienced stalkers avoided the anomaly itself by jumping along the remains of the concrete columns.</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="ah_up_h2_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Anomalous Grove"</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_up_h2_desc">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Anomalous Grove". You will need serious protection against toxins.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="ah_juk_quest2_title">
        <text>Researchers: Find the remaining samples for Professor Zhuk</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_juk_quest2_desc">
        <text>The second set of samples is located in the remaining anomalous zones, and Professor Zhuk gave me exact coordinates to explore them.</text>
    </string>	
    <string id="ah_up_e2_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Train" anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_up_e2_desc">
        <text>The unmarked "Train" anomaly is not far from the scientists' bunker. No one looks for artifacts there, but that doesn't mean the samples we're interested in aren't there. Most likely, there's a hatch somewhere in the train cars that will let you get inside.</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="ah_up_e1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the northwestern tunnel</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_up_e1_desc">
        <text>This tunnel is poorly explored, which means it's interesting. Rumor has it that there might be a controller's lair in there.</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="ah_up_g2_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Volkhov" complex</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_up_g2_desc">
        <text>The old anti-aircraft missile complex was abandoned due to the abundance of underground anomalies. There are sure to be the samples we need there... along with mutants.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="ah_juk_quest3_title">
        <text>Researchers: Find four samples in Pripyat and its surroundings</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_juk_quest3_desc">
        <text>Pripyat is practically inaccessible to scientists due to the presence of Monolith. However, samples from there are critical to completing their research. I need to track them down.</text>
    </string>	
    <string id="ah_p_h1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Vine" anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_p_h1_desc">
        <text>The Vine is a most amazing anomalous formation in the eastern part of Pripyat. The sample should be somewhere up high, so I'll have to climb.</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="ah_p_g1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the school</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_p_g1_desc">
        <text>A giant gravitational anomaly in the area of the old school. It covers several floors at once, so it's worth checking the interior rooms.</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="ah_p_g2_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Avangard" anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_p_g2_desc">
        <text>The instrument readings are off the charts there. Even from a distance of several kilometers around the Avangard stadium, a multitude of anomalous formations are detected. A sample from that territory is absolutely mandatory for us.</text>
    </string>
	<string id="ah_p_e1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in an unmarked electrical anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_p_e1_desc">
        <text>Find the artifact in an anomaly located somewhere in the southern regions of Pripyat.</text>
    </string>	
	
    <string id="ah_vorobushkin_quest1_title">
        <text>Researchers: Find a memory module and three samples for Docent Vorobushkin</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_vorobushkin_quest1_desc">
        <text>Vorobushkin was able to repair and use old equipment from the Krug Antenna Complex. He left his memory module there, which contains the coordinates of the anomalous zones from which the samples must be extracted.</text>
    </string>	
    <string id="ah_zat_pda_title">
        <text>Find the memory module at the Krug Antenna Complex</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_zat_pda_desc">
        <text>Docent Vorobushkin placed scanning equipment at the "Krug" radar station. This is how he gathered all the necessary information about the anomalies in Zaton. Vorobushkin is currently in a safe place, but the memory module was left at the station. To get the coordinates of the anomalies needed for the study, you must retrieve this module.</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="ah_zat_h1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Swamp" anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_zat_h1_desc">
        <text>A strange territory with an abundance of gravitational and toxic formations. You need to be careful not to lose all your limbs.</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="ah_zat_h2_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Pineoak" anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_zat_h2_desc">
        <text>Reminiscent of the "Vine", and toxic. Most likely, you'll manage to climb to the top here too?</text>
    </string>
	<string id="ah_zat_none_title">
        <text>Find the artifact somewhere in Zaton</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_zat_none_desc">
        <text>In order to find out the exact location of the anomalies that need to be investigated, you must download the scan readings from Vorobushkin's memory module.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="ah_vorobushkin_quest2_title">
        <text>Researchers: Find three more artifacts in Zaton for Docent Vorobushkin</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_vorobushkin_quest2_desc">
        <text>To finish compiling the spectrogram of different artifacts, Vorobushkin asked me to scan the remaining three anomalous zones in Zaton.</text>
    </string>	
    <string id="ah_zat_o1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Boiler" anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_zat_o1_desc">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Boiler" anomaly. You'll need either good thermal protection or fast legs.</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="ah_zat_g1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Claw" anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_zat_g1_desc">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Claw" anomaly. This gravitational anomaly intersects with a network of tunnels. Scan data suggests that the sample has moved somewhere down there.</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="ah_zat_g2_title">
        <text>Find the artifact on the Preobrazhensky Bridge</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_zat_g2_desc">
        <text>Not all anomalies are marked on the map. The Preobrazhensky Bridge, although intact, is impassable due to severe anomalies. You need to find a sample there.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="ah_skabinsky_quest1_title">
        <text>Researchers: Bring the "Talking Stone" to Academician Skabinsky</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_skabinsky_quest1_desc">
        <text>The final phase. We trampled the whole Zone for this moment. The artifact that the research group led by Academician Skabinsky dreams of getting by any means. I need to hurry, he's waiting for me in Zaton.</text>
    </string>	
    <string id="ah_gen_f1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the "Anomalous Canyon" giga-anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_gen_f1_desc">
        <text>Perhaps this place can be called the center of the Zone. This is where all the noosphere disturbances begin. The scanner reports underground activity, so you should look for a way down, and stay careful.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="cs_story_task0_name">
        <text>Last Dawn: Return the scanner to Spore</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_story_task0_name1">
        <text>Last Dawn: Retrieve the scanner from the anomaly in the southwestern part of the swamps</text>
    </string>

    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_story_name">
        <text>Last Dawn: Return to Cold</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_story_name1">
        <text>Last Dawn: Repel the Renegade attack</text>
    </string>

    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_story_name3">
        <text>Last Dawn: Return to Cold</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_story_name4">
        <text>Last Dawn: Clear the southeastern farmstead of Renegades</text>
    </string>

    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_story_descr">
        <text>Help Clear Sky hold the pump station.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_story_descr2">
        <text>Help the Clear Sky assault team capture the road to the Cordon.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="cs_story_task0_descr">
        <text>The scanner is located in an arch-anomaly, south of the western tower and directly northwest of the Clear Sky base.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_story_task2_name">
        <text>Last Dawn: Bring the PDA to Spore</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_story_task2_descr">
        <text>Crutch died in a fight with bloodsuckers, but I managed to retrieve his PDA.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_story_task1_name">
        <text>Last Dawn: In search of the scout</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_story_task1_descr">
        <text>I need to find the Clear Sky scout named Crutch before some beast drags him off to its lair. Spore reported that the last signal came from the north of the Swamps, by the road.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_story_task3_start_name">
        <text>Last Dawn: Meet with Cold</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_story_task3_start_descr">
        <text>Cold reported that the scout's PDA has been decrypted and he's waiting to meet with me.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task4_storytask_name">
        <text>Last Dawn: Meet with the mercenary Scar</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task4_storytask_descr">
        <text>I managed to find out where Scar is located. Now my task is to learn what he knows about the missing Clear Sky members.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task5_storytask_name">
        <text>Last Dawn: Fight off the mutants</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task5_storytask_name1">
        <text>Last Dawn: Talk to Scar</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task5_storytask_descr">
        <text>A pack of pseudodogs caught our scent, so we'll have to fight them off.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task3_storytask_name">
        <text>Last Dawn: Find out about Scar</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task3_storytask_descr">
        <text>I need to ask Sidorovich about the mercenary named Scar.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task9_storytask_name">
        <text>Last Dawn: Talk to Strider</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task9_storytask_descr">
        <text>I need to bring the decryptor to Strider. His squad is located in the Jupiter surroundings, at the checkpoint south of Yanov station.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task11_storytask_name">
        <text>Last Dawn: Talk to Strider</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task11_storytask_descr">
        <text>Scar reported that the surviving Clear Sky members might be among the ranks of the Monolith Outcasts. Their squad is located in the Jupiter surroundings, at the checkpoint. I need to find the squad leader, Strider, and gather all the information about the missing people.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task10_storytask_name">
        <text>Last Dawn: Talk to Cold</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task10_storytask_descr">
        <text>I have completed my task. I need to report back to Cold and let him know his people are still alive.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task8_storytask_name">
        <text>Last Dawn: Repel the counterattack</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task8_storytask_name1">
        <text>Last Dawn: Talk to Strider</text>
    </string>
</string_table>