<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
    <string id="kvartet_1">
        <text>This is Quartet - absence of emissions confirmed, no large enemy concentrations detected. I've requested a squad be dropped at the Radar for reconnaissance. The operation to seize the Center of the Zone is beginning! All special forces and military stalker units, regroup and prepare to move on the ChNPP!</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kvartet_2">
        <text>This is Quartet - we're launching the attack! The enemy has concentrated their forces in three locations: the entrance to the Sarcophagus, the road along the railway tracks, and the main entrance to the station. All units, disperse!</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kvartet_3">
        <text>This is Quartet - we control the southern section of the NPP. Now we need to push north and seize the generators. Stay sharp - Monolith soldiers have taken up concealed sniper positions in the northern part of the station.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kvartet_4">
        <text>This is Quartet - we've taken the generators! Objective complete! All units hold your positions and await further orders. As for you, soldier - collect all available information from the laboratories and report back to command.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kvartet_5">
        <text>This is Quartet - we're launching the attack!</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_cherep_1">
        <text>Mission complete - head to General Voronin. We'll hold things down here.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task1_news">
        <text>Spore: Hey buddy, I need your help. Our scout, Kostyl, sent a distress signal and then went dark. I hope not, but... you should expect the worst. The last SOS we received came from the northern Marshes, somewhere near the road between the farmstead and the Mechanizers' Yard. Can you look for him? If we don't find him by morning, there probably won't be anything left to find.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task1_news1">
        <text>Me: I'll do my best to find him.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task1_news2">
        <text>Kholod: Hey! We've managed to decode Kostyl's PDA. Got a job offer for you, since you're already mixed up in all this. Come on by!</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task8_news3">
        <text>Gamajun: The fanatics are gearing up for an attack! Give 'em hell!</text>
    </string>
</string_table>
