<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>

 <!-- Dusman (Mercenary Leader) -->
 	<string id="find_blackbox_mlr_reward_killer_0">
		<text>Dushman, check this out, I found a flight recorder. I assume it contains knowledge that this outfit would pay a pretty penny for, hmm?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="find_blackbox_mlr_reward_killer_1">
		<text>A military one? Great. That's actually a nice gizmo you've got there - I'll take it off your hands for some paper.</text>
	</string>


<!-- (Mercenary Guide) -->
	<string id="meet_ds_killer_guide_main_base_0">
		<text>How do I get out of here?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="meet_ds_killer_guide_main_base_1">
		<text>This place is surrounded by all sorts of danger, but we've got an underground sewer network. There's a guide who can get you out of the city to one of our few bases, located in southern Zaton.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="meet_ds_killer_guide_main_base_list_0">
		<text>Remind me, where do the routes lead?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="meet_ds_killer_guide_main_base_list_1">
		<text>Your only option is the waste processing plant in southeastern Zaton. It'll cost you eight thousand rubles.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="travel_ds_killer_guide_main_base_0">
		<text>I want to leave the city.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_ds_killer_guide_main_base_1">
		<text>You sure? Our only option is to the north - we'll be arriving at the waste processing station in southern Zaton. Eight thousand rubles.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_ds_killer_guide_main_base_2">
		<text>I'm ready, let's head to Zaton. %c[d_orange][8000 RU]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_ds_killer_guide_main_base_3">
		<text>I've changed my mind.</text>
	</string>
	
	
 <!-- Aslan (Mercenary Barman) -->
	<string id="talk_to_aslan_on_main_base_merk_0">
		<text>Tell me about yourself.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="talk_to_aslan_on_main_base_merk_1"> <!-- Fixed -->
		<text>What's there to tell? I'm the local bartender - but who can tell amidst this crap, yeah? We've been stuck here for days, barely maintaining ourselves. I took part in the defense of the president's palace back then, migrated to Switzerland. Then I came to the Zone. I enjoyed visiting the Bar with friends, drinking and reminiscing of older days... During one of such visits I was offered a place in the the Syndicate. It was barely upholding at the time, so Dushman and I are sort of pioneers in this. So what? The roundabouts are fitting, there are people who've been in Afghanistan and Georgia. But people from the Baltic aren't too eager to come, never mind the first world countries.</text>
	</string>


	<string id="talk_to_aslan_about_lottery_0">
		<text>Heard that you're interested in faction patches.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="talk_to_aslan_about_lottery_1">
		<text>How can I put this? Personally, no, I'm not "interested" in them - the higher-ups want them - I'm just a middle manager for everything, I'd rather deal with stuff that's easier to understand... like tangible goods and straight up cash. What I think it is, with morale being rather low lately and all, that it could be another engaging way for our guys to earn some spoils of war. You know, to keep things interesting and fresh, I guess contract payouts are too predictable nowadays... So, here's how it works: you bring me patches from stalkers, you get a chance to dip into a number of goods that my men gathered, sounds like a good deal, eh?  For fifteen patches of any faction, you have a chance to get artefact containers, medical supplies, tools or artefacts. With thirty patches, you'll have a chance to get rewards of the same kind but upgraded, this time you'll also be able to win some high-end weapons and armor. Oh, and one more thing to note - patches from stronger, better equipped factions mean better rewards, Duty patches for example will tend to have higher payout than from those Bandit thugs. You might ask, "why so generous?"... Because many people prefer to keep the patches for themselves as combat trophies, especially the ones that are worth gloating over, this will ensure that those patches get circulated around, now that there is real value in them.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="talk_to_aslan_about_lottery_2">
		<text>What about you? What are you doing with them all?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="talk_to_aslan_about_lottery_3">
		<text>Not really your business. Just get me the patches, and hope for something good. That's how the lottery works, end of story.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_0">
		<text>I have some patches.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_1">
		<text>Excellent, which ones?</text>
	</string>
		<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_2">
			<text>Clear Sky, twenty patches.</text>
		</string>
		<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_3">
			<text>Freedom, twenty patches.</text>
		</string>
		<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_4">
			<text>Loners, twenty patches.</text>
		</string>
		<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_5">
			<text>Ecologists, twenty patches.</text>
		</string>
		<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_6">
			<text>Bandits, twenty patches.</text>
		</string>
		<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_7">
			<text>Duty, twenty patches.</text>
		</string>
		<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_8">
			<text>Monolith, twenty patches.</text>
		</string>
		<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_9">
			<text>Military, twenty patches.</text>
		</string>
		<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_50">
		     <text>Mercenaries, twenty patches.</text>
		</string>
		<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_53">
		     <text>Renegades, twenty patches.</text>
		</string>
		<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_51">
		    <text>Sin, twenty patches.</text>
		</string>
		<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_52">
		     <text>UNISG, twenty patches.</text>
		</string>									   
		<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_11">
			<text>Clear Sky, thirty patches.</text>
		</string>
		<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_12">
			<text>Freedom, thirty patches.</text>
		</string>
		<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_13">
			<text>Loners, thirty patches.</text>
		</string>
		<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_14">
			<text>Ecologists, thirty patches.</text>
		</string>
		<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_15">
			<text>Bandits, thirty patches.</text>
		</string>
		<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_16">
			<text>Duty, thirty patches.</text>
		</string>
		<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_17">
			<text>Monolith, thirty patches.</text>
		</string>
		<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_18">
			<text>Military, thirty patches.</text>
		</string>
		<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_56">
		     <text>Renegades, thirty patches.</text>
		</string>
		<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_54">
		     <text>Sin, thirty patches.</text>
		</string>
		<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_55">
		     <text>UNISG, thirty patches.</text>
		</string>  
		<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_57">
		     <text>Mercenaries, thirty patches.</text>
		</string>
	<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_10">
		<text>Changed my mind.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_19">
		<text>Here, take it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_20">
		<text>Here, take it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_21">
		<text>Here, take it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_22">
		<text>Here, take it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_23">
		<text>Here, take it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_24">
		<text>Here, take it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_25">
		<text>Here, take it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_26">
		<text>Here, take it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_27">
		<text>Here, take it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_28">
		<text>Here, take it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_29">
		<text>Here, take it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_30">
		<text>Here, take it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_31">
		<text>Here, take it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_34">
		<text>Here, take it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_35">
		<text>Here, take it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_36">
		<text>Here, take it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_40">
		<text>Here, take it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_41">
		<text>Here, take it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_42">
		<text>Here, take it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_43">
		<text>Here, take it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_44">
		<text>Here, take it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_45">
		<text>You landed on an artefact application container. The materials here are better than the improvised stuff from what I've been told by the scientists, should provide some pretty good radiation shielding from artefacts.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_46">
		<text>Here's an army medical package, we've stockpiled plenty of these off dead Military and Duty soldiers. Contains most of the staple items you'd find in a basic med pack, but got some extra utility items as well.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_47">
		<text>An advanced tool set here for ya. This one includes some precision tools for working with more complex equipment.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_48">
		<text>You now got your hands on an artefact application module, a piece of brilliant engineering from some the best scientists. You will not find anything better in the Zone for personal carry of Artefacts. Let's add three empty artefacts to that, you just hit the jackpot!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_49">
		<text>Ding ding ding! We got a winner, prestine MP7 with some attachments and AP ammo!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_58">
		<text>This advanced toolkit is pretty sweet, and it's now yours! Got some of the best tools an electrical or mechanical technician could ask for, at least in the Zone anyway.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_59">
		<text>Here's some AP 7.62x51 ammo and some grenades, that's a whole lot of damage!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_60">
		<text>AP Slugs for you, that's about 30 dead freedomers pal.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lottery_ds_aslan_mlr_61">
		<text>God damn, you won the gun lottery jackpot, congratulations, Stalker! Don't ask me where I found this beast of a gun though, I didn't find it, someone else did, two identical one in fact! He owed me 25,000 rubles though, with some heavy interests, and made due with one of them to pay off his debt. Hopefully you'll never have to give up this monster of a gun to pay off your debt, eh? </text>
	</string>

	<string id="aslan_st_0">
		<text>What's the current situation?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="aslan_st_1">
		<text>Well, the Syndicate only has one central base in the Zone, and it's right here. The path to Yantar is cut off because of the psy-installation, and crowds of zombies sometimes come out of there, along with mutants. Limansk has gone to shit - it's a maze full of dangers. The Red Forest is even more dangerous, since Monolith fighters have settled at the bridge to Limansk while the rest of the area is crawling with mutants. At the Army Warehouses in the east, it's all Freedom territory.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="aslan_st_2">
		<text>Go on.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="aslan_st_3">
		<text>As for any dangers, you'll see those for yourself. Keep in mind, though; when carrying out orders, you've got a job to do, and any emotions are just gonna distract you. Put those aside... There's no room for emotion, no room for morality - only intellect and calculation. And regarding other paths, the safest route is through Limansk. There's plenty of closed space where you'll be safe from sniper fire, and there is shelter where you can hide from firefights, as well as anomalies. The area's quite unpredictable, however - never gonna know what exactly's around the corner.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="aslan_st_4">
		<text>You say the base is central. Does that mean there are any other outposts?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="aslan_st_5">
		<text>There are two minor ones that I know of. The first one is in Zaton, at the edge of the northern marshes. The second one is in the southwest part of the Pripyat outskirts. We've also got a group stationed in the Wild Territory, and you can find our squads in different parts of the Zone when they carry out contracts.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="aslan_st_6">
		<text>So anything north of Limansk is Monolith territory.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="aslan_st_7">
		<text>Pretty much. There's an old hospital not far from Limansk. No point in going there - the path to the Chernobyl NPP, as well as the one leading to Yantar are both cut off by psy-emissions.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="aslan_st_8">
		<text>Understood, thanks for the info.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="information_about_stash_aslan_0">
		<text>Heard you got information on stashes.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="information_about_stash_aslan_1">
		<text>You heard right. We always keep an eye on loot after raids. It's yours for six and a half thousand.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="information_about_stash_aslan1_0">
		<text>Any paid stashes location available? %c[d_orange][6500 RU]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="information_about_stash_aslan1_1">
		<text>Sweet. Enjoy.</text>
	</string>

</string_table>
