<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>

    <string id="test_dialog_0">
        <text>Do I need a test assignment?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="test_dialog_1">
        <text>Here's a test assignment.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="test_dialog_2">
        <text>I'll find it.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="test_dialog_3">
        <text>No need.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="test_dialog_4">
        <text>Alright \n</text>
    </string>
    <string id="test_dialog_end_0">
        <text>I completed the quest</text>
    </string>
    <string id="test_dialog_end_1">
        <text>Excellent\n</text>
    </string>
    <string id="test_dialog_end_2">
        <text>Where's my reward?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="test_dialog_end_3">
        <text>Here it is</text>
    </string>
    <string id="test_dialog_end_4">
        <text>Thanks.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="test_dialog_end_4">
        <text>Thanks.</text>
    </string>	
	
    <string id="sarik_dialog_0">
        <text>You're one of the eggheads, right? Tell me, does anyone around here take orders for artifacts?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="sarik_dialog_1">
        <text>If the artifacts are decent, it's either the traders or the guys at the bunker. Unless... there's a group nearby, also into artifacts. But they're not after just any - they want specific artefacts. No properties, barely worth anything, so nobody bothers with them. You won't make much money, but you'd build a good rep with the ecologists.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="sarik_dialog_2">
        <text>Interesting. How do I find them?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="sarik_dialog_3">
        <text>Forget it. I'm not busting my ass for pennies...</text>
    </string>
    <string id="sarik_dialog_4">
        <text>They're spread out across the Zone. Last time I spoke to one, he'd set up camp in a church out on the Marshes. His surname was either Kovalev or Kovalyov - something like that. Anyway, if you decide to go for it, I'd start with him.</text>
    </string>
	
<!-- Meeting the scientists -->	
    <string id="meet_ah_ti_kto_takoy">
        <text>How's the research going?</text>
    </string>	
    <string id="meet_ah_1">
        <text>What research... I finished my part of the work a long time ago, and now I just need someone to go out and find the samples I need. The problem is that nobody wants to take the job once they hear there's no real money in it.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="meet_ah_2">
        <text>Care to elaborate?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="meet_ah_no">
        <text>Don't give up - you'll find someone.</text>
    </string>	
    <string id="meet_ah_4">
        <text>For the current experiment, I need someone to check a few anomalies and collect some radioactive dirt. These are almost-formed artifacts, but they're ranked even below junk-tier, so stalkers don't bother picking them up. They can be detected the same way as regular artifacts - through a detector.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="meet_ah_5">
        <text>Sounds simple enough. Here's the deal: I'll bring you your dirt out of the goodness of my heart, and you toss me a little something for the trouble. I won't ask for much.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="meet_ah_6">
        <text>Get me a detector and I'm in.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="meet_ah_7">
        <text>Thank you so much... I didn't expect anyone to come along so easily. In that case, I'll upload all the coordinates of the anomalous fields I need to your PDA.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="meet_ah_8">
        <text>Thank you so much... I didn't expect anyone to come along so easily. I'll give you one of my detectors then. It's a bit dated, but it'll react to the samples I need. In that case, I'll upload all the coordinates of the anomalous fields I need to your PDA.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="cancel_ah_0">
        <text>I'm here about the assignment.</text>
    </string>	
    <string id="cancel_ah_1">
        <text>Found the samples?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cancel_ah_2">
        <text>No, I need more time.</text>
    </string>	
    <string id="cancel_ah_3">
        <text>No, unfortunately. I wanted to say... I'm dropping this.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cancel_ah_4">
        <text>Are you serious? You gave me your word!</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cancel_ah_5">
        <text>It's not going to work out. Sorry.</text>
    </string>	
    <string id="cancel_ah_6">
        <text>Well... a man's word... Fine, I'll keep looking.</text>
    </string>		
    <string id="cancel_ah_7">
        <text>Screw it all! I might as well crawl into those anomalies myself! Guess I'm heading back to HQ empty-handed...</text>
    </string>
 

    <string id="kovalev_1_quest_0">
        <text>Can I get the detector?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kovalev_1_quest_3">
        <text>Yes, of course! It activates when you open the lid - no buttons needed. If there's an artifact nearby it'll beep, you'll know.</text>
    </string>	
    <string id="kovalev_1_quest_end_0">
        <text>Here's your dirt.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kovalev_1_quest_end_1">
        <text>Oh, thank you so much! If it weren't for you, I'd have already given up! I'm terribly embarrassed about how little I can pay you - I'm sorry - but we have a strictly fixed budget for all operations. There's simply nothing more I can give.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="kovalev_2_quest_0">
        <text>Need any other help?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kovalev_2_quest_3">
        <text>Glad you asked. You see, I was previously conducting anomaly readings at the Agroprom and discovered some strange deviations. The artifacts that form in those anomalies have unique noosphere modulation characteristics. Only we couldn't finish the expedition - some lunatics opened fire on the complex and even threw a grenade through the window. In the chaos, I couldn't go back for my laptop, and all my anomaly scan results are on it. Not to mention my other work. If you can, please find my laptop - you'll be able to transfer the coordinates of the anomalies with the samples I need directly from it.</text>
    </string>  
	
    <string id="kovalev_2_quest_end_0">
        <text>Your environmental protection suits are impressive if they handle that kind of psi-radiations in the complex so easily. No wonder nobody's swiped the laptop. Here's your toy back, and the artifacts.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kovalev_2_quest_end_1">
        <text>Ha, what did you expect! Our suits are built to last - unlike some of the body armor out there. Walk right through hellfire in them. The only problem is they're useless against shockwaves, claws, and bullets - which is exactly why I'm scared to go on expeditions myself. Anyway, thank you for your help! Same as last time, I'm sharing what I have.</text>
    </string>	
	
	<string id="markov_1_quest_0">
        <text>Interested in work? Got something artifact-related.</text>
    </string>
	<string id="markov_1_quest_2">
        <text>Why not put your colleagues to work?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="markov_1_quest_3">
        <text>Not within my authority. I work separately from the science group. Those deadbeats still haven't studied the anomalies closest to them. Look, find these artifacts and I'll pay you out of my own pocket. The sooner you're done, the better.</text>
    </string>  

    <string id="markov_1_quest_end_0">
        <text>Found your little rocks.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="markov_1_quest_end_1">
        <text>Brilliant. Hand them over. I can see you're someone worth working with. Interested in more of the same?</text>
    </string>		
	
	<string id="markov_2_quest_0">
        <text>What've you got?</text>
    </string>	
    <string id="markov_2_quest_3">
        <text>During field research, my instruments picked up strange fluctuations in the noosphere. Out in the Wild Territory. Seems like these fluctuations are somehow affecting the artifacts forming there. Simple enough task - find the same kind of rocks you found before. I'll give you the coordinates of the locations I'm interested in.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="markov_2_quest_end_0">
        <text>Still got a headache from all the electros. A heads-up would've been nice! Here, take your order. Got any painkillers on you?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="markov_2_quest_end_1">
        <text>Sorry, I'm running low myself. I hope the payment makes up for the inconvenience.</text>
    </string>		
	
	<string id="markov_3_quest_0">
        <text>Anything else?</text>
    </string>
	<string id="markov_3_quest_3">
        <text>Hmm, let me think... There's one more field study I haven't gotten around to yet. We recently formed a hypothesis that the psi-emissions from the installation had some effect on artifact formation in its immediate vicinity. But the area's dangerous and nobody's rushing to organize an expedition. If you happen to be in those parts and find any unusual artefacts - you'd be doing our work a huge favor.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="markov_3_quest_end_0">
        <text>Unusual enough samples for you? Nothing more interesting out there.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="markov_3_quest_end_1">
        <text>Very nice indeed! Huge thanks to you! I'm exhausted - I just want to get back to lab work instead of, pardon me, trudging through this muck. The Zone, you know, is like rain - you only appreciate it when you're watching from a cozy den with a cup of coffee.</text>
    </string>		
	
	<string id="pirogov_1_quest_0">
        <text>Looks like you've got some problems.</text>
    </string>
	<string id="pirogov_1_quest_1">
        <text>Yeah, this godforsaken hole is crawling with mutants and lowlifes of every stripe, and those morons sent me here alone! Did they really think I could just ignore all that and stroll around conducting research without a care in the world? This is torture! Actual torture! Either you die here, or... Oh, Lord Almighty...</text>
    </string>
    <string id="pirogov_1_quest_2">
        <text>Take a breath. I'll help. I'll take a purely symbolic payment - your bonus check will cover it easily. Deal?</text>
    </string>  
    <string id="pirogov_1_quest_5">
        <text>Of course, money... like I earn so much! Oh, to hell with it, I don't want anything anymore... There are some anomalies around here. The lowlifes don't touch them - apparently beneath them. I need specific proto-artifact samples from those anomalies. Bring them to me and take my bonus - good riddance.</text>
    </string> 	

    <string id="pirogov_1_quest_end_0">
        <text>Here you go. Head back to your people. This place is hostile.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="pirogov_1_quest_end_1">
        <text>I'd love to... But they dumped a mountain of crap on my head. Can't go back until all of it is done.</text>
    </string>	
    
	<string id="pirogov_2_quest_0">
        <text>Can I help with anything?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="pirogov_2_quest_3">
        <text>Yes. Command also tasked me with inspecting the Vehicle Graveyard. You see, the Graveyard is poorly studied territory, and most people avoid it for obvious reasons. If you feel like taking the risk - go for it, same deal as before.</text>
    </string>  

    <string id="pirogov_2_quest_end_0">
        <text>Command clearly has it in for you. I wouldn't go back in there for anything - all kinds of nasty in there. Regardless, here are your trinkets.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="pirogov_2_quest_end_1">
        <text>You're a lifesaver, thanks!</text>
    </string>	
	
	<string id="pirogov_3_quest_0">
        <text>Anything else?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="pirogov_3_quest_3">
        <text>If you're not too tired... I recently sent my assistant to the Garbage to set up equipment in some anomalous fields. I'm already receiving data from most of them, but there's nothing coming in from the last few fields. I'm worried something might have happened to him. Could you find out what happened?</text>
    </string>
	<string id="pirogov_3_quest_4">
        <text>I'll look for him. I hope that's everything?</text>
    </string>
	<string id="pirogov_3_quest_5">
        <text>You think I don't hope the same? It's not up to me, unfortunately.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="pirogov_3_quest_end_0">
        <text>Found your assistant. He's gone, unfortunately. Grabbed his PDA and finished the work.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="pirogov_3_quest_end_1">
        <text>How did he... Ah, what the hell does it matter! Anyway, thank you very much... I've just got a little more to wrap up here, then I can head back to the bunker. I hope this is all over soon...</text>
    </string>		
	
	<string id="chernov_1_quest_0">
        <text>Hi - I'm here to help with your research.</text>
    </string>
	<string id="chernov_1_quest_1">
        <text>Commendable initiative. I hope you're not after my doctoral thesis?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="chernov_1_quest_2">
        <text>For now, I'm only interested in money.</text>
    </string>  
    <string id="chernov_1_quest_5">
        <text>Very well. Let's see how good you are. In this area locals call the Army Warehouses, there are many interesting anomalies that most stalkers simply steer clear of. Bring me samples from the ones I've marked on your PDA, and then we'll talk further.</text>
    </string> 	

    <string id="chernov_1_quest_end_0">
        <text>Here you go - a pile of glowing junk.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="chernov_1_quest_end_1">
        <text>Excellent. Here's your reward. Do you have any questions?</text>
    </string>			


	
	<string id="chernov_3_quest_0">
        <text>I'm curious - how do you know where the artifacts you need will be?</text>
    </string>
	<string id="chernov_3_quest_1">
        <text>Our research group is part of the ISTAZ - the Institute for the Scientific Study of the Chernobyl Anomalous Zone. We continuously study the Zone in order to find a way to destroy it or, at the very least, control it. We've learned a great deal from information provided by local stalkers and our own expeditions. We even have preliminary anomaly maps for certain areas. Using this data alongside our scanner readings, we can estimate the probability of artifact formation.</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="chernov_3_quest_2">
        <text>Interesting. So that's how you knew exactly where to send me.</text>
    </string>
	<string id="chernov_3_quest_3">
        <text>Precisely. However, your next assignment will require caution. I don't want you getting killed - after all, you seem like a capable assistant so far. I assigned a stalker to survey anomalous fields in the Red Forest. Unfortunately, he appears to have gone missing. The last place he contacted me from was a collapsed tunnel near the bridge to Limansk. Find his PDA - which contains the scan data I gave him - and collect the remaining samples. I must warn you though: I've lost many friends and colleagues in the Red Forest, so be careful.</text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="chernov_3_quest_end_0">
        <text>What a trip - had to fight my way through. Nevertheless, I found all the samples. Hope they were worth it!</text>
    </string>
    <string id="chernov_3_quest_end_1">
        <text>Excellent - I was starting to worry. I hope this bonus helps cover your medical expenses.</text>
    </string>	
	
	<string id="chernov_4_quest_0">
        <text>So, have you managed to create artifacts in the lab? I mean, you've been studying them for quite a while - wouldn't the need for the Zone drop sharply if artifacts could be produced without it?</text>
    </string>
	<string id="chernov_4_quest_1">
        <text>Work on creating artificial artifacts was underway even before the nuclear disaster and the Zone's appearance. My scientific supervisor lived and worked in Limansk. We often stayed at his home, discussing the possible origins of artifacts. We even managed to create a proto-artifact by borrowing a cultivator from the laboratory - the same kind you've been bringing me.</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="chernov_4_quest_2">
        <text>Interesting. Whatever happened to your friend?</text>
    </string>
	<string id="chernov_4_quest_3">
        <text>I don't know - there was no evacuation from Limansk during the catastrophe. Where all the residents disappeared to is a mystery to me. That reminded me that I still have his home address. Could you go there and see if the artifact survived? Who knows - it might be the key to understanding all of this.</text>
    </string>	

    <string id="chernov_4_quest_end_0">
        <text>Limansk is in terrible shape. No residents - just all kinds of deranged fanatics - but I managed to find the artifact. Here.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="chernov_4_quest_end_1">
        <text>I expected as much. And yet I can't help but grieve for my old friend... Regardless, let's honor his memory and try to figure out how to prevent all of this from happening again.</text>
    </string>		
	
	<string id="chernov_5_quest_0">
        <text>How's the work coming along, Professor? Any news on the origins of artifact formation?</text>
    </string>
	<string id="chernov_5_quest_1">
        <text>Yes, look here. You see this? This artifact has a completely unique radiation pattern. My friend, right here we have irrefutable proof that artifacts can be produced artificially.</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="chernov_5_quest_2">
        <text>Incredible! Do you really believe artifacts could have existed before the Zone itself appeared?</text>
    </string>
	<string id="chernov_5_quest_3">
        <text>I think I can tell you, since you'd find out sooner or later anyway. Have you ever heard of an artifact farm? Research in that direction has been ongoing for a long time, and a great deal of effort was invested in it at the now-abandoned Laboratory X-19. They created capsules they called "cultivators," in which artifacts could be formed under controlled conditions. The area is currently occupied by fanatics who call themselves Monolith, and it is an extremely dangerous place. However, if you somehow manage to get in there and find any remaining artifacts or documentation, I'd be in your debt.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="chernov_5_quest_end_0">
        <text>Holy hell, you weren't kidding - the place is crawling with Monolith soldiers, but I managed to infiltrate the lab. Believe it or not, you were right. I found three artifacts and some papers that look important. Here.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="chernov_5_quest_end_1">
        <text>Magnificent. Don't ask me how I knew it would all be there - you won't like the answer. Given the nature of our research, I must ask for your discretion. In due time, I will tell the world what happened here. But before I can do that, I need to finish my theory on these artifacts.</text>
    </string>	
	
	<string id="chernov_6_quest_0">
        <text>I understand. How can I be of help, Professor?</text>
    </string>
	<string id="chernov_6_quest_3">
        <text>After our last area scan, we found something interesting. A large group of mercenaries controls a district they call the Dead City. I'm getting very stable readings from that area, so it can be used as a control baseline. If you can bring me samples from those locations, I'll be able to establish baseline readings from them.</text>
    </string>	

    <string id="chernov_6_quest_end_0">
        <text>Nice little town - very hospitable locals too. Doesn't look very dead to me. Here are the samples, Prof.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="chernov_6_quest_end_1">
        <text>Outstanding work - here's your bonus. Given how much you've helped me, I could mention you in the foreword of my dissertation. Though I doubt that interests you much - for now. If you want more work, you could look for some of my colleagues here in the Zone. Perhaps they'll have something for you. I'll point you in their direction.</text>
    </string>	
			

	<string id="juk_1_quest_0">
        <text>Hey - I was told you might have some work for me.</text>
    </string>
	<string id="juk_1_quest_3">
        <text>Actually, yes. There are several anomalous fields I want to study, but I'm currently stuck here and can't leave the area. I'll mark the anomalies I'm interested in on your PDA. I hope you know what you're doing - Sakharov will be furious if I come up empty-handed.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="juk_1_quest_end_0">
        <text>I completed your assignment. Here are the artifacts I was able to find.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="juk_1_quest_end_1">
        <text>Hmm - I didn't expect you to manage it. Good work. Here's your reward.</text>
    </string>
	
	<string id="juk_2_quest_0">
        <text>Can I help with anything else?</text>
    </string>
	<string id="juk_2_quest_3">
        <text>Yes - while you were in the field, I received a new batch of scan data. As you're probably aware, the Zone keeps many secrets from us, and many anomalous zones still haven't been mapped. I'll forward you these preliminary scan results, as they contain approximate locations of some anomalies not yet on any map. Please verify whether the data is accurate, and keep an eye out for any potential artifacts. But please be careful - there are bound to be errors in the location data.</text>
    </string>	
	
    <string id="juk_2_quest_end_0">
        <text>Running low on bolts, but your data checks out, Professor. Managed to pull out a few artifacts too.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="juk_2_quest_end_1">
        <text>Excellent - that confirms our scanners are working correctly. Thank you for the report. Payment should be hitting your account right about now.</text>
    </string>
	
	<string id="juk_3_quest_0">
        <text>Looks like you've got something else on your mind.</text>
    </string>
	<string id="juk_3_quest_3">
        <text>Well... yes. You see, there are extremely interesting emission patterns being observed in Pripyat. However, as you may know, the city is just as dangerous as it is fascinating, and I honestly don't think I'd make it there and back alive. If you can manage it, please check out those locations and bring me any artifacts you can find. Don't worry - the reward will more than cover your expenditure on ammo and bandages.</text>
    </string>		
	
    <string id="juk_3_quest_end_0">
        <text>Think my suit's still got a hole in it from those fanatics' bullets, but I checked the anomalies. Pulled out a few samples too.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="juk_3_quest_end_1">
        <text>Phenomenal! Please take this - you've earned it. That's all for now. If you want to earn a bit more collecting artifacts, you could look for my colleagues in the Zone. I'll let them know you're coming.</text>
    </string>	
	
	<string id="vorobushkin_1_quest_0">
        <text>How's it going, Prof? Need help?</text>
    </string>
	<string id="vorobushkin_1_quest_3">
        <text>Perhaps. This area is poorly studied, so I don't know what to expect. However, my calculations suggest I should be able to find the artifacts I need here. Yesterday, to precisely identify the anomalous fields that need investigating, I repaired some equipment at the SIRCLE antenna complex. But the scanning took quite a long time, and the longer I stayed, the more dangerous it became - so I had to rush back here. You need to enter the station and retrieve the memory module I left there. It should contain all the necessary data. There are also a few anomalies nearby that might hold samples I'm after, but I can't confirm that until I get the scan data.</text>
    </string>		

    <string id="vorobushkin_1_quest_end_0">
        <text>Easy walk. Your equipment survived - here's the data and the samples.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="vorobushkin_1_quest_end_1">
        <text>Finally, some good news. These scan results look interesting...</text>
    </string>
	
	<string id="vorobushkin_2_quest_0">
        <text>What's going on, Professor?</text>
    </string>
	<string id="vorobushkin_2_quest_3">
        <text>Hmm - some of these readings simply don't make sense. Could you check them for me? If you find any artifacts and bring them to me, I can pay you well.</text>
    </string>	
	
    <string id="vorobushkin_2_quest_end_0">
        <text>Checked those areas, found samples. Now you do the checking.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="vorobushkin_2_quest_end_1">
        <text>Yes, astounding! My friend, this is a major breakthrough. Here's your reward.</text>
    </string>

	
    <string id="vorobushkin_redirect_dialog_0">
        <text>Can I help with anything else?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="vorobushkin_redirect_dialog_1">
        <text>That's all for now. If you'd like to continue helping us, I'll send you to a colleague who would be grateful for your assistance. I'll pass along his location and let him know you're coming. Safe travels, stalker!</text>
    </string>	
    <string id="vorobushkin_redirect_dialog_2">
        <text>Thank you for your invaluable help. I still need to run some calculations. Head north toward the Chernobyl Nuclear Power Plant - the head of our group, Professor Skabinskiy, is already there. I have no idea how he got through, but please hurry! He may need your help.</text>
    </string>	
    <string id="vorobushkin_redirect_dialog_3">
        <text>Our calculations still have many gaps due to insufficient data, but we've managed to approximate the location of an anomaly we couldn't predict before. Our operation leader, Professor Skabinskiy, has gone to investigate it. He may need your help, so hurry and find him. The location is dangerous, and he shouldn't have gone alone.</text>
    </string>		

    <string id="ah_start_dialog_0">
        <text>Hello, stalker.</text>
    </string>
	<string id="ah_start_dialog_1">
        <text>Hey.</text>
    </string>    	
    <string id="ah_start_dialog_2">
        <text>Hey, brother.</text>
    </string>		

	
	<string id="skabinsky_1_quest_0">
        <text>God, I finally found you, Professor! How did you get past all those fanatics?</text>
    </string>
	<string id="skabinsky_1_quest_1">
        <text>Ah, you must be that capable stalker Vorobushkin mentioned. Good thing you found me in time. Here's the situation: a group of mercenaries escorted me here, but most of them have already taken a bullet, so we need to move fast. There's a dangerous anomaly nearby - unlike anything I've seen before. Some of our calculations predict that a very rare and powerful artifact should form around this time. You have more experience working with anomalous fields than any of us, so we need you to go in there and verify whether our predictions are correct. I must warn you though - it will be very dangerous. Ready?</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="skabinsky_1_quest_2">
        <text>Well, I didn't come all this way for nothing. Let's do this!</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="skabinsky_1_quest_3">
        <text>I'm not ready.</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="skabinsky_1_quest_4">
        <text>Good - I like your attitude. Getting there will be extremely difficult though. I hope you have a decent detector to find the samples and spot the anomalies - this area is quite dangerous. Now go - we don't have much time!</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="skabinsky_1_quest_5">
        <text>I will. See you soon, Professor.</text>
    </string>		
	<string id="skabinsky_1_quest_6">
        <text>Wait - do you hear that? The Zone is calling to us, I can feel it... Move out. Go and take what it offers. I'll be waiting for you at Zaton.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="skabinsky_1_quest_end_0">
        <text>Professor... Look at this. I've never seen an artifact like this before. Just holding it feels strange.</text>
    </string>	
    <string id="skabinsky_1_quest_end_1">
        <text>So it's true... I thought it was just an error in our calculations. Thank you, stalker. Our team and the scientific community at large owe you an immeasurable debt. Quickly - give me the artifact so I can pack it securely. After that we can discuss your reward.</text>
    </string>
	<string id="skabinsky_1_quest_end_2">
        <text>With pleasure, Professor. Happy to help uncover the Zone's secrets. Here you go. I hope it was all worth it.</text>
    </string>    	
    <string id="skabinsky_1_quest_end_3">
        <text>Hmm - actually, no. An artifact like this could come in handy for me too.</text>
    </string>	
    <string id="skabinsky_1_quest_end_4">
        <text>You forget yourself - we had a deal. I will not tolerate it being broken!</text>
    </string>
	<string id="skabinsky_1_quest_end_5">
        <text>Alright, alright - I was just joking, relax. Here's your artifact.</text>
    </string>    	
    <string id="skabinsky_1_quest_end_6">
        <text>Ha - look at you. With this artifact I'm practically invincible. You can't do a thing to me! Now get out of my way.</text>
    </string>	
    <string id="skabinsky_1_quest_end_7">
        <text>This is the work of my entire life! I won't let you walk away with it - over my dead body!</text>
    </string>	
    <string id="skabinsky_1_quest_end_8">
        <text>Thank you. My work here is done, and I need to return to base to evaluate everything we've found. Even though our paths diverge here, our team will always remember you. No amount of money can compensate for your contribution to science, but this is all I have with me right now. Please take it. If we ever need help with our research again, we'll be sure to reach out. I hope our paths cross again, stalker. Thank you once more - and farewell.</text>
    </string>		
	
    <string id="skabinsky_fail_quest_0">
        <text>I found you. How's the search going?</text>
    </string>	
    <string id="skabinsky_fail_quest_1">
        <text>Ah, hello. You're the stalker who was helping our group with research, aren't you? It seems we were wrong to count on your help - the calculations are off, this damned place isn't the center of the Zone. It was all for nothing.</text>
    </string>		
    <string id="skabinsky_fail_quest_2">
        <text>Isn't there anything else we can do?</text>
    </string>		
    <string id="skabinsky_fail_quest_3">
        <text>You've already done all you could. Now get out of here. The failure of our operation is on your hands.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_0">
        <text>Reporting for duty - ready to take on an extremely dangerous assignment.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_1">
        <text>At ease, soldier. I respect your courage, but I expect you to know your limits. Keep this in mind: out here your life is your own responsibility. If you're sure, here's a list of priority targets for the Combined Command HQ:</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_2">
        <text>Retrieve documents from the underground tunnels beneath Agroprom?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_22">
        <text>Someone local tipped us off about a hideout down here, underground. Most of the important documentation was taken long ago, but we've been informed that some young hotshot stashed certain papers in a hidden spot. Your objective: find that hideout and seize all documentation you find there. Orders clear?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_221">
        <text>Affirmative.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_222">
        <text>I'm not ready.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_3">
        <text>Retrieve documents from the X-18 complex?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_33">
        <text>HQ is very interested in data on the "Kaimanov Experimental Emitter." Your objective: recover all surviving documentation on this research and bring it back here in one piece. A worthy reward will be waiting upon your return. Orders clear?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_331">
        <text>Affirmative.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_332">
        <text>I'm not ready.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_4">
        <text>Retrieve documents from Laboratory X-16?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_44">
        <text>X-16 was where the finished blocks for the psi-installation were sent. This won't be easy: you'll need to push through the emissions to reach the underground lab complex and locate any surviving documentation. Originals, copies - doesn't matter. For psi-protection, see Sakharov - he should be able to help. Orders clear?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_441">
        <text>Affirmative.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_442">
        <text>I'm not ready.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_5">
        <text>Retrieve documents from Laboratory X-10?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_55">
        <text>This one is especially tough - bordering on impossible. If it were up to me, I wouldn't even be suggesting it, but command knows best, I suppose... After all the intel we've gathered, command is more interested than ever in the documents from the Radar's emitter. They want both the documentation and for the installation to be shut down... I'm not insisting on this one - I get it. This is a job for an entire army, nothing less. But if you somehow manage to bring back even a shred of information from there - a generous bonus will be yours. So - do you understand the objective?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_551">
        <text>The Radar... Are they completely out of their minds back at HQ? The objective's clear enough, but you understand, Colonel - I could promise you anything - but this isn't an assignment, it's a death sentence. I'll think about what can be done and keep you posted.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_552">
        <text>What?! No, I understand! But with all due respect, Colonel, tell your superiors they can kiss my ass. Storm the Radar - are you serious... Let them even show their faces on the Cordon first, then they can start talking about pulling stunts like that.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_6">
        <text>Retrieve documents from Laboratory X-8?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_66">
        <text>I know this sounds like a bad joke, but don't take it that way - these labs are stuck in my throat too. This time your target is the complex beneath the Yubileiniy. The territory was last held by Monolith soldiers, so getting in may be tricky. Your objective: find a way inside and bring back all surviving intel you can find. Orders clear?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_661">
        <text>Affirmative.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_662">
        <text>I need time to prepare.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_7">
        <text>Retrieve documents from the Pripyat underground tunnels?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_77">
        <text>Secret facility codenamed "Pripyat Underpass-1." HQ wants any information: who built it, what was transported, and how it stayed secret for so many years. Stalkers aren't particularly interested in this type of place - not really their thing - so the chances that some papers survived in there are actually quite decent. Orders clear?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_771">
        <text>Affirmative.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_772">
        <text>I need to prepare.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_8">
        <text>The Monolith Command Center? I've stopped being surprised at this point... What are my orders?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_9">
        <text>I've had enough. I refuse.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_88">
        <text>The control center remains a high-priority target. Your objective: infiltrate it and return with all the intelligence you can find. Destroy the command post whenever possible - but remember: the data comes first. As before, use any means available - you have my authorization. Orders clear?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_881">
        <text>Affirmative. These Monolith bastards have been a thorn in my side for too long - I'll find volunteers to help clear their nest. But you know as well as I do, Colonel - nobody else is going to organize this madness, which means my compensation needs to match... Unrestricted passage to the mainland whenever I want, a decent plot of land, a veteran's pension, and full amnesty. Those are my terms.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_882">
        <text>I've had enough. I refuse.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="work_vip_kuznecov_agr_undr_0">
        <text>Mission complete - hideout found, documents in hand.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="work_vip_kuznecov_agr_undr_1">
        <text>Outstanding, soldier. Just outstanding. You've earned your bonus.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="work_vip_kuznecov_x18_0">
        <text>Here's everything I found on X-18.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="work_vip_kuznecov_x18_1">
        <text>Outstanding, soldier. Just outstanding. You've earned your bonus.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="work_vip_kuznecov_x16_0">
        <text>The psi-installation won't be a problem anymore - you can safely send your forces in. As for the documents... here they are.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="work_vip_kuznecov_x16_1">
        <text>Outstanding work! This is a genuine achievement! Now we'll be able to ensure safe operations for our science teams in that area. You've proven yourself exceptionally. You're going places!</text>
    </string>
    <string id="work_vip_kuznecov_x10_0">
        <text>Operation successful: the Brain Scorcher is offline, and here are the documents I managed to find inside X-10.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="work_vip_kuznecov_x10_1">
        <text>You've already stirred things up - your reputation has reached us all the way out here. A huge thank you from Command! Thanks to you, we can finally expand operations deeper into the Zone.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="work_vip_kuznecov_x8_0">
        <text>Back from Pripyat. Got the intel.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="work_vip_kuznecov_x8_1">
        <text>Excellent work!</text>
    </string>
    <string id="work_vip_kuznecov_jupiter_ugr_0">
        <text>Task complete. Papers from the Underpass are in hand.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="work_vip_kuznecov_jupiter_ugr_1">
        <text>Good work, soldier... Just a little more. A little more, damn it, before those bureaucrats are satisfied! And then all of us get our ticket out of this cesspit! You, me... Trust me - right now I can only give you what I can in my position, but the real reward is waiting for us out there, beyond the Zone.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="work_vip_kuznecov_control_bunker_0">
        <text>The command post is done! Monolith is done! Mission complete - those bastards didn't even know what hit them!</text>
    </string>
    <string id="work_vip_kuznecov_control_bunker_1">
        <text>You pulled it off?! That's my soldier! You absolute beast!!! I'm radioing Command immediately - Monolith has been dealt a devastating blow and all their classified intelligence is in our hands! Now it's up to the higher-ups to decide when we launch the next operation to seize the Center, but thanks to you, we have a real shot at taking FULL control of the Zone and flushing out all that stalker scum! Incredible work! You're a hero - no exaggeration! I remember our agreement - now we just have to wait for command's decision. But in the meantime... accept this reward personally from me.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="vasil_nevezuchi_1_0">
        <text>Good day - I've arrived to assist.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="vasil_nevezuchi_1_2">
        <text>Good to see a friendly face. Hope the battle at the NPP went well? I'm Sergeant Shchaslivenko - pleasure to meet you, but just call me Vasyl. Down to business: the Monolith boys have dug in at a base to the southeast of that glowing thing in the center of the forest. Mines all around, snipers on the towers. Bottom line - we're moving out. Try to take those bastards down before they spot us.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="vasil_nevezuchi_1_3">
        <text>Let's go, Sergeant - I'll cover you.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kvartet_1_0">
        <text>Captain - I'm ready to join the assault.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kvartet_1_2">
        <text>Good. These bastards are holding three checkpoints: two on the approaches to the sarcophagus, one right in front of the fourth reactor block. Two of our squads will attack from both sides. Your job: give our guys fire support and put down as many of these damn Monolith soldiers as you can.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kvartet_1_3">
        <text>Affirmative! Moving out.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_0">
        <text>You wouldn't happen to know where I can get my hands on some tools around here?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_1">
        <text>Might know something - toss me a few rubles first. Say... two thousand.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_9">
        <text>Here you go.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_10">
        <text>I'll come back later.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_2">
        <text>I know, and for four thousand I'll tell you.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_11">
        <text>Take it.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_12">
        <text>Thanks, but no thanks.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_3">
        <text>Pay me a little something - say, a thousand - and I'll tell you.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_13">
        <text>Here's your money.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_14">
        <text>I changed my mind.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_4">
        <text>Two thousand five hundred, not a ruble less. Then we'll talk.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_15">
        <text>Take it.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_16">
        <text>Money's tight right now.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_5">
        <text>Listen up, friend:</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_24">
        <text>[continued...]</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_6">
        <text>No idea.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_7">
        <text>Check the stashes.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_8">
        <text>Beat it - I'm busy.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_17">
        <text>Try the Dark Valley at the bandit base. Their tech is pretty shoddy, so you might be able to borrow a spare set. As for exactly where - they didn't give me specifics.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_18">
        <text>Try the Garbage - the boys told me recently they've got something like a base in the local hangar. You'll probably find the rough tools in there.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_19">
        <text>Cordon, the ATP. Some bandits wanted to set up a big base there - even hauled in equipment and machinery - but their guy vanished, and apparently his gear stayed behind.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_20">
        <text>On the Cordon, near the Southern Checkpoint. Hope you can read a map. It's dangerous out there - nobody goes near it - so there's a decent chance the precision tools are just sitting there. And there's some other reliable intel backing that up.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_21">
        <text>Agroprom - the main complex. You know that anomaly with all the electros and the psi? Somewhere around that complex is worth checking. There's a constant fight over that strategic point so nobody's stopping to pick through the scrap, but some technical junk has definitely been spotted there.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_22">
        <text>Vehicle Graveyard. Step out of the bar right now and look for a vehicle with the plate "9941KIL" - it'll lead you straight to the goods. Heard it from a Duty guy who was out on a recon sweep. They were clearing the area but ran into a swarm of Snorks. Made a "tactical withdrawal," heh. One of them spotted the vehicle while running for his life.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_23">
        <text>Head to Agroprom - the main military base. Sounds too tough? Well, what can you do - but at least they're well-funded. Their gear is top-notch, not like ours. If anyone has calibration tools, it's them. You didn't think it'd be easy getting your hands on calibration tools, did you?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_25">
        <text>Thanks for the cash - now get lost. I don't know where your tools are, Mr. Fix-It.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_26">
        <text>Ah, sorry pal - I've already forgotten where it was. Check the stashes, ask the traders.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task0_dialog_0">
        <text>Any special jobs?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task0_dialog_1">
        <text>No special jobs right now, but there's some odd work available. I need someone to retrieve a scanner from the archanomaly south of the western tower - it should have finished measuring anomalous activity by now. You up for it?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task0_dialog_3">
        <text>Maybe another time.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task0_dialog_2">
        <text>I'm in.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task0_dialog1_0">
        <text>Here's the device - take it.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task0_dialog1_2">
        <text>Thanks. By the way, a scout is due to arrive this evening, sometime around 20:00-22:00. So don't go anywhere. We'll meet him together.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_0">
        <text>Is there anything I can do to help Clear Sky?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_1">
        <text>Yes. You know, even though we've regained some control over the Marshes, our numbers leave a lot to be desired. Anomalous activity has dropped sharply, so all sorts of bandits, renegades, and other trash have flooded in... We keep losing one position after another. We're basically locked down at our starting points, the renegades won't give us a moment's peace - I've been informed that another attack on our outpost at the Pumping Station is being planned. Help our boys hold it.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_3">
        <text>Maybe another time.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_2">
        <text>I'm in.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_vip_0">
        <text>Renegades eliminated...</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_vip_2">
        <text>Excellent! I've prepared an assault squad to capture the Southern Village - we need to secure the road to the Cordon. Move to position and support our group. You can move up with them - the boys are already heading out from base.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_vip2_0">
        <text>Road to the Cordon is secured.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_vip2_2">
        <text>Good work - we've consolidated our hold on the key positions. Thanks for your help. Take your reward. But there's another problem. The military. Before, the soldiers' presence used to scare off the renegades and other trash - they left us alone, we left them alone. But now they're sending more and more military stalker units into the Marshes, and we're taking casualties. I think it's time to put an end to this. Their base is at the Mechanizers' Yard - if we drive them out, we'll have the advantage and consolidate our position here for good. I can't afford to wait - I'm sending our best assault squad, they're already heading out from base. Join them and give them support in the fight.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_vip3_0">
        <text>The military have been pushed out of the Mechanizers' Yard - it was a tough fight.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_vip3_2">
        <text>Thank you - with your help we've taken back the key locations and are once again a force to be reckoned with. Ah, if only Lebedev were here... Alright, enough sentimentality - we've still got a lot of work ahead. Take your reward, and thank you again.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task2_dialog_0">
        <text>The scout is dead. Here's his PDA.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task2_dialog_2">
        <text>A shame. He was one of our best. Thank you.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task3_cold_dialog_0">
        <text>I'm here about the decoded PDA.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task3_cold_dialog_1">
        <text>We have good news - take a seat. Kostyl managed to determine that some of our missing comrades from 2011 survived! According to information on the PDA, a mercenary known as Scar - who in 2011 fought alongside our assault squads through Limansk and the Hospital toward the ChNPP in pursuit of Strelok - made it out alive. It is also known that he was in contact with several stalkers who, by description, match members of Lebedev's group. Our scout confirms the information is solid. Stalker - make inquiries about Scar among those who deal with neutrals, and find him. We may be able to reunite with our lost comrades. Your best bet is to start with Sidorovich.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task3_cold_dialog_2">
        <text>That's great news. Maybe Sidorovich knows this stalker. I'll ask him and track down the survivors.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="holod_end_cs_story_0">
        <text>I found one surviving member of Clear Sky.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="holod_end_cs_story_1">
        <text>Found one, you say? Who is it? Where are they?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="holod_end_cs_story_2">
        <text>It's Gamajun - one of Lebedev's men. He's currently fighting in the ranks of the Monolith Outcasts. Unfortunately, he refused to come back to the Marshes with me. Says he won't abandon his brothers.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="holod_end_cs_story_3">
        <text>Well, that's his choice to make. If he survived, others may have too. Your account gives us hope. Perhaps we'll reunite with our comrades someday. I'll also give orders for our recon units to cooperate with the Outcasts. Ah yes - I think you've earned a reward.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="holod_end_cs_story_4">
        <text>Thank you.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task4_dragun_dialog_0">
        <text>Hello - are you the one they call Scar? I need some information.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task4_dragun_dialog_1">
        <text>The one and only. And who the hell are you? Not right now - help me fend off this pack of pseudodogs. They've been on my tail for two kilometers.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task4_dragun_dialog_2">
        <text>Two of us should be enough to hold them off.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task5_dragun_dialog_0">
        <text>Phew - we held them off. Please tell me what you know about the surviving members of Lebedev's group. I have reason to believe you know something.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task5_dragun_dialog_1">
        <text>Yes, I do know something. But I can't tell you much - it's mostly rumors. Have you heard of Wanderer and his group? They're all former Monolith soldiers who turned against the Zone's masters and are now waging a guerrilla war against Monolith. Word has it that some Clear Sky members are among these Monolith Outcasts. His squad is stationed in the Jupiter outskirts, at an old military checkpoint - the same place where the local bandit boss called Valet used to hang around, before someone put a bullet in his head.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task5_dragun_dialog_2">
        <text>Thank you very much.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="brodyaga_cs_story_dialog2_0">
        <text>I found Gamajun's squad, and he asked me to give you this device. The squad completed their objective.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="brodyaga_cs_story_dialog2_1">
        <text>Good - this device will tip the odds in our favor. I'm glad you found your comrade. It's a shame to lose a soldier like that.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="brodyaga_cs_story_dialog2_2">
        <text>He decided to stay with the Outcasts.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="brodyaga_cs_story_dialog2_3">
        <text>Understood. I think you deserve a reward for helping our group. We're not exactly well-off, but we have something. Take it.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="brodyaga_cs_story_dialog2_4">
        <text>Thank you.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="brodyaga_cs_story_dialog1_0">
        <text>I've heard there are former Clear Sky members in your ranks. Can I meet with them? I work for Clear Sky and we're searching for our lost comrades.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="brodyaga_cs_story_dialog1_1">
        <text>Hmm... There are indeed ex-Clear Sky members in our ranks. Like all of us, they were Monolith soldiers - until C-Consciousness loosened its grip. Now we fight against Monolith together.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="brodyaga_cs_story_dialog1_2">
        <text>So where can I meet with them?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="brodyaga_cs_story_dialog1_3">
        <text>I'm afraid you've come too late. Their squad left on a mission in eastern Pripyat. Unfortunately, they haven't made contact since. If you hurry, you might be able to catch up with them. I don't have enough men to send anyone to their aid.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="brodyaga_cs_story_dialog1_4">
        <text>Thank you for the information. I'll find them and help if they're in danger.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="gamajun_cs_story_dialog1_0">
        <text>Looks like I arrived just in time.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="gamajun_cs_story_dialog1_1">
        <text>Yeah, you could say that... A little longer and those fanatics would have wiped us out. Did Wanderer send you?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="gamajun_cs_story_dialog1_2">
        <text>Actually, I've been looking for you specifically. You're a member of Lebedev's group? Clear Sky is searching for you.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="gamajun_cs_story_dialog1_3">
        <text>Hmm... I used to be. But now I'm a Monolith Outcast. I'll tell you everything and we can decide what to do - but first, help me complete my mission since you're already here. The Monolith soldiers turned out to be tougher than we expected. I sent a squad to the river port to capture a device that lets us intercept the fanatics' communications, but the squad went silent. They've probably been taken. Recon the situation and help us capture that device.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="gamajun_cs_story_dialog1_4">
        <text>Alright, I'll help.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="gamajun_cs_story_dialog2_0">
        <text>Here's the device.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="gamajun_cs_story_dialog2_1">
        <text>Thank you - better give it to Wanderer. I'll stay here and hold this outpost with my men.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="gamajun_cs_story_dialog2_2">
        <text>So you won't come to the Marshes with me?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="gamajun_cs_story_dialog2_3">
        <text>No. Sorry - but I'm an Outcast now. I can't abandon my brothers. By the way, I promised to tell you my story, so listen. In 2011, I fought with Lebedev as part of the assault squad pushing through Limansk. Our chief moved north with some of the men and a mercenary, while I held position in the city. Then that emission hit - the one that wiped my memory. According to Wanderer, I served Monolith just like the rest of them. After the events of 2012, I came back to myself - woke up somewhere in the Jupiter outskirts. I survived thanks to Wanderer, and I became a member of his group.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="gamajun_cs_story_dialog2_4">
        <text>Thanks for telling me. I'll deliver the device to Wanderer and pass along your regards to Kholod.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="dolg_story_task_1_dialog_start_0">
        <text>Any special work available?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="dolg_story_task_1_dialog_start_1">
        <text>Come to think of it, yes. There's a war on with Freedom and the bandits, and Monolith fanatics are pushing down from the north. All our forces are tied up in the fighting, but we need hunters to carry out our core mission - destroying the Zone. I'm offering you a position as a witcher. Simple enough: I offer you a witcher's contract, you complete it, you get paid. What do you say?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="dolg_story_task_1_dialog_start_2">
        <text>Sounds decent. If the pay is fair, I'm in. What's my first contract?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="dolg_story_task_1_dialog_start_3">
        <text>Don't worry about the pay - we'll pay in cash and good gear if you prove yourself. Your first contract: eliminate a bloodsucker nest that's migrated south. It's been a real pain in our ass - the bloodsuckers slipped past all our posts and patrols. Wipe them out and come back for your reward. I'd suggest starting your search with the Butcher - he's the leader of the local hunters.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="dolg_story_task_1_dialog_start_4">
        <text>I'll take the contract. Consider those bloodsuckers already dead.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="dolg_story_task_1_dialog_end_0">
        <text>Assignment complete - bloodsuckers eliminated.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="dolg_story_task_1_dialog_end_1">
        <text>Good work. Here's your reward.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="prinesi_military_docs_start_0">
        <text>So - what do I need to do to get the information on Scar?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="prinesi_military_docs_start_1">
        <text>Here's the thing... A crate containing a report from one of the expeditions that went north got transferred to the checkpoint from deep in the Zone. During the day they guard it like it's full of pure plutonium, but for some reason at night they leave no more than two guards on it. Sneak onto the checkpoint and take that crate for me. And I won't spare anything for you... within reason. Deal or no deal?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="prinesi_military_docs_start_21">
        <text>I'm in.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="prinesi_military_docs_start_22">
        <text>You know what, no. I'd rather stay alive.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="prinesi_military_docs_start_31">
        <text>Well, I'll have the money ready - just don't make a scene, alright? If the soldiers get upset, the sky's going to feel very small for all of us...</text>
    </string>
    <string id="prinesi_military_docs_done_0">
        <text>I found them, here.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="prinesi_military_docs_done_1">
        <text>prinesi_military_docs_done_1</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task3_sidor_dialog_0">
        <text>I'm looking for a mercenary known as Scar. You know him?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task3_sidor_dialog_1">
        <text>Maybe I do. But why do you need him?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task3_sidor_dialog_3">
        <text>He has important information that's crucial for Clear Sky.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task3_sidor_dialog_2">
        <text>I can sell you some information, but it'll cost you twenty thousand, plus a little favor. Complete a special job for me as a show of trust, and we'll see what I know about Scar.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task3_sidor_dialog_4">
        <text>Fine. I'll complete one of your errands and buy the information.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task3_sidor_dialog_5">
        <text>I don't have time for these games.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task3_sidor_dialog_6">
        <text>Then stop bothering me and get out of here.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task3_sidor_dialog1_0">
        <text>I'm here about the info on Scar.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task3_sidor_dialog1_1">
        <text>Got the money? Done my job?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task3_sidor_dialog1_3">
        <text>Not yet.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task3_sidor_dialog1_2">
        <text>Yes - here's your money. Job's done.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task3_sidor_dialog1_4">
        <text>Alright, listen up - or better yet write it down, heh. This mercenary stopped by to see me. He needed some equipment for a deep raid into the northern territories. Generous fellow - spent a fair amount. From what he said, I gathered he's looking for something on the Zaton. My guess is he's there now. There are also rumors that he's set up in the Substation Workshops, picking up some scrap. That's all - good luck finding him.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task3_sidor_dialog1_5">
        <text>Good doing business with you. Thanks for the info.</text>
    </string>

</string_table>
