<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>

<!-- General -->
	<string id="story_line_dialog_1">
		<text>Here are the anomaly coordinates. Survey them with your detector. The samples I'm interested in should be there.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="story_line_answer_1">
		<text>Understood.</text>
	</string>	
	<string id="story_line_dialog_2">
		<text>As you have probably guessed, I work in a scientific group of the Institute for the Research of the Chernobyl Anomalous Zone. Artifacts are invisible to the human eye, but the frequency they emit can be registered by detectors.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="story_line_answer_2">
		<text>Yeah, I know that.</text>
	</string>	
	<string id="story_line_dialog_3">
		<text>Each artifact radiates energy on its own unique frequency. It's like a fingerprint, an artist's signature on a canvas. The broader the detector database and scanning spectrum are, the more artifacts it can find. As a rule, stalkers look for artifacts with outstanding properties. Meanwhile, any samples from anomalies are of immense interest to science.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="story_line_answer_3">
		<text>Very interesting.</text>
	</string>	
	<string id="story_line_dialog_4">
		<text>As you know, Strelok managed to uncover the secret behind the Zone's creation. Now this information is available to many scientists. This has greatly advanced our understanding of the amazing nature of anomalies and how they affect the environment and living organisms. That is even how some research groups created Artefact Melters, a tool allowing to fuse and empower existing artefacts. But right now we are compiling a database of practical field observations and measurements. You couldn't exactly call this easy work. That's why we are looking for assistants among free stalkers.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="story_line_answer_4">
		<text>For a worthy reward, of course.</text>
	</string>	
	<string id="story_line_dialog_5">
		<text>Indeed... The rupture of the Noosphere, which everyone knows as the Second Explosion, caused the creation of the anomalous Zone. The power lines of psi-fields envelop this territory like tentacles. Every object within the Zone falls under their influence. Even you, are already marked by the Zone. Artefacts are an amazing gift that not everyone can appreciate. And it's not about the money they're worth. Artifacts are the Zone's messengers; through them, it communicates with us. That's why we need them so badly: to better understand the Zone.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="story_line_answer_5">
		<text>Spare me the egghead talk please... you can't spread an artifact on a piece of bread you know?</text>
	</string>	
	<string id="story_line_dialog_6">
		<text>Last but not least, each artifact has a unique modulation, even if they are of the same type. It can tell us a lot about the Noosphere. The most foolish thing you can do is hang them on your belt and hope they save you from bullets or anomalies. We are only just getting closer to an answer, and our plan is to compile a complete spectrogram of the Zone. To do that, we'll have to wander at the four corners of the Zone.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="story_line_answer_6">
		<text>Well, what do you think I'm doing? Writing a PhD all day along?</text>
	</string>	
	<string id="story_line_dialog_7">
		<text>Have you ever wondered what artifacts are made of? Most often, they are the remains of living creatures that stumbled into anomalies. So the next time you decide to show off a rare find, remember: it could be the remains of a fellow stalker. Or a boar, who knows.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="story_line_answer_7">
		<text>That... was a useful piece of information. Thanks. I'll try to remember that.</text>
	</string>	
	<string id="story_line_dialog_8">
		<text>It is believed that anomalies are some kind of space-time ruptures where the physical laws of our world cease to apply. But there is another point of view: that they are a powerful signal source that we are simply unable to receive. Who is transmitting them, and why? Or maybe it's just a pot lid rattling from the boiling broth inside?</text>
	</string>	
	<string id="story_line_answer_8">
		<text>The main thing is that it doesn't blow up again.</text>
	</string>	
	<string id="story_line_dialog_9">
		<text>An anomaly usually selects organic samples as an information receiver. For example, wild beasts or zombies that frequently perish within them. That's how artifacts appear. Knowing the exact place of an artifact's origin, you can read it like a book or a flash drive.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="story_line_answer_9">
		<text>I hope you guys haven't thought of throwing random crap into anomalies yourselves?</text>
	</string>	
	<string id="story_line_dialog_10">
		<text>We do not buy artifacts from stalkers or bandits. Without knowing their exact point of origin, they are useless to us. Our task is to collect samples from every corner of the Zone.</text>
	</string>	
	<string id="story_line_answer_10">
		<text>Got it.</text>
	</string>	
	<string id="story_line_dialog_11">
		<text>Every artifact, even of the same type, has a unique radiation signature depending on where it was found. The Zone has left a unique imprint on each of them that cannot be confused with anything else. By knowing the full spectrum of emissions, we'll be able to map the Zone's psionic fields. To understand the origins of the disturbances that caused the Zone. And perhaps even control them or predic how they shift.</text>
	</string>	
	<string id="story_line_answer_11">
		<text>Ambitious plans. But this would be very useful for us.</text>
	</string>	
	<string id="story_line_dialog_12">
		<text>Thanks to you, our computing cluster is busy with calculations around the clock. There is enough information for years of analysis. It really was the right decision, despite the risks, to split the team across the entire territory. Our leader, Academician Skabinsky, acted with great foresight here. It is impossible for one person to comprehend such a massive structure in its entirety. Only by pooling our cognitive abilities could we achieve success.</text>
	</string>	
	<string id="story_line_answer_12">
		<text>Happy for you.</text>
	</string>	
	<string id="story_line_dialog_13">
		<text>Thank you for staying with us. Usually, the stalkers who help us end up disappearing constantly. The preliminary spectrogram analysis is full of surprises; it seems the center of the Zone has been right under our noses this whole time. Our colleague couldn't wait for the final calculations and has already headed out there. But I, however, am inclined to finish compiling the map. I'm still missing a few more samples.</text>
	</string>	
	<string id="story_line_answer_13">
		<text>This work never ends.</text>
	</string>	
	<string id="story_line_dialog_14">
		<text>Our work is nearing its end. Soon we will prove that we are worthy of taking our place... Do you know that there is a giga-anomaly in the center of the Zone, and all psi-lines intersect there? An artifact born in this unique place will possess unique properties. The Zone will finally speak to us.</text>
	</string>	
	<string id="story_line_answer_14">
		<text>To "us"?</text>
	</string>	
	<string id="story_line_dialog_15">
		<text>Sad news. Our brother has stopped communicating. There is no reason to hope for the best; he has most likely died. There is a giga-anomaly in the center of the Zone. Getting through it is almost impossible. We'll have to think about how to solve this problem; perhaps we should refine the calculations.</text>
	</string>	
	<string id="story_line_answer_15">
		<text>In the Zone, you always need to think first and act later.</text>
	</string>	
	
</string_table>