<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<string_table>

<!--
PISTOLS
-->
	<string id="st_wpn_aps">
		<text>APS Stechkin</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aps_descr">
		<text>The Stechkin APS is a Russian selective fire machine pistol, bearing the name of its designer Igor Stechkin. Originally chambered for 7.62x25mm Tokarev, the pistol was changed to use 9x18mm as it became clear that this cartridge was set to become the new service ammunition for handguns in the Soviet Army. In 1951, the Stechkin was introduced into the Soviet military arsenal, replacing the aging TT-33.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Tula Arms Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_beretta">
		<text>Beretta 92F</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_beretta_alt">
		<text>Beretta 92F</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_beretta_modern">
		<text>Beretta 92F</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_beretta_descr">
		<text>The Beretta is perhaps best known as the standard pistol of the US Military that replaced the legendary M1911. Known for being accurate, durable and reliable, it's been adopted by several countries and has been setting the standards for military, police and tactical pistols for over a quarter century.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Italy\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Fabbrica d'Armi Pietro Beretta\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_hpsa">
		<text>Browning Hi-Power</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_hpsa_alt">
		<text>Browning Hi-Power</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_hpsa_descr">
		<text>A single-action, semi-automatic pistol based on the ideas of American firearms inventor John Browning. Browning died in 1926 before finishing a production version, but FN arms designer Dieudonne Saive completed the pistol's development. The Hi-Power pistol was noted for its 13-round magazine, twice that of contemporary designs such as the Luger or Mauser 1910. Despite its venerable age, the Browning HP enjoys popularity around the world.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Belgium, United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Browning Arms, FN Herstal\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911">
		<text>Colt M1911</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_alt">
		<text>Colt M1911</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_modern">
		<text>Colt M1911</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_new">
		<text>Colt M1911</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_descr">
		<text>Designed by John Browning, the M1911 is an extremely reliable and robust pistol that remained the standard-issue side arm of the US military from 1911 to 1985. To this day, it remains very popular for military, police and civilian use around the world.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Colt Manufacturing Company\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_duty">
		<text>Colt M1911 "Aries"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_duty_descr">
		<text>Designed by John Browning, the M1911 is an extremely reliable and robust pistol that remained the standard-issue side arm of the US military from 1911 to 1985. To this day, it remains very popular for military, police and civilian use around the world. The "Aries" has been modified with a feather-trigger for faster firing, lightweight parts for easier concealed carry and a tritium ironsight.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Colt Manufacturing Company\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_merc">
		<text>Colt M1911 "Orion"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_merc_descr">
		<text>Designed by John Browning, the M1911 is an extremely reliable and robust pistol that remained the standard-issue side arm of the US military from 1911 to 1985. To this day, it remains very popular for military, police and civilian use around the world. The "Orion" has been modified with a a tritium ironsight and a heavier barrel and stock, greatly increasing its accuracy.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Colt Manufacturing Company\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_cz75">
		<text>CZ-75</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_cz75_descr">
		<text>Developed by the Koucky brothers, this semi-automatic pistol was intended for the export market. The CZ-75 accumulated the best features from many preceding designs with the resulting pistol being aesthetically attractive, comfortable, accurate and reliable in operation.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Czechoslovak Socialist Republic\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Ceska zbrojovka\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_fnp45">
		<text>FNP-45</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fnp45_custom">
		<text>FNP-45</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fnp45_descr">
		<text>A recoil-operated, polymer-framed pistol that provides good accuracy, outstanding reliability and versatility in a weapon that is comfortable to handle. Created as a homage to John Browning of the M1911 in .45 ACP, it offers an impressive amount of ambidextrous features, even when compared to modern pistols.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States, Belgium\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]FNH USA\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_fnx45">
		<text>FNX-45</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fnx45_alt">
		<text>FNX-45</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fnx45_custom">
		<text>FNX-45</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fnx45_descr">
		<text>Improving on the FNP-45, the FNX-45 is the latest in technological advancements in handgun engineering, offering .45 ACP performance and a host of unique features that no other handgun can match. The cold hammer-forged stainless steel barrel has a threaded muzzle for the integrated suppressor and the stainless steel slide comes with high-profile combat night sights for easier target acquisition.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States, Belgium\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]FN America\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_glock">
		<text>Glock 19</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_glock_descr">
		<text>Reliability, durability and simplicity have made the Glock 19 one of the most widely used sidearms in law enforcement. Due to its reduced dimensions when compared to the Glock 17, it is ideal for use as a backup weapon or for concealed carry purposes.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Austria\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Glock Ges.m.b.H.\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_glock_modern">
		<text>Glock 19 "Hornet"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_glock_modern_descr">
		<text>Reliability, durability and simplicity have made the Glock 19 one of the most widely used sidearms in law enforcement. Due to its reduced dimensions when compared to the Glock 17, it is ideal for use as a backup weapon or for concealed carry purposes. The "Hornet" is equipped with a 40-round extended magazine and fully automatic fire for an unprecedented amount of firepower in a small package.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Austria\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Glock Ges.m.b.H.\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_gsh18">
		<text>Gsh-18</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_gsh18_custom">
		<text>Gsh-18</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_gsh18_descr">
		<text>In the early 2000s, the Russian military sought a new light, effective and easily concealable sidearm to replace the Makarov. Designed by Gryazev and Shipunow, the outcome was the Gsh-18; a recoil-operated, striker-fired, locked breech pistol and, at the time of production, the lightest pistol in the world. It was immediately adopted by all branches of the Russian military.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]KBP Instrument Design Bureau\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_hs2000">
		<text>HS2000</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_hs2000_descr">
		<text>The choice sidearm of the Croatian military and law enforcement, the HS2000 is a semi-automatic, striker-fired pistol known for its excellent ergonomics and outstanding safety features. Today, the HS family of pistols, based on the HS2000, has evolved into more than 50 different models.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Croatia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]HS Produkt\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_pm">
		<text>Makarov PM</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pm_custom">
		<text>Makarov PM</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pm_descr">
		<text>This Soviet legacy is one of the best compact self-defence handguns available. Small, highly reliable, easy to use and easy to maintain, the Pistol Makarova was selected because of its simplicity, easy manufacturing, accuracy and reasonable stopping power. Unfortunately though, it loses out to modern pistols in its class in terms of weight, magazine size and general performance.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Izhevsk Mechanical Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_pm_actor">
		<text>Makarov PM "Ceremonial"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pm_actor_descr">
		<text>This Soviet legacy is one of the best compact self-defence handguns available. Small, highly reliable, easy to use and easy to maintain, the Pistol Makarova was selected because of its simplicity, easy manufacturing, accuracy and reasonable stopping power. Unfortunately though, it loses out to modern pistols in its class in terms of weight, magazine size and general performance. The "Ceremonial" was originally given to Alexander Degtyarev as a reward for "Successful execution of highly dangerous state orders, as well as valor and courage shown in the line of duty". Other than the addition of tritium iron sights, the pistol's differences are of little note.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Izhevsk Mechanical Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_pmm">
		<text>Makarov PMM</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pmm_descr">
		<text>A redesign of the legendary Makarov, the PMM uses a 25% increase in gas pressure to significantly increase muzzle velocity and features a larger 12-round magazine. Though, even with these changes slightly bridging the gap between itself and modern pistols, it still loses out in terms of weight and general performance.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Izhevsk Mechanical Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_mp412">
		<text>MP-412 Rex</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp412_descr">
		<text>A Russian .357 double-action revolver most notable for its unique break-action chamber and automatic ejector. Though it was designed for export (REvolver for eXport), it never was put into full production due to lack of a market and restrictive gun import laws in the United States.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Izhmekh Mechanical Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_grach">
		<text>MP-443 Grach</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_grach_descr">
		<text>One of the standard military-issued sidearms in Russia, the MP-443 Grach is a double-action, short-recoil, semi-automatic pistol known for its reliability and versatility in the field. It is widely recognized for its smooth trigger pull and simplified design making it easy to disassemble and maintain.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Austria\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Izhevsk Mechanical Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_oc33">
		<text>OTs-33 Pernach</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_oc33_descr">
		<text>Developed to replace the Stechkin APS in special paramilitary units, the OTs-33 is a blowback-operated pistol capable of automatic and semi-automatic fire. The Pernach was specifically tasked with resolving the difficulty of controlling recoil in full-auto mode present in the Stechkin APS pistol and simplifying it for combat deployment. It is cheaper to manufacture, more controllable and boasts improved recoil.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]KBP Instrument Design Bureau\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_pb">
		<text>PB</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pb_custom">
		<text>PB</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pb_descr">
		<text>The PB (Pistolet Besshumnyj or Silent Pistol) was developed in 1967 for Spetsnaz units of the Soviet Army and KGB operatives. The pistol is based on a modified Makarov PM and features a unique integrated two-part suppressor that reduces bullet velocity to below subsonic levels.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Belgium\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]FN Herstal\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_sig220">
		<text>SIG P220</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig220_custom">
		<text>SIG P220</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig220_descr">
		<text>Often considered the best out-of-the-box .45 caliber double-action pistol available, the P220 is known for accuracy that parallels that of competition handguns. An instant success, it has been adopted by the Swiss and Japanese SDF and many European police organizations.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]West Germany, Switzerland\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]SIG Sauer\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_sig220_nimble">
		<text>SIG P220 "Alpine"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig220_nimble_descr">
		<text>Often considered the best out-of-the-box .45 caliber double-action pistol available, the P220 is known for accuracy that parallels that of competition handguns. An instant success, it has been adopted by the Swiss and Japanese SDF and many European police organizations. This limited edtion model has been fine tuned for better performance.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]West Germany, Switzerland\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]SIG Sauer\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_tt33">
		<text>TT-33</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_tt33_modern">
		<text>TT-33</text>
	</string>
	<string id="wpn_tt33_descr">
		<text>A Soviet, semi-automatic pistol developed as a service pistol for the Soviet military to replace the Nagant M1895 revolver. During its lifetime, many communist or Soviet bloc countries made variations of the TT-33 pistol until it was eventually replaced by the Makarov PM in 1952.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Tula Arms Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_usp">
		<text>USP45</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_usp_custom">
		<text>USP45</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_usp_descr">
		<text>Originally designed for the American market, the United States law enforcement and military provided much of the design criteria for the USP. Used by many police and special forces units worldwide, the Universal Self-Loading Pistol is known as an accurate and reliable handgun able to withstand extreme punishment and adverse conditions.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Germany\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Heckler &amp; Koch\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_usp_match">
		<text>USP Match</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_usp_match_descr">
		<text>A semi-automatic pistol designed as an improvement of the USP featuring a weighted barrel extension, polygonal rifling and an adjustable trigger that improves weapon accuracy and performance. Used by special forces and competitive shooters worldwide, the USP Match considered a top-of-the-line weapon able to compete with the elite.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Germany\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Heckler &amp; Koch\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_usp_nimble">
		<text>USP Match "Wolfhound"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_usp_nimble_descr">
		<text>Originally designed for the American market, the United States law enforcement and military provided much of the design criteria for the USP. Used by many police and special forces units worldwide, the Universal Self-Loading Pistol is known as an accurate and reliable handgun able to withstand extreme punishment and adverse conditions. The "Wolfhound" is a heavily modified USP Match once belonging to a mercenary of the same name.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Germany\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Heckler &amp; Koch\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_walther">
		<text>Walther P99</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_walther_custom">
		<text>Walther P99</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_walther_descr">
		<text>Legacy and innovation collide to create one of the most iconic and influential pistols in Walther’s history.  High-performance and feature-rich, the P99 quickly became one of the most trusted pistols of Law Enforcement officers around the world.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Germany\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Carl Walther GmbH Sportwaffen\n
		</text>
	</string>

<!--
	SHOTGUNS
-->
	<string id="st_wpn_protecta">
		<text>Armsel Protecta</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_protecta_camo">
		<text>Armsel Protecta</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_protecta_custom">
		<text>Armsel Protecta</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_protecta_descr">
		<text>The uniquely designed Armsel Protecta (also known as the Striker) is a rotating cylinder-fed 12-gauge shotgun developed for riot control and infantry combat and was intended to provide extreme firepower for militarized units. Antiquated now by the Russian Saiga-12 and the American AA-12, the Protecta was a revolutionary weapon at the time benefiting from a large magazine and a high effective rate of fire, though its bulkiness, considerable weight and long reload time are the trade-offs for these advantages.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]South Africa\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Hilton R. Walker\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_protecta_aim">
		<text>Armsel Protecta Custom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_protecta_aim_descr">
		<text>The uniquely designed Armsel Protecta (also known as the Striker) is a rotating cylinder-fed 12-gauge shotgun developed for riot control and infantry combat and was intended to provide extreme firepower for militarized units. Antiquated now by the Russian Saiga-12 and the American AA-12, the Protecta was a revolutionary weapon at the time benefiting from a large magazine and a high effective rate of fire, though its bulkiness, considerable weight and long reload time are the trade-offs for these advantages. This model features an integrated Aimpoint sight.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]South Africa\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Hilton R. Walker\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_protecta_nimble">
		<text>Armsel Protecta "Tank"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_protecta_nimble_descr">
		<text>The uniquely designed Armsel Protecta (also known as the Striker) is a rotating cylinder-fed 12-gauge shotgun developed for riot control and infantry combat and was intended to provide extreme firepower for militarized units. Antiquated now by the Russian Saiga-12 and the American AA-12, the Protecta was a revolutionary weapon at the time benefiting from a large magazine and a high effective rate of fire, though its bulkiness, considerable weight and long reload time are the trade-offs for these advantages. This model once belonged to a mercenary named "Tank" who took the time to modify the weapon for increased muzzle velocity and rate of fire.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]South Africa\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Hilton R. Walker\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_fort500">
		<text>Fort-500</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fort500_descr">
		<text>A smoothbore, pump-action shotgun intended to arm the Ministry of Internal Affairs, security services of Ukraine and civilians for amateur hunting and general use purposes. At present, the FORT-500 rifle has been discontinued in favor of newer models more specifically built for law enforcement use.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Ukraine\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Fort NGO\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_remington870">
		<text>Remington 870</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_remington870_descr">
		<text>Widely used by the public for sport, hunting and self-defence as well as by law enforcement and military organizations worldwide, the Remington 870 is one of the most famous and iconic pump-action shotguns in the world due to its characteristic recharge.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Remington Arms\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_toz34">
		<text>TOZ-34</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_toz34_custom">
		<text>TOZ-34</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_toz34_decor">
		<text>TOZ-34</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_toz34_descr">
		<text>Intended for professional and amateur hunting, the TOZ-34 is an over/under double-barreled shotgun that acquired the state quality mark of the USSR. It is heavy, dependable and packs a punch.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]USSR\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Tulsky Oruzheiny Zavod\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_toz34_obrez">
		<text>TOZ-34 (Sawn-off)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_toz34_obrez_custom">
		<text>TOZ-34 (Sawn-off)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_toz34_obrez_decor">
		<text>TOZ-34 (Sawn-off)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_toz34_obrez_descr">
		<text>Intended for professional and amateur hunting, the TOZ-34 is an over/under double-barreled shotgun that acquired the state quality mark of the USSR. The barrels and stock have been manually shortened to make the weapon lighter and more compact. Though quick to wield, its range and accuracy suffers but it is a devastating close range weapon, nonetheless.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]USSR\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Tulsky Oruzheiny Zavod\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_toz34_mark4">
		<text>TOZ-34 "Bison"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_toz34_mark4_descr">
		<text>Intended for professional and amateur hunting, the TOZ-34 is an over/under double-barreled shotgun that acquired the state quality mark of the USSR. It is heavy, dependable and packs a punch. The "Bison" is fitted with a reinforced barrel and Leupold Mark 4 scope for long distance big game hunting.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]USSR\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Tulsky Oruzheiny Zavod\n
		</text>
	</string>


	<string id="st_wpn_toz34_bull">
		<text>TOZ-34 "Bull"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_toz34_bull_descr">
		<text>Intended for professional and amateur hunting, the TOZ-34 is an over/under double-barreled shotgun that acquired the state quality mark of the USSR. It is heavy, dependable and packs a punch. The "Bull" was built with target aquisition in mind and features a red dot sight. If you need a hunting rifle to rival others, this may very well be your best choice.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]USSR\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Tulsky Oruzheiny Zavod\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_bm16_full">
		<text>TOZ-66</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_bm16_full_descr">
		<text>A break-action double barrel shotgun intended for amateur hunting and general civilian use. Though heavy and unwieldy, it packs an undeniable punch.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Tula Arms Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_bm16_full_alt">
		<text>TOZ-66</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_bm16_full_descr">
		<text>A break-action double barrel shotgun intended for amateur hunting and general civilian use. Though heavy and unwieldy, it packs an undeniable punch.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Tula Arms Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_bm16">
		<text>TOZ-66 (Sawn-off)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_bm16_descr">
		<text>A break-action, double barrel shotgun intended for amateur hunting and general civilian use. The barrels and stock have been manually shortened to make the weapon lighter and more compact. Though quick to wield, its range and accuracy suffers but it is a devastating close range weapon, nonetheless.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Tula Arms Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_bm16_alt">
		<text>TOZ-66 (Sawn-off)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_bm16_alt_descr">
		<text>A break-action, double barrel shotgun intended for amateur hunting and general civilian use. The barrels and stock have been manually shortened to make the weapon lighter and more compact. Though quick to wield, its range and accuracy suffers but it is a devastating close range weapon, nonetheless.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Tula Arms Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_toz194">
		<text>TOZ-194</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_toz194_descr">
		<text>A conventional pump-action shotgun intended for amateur hunting and general civilian use. Its main feature is its oddly long 540mm barrel; a necessary feature to meet the 805mm requirement for legal civilian ownership in Russia.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Tula Arms Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_usas12">
		<text>USAS-12</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_usas12_descr">
		<text>A gas-operated, selective fire, automatic shotgun designed to provide sustained firepower in close-combat scenarios. Although semi-automatic shotguns are common in military and law enforcement use, automatic shotguns are a niche market. Within that niche market, the USAS-12 is one of the most common and successful models available.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]South Korea\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Daewoo Precision Industries\n
		</text>
	</string>

<!--
	SMGS
-->
	<string id="st_wpn_p90">
		<text>FN P90</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_p90_descr">
		<text>Developed in the late 1980s as a personal defence weapon, the P90 is an unconventional submachine gun with a futuristic appearance, featuring a compact bullpup design with an integrated reflex sight, a unique top-mounted magazine and fully ambidextrous controls. Utilizing the SS90 round, the weapon was developed specifically to achieve high penetration against armored targets while keeping recoil low.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Belgium\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]FN Herstal\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_mp5">
		<text>MP5A3</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp5_descr">
		<text>One of the most famous and widespread firearms of its class, the MP5's compactness, accuracy and reliability have made it a favorite of numerous military, law enforcement, intelligence and security organizations the world over. The A3 variant is fitted with a retractable metal stock further increasing the weapon's CQB capabilities.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]West Germany\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Heckler &amp; Koch\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_mp5_alt">
		<text>MP5A3</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp5_alt_descr">
		<text>One of the most famous and widespread firearms of its class, the MP5's compactness, accuracy and reliability have made it a favorite of numerous military, law enforcement, intelligence and security organizations the world over. The A3 variant is fitted with a retractable metal stock further increasing the weapon's CQB capabilities.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]West Germany\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Heckler &amp; Koch\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_mp5_custom">
		<text>MP5A3</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp5_custom_descr">
		<text>One of the most famous and widespread firearms of its class, the MP5's compactness, accuracy and reliability have made it a favorite of numerous military, law enforcement, intelligence and security organizations the world over. The A3 variant is fitted with a retractable metal stock further increasing the weapon's CQB capabilities.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]West Germany\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Heckler &amp; Koch\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_mp5_nimble">
		<text>MP5A3 "Frasier"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp5_nimble_descr">
		<text>One of the most famous and widespread firearms of its class, the MP5's compactness, accuracy and reliability have made it a favorite of numerous military, law enforcement, intelligence and security organizations the world over. The A3 variant is fitted with a retractable metal stock further increasing the weapon's CQB capabilities. The "Frasier" features a vertical foregrip and fires the more powerful .45 ACP.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]West Germany\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Heckler &amp; Koch\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_mp5sd">
		<text>MP5SD6</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp5sd_descr">
		<text>One of the most famous and widespread firearms of its class, the MP5's compactness, accuracy and reliability have made it a favorite of numerous military, law enforcement, intelligence and security organizations the world over. The A3 variant is fitted with a retractable metal stock further increasing the weapon's CQB capabilities. The SD6 variant comes with a retractable buttstock, integrated suppressor and 3-round burst fire select.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]West Germany\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Heckler &amp; Koch\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_mp5sd_custom">
		<text>MP5SD6</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp5sd_custom_descr">
		<text>One of the most famous and widespread firearms of its class, the MP5's compactness, accuracy and reliability have made it a favorite of numerous military, law enforcement, intelligence and security organizations the world over. The A3 variant is fitted with a retractable metal stock further increasing the weapon's CQB capabilities. The SD6 variant comes with a retractable buttstock, integrated suppressor and 3-round burst fire select.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]West Germany\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Heckler &amp; Koch\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_mp5sd_new">
		<text>MP5SD6</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp5sd_new_descr">
		<text>One of the most famous and widespread firearms of its class, the MP5's compactness, accuracy and reliability have made it a favorite of numerous military, law enforcement, intelligence and security organizations the world over. The A3 variant is fitted with a retractable metal stock further increasing the weapon's CQB capabilities. The SD6 variant comes with a retractable buttstock, integrated suppressor and 3-round burst fire select.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]West Germany\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Heckler &amp; Koch\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_mp7">
		<text>MP7</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_kiparis">
		<text>OTs-02 Kiparis</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_kiparis_descr">
		<text>Based on the Czechoslovak Skorpion vz.61, the OTs-02 is a blowback operated submachine gun used by the Russian Internal Affairs Ministry as a special purpose police weapon. Powered by free bolt recoil with shots fired from a closed bolt, the weapon's accuracy is surprisingly good, even under fully automatic fire. To further increase weapon stability, a folding stock is included that folds up on top of the receiver.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]KBP Instrument Design Bureau\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_bizon">
		<text>PP-19 Bizon</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_bizon_descr">
		<text>Developed at the request of the Russian Ministry of Internal Affairs for counter-terrorist and law enforcement units that needed a lightweight weapon capable of fast and accurate fire at close ranges. The Bizon is most notable for it's distinctive under-barrel helical magazine.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Izhmash\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_pp2000">
		<text>PP-2000</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pp2000_descr">
		<text>Used by special operations units and law enforcement personnel, the PP-2000 personal defense weapon is often considered to be one of the best in its class. It is compact, lightweight and simple in design for increased reliability and simplified maintenance.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]KBP Instrument Design Bureau\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ump45">
		<text>UMP45</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ump45_descr">
		<text>Developed as a more powerful, lighter and cheaper successor to the MP5, the UMP45 provides greater stopping power but also produces more recoil. To mitigate this issue, the UMP's cyclic rate of fire was lowered significantly. Though created to replace the MP5, both submachine guns still see production to this day with the UMP being used in more than 20 countries, worldwide.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Germany\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Heckler &amp; Koch\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ump45_custom">
		<text>UMP45</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ump45_custom_descr">
		<text>Developed as a more powerful, lighter and cheaper successor to the MP5, the UMP45 provides greater stopping power but also produces more recoil. To mitigate this issue, the UMP's cyclic rate of fire was lowered significantly. Though created to replace the MP5, both submachine guns still see production to this day with the UMP being used in more than 20 countries, worldwide.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Germany\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Heckler &amp; Koch\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_vz61">
		<text>Skorpion vz.68</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vz61_descr">
		<text>Originally chambered for .32 ACP (vz.61), it was developed for use with security forces and was adopted by the Czechoslovak Army in 1961 as a personal sidearm for lower-ranking army staff, vehicle drivers, armoured vehicle personnel and special forces. Although mass production of the model vz.68 never took place, a large number of pre-production vz.68 models made their way into the Zone.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Czechoslovak Socialist Republic\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Ceska zbrojovka Uhersky Brod\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_vz61_alt">
		<text>Skorpion vz.68</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vz61_alt_descr">
		<text>Developed for use with security forces and adopted by the Czechoslovak Army as a personal sidearm for lower-ranking army staff, the vz.68 is a heavier version of the vz.61 chambered in the larger 9x19mm cartridge. As this model never went into mass production, they are considered a unique addition for any collector.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Czechoslovak Socialist Republic\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Ceska zbrojovka Uhersky Brod\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_vz61_camo">
		<text>Skorpion vz.68</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vz61_camo_descr">
		<text>Developed for use with security forces and adopted by the Czechoslovak Army as a personal sidearm for lower-ranking army staff, the vz.68 is a heavier version of the vz.61 chambered in the larger 9x19mm cartridge. As this model never went into mass production, they are considered a unique addition for any collector.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Czechoslovak Socialist Republic\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Ceska zbrojovka Uhersky Brod\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_vz61_freedom">
		<text>Skorpion vz.68 "Freedom"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vz61_freedom_descr">
		<text>Developed for use with security forces and adopted by the Czechoslovak Army as a personal sidearm for lower-ranking army staff, the vz.68 is a heavier version of the vz.61 chambered in the larger 9x19mm cartridge. As this model never went into mass production, they are considered a unique addition for any collector. The "Freedom" has had its internals extensively modified for better performance.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Czechoslovak Socialist Republic\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Ceska zbrojovka Uhersky Brod\n
		</text>
	</string>

<!--
	RIFLES
-->

	<string id="st_wpn_9a91">
		<text>9A-91</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_aek971">
		<text>AEK-971</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aek971_descr">
		<text>Developed to participate in a competition announced by the USSR's Ministry of Defense, the internal design and layout is based on previous AK rifles and is equipped with a recoil-balancing mechanism, resulting in more controllable automatic fire. Small batches of this rifle were manufactured for the Russian MVD.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Degtyarev Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_aek973">
		<text>AEK-973</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aek973_descr">
		<text>The AEK-973 is a 7.62x39mm version of the AEK-971 which is based on previous AK rifles in internal design and layout. It is also equipped with a recoil-balancing mechanism, resulting in more controllable automatic fire. Small batches of this rifle were manufactured for the Russian MVD.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Degtyarev Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak">
		<text>AK-47</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak_descr">
		<text>The Avtomat Kalashnikova, is a gas-operated assault rifle developed by Russian small-arms designer Mikhail Kalashnikov. After more than seven decades since its creation, the AK-47 and its variants remain one of the most popular and widely used firearms in the world due to their reliability under harsh conditions, low production cost, and ease of use.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Kalashnikov Concern\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak74_old">
		<text>AK-74</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74_old_descr">
		<text>Developed in the early 1970s by Mikhail Kalashnikov to replace the AKM, the AK-74 is an adaptation of the 7.62x39mm AKM assault rifle and features several important design improvements including the use of the newer, high velocity 5.45x39mm round. Compared with the preceding AKM, it has better effective firing range, accuracy and reliability.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Izhmash\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak74m">
		<text>AK-74M</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74m_alt">
		<text>AK-74M</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74m_camo">
		<text>AK-74M</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74m_custom">
		<text>AK-74M</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74m_duty">
		<text>AK-74M</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74m_descr">
		<text>An improved version of the AK-74 and the service rifle of the Russian Federation, designed with modern and composite materials to significantly reduce weight and improve accuracy. Each AK-74M is fitted with a side-rail bracket for mounting optics.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Kalashnikov Concern\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak74m_pk-a">
		<text>AK-74M PK-A</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74m_pk-a_descr">
		<text>An improved version of the AK-74 and the service rifle of the Russian Federation, designed with modern and composite materials to significantly reduce weight and improve accuracy. This model has a PK-A sight installed on the side-rail bracket.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Kalashnikov Concern\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak74">
		<text>AK-74N</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74_alt">
		<text>AK-74N</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74_custom">
		<text>AK-74N</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74_modern">
		<text>AK-74N</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74_descr">
		<text>Developed in the early 1970s by Mikhail Kalashnikov to replace the AKM, the AK-74 is an adaptation of the 7.62x39mm AKM assault rifle and features several important design improvements including the use of the newer, high velocity 5.45x39mm round. Compared with the preceding AKM, it has better effective firing range, accuracy and reliability. The AK-74N variant comes with a side dovetail rail for mounting optical sights.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Izhmash\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak74_eot">
		<text>AK-74N EOTech</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74_eot_descr">
		<text>Developed in the early 1970s by Mikhail Kalashnikov to replace the AKM, the AK-74 is an adaptation of the 7.62x39mm AKM assault rifle and features several important design improvements including the use of the newer, high velocity 5.45x39mm round. Compared with the preceding AKM, it has better effective firing range, accuracy and reliability. This special variant comes with an EOTech sight.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Izhmash\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak101">
		<text>AK-101</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak101_camo">
		<text>AK-101</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak101_descr">
		<text>An assault rifle of the Kalashnikov series marketed at those looking for a weapon that combines the logistical compatibility and familiarity of the 5.56x45mm NATO round with the reliability of a Kalashnikov. The design of this rifle is similar to the AK-74 and is designed with modern and composite materials, including plastics that reduce weight and improve accuracy.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Kalashnikov Concern\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak102">
		<text>AK-102</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak102_descr">
		<text>Designed entirely for export purposes, the AK-102 is a shortened carbine version of the AK-101 rifle, combining the logistical compatibility and familiarity of the 5.56x45mm NATO round with the reliability of a Kalashnikov. The design of this rifle is similar to the AK-74 and is designed with modern and composite materials, including plastics that reduce weight and improve accuracy.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Kalashnikov Concern\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak103">
		<text>AK-103</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak103_camo">
		<text>AK-103</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak103_descr">
		<text>The AK-103 is an AK-100 derivative of the AK-74M chambered for the 7.62x39mm round. The rifle is designed with modern and composite materials to significantly reduce weight and improve accuracy.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Kalashnikov Concern\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak104">
		<text>AK-104</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak104_descr">
		<text>A compact version of the AK-103 rifle featuring a shortened barrel. The rifle is designed with modern and composite materials to significantly reduce weight and improve accuracy.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Kalashnikov Concern\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_aks">
		<text>AKS-47</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aks_descr">
		<text>The Avtomat Kalashnikova, is a gas-operated assault rifle developed by Russian small-arms designer Mikhail Kalashnikov. After more than seven decades since its creation, the AK-47 and its variants remain one of the most popular and widely used firearms in the world due to their reliability under harsh conditions, low production cost, and ease of use. All AKS-47 rifles featured a downward-folding metal stock.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Kalashnikov Concern\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_aks74">
		<text>AKS-74</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aks74_new">
		<text>AKS-74</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aks74_descr">
		<text>Developed in the early 1970s by Mikhail Kalashnikov to replace the AKM, the AK-74 is an adaptation of the 7.62x39mm AKM assault rifle and features several important design improvements including the use of the newer, high velocity 5.45x39mm round. Compared with the preceding AKM, it has better effective firing range, accuracy and reliability. All AKS-74 rifles came with a side-folding metal shoulder stock.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Izhmash\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_old">
		<text>AK-74U</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_old_descr">
		<text>The AKS-74U bridges the tactical deployment gap between a submachine gun and an assault rifle and was intended as a compact but relatively powerful automatic alternative to the AKS-74. It is significantly lighter and more maneuverable in tight quarters while still boasting the reliability of a Kalashnikov.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Kalashnikov Concern\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u">
		<text>AKS-74UN</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_descr">
		<text>The AKS-74U bridges the tactical deployment gap between a submachine gun and an assault rifle and was intended as a compact but relatively powerful automatic alternative to the AKS-74. It is significantly lighter and more maneuverable in tight quarters while still boasting the reliability of a Kalashnikov. Each AK-74UN is fitted with a side-rail bracket for mounting optics.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Kalashnikov Concern\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_camo">
		<text>AKS-74UN</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_camo_descr">
		<text>The AKS-74U bridges the tactical deployment gap between a submachine gun and an assault rifle and was intended as a compact but relatively powerful automatic alternative to the AKS-74. It is significantly lighter and more maneuverable in tight quarters while still boasting the reliability of a Kalashnikov. Each AK-74UN is fitted with a side-rail bracket for mounting optics.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Kalashnikov Concern\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_custom">
		<text>AKS-74UN</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_custom_descr">
		<text>The AKS-74U bridges the tactical deployment gap between a submachine gun and an assault rifle and was intended as a compact but relatively powerful automatic alternative to the AKS-74. It is significantly lighter and more maneuverable in tight quarters while still boasting the reliability of a Kalashnikov. Each AK-74UN is fitted with a side-rail bracket for mounting optics.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Kalashnikov Concern\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_snag">
		<text>AK-74UNB</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_snag_descr">
		<text>The AKS-74U bridges the tactical deployment gap between a submachine gun and an assault rifle and was intended as a compact but relatively powerful automatic alternative to the AKS-74. It is significantly lighter and more maneuverable in tight quarters while still boasting the reliability of a Kalashnikov. This special variant comes with a 45 round RPK magazine and an integrated Kobra sight and suppressor.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Kalashnikov Concern\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_akm">
		<text>AKM</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_akm_descr">
		<text>An improved version of the AK-47 rifle featuring detailed improvements and enhancements that optimized the rifle for mass production. Among these changes, the AKM's weight was reduced, the accuracy during automatic fire was increased and several reliability issues were addressed.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Tula Arms Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_akms">
		<text>AKMS</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_akms_alt">
		<text>AKMS</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_akms_descr">
		<text>An improved version of the AK-47 rifle featuring detailed improvements and enhancements that optimized the rifle for mass production. Among these changes, the AKM's weight was reduced, the accuracy during automatic fire was increased and several reliability issues were addressed.  All AKMS rifles came equipped with an under-folding metal shoulder stock in place of the fixed wooden stock.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Tula Arms Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_abakan">
		<text>AN-94</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_abakan_camo">
		<text>AN-94</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_abakan_descr">
		<text>Designed as a potential replacement to the AK-74 series of rifles, it failed to fill its intended role due to its complex design and price. Still in use as a limited special purpose weapon, the AN-94 offers a unique two-shot burst function at a stated 1800 rounds per minute with the unique feature of delaying recoil for the first two rounds. Capable of a hyperburst fire mode.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Izhmash\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_val">
		<text>AS Val</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_val_descr">
		<text>Engineered for Soviet special operations units, the AS Val is a gas operated, integrally suppressed weapon that was set to supersede the AK-47 and AKM rifles. It is easily disassembled and concealed, lightweight and comfortable to fire with the suppressor reducing bullet velocity to below subsonic levels. Today, the AS VAL sees widespread use among Russian special forces.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Tula Arms Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_val_modern">
		<text>AS Val</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_val_modern_descr">
		<text>Engineered for Soviet special operations units, the AS Val is a gas operated, integrally suppressed weapon that was set to supersede the AK-47 and AKM rifles. It is easily disassembled and concealed, lightweight and comfortable to fire with the suppressor reducing bullet velocity to below subsonic levels. Today, the AS VAL sees widespread use among Russian special forces.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Tula Arms Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

    <string id="st_wpn_famas3">
        <text>FAMAS F1</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_famas3_descr">
        <text>Adopted by the French in 1978, the FAMAS has since became the standard French Army rifle. The weapon features a unique bullpup design, is very accurate and is easily controlled during its burst fire mode. Notably, the length of the weapon allows it to be used in roles that would ordinarily require a submachine gun.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]France\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]GIAT Industries\n
		</text>
    </string>

<!-- oddly only uses names -->
	<string id="st_wpn_fn2000">
		<text>FN F2000</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fn2000_camo">
		<text>FN F2000</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fn2000_custom">
		<text>FN F2000</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_fal">
		<text>FN FAL</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fal_descr">
		<text>One of the most widely used, recognized and popular automatic rifles in history, the FN FAL has seen use by more than 90 countries. Because of its prevalence and widespread usage among the military of many NATO and first world countries during the Cold War, it was given the title "The right arm of the Free World".\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Belgium\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]FN Herstal\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_fnc">
		<text>FN FNC</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fnc_descr">
		<text>A selective fire, gas-operated assault rifle developed as a less expensive alternative to the M16. Using mostly pressed steel and plastic components, the FN FNC is surprisingly light and controllable and when comparing its cost to similar imports, the true value of the rifle becomes even more apparent.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Belgium\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]FN Herstal\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_scar">
		<text>FN SCAR-H</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_scar_custom">
		<text>FN SCAR-H</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_scar_new">
		<text>FN SCAR-H</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_scar_descr">
		<text>In early 2004, USSOCOM issued a design request for a family of assault rifles using two different calibers while keeping the parts and ergonomics nearly-identical; hence the Special Operations Forces Combat Assault Rifle "SCAR" was born into service. Firing the long-range, hard-hitting 7.62x51mm NATO cartridge, the selective-fire FN SCAR-H's innovative gas-operated, short-stroke piston system reduces fouling for greater reliability.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Belgium\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]FN Herstal, FN America\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_g3">
		<text>G3A3</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g3_descr">
		<text>In the world of battle rifles, the Heckler and Koch G3 is an important part of firearms history, known for being incredibly durable, reliable and decently accurate. The A3 varient features a retractable stock.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Germany\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Heckler &amp; Koch\n
		</text>
	</string>	

	<string id="st_wpn_g3sg1">
		<text>G3SG1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g3sg1_descr">
		<text>In the world of battle rifles, the Heckler and Koch G3 is an important part of firearms history, known for being incredibly durable, reliable and decently accurate. The G3SG1 is a G3A3 that has been hand picked and modified for accuracy. Adopted by several nations as a designated marksman rifle for military use, its similarity to the G3 makes it easier to train soldiers that already have experience with the standard G3.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Germany\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Heckler &amp; Koch\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ace21">
		<text>Galil ACE-21</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ace21_descr">
		<text>The Galil "ACE" series is based upon the original design of the IMI Galil, but with a modern design increasing accuracy and lowering weight while maintaining ergonomics, ease of maintenance and reliability under battle conditions. It has since been adopted as a standard service rifle in multiple countries, such as the Chilean Army and People's Army of Vietnam.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Israel\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Israel Weapon Industries\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_galil">
		<text>Galil AR</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_galil_custom">
		<text>Galil AR</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_galil_modern">
		<text>Galil AR</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_galil_descr">
		<text>Designed for operation in arid conditions, the Galil is noted for its reliability in combat conditions, and ease of maintenance. It has a line chambered for 5.56x45mm and one for 7.62x51mm.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Israel\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Israel Military Industries\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_hk416">
		<text>HK416</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_hk416_descr">
		<text>Developed for United States special operations forces as a major product improvement of the M4, the HK416 uses the proprietary gas piston system found on the G36 and therefore does not introduce propellant gases and carbon fouling back into the weapon’s interior, making it the most reliable of any M4/M16 type weapons. The rifle has been combat-proven and has rightfully gained worldwide attention of military and law enforcement.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Germany\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]	Heckler &amp; Koch\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_hk417">
		<text>HK417</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_hk417_descr">
		<text>A reliable, gas-operated, selective-fire rifle with a rotating bolt, intended for use in roles where the greater penetrative power, stopping power and range of the 7.62x51mm cartridge are required. It has been adopted for service by a number of armed forces, special forces and police organizations.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Germany\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Heckler &amp; Koch\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_l85">
		<text>L85A1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_l85_alt">
		<text>L85A1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_l85_custom">
		<text>L85A1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_l85_modern">
		<text>L85A1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_l85_descr">
		<text>Once the standard weapon for the British armed forces, now replaced by the L85A2 and A3 respectively, the L85A1 shares the same general performance as its younger brothers but suffered numerous reliability-related issues.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United Kingdom\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]RSAF Enfield, Royal Ordnance, Heckler &amp; Koch\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_l85a2">
		<text>L85A2</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_l85a2_alt">
		<text>L85A2</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_l85a2_custom">
		<text>L85A2</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_l85a2_modern">
		<text>L85A2</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_l85a2_descr">
		<text>Recognized for being extremely reliable and impressively accurate, the L85A2 is the standard weapon of the British armed forces and an improvement over the L85A1, fixing many of its design flaws. Notably, the A2 is extremely reliable over a range of climates and adverse conditions allowing it to be fielded for various operational scenarios.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United Kingdom\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Royal Ordnance, Heckler &amp; Koch\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_lr300">
		<text>LR-300ML</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_lr300_camo">
		<text>LR-300ML</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_lr300_custom">
		<text>LR-300ML</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_lr300_descr">
		<text>Based on the AR-15, the LR-300 is an excellent weapon system suitable for military use in close quarters battle. Its folding skeletal stock makes it ideal for aggressive and rapid building entries that require a compact yet powerful selective fire weapon. Ergonomic and lightweight, it is highly accurate but is sensitive to dirt and therefore, not ideal for tough field conditions. The ML variant has a Picatinny rail for accessory attachment.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Z-M Weapons\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_mossberg590">
		<text>Mossberg 590A1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mossberg590_descr">
		<text>Developed as a modification of the Mossberg model 500 shotgun for adoption by the US Military, this was the standard shotgun of the US Armed forces until being officially replaced by the Benelli M1014. Modifications included strengthening of the receiver, installation of a vented heatshield around the barrel, a bayonet lug, extended magazine and an aluminium trigger guard. Since 1987, Mossberg 590A1 shotguns are still used by the US Navy and US Marine Corp.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]O.F. Mossberg &amp; Sons\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_groza">
		<text>OTs-14 Groza</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_groza_descr">
		<text>The Groza "Thunder" modular assault rifle was intended for various special forces in the Russian Army and Internal Affairs Ministry as a dedicated urban warfare weapon. It features a bullpup design with a 40mm grenade launcher located in place of the removable foregrip.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255] PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]TsKIB SOO\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_m4">
		<text>M4</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m4_descr">
		<text>The M4 Carbine descends from a family of firearms tracing its lineage back to the original AR-15 by ArmaLite. It is a gas operated, air cooled, selective fire rifle, sharing 80% of its parts with the M16 assault rifle, though it is notably shorter and lighter. It has been adopted by United States Special Operations Command (USSOCOM) and is the preferred weapon of the U.S. Army Special Forces and Navy SEALs.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Colt's Manufacturing Company\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_m4a1">
		<text>M4A1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m4a1_camo">
		<text>M4A1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m4a1_custom">
		<text>M4A1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m4a1_freedom">
		<text>M4A1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m4a1_descr">
		<text>The M4 Carbine descends from a family of firearms tracing its lineage back to the original AR-15 by ArmaLite. It is a gas operated, air cooled, selective fire rifle, sharing 80% of its parts with the M16 assault rifle, though it is notably shorter and lighter. It has been adopted by United States Special Operations Command (USSOCOM) and is the preferred weapon of the U.S. Army Special Forces and Navy SEALs. The A1 variant strengthened the barrel and replaced the burst-fire fire select with a fully automatic option.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Colt's Manufacturing Company\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_m16a2">
		<text>M16A2</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m16a2_descr">
		<text>The M16 is the U.S. military designation for a family of rifles derived from the ArmaLite AR-15 that have been the primary infantry rifle of the United States military since the 1960s. It is a lightweight, air cooled, gas operated, assault rifle with a rotating bolt. The A2 variant is the second generation in the M16 series and a significant upgrade over the A1, with notable upgrades being a semi-auto and three-round burst fire selector, use of the improved 5.56x45mm cartridge and an improved handguard, pistol grip,  buttstock and heavy barrel.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Colt Manufacturing Company, FN Herstal\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_m16">
		<text>M16A4</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m16_descr">
		<text>The M16 is the U.S. military designation for a family of rifles derived from the ArmaLite AR-15 that have been the primary infantry rifle of the United States military since the 1960s. It is a lightweight, air cooled, gas operated, assault rifle with a rotating bolt. The A4 variant is the fourth generation in the M16 series and comes with a removable carrying handle and Picatinny rail for mounting optics and other devices.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Colt's Manufacturing Company, FN Herstal\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_m60">
		<text>M60</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m60_descr">
		<text>From a family of American general-purpose machine guns firing from a disintegrating belt of M13 links, the M60 has served with every branch of the U.S. military and its manufacture and continued upgrade for military and commercial purchase continues into the 21st century. Although replaced or supplemented in most roles by other designs, most notably the M240 machine gun, it remains a tried-and-true ammunition-eating, suppressive fire, anti-personnel weapon.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Saco Defense, U.S. Ordnance\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_m249">
		<text>M249 SAW</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m249_descr">
		<text>The M249 is a belt fed, American adaptation of the Belgian FN Minimi machine gun that has seen action in every major conflict involving the United States since the U.S. invasion of Panama in 1989. The M249 SAW provides infantry squads with a high rate of machine gun fire, combined with the accuracy and portability of a rifle.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]FN Herstal\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_mk14">
		<text>Mk 14 EBR</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mk14_descr">
		<text>The Mk 14 Enhanced Battle Rifle is an American military selective-fire battle rifle and a designated marksman rifle originally built for USSOCOM. Known for it's incredible long range accuracy, modularity and controllable recoil, the EBR is a favorite among many.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Naval Surface Warfare Center Crane Division\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_rp">
		<text>PKM</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_rp_descr">
		<text>A modernized and improved version of the PK, the PKM's upgrades were primarily aimed at reducing weight, facilitating easier operation and simplifying production. A very reliable machine gun that remains in use as a front-line infantry and vehicle-mounted weapon with Russia's armed forces. This model has been manually altered to include an enlarged ammo box.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Degtyaryov Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_pkm_zulus">
		<text>PKM "Zulu"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pkm_zulus_descr">
		<text>A modernized and improved version of the PK, the PKM's upgrades were primarily aimed at reducing weight, facilitating easier operation and simplifying production. A very reliable machine gun that remains in use as a front-line infantry and vehicle-mounted weapon with Russia's armed forces. Equipped with a heavier barrel and Kobra sight, the "Zulu" has also been manually altered for a faster rate of fire and increased muzzle velocity.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Degtyaryov Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_pkp">
		<text>PKP Pecheneg</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pkp_descr">
		<text>A modernized PKM machine gun chambered for the 7.62x54mm round, said to be more accurate than all its predecessors due to a heavier, non-removable forced air cooling barrel with radial cooling ribs and a unique handle which eliminates the haze effect from hot gases. Currently in use by Russian Army Spetsnaz and, though it was developed mainly for infantry use, is often fitted to light vehicles.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russian\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Mikhail Kalashnikov\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ppsh41">
		<text>PPSh-41</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ppsh41_camo">
		<text>PPSh-41</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ppsh41_new">
		<text>PPSh-41</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ppsh41_old">
		<text>PPSh-41</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ppsh41_descr">
		<text>A selective-fire, open bolt, blowback submachine gun known for it's high rate of fire, the PPSh saw extensive combat use during World War II, becoming one of the most common infantry weapons of the Soviet Armed Forces with about six million manufactured, making it the most-produced submachine gun of the war. A PPSh with a drum magazine has become one of the symbols of the Soviet soldier on the Eastern Front of WWII Europe.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_rpd">
		<text>RPD</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_rpd_descr">
		<text>A light machine gun developed in the Soviet Union by Vasily Degtyaryov, created as a replacement for the DPM light machine gun. The new open bolt, gas operated, striker fired RPD was, at the time, 10 pounds lighter than any other weapon of its kind in service and used a cartridge that produced significantly less recoil under automatic fire.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Degtyaryov Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_rpk">
		<text>RPK</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_rpk_descr">
		<text>A light machine gun developed by Mikhail Kalashnikov as part of Soviet efforts to standardize the armory of the Red Army, the RPK replaced the RPD and is still in use as of present day. Featuring a similar design layout to the Kalashnikov series of rifles, it boasts modifications to increase its effective range and accuracy. It is also equipped with an improved barrel to improve sustained fire capability; a common issue with the RPD.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Vyatskiye Polyany Machine-Building Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_rpk74">
		<text>RPK-74</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_rpk74_descr">
		<text>A light machine gun developed by Mikhail Kalashnikov as part of Soviet efforts to standardize the armory of the Red Army, the RPK replaced the RPD and is still in use as of present day. The RPK-74 features a large amount of improvements, including but not limited to an improved barrel, a new gas block for improved muzzle velocity and a bipod.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Vyatskiye Polyany Machine-Building Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ash12">
		<text>ShAK-12</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ash12_descr">
		<text>A dedicated CQB/Urban Operations rifle, developed by request of the Russian FSB for special units that operate in urban environments against heavily armed and organized targets that need to be killed in one shot. Therefore, the ShAK-12 is designed with extreme short-range stopping power in mind.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Izhmash\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_type63">
		<text>Type 63</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_type63_descr">
		<text>A fully-automatic, rotating bolt assault rifle bearing a striking resemblance to the Soviet-made SKS. The Type 63 was intended to replace the Type 56 semi-automatic carbine in Chinese service when military infantry needed a compromise between firepower and long range accuracy.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]China\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]PRC Government Arsenals\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_vepr12">
		<text>Vepr-12</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vepr12_descr">
		<text>Conceived for the Russian military and law enforcement market, with civilian applications ranging from hunting to self-defense and competition, the Vepr-12 is a multi-purpose, semi-automatic shotgun patterned after Kalashnikov rifles and built on the heavy RPK light machine gun receiver. With its fixed open port gas system, the Vepr-12 can effectively cycle a multitude of 12-gauge loads, making it a highly versatile semi-automatic shotgun.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Molot Oruzhie Ltd.\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_vsk94">
		<text>VSK-94</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_vintorez">
		<text>VSS Vintorez</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vintorez_alt">
		<text>VSS Vintorez</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vintorez_descr">
		<text>Intended for various Spetsnaz troops of the Soviet Army, KGB and MVD, the VSS is quite popular among its users for its stealthy capabilities, integral suppressor and the great lethality of the heavy 9x39mm round.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Tula Arms Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_vintorez_1pn93">
		<text>VSS Vintorez 1PN93</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vintorez_1pn93_descr">
		<text>Intended for various Spetsnaz troops of the Soviet Army, KGB and MVD, the VSS is quite popular among its users for its stealthy capabilities, integral suppressor and the great lethality of the heavy 9x39mm round. This model has an integrated 1PN93 scope.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Tula Arms Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_vintorez_nimble">
		<text>VSS Vintorez "Tide"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vintorez_nimble_descr">
		<text>Intended for various Spetsnaz troops of the Soviet Army, KGB and MVD, the VSS is quite popular among its users for its stealthy capabilities, integral suppressor and the great lethality of the heavy 9x39mm round. The "Tide" has been extensively modified and fitted with a 1PN93 scope.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Tula Arms Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_umirotvoritel">
		<text>Unidentified Weapon</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_umirotvoritel_descr">
		<text>An unknown weapon. Appears faulty as squeezing the trigger does nothing. After close inspection, it does not appear to fire rounds based on ignition but instead by electro-magnetic force.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Unknown\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Unknown\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_xm8">
		<text>XM8</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_xm8_descr">
		<text>A lightweight assault rifle system sharing design and engineering with the G36 rifle originally part of the Objective Individual Combat Weapon program for development of a "smart" grenade launcher system with an underslung carbine rifle. Unable to meet performance and weight requirements, the program was eventually canceled and separated, resulting in the XM8 project.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Germany, United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Heckler &amp; Koch, Alliant Technosystems\n
		</text>
	</string>
-->

<!--
	SNIPERS
-->
	<string id="st_wpn_l96a1m">
		<text>AWSM </text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_l96a1m_descr">
		<text>The Arctic Warfare Super Magnum is a variant of the L96A1 chambered in .338 Lapua Magnum with a revised locking ring, extractor and magazine to work with the increased size and operating pressures of magnum rifle cartridges.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United Kingdom\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Accuracy International\n
		%c[d_orange] • Increased penetration: +5\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_m82">
		<text>Barrett M82</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m82_descr">
		<text>A recoil-operated, semi-automatic, anti-materiel sniper rifle engineered as the first shoulder fired semi-automatic capable of firing 50 BMG. The M82 has been proven in combat in every environment from the snow covered mountains, to the desolate deserts and everything in between. Its low recoil and reliable power delivers on target with every pull of the trigger. Despite being designated as an anti-materiel rifle, the M82 is often deployed as an anti-personnel system. More than just a rifle, the M82 is an American icon.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Barrett Firearms Manufacturing\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_m98b">
		<text>Barrett M98B</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m98b_descr">
		<text>Barrett wanted to create a tactical firearm chambered for .338 Lapua Magnum but rather than modifying a hunting rifle, they created an original design for the M98B. Sporting a simple design, it is easy for users to disassemble and clean, and thanks to its durability, versatility, and accuracy, is popular among those who demand optimum performance with unmatched reliability.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Barrett Firearms Manufacturing\n
		%c[d_orange] • Increased penetration: +5\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_g43">
		<text>Gewehr 43</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g43_descr">
		<text>In 1940, the Germans enacted a program to deliver a standard semi-automatic rifle to their infantry ranks to help improve upon their outdated bolt-action rifles. With the Gewehr 41 being too expensive for wartime mass production, the Gewehr 43 was created fielding a number of improvements over its predecessor, including a redesigned gas system, detachable magazine and machined side mount. This model comes with a ZF4 scope.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Nazi Germany\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Walther GmbH\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_k98">
		<text>Karabiner 98k</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_k98_descr">
		<text>One of the final developments in the long line of Mauser military rifles and the standard service rifle of the German Wehrmacht, the Kar98 was selected by Nazi Germany for its exceptional accuracy and effectiveness in long distance situations. In skilled hands with a ZF39 telescopic sight, these rifles had an effective range of up to 1000 meters. This model has been fitted with a sniper scope by MARCH, Japan.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Nazi Germany\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Mauser\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_l96a1">
		<text>L96A1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_l96a1_descr">
		<text>The Accuracy International Arctic Warfare rifle has proved popular as a civilian, police and military rifle since its introduction in the 1980s and is the standard sniper rifle for the British army. Impressive performance modifications allow the weapon to be used in temperatures as low as -40°C, without impairing operation in less extreme conditions.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United Kingdom\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Accuracy International\n
		%c[d_orange] • Increased penetration: +5\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_m24">
		<text>M24 SWS</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m24_descr">
		<text>Known as the "Green Dragon", the M24 Sniper Weapon System is the military and police version of the Remington Model 700 rifle, currently used by the United States Army. It has the "long action" bolt version of the Remington 700 receiver but is chambered for the 7.62x51mm NATO cartridge and fitted with a Leupold 10x40mm scope.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Remington Arms\n
		%c[d_orange] • Increased penetration: +5\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_mosin">
		<text>Mosin-Nagant</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mosin_descr">
		<text>The M1891 is bolt-action, internal magazine–fed military rifle used by the armed forces of the Russian Empire, the Soviet Union and various other states. It is one of the most mass-produced military bolt-action rifles in history, with over 37 million units produced since 1891. In spite of its age, it has been used in various conflicts around the world up to present day. Though the Mosin is unable to accommodate the increased barrel pressure of AP rounds, that didn't stop it from being extremely successful in World War II as a sniper rifle when equipped with a 4.0x PE or 3.5x PU scope.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Tula Arms Plant\n
		%c[d_orange] • Increased penetration: +5\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_svu">
		<text>OTs-03 SVU</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_svu_alt">
		<text>OTs-03 SVU</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_svu_descr">
		<text>A rare, compact version of the SVD sniper rifle created for use by the airborne infantry but later employed mainly by the Russian Ministry of Internal Affairs. The main difference between it and the SVD is its compact size and thus improved handling, thanks to a bullpup configuration and shortened barrel.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]KBP Instrument Design Bureau\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_svu_nimble">
		<text>OTs-03A SVU-A</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_svu_nimble_descr">
		<text>A rare, compact, fully automatic version of the SVD sniper rifle created for use by the airborne infantry but later employed mainly by the Russian Ministry of Internal Affairs. The main difference between it and the SVD is its compact size and thus improved handling, thanks to a bullpup configuration and shortened barrel.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]KBP Instrument Design Bureau\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_trg_sako">
		<text>Sako TRG-42</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_trg_descr">
		<text>A firearm designed for serious long-range competitions, able to be equipped with a vast array of accessories to meet the most demanding requirements. Its consistent accuracy and reliability have made it popular both in long-range competitions and military sniper operations.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Finland\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Sako\n
		%c[d_orange] • Increased penetration: +5\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_sig550_sniper">
		<text>SIG SG 550-1 Sniper</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig550_sniper_descr">
		<text>A marksman variant of the popular SG 550 rifle, the 550-1 constitutes a perfect middle ground between a sniper and an assault rifle while retaining the strong points of both types of weaponry. Though it is somewhat lacking in stopping power and accuracy when compared to a dedicated sniper rifle, it retains the reliability and build quality of the SG 550.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Switzerland\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Swiss Arms AG\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_sks">
		<text>SKS</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sks_modern">
		<text>SKS</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sks_descr">
		<text>A semi-automatic, gas-operated, self-loading carbine used primarily during the Cold War, the SKS still sees service today with second-line and reserve army units. As it lacked a fire select and was limited to 10 rounds, it was made obsolete by the AK-47.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Swiss Arms AG\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_sks_b">
		<text>SKS</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sks_b_descr">
		<text>A semi-automatic, gas-operated, self-loading carbine used primarily during the Cold War, the SKS still sees service today with second-line and reserve army units. As it lacked a fire select and was limited to 10 rounds, it was made obsolete by the AK-47.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Swiss Arms AG\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_sv98">
		<text>SV98</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sv98_custom">
		<text>SV98</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sv98_descr">
		<text>A highly ergonomic, highly accurate Russian bolt action sniper rifle, the Snaiperskaya Vintovka Model 1998 was designed as a precision weapon for the Russian military and law enforcement snipers to effectively engage enemy personnel at ranges up to 1,000 meters.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Izhmash, Kalashnikov Concern\n
		%c[d_orange] • Increased penetration: +5\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_svd">
		<text>SVD</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_svd_custom">
		<text>SVD</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_svd_descr">
		<text>One of the most iconic sniper rifles despite not technically being a sniper rifle, the SVD was intended to provide precise, suppressive fire on enemy positions as well as pick off high value targets. However, this squad-level DMR was eventually pressed into service as a sniper by those with access to nothing else. Relatively light, precise and well-balanced, it unfortunately loses out to dedicated sniper rifles in performance.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Kalashnikov Concern\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_svd_nimble">
		<text>SVD "Lynx"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_svd_nimble_descr">
		<text>One of the most iconic sniper rifles despite not technically being a sniper rifle, the SVD was intended to provide precise, suppressive fire on enemy positions as well as pick off high value targets. However, this squad-level DMR was eventually pressed into service as a sniper by those with access to nothing else. Relatively light, precise and well-balanced, it unfortunately loses out to dedicated sniper rifles in performance. Fit with a 1P59 "Hyperon" scope, the "Lynx" is a custom-built masterpiece befit for a marksman of equal prestige.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Kalashnikov Concern\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_svt40">
		<text>SVT-40</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_svt40_modern">
		<text>SVT-40</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_svt40_descr">
		<text>A semi-automatic rifle that saw widespread service during and after World War II. Originally intended to be the Soviet Army's new service rifle, its production was disrupted by the German invasion in 1941, resulting in a change back to the Mosin–Nagant for the duration of World War II. After the war, the Soviet Union adopted new rifles, such as the SKS and AK-47.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Fedor Vasilievich Tokarev\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_desert_eagle">
		<text>Desert Eagle</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_desert_eagle_descr">
		<text>The IMI Desert Eagle is a semi-automatic handgun notable for chambering the largest centrefire cartridge of any magazine fed, self-loading pistol and also being the heaviest and blockiest gun of its type. You can use it to bludgeon your enemies to death because of its blockiness and weight. Rumour is that there's a stalker with a crowbar wandering around the Zone with a rechambered version of this gun.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_desert_eagle_nimble">
		<text>Desert Eagle "Steppe Eagle"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_desert_eagle_nimble_descr">
		<text>This weapon was brought to the Zone by a stalker named Logan Williams. Disguised as a TIME photographer he managed to single-handedly enter the centre of Pripyat. His current whereabouts are unknown, but he is rumoured to work as an information broker specializing in all matters related to the Zone.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	

	<string id="st_wpn_vssk">
		<text>VSSK Vykhlop</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vssk_descr">
		<text>A integrally suppressed Russian bullpup, straight-pull bolt-action sniper rifle chambered for subsonic rounds. Intended for special stealth operations, typical targets for the VKS are combatants in heavy body armor or located behind cover.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]CKIB SOO\n
		%c[d_orange] • Increased penetration: +5\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_wa2000">
		<text>Walther WA 2000</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_wa2000_descr">
		<text>The Walther WA 2000 is a semi-automatic bullpup sniper rifle produced by the Carl Walther GmbH Sportwaffen company from 1982 until 1988. It was produced in three different calibers. Production of the rifle was limited and was shortly stopped because it was too expensive to achieve widespread sales and not robust enough for military use as a sniper rifle. Only 176 were built, making it one of the rarest and most sought out production firearms ever made.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]West Germany\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Walther GmbH\n
		%c[d_orange] • Increased penetration: +5\n
		</text>
	</string>

<!--
	EXPLOSIVES
-->
	<string id="st_grenade_launcher">
		<text>GP-25 Grenade Launcher</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_grenade_launcher_descr">
		<text>A single shot, front loaded, rifled under-barrel grenade launcher for assault rifles made in Warsaw Pact countries. Designed to greatly expand fire-power of a basic infantry squad. The firing mechanism is self-cocking, with a manual safety catch and automatic shot prevention if incorrectly installed onto a rifle.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Kalashnikov Concern\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_m79">
		<text>M79</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m79_descr">
		<text>A shoulder-fired, break-action, single shot grenade launcher first appearing during the Vietnam War. Recoil is kept low by means of a 'High-Low Propulsion System' where propellant is stored in a high-pressure chamber, allowing much larger projectiles to be launched without the heavy equipment usually needed. When the propellant is ignited, the gases are bled out through vents at reduced pressure to a much larger, low-pressure chamber to push the projectile forward. The high-low system allows the weight of the weapon and its ammunition to be reduced significantly.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Springfield Armory\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_grenade_launcher_m203">
		<text>M203 Grenade Launcher</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_grenade_launcher_m203_descr">
		<text>A modified, shorter M203 that can be attached by means of a Picatinny rail. Although modern, it has similar properties as its Soviet counterpart, the GP-25.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Colt Defense\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_rg6">
		<text>RG-6 Grenade Launcher</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_rg6_descr">
		<text>The stand-alone, rapid-firing multi-shot RG-6 grenade launcher was designed to increase infantry firepower during urban combat due to recent small scale conflicts, such as the Chechen Wars. The RG-6 entered limited production by the mid-1990s and is now in use by various elements of the Russian Army and special forces.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]TsKIB SOO\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_rpg7">
		<text>RPG-7</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_rpg7_descr">
		<text>Considered as one of the most successful anti-tank grenade launchers ever made, the RPG-7 is a shoulder fired, single shot, smoothbore launcher. Grenades are loaded from the front with the rear of the barrel using a venturi nozzle to make the weapon nearly recoilless.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Degtyaryov Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_grenade_f1">
		<text>F1 Grenade</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_grenade_f1_descr">
		<text>A Soviet anti-personnel fragmentation grenade based on the French F1 grenade with a kill zone of around 4 meters. Contains a 60-gram charge of TNT with a notched, steel exterior to promote fragmentation that is capable of piercing medium level body armor.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] explosive\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_grenade_rgd5">
		<text>RGD-5 Grenade</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_grenade_rgd5_descr">
		<text>A post-World War II Soviet anti-personnel fragmentation grenade with a small kill zone of around 3 meters. Contains a 110-gram charge of TNT with an internal fragmentation liner that produces fragments capable of piercing medium level body armor.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] explosive\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_grenade_smoke">
		<text>Smoke Grenade</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_grenade_smoke_descr">
		<text>A grenade used as a signaling or screening device for unit movement.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_grenade_thermite">
		<text>Thermite Grenade</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_grenade_thermite_descr">
		<text>A grenade filled with 600 to 800 grams of thermite that produces intense heat by means of chemical reaction in which powdered aluminum and iron oxide react to produce a stream of molten iron and aluminum oxide.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] explosive\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_grenade_light">
		<text>M68 Grenade</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_grenade_light_descr">
		<text>An anti-personnel fragmentation grenade with a small kill zone of around 5 meters. Contains a 180-gram charge of TNT which produces fragments capable of piercing medium level body armor The M68 is a variant of the M67 grenade fitted with an impact fuze.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		</text>
	</string>

<!--
	MELEE
-->
	<string id="st_knife_6x4">
		<text>6h4 Bayonet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_knife_6x4_descr">
		<text>First adopted in 1972 for use with AK rifles. Although highly durable, it is much better at thrusting than it is at chopping or slashing.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Russia, Poland\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] melee weapon\n
		%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] cuts thick skin?: %c[ui_red]NO\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_knife_hunting">
		<text>Hunting Knife</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_knife_hunting_descr">
		<text>A modern, highly durable hunting knife with a large stainless steel blade. As it wasn't intended for use in battle, it struggles against combat armors but is ideal for field dressing.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] melee weapon\n
		%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] cuts thick skin?: %c[ui_green]YES\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_knife_combat">
		<text>M9 Bayonet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_knife_combat_descr">
		<text>A large, multi-purpose knife with a rugged rubber handle and 7 inch blade, officially adopted in 1986. Commonly used by US soldiers as a bayonet.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] melee weapon\n
		%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] cuts thick skin?: %c[ui_green]YES\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_knife_m">
		<text>Military Knife</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_knife_m_descr">
		<text>Standard issue military knife.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] melee weapon\n
		%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] cuts thick skin?: %c[ui_green]YES\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_knife_needle">
		<text>NR-40 Scout Knife</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_knife_needle_descr">
		<text>Designed officially for utility purposes, the NR-40 lacks in significant cutting power. Unique to the blade is the inverted S-shaped guard made for holding the knife edge-up where it makes up for its shortcomings with considerable piercing ability.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] melee weapon\n
		%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] cuts thick skin?: %c[ui_red]NO\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_knife_nr40">
		<text>NR-40 Scout Knife</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_knife_nr40_descr">
		<text>Designed officially for utility purposes, the NR-40 lacks in significant cutting power. Unique to the blade is the inverted S-shaped guard made for holding the knife edge-up where it makes up for its shortcomings with considerable piercing ability.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] melee weapon\n
		%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] cuts thick skin?: %c[ui_red]NO\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_knife_swat">
		<text>Spetsnaz Switchblade</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_knife_swat_descr">
		<text>A blade ideal for special forces operators. It is good at piercing armors and dealing massive tissue damage and is often considered the ultimate combat cutlery.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] melee weapon\n
		%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] cuts thick skin?: %c[ui_green]YES\n
		</text>
	</string>	

<!--USES 'st_axe' for name and 'st_axe2_descr' for description-->
	<string id="st_axe">
		<text>Hunting Axe</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_axe2_descr">
		<text>An implement used for a millennia to shape, split and cut wood, to harvest timber, as a weapon and as a ceremonial or heraldic symbol. The axe has many forms, is versatile and dangerous when used offensively.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Various\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] melee weapon\n
		%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] greater reach compared to knives\n
		</text>
	</string>

<!--
	OTHER
-->
	<string id="st_wpn_flamewerfer">
		<text>Flamethrower</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_flamewerfer_descr">
		<text>UNUSED.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_dynamo_hand_name">
		<text>Portable Dynamo</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_dynamo_hand_name_descr">
		<text>A home-made portable electricity generator with a manual drive based on a single-phase asynchronous motor from an old electrical appliance. Due to its design, it is heavy but still very much appreciated in the Zone. Some craftsmen can refine this device.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] portable power generator\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] 40W rated motor\n
		</text>
	</string>

</string_table>