<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<!--
	Advanced Weapon Repair Mod 0.3 by Faustle (2017)
-->

<string_table>
	<!--
		Interface
	-->
	<string id="st_current_condition">
		<text>Current condition: </text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_detail_success">
		<text>+++ Part [%s] has successfully been installed</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_detail_fail">
		<text>--- Part [%s] has been damaged during replacement</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_quality_worn">
		<text>++++ One or more parts have been replaced with worn ones. Weapon quality has been changed to worn.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_quality_good">
		<text>++++ All parts have been replaced with serviceable ones. Weapon is now in fresh condition.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_quality_wgood">
		<text>++++ All parts have been replaced. Weapon quality has not changed.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_already_repair">
		<text>--- Part replacement procedure has been completed. To increase the quality of the weapon, the condition must be at 100%</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_no_barrel">
		<text>--- It is not possible to replace any parts before replacing the barrel</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bar_no_need_new">
		<text>--- The barrel of this weapon does not require any replacement</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_part_no_need_new">
		<text>--- The weapon parts do not require any replacement</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bar_no_need_old">
		<text>--- The barrel of this weapon does not require any replacement. To increase the quality of the weapon, the condition must be at 100%</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_part_no_need_old">
		<text>--- The weapon parts do not require any replacement. To increase the quality of the weapon, the condition must be at 100%</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_no_barrel_to_kit">
		<text>--- There are no compatible barrels of [%s] calibre</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_no_details">
		<text>--- There are no available parts for [%s]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_selected_worn">
		<text>--- Selected%s: [%s] Chance of successful repair: %i%% To repair, restore part</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_selected_good">
		<text>--- Selected%s: [%s] Chance of successful repair: %i%%</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_selected_r_kit">
		<text>--- Selected: [%s]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sel_detail">
		<text>--- Click on the image of the corresponding part to commence a replacement</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_cond_grow">
		<text>Condition: %i%%</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_awr_back">
		<text>Back</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_awr_exit">
		<text>Exit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_awr_ctrl">
		<text>%sTo prevent unintentional disassembly of items,\nthe procedure can be carried out only when the ALT key is held down%s</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_unload">
		<text>Weapon needs to be unloaded and free of any attachments before maintenance</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_no_weap">
		<text>A weapon must be pulled out to use the vice</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_handsfree">
		<text>Your hands are full</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_stolen_1">
		<text>The trigger mechanism has been stolen from your weapon during your absence. Condition has been worsened</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_stolen_2">
		<text>The breech head has been stolen from your weapon during your absence. Condition has been worsened</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_stolen_3">
		<text>The breech block has been stolen from your weapon during your absence. Condition has been worsened</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_not_in_list">
		<text>You do not possess the knowledge to repair this weapon</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_awr_timer_msg_on">
		<text>%sYou have five minutes%s</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_awr_timer_msg_off">
		<text>%sTime is up%s</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_awr_dead_mechanic">
		<text>%sThe technician %s has been killed by %s.%s \nYou no longer need permission to use his vice.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_by_unknown">
		<text>unknown</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mech_tiski">
		<text>technician's vice\n</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mech_tiski_w">
		<text>Technician's vice with %s</text>
	</string>
	<!-- ListBox status texts -->
	<string id="st_ending_1">
		<text>?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ending_2">
		<text>?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ending_3">
		<text>?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_text_status">
		<text>[CONDITION]:%s%s%%</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_text_wpn">
		<text>[WEAPON]:%s%s</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_text_mode">
		<text>[MODE]:%s%s</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_text_mode_1">
		<text>RESTORATION</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_text_mode_2">
		<text>REPAIR WITH POSSIBILITY OF RESTORATION</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_text_mode_3">
		<text>NOT AVAILABLE</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_text_warning_mode_1_4">
		<text>%sAfter upgrading, the state of the weapon will be %s%%, and quality - new</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_text_warning_mode_1_3">
		<text>%sWhen upgrading, it is possible to use only serviceable parts</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_text_warning_mode_1_1">
		<text>[Attention]: In this mode, it is only possible to upgrade rusty and worn-out weapons</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_text_warning_mode_2_5">
		<text>%sAfter finishing the repair with upgrading: %i%% for worn out and %i%% for a new</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_text_warning_mode_2_4">
		<text>%sAfter the repair is completed without upgrading, the condition of the weapon will be equal to %i%%</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_text_warning_mode_2_3">
		<text>%sThe quality of the weapon, at the same time, will correspond to the replaced part of the lowest quality</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_text_warning_mode_2_1">
		<text>[Attention]: In this mode it is possible to repair and upgrade weapons</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_text_warning_mode_3_3">
		<text>%sUpgrade is not possible until the state is raised to 100%%</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_text_warning_mode_3_2">
		<text>[WARNING]: Repair of this weapon is not possible, as the condition for the quality of the weapon is at maximum.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_text_warning_mode_3_1">
		<text>[WARNING]: The quality of the weapon is already at maximum. Further restoration is not possible.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_text_warning_mode_help">
		<text>For help, press F1</text>
	</string>
	<!-- Disassembly -->
	<string id="st_dis_news">
		<text>[AWR]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_dis_count">
		<text>??.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_dis_text_1">
		<text>%s%s %s%s has been disassembled</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_dis_text_2">
		<text>%sYou attempted to disassemble %s %s, but no parts have been obtained.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_dis_text_3">
		<text>%sRequired tools missing%s:%s %s</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_dis_text_4">
		<text>\nThe cartridges were removed: %iPC type %s\nItems Received: </text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_dis_text_5">
		<text>%sYou managed to restore the part %s\n%s</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_dis_text_6">
		<text>%sYou were unable to restore the part %s</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_dis_text_7">
		<text>%s%s %s %s%s</text> <!--text>%s %s %s %s has been disassembled</text-->
	</string>
	<string id="st_dis_text_8">
		<text>%s%s %s %s%s has been cut</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_dis_text_9">
		<text>\nObtained parts: </text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_dis_text_10">
		<text>%sYou disassembled the %s%s, but no parts were obtained.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_dis_text_11">
		<text>%s%s %s %s%s</text>
	</string>
	<!-- Dialogues -->
	<string id="st_awr_dialog_1">
		<text>Can I use your vice? I need to fix something up.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_awr_dialog_2">
		<text>Alright... It's yours for a thousand roubles.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_awr_dialog_3">
		<text>Here.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_awr_dialog_4">
		<text>Great. I will have a rest for the moment. In the meantime, be quick. I've got more work to finish today.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_awr_dialog_5">
		<text>I haven't got that much.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_awr_dialog_6">
		<text>Got it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_awr_dialog_7">
		<text>After all you have done to help me? Of course! Still, try to be quick. I've got more work to finish today.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- Sell dialog -->
	<string id="st_awr_sell_dialog_1">
		<text>I have spare parts. Do you know who would buy them?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_awr_sell_dialog_2">
		<text>Technicians like me store all sorts of junk you can think of. I might buy what you've got. For the right price, of course.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_awr_sell_dialog_3">
		<text>And what can you offer?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_awr_sell_dialog_4">
		<text>Well, for functional parts I can give you 300 RU per new part. The worn ones for 150. About the rest of the junk, you get 250 for new parts, and 125 for worn out parts. Eh, 60 should be good for rusty parts. These are not that useful, you know.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_awr_sell_dialog_5">
		<text>Hmm... Well, your offer is so-so. But I have no actual use for these. Here, give me the money.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_awr_sell_dialog_6">
		<text>That's a bit cheap for me. Guess I'll think about it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_awr_sell_dialog_7">
		<text>Nice doing business with you. If you get more spare parts, you know where to find me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_awr_sell_dialog_8">
		<text>Uh, I'll keep that in mind. Thanks.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- Help -->
	<string id="st_awr_help_0">
		<text>Instructions</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_awr_help_1">
		<text>The repair procedure is affected by the overall quality of the weapon (new, worn, rusty) and its current condition. Moreover, the terms 0?65, 0?75 and 0?85 determine the weapon status for each of the quality types: 0?65% for rusty weapons, 0?75% for worn weapons and 0?85% for new weapons.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_awr_help_2">
		<text>Repair and upgrade procedure (weapons with condition from 0?65/0?75/0?85):</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_awr_help_3">
		<text>1. Select a repair kit to replace the weapon barrel with another barrel of the same calibre with the weapon status from 0?20/0?25/0?30 or using a weapon upgrade kit in a condition from 20?65/25?75/30?85 by double clicking on the name of the set with the list.\n2. Select a part in the list with a single mouse click. Replacing parts when repairing weapons with a low state occurs in a certain sequence:\n \nAt condition 0?20/0?25/0?30%: Replacement of barrel\nAt condition 20?35/25?45/30?55%: Replacement of trigger (shock?trigger mechanism)\nAt condition 35?45/45?60/55?70%: Replacement of breech head\nAt condition 45?55/60?70/70?80%: Replacement of gas tube\nAt condition 55?65/70?75/80?85%: Replacement of breech block\n \n3. Click on the image of the part that is being currently replaced (the part selected for the replacement that is available for replacement is indicated by a green light). Attempting to replace one part spends one charge of a belt. set\n4. In case the replacement is successful, this procedure is repeated for all parts in the specified order\n5. In case the part has been damaged, try again if there is a repair kit and any more weapon parts.\n6. All replaced parts are retained until the condition of the weapon is lowered. In this case, to improve the quality, the parts will need to be replaced anew.\n7. When all five parts have been replaced, the quality of the weapon will be changed to the corresponding one. On that note, if at least one of the replaced items has been worn out, the quality of the weapon will be changed to "worn", even if other weapon parts are replaced with new ones.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_awr_help_4">
		<text>The predetermined order of replacing weapon parts is due to the need to match the parts to the state of the weapon, since all replaced parts for each weapon that have ever been partially repaired in the vice are stored in the game memory. This allows you to continue repairs from the same location without having to re-replace parts, provided that the weapon condition has not been lowered after repair.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_awr_help_5">
		<text>Weapon upgrade procedure is only available at a condition of 95?100% for weapons of rusty or worn quality:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_awr_help_6">
		<text>1. Select a repair kit for the replacement of barrel or a weapon upgrade kit in the list by double clicking on the name of the set in the list. The replacement order is not available for upgrades.\n2. Select a part corresponding to the repair kit in the list with a single mouse click. When upgrading, only working parts can be used.\n3. Click on the image of the part that is being currently replaced\n4. In case the replacement is successful, this procedure remains the same for all other weapon parts.\n5. In case the part has been damaged, try again if there is a repair kit and any more weapon parts.\n6. All replaced parts are retained until the state of the weapon is lowered. In this case, to improve the quality, the parts will require further replacements.\n7. When all five parts have been replaced with new ones, the quality of the weapon will be changed to "new".</text>
	</string>
</string_table>
