<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<string_table>

<!--
	PISTOLS
-->
	<string id="st_wpn_aps_bas">
		<text>APS Stechkin</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aps_bas_descr">
		<text>The Stechkin APS is a Russian selective fire machine pistol, bearing the name of its designer Igor Stechkin. Originally chambered for 7.62x25mm Tokarev, the pistol was changed to use 9x18mm as it became clear that this cartridge was set to become the new service ammunition for handguns in the Soviet Army. In 1951, the Stechkin was introduced into the Soviet military arsenal, replacing the aging TT-33.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Tula Arms Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_aps_bas_apsabigo">
		<text>APS Stechkin</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aps_bas_apsabigo_descr">
		<text>The Stechkin APS is a Russian selective fire machine pistol, bearing the name of its designer Igor Stechkin. Originally chambered for 7.62x25mm Tokarev, the pistol was changed to use 9x18mm as it became clear that this cartridge was set to become the new service ammunition for handguns in the Soviet Army. In 1951, the Stechkin was introduced into the Soviet military arsenal, replacing the aging TT-33.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Tula Arms Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_n">
		<text>Colt M1911</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_colt1911_n_descr">
		<text>Designed by John Browning, the M1911 is an extremely reliable and robust pistol that remained the standard-issue side arm of the US military from 1911 to 1985. To this day, it remains very popular for military, police and civilian use around the world.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Colt Manufacturing Company\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_fn57">
		<text>FN Five-seveN</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fn57_descr">
		<text>A delayed blowback, semi-automatic pistol designed as a complimentary sidearm for the FN P90 submachine gun as they both share the same 5.7x28mm cartridge. This allows the Five-seveN to provide good penetration against targets protected by body armor while keeping the weapon's weight, dimensions and recoil reasonable.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Belgium\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]FN Herstal\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_glock17_m1">
		<text>Glock 17 "Bruder"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_glock17_m1_descr">
		<text>A classic polymer-framed, short recoil-operated pistol trusted by law enforcement officers and military personnel around the globe because of its unsurpassed reliability, optimal magazine capacity and low weight. The Glock 17 is easy to operate and maintain and is a versatile weapon that can be used for self-defense, target shooting, or combat situations. The "Bruder" has been equipped with an integrated base for sight installation, a tactical rubber grip and a threaded barrel among various intermal modifications.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Austria\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Glock Ges.m.b.H.\n
		</text>
	</string>	

	<string id="st_wpn_korth">
		<text>Korth Custom 4</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_korth_descr">
		<text>A custom pistol made by the legendary, high-end firearms manufacturer, Korth. For some gun aficionados, nothing more needs to be said. Korth weapons are perhaps best known for having price tags that most people would find easier to associate with German cars than German guns, though the entry point is far more accessible. Simply put, Korth guns are legendary.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Germany\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Korth Waffen\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_korth_custom">
		<text>Korth Custom 6</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_korth_custom_descr">
		<text>A custom pistol made by the legendary, high-end firearms manufacturer, Korth. For some gun aficionados, nothing more needs to be said. Korth weapons are perhaps best known for having price tags that most people would find easier to associate with German cars than German guns, though the entry point is far more accessible. Simply put, Korth guns are legendary.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Germany\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Korth Waffen\n
		</text>
	</string>

<!--Also overwrites 'pl15_tan'-->
	<string id="st_wpn_pl15">
		<text>Lebedev PL-15</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pl15_descr">
		<text>A Russian recoil-operated, locked-breech, semi-automatic pistol, using a modified Browning cam-lock system adapted from the Browning Hi-Power pistol. Built for police and military use, the PL-15's key focus was on ergonomics and safety.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Kalashnikov Concern\n
		</text>
	</string>

<!--Also overwrites 'pl15_tan_pl15_scolaz'-->
	<string id="st_wpn_pl15_pl15_scolaz">
		<text>Lebedev PL-15 "Bearcat"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pl15_pl15_scolaz_descr">
		<text>A Russian recoil-operated, locked-breech, semi-automatic pistol, using a modified Browning cam-lock system adapted from the Browning Hi-Power pistol. Built for police and military use, the PL-15's key focus was on ergonomics and safety. The "Bearcat" featuring an Aimpoint T1 scope and laser designator, among numerous other internal modifications. This is more than just a sidearm.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Kalashnikov Concern\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[0,255,255,255] tactical kit upgrade\n
		</text>
	</string>
		
	<string id="st_wpn_pm_bas">
	      <text>Makarov PM</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pm_bas_descr">
		<text>This Soviet legacy is one of the best compact self-defence handguns available. Small, highly reliable, easy to use and easy to maintain, the Pistol Makarova was selected because of its simplicity, easy manufacturing, accuracy and reasonable stopping power. Unfortunately though, it loses out to modern pistols in its class in terms of weight, magazine size and general performance.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Izhevsk Mechanical Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_pm_bas_custom">
		<text>Makarov PM Custom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pm_bas_custom_descr">
		<text>This Soviet legacy is one of the best compact self-defence handguns available. Small, highly reliable, easy to use and easy to maintain, the Pistol Makarova was selected because of its simplicity, easy manufacturing, accuracy and reasonable stopping power. Unfortunately though, it loses out to modern pistols in its class in terms of weight, magazine size and general performance. The Custom includes a threaded barrel and tritium iron sights.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Izhevsk Mechanical Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_pm_bas_actor">
		<text>Makarov PM "Mythic"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pm_bas_actor_descr">
		<text>This Soviet legacy is one of the best compact self-defence handguns available. Small, highly reliable, easy to use and easy to maintain, the Pistol Makarova was selected because of its simplicity, easy manufacturing, accuracy and reasonable stopping power. Unfortunately though, it loses out to modern pistols in its class in terms of weight, magazine size and general performance. Some say this pistol was manufactured as a limited run of PMs. Others say its a handcrafted upgrade. Regardless of the truth, it is a fine weapon and comes with a pre-threaded barrel for easy suppressor installation.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Izhevsk Mechanical Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_pmm_bas">
		<text>Makarov PMM</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pmm_bas_descr">
		<text>A redesign of the legendary Makarov, the PMM uses a 25% increase in gas pressure to significantly increase muzzle velocity and features a larger 12-round magazine while keeping the same simplicity, ease of manufacturing and accuracy of the PM. Though, even with these changes slightly bridging the gap between itself and modern pistols, it still loses out in terms of weight and general performance. This model features a threaded barrel.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Izhevsk Mechanical Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_pb_bas">
		<text>PB</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pb_bas_custom">
		<text>PB</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pb_bas_descr">
		<text>The PB (Pistolet Besshumnyj or Silent Pistol) was developed in 1967 for Spetsnaz units of the Soviet Army and KGB operatives. The pistol is based on a modified Makarov PM and features a unique integrated two-part suppressor that reduces bullet velocity to below subsonic levels.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Belgium\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]FN Herstal\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_sr1m">
		<text>Serdyukov SR1M Gyurza</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sr1m_descr">
		<text>A semi-automatic pistol designed as an analogue of the famous Italian Beretta for the Russian military. However, the constructors decided to make their upcoming creation more powerful and effective in close combat. The result surpassed their greatest expectations, as the newly arrived SR-1 Gyurza was immediately adopted by the Federal Protective Services.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]TsNIITochMash Institute\n
		</text>
	</string>

<!--Also overwrites 'sr1m_gurza_up'-->	
		<string id="st_wpn_sr1m_sr1upgr1">
		<text>Serdyukov SR1M Gyurza Custom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sr1m_sr1upgr1_descr">
		<text>A semi-automatic pistol designed as an analogue of the famous Italian Beretta for the Russian military. However, the constructors decided to make their upcoming creation more powerful and effective in close combat. The result surpassed their greatest expectations, as the newly arrived SR-1 Gyurza was immediately adopted by Federal Protective Services. Includes a threaded barrel and laser designator.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]TsNIITochMash Institute\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[0,255,255,255] tactical kit upgrade\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_sig220_n">
		<text>SIG P220</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig220_n_descr">
		<text>Often considered the best out-of-the-box .45 caliber double-action pistol available, the P220 is known for accuracy that parallels that of competition handguns. An instant success, it has been adopted by the Swiss and Japanese SDF and many European police organizations.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]West Germany, Switzerland\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]SIG Sauer\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_sig220_n_u2p2g0r">
		<text>SIG P220 "Stalker"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig220_n_u2p2g0r_descr">
		<text>Often considered the best out-of-the-box .45 caliber double-action pistol available, the P220 is known for accuracy that parallels that of competition handguns. An instant success, it has been adopted by the Swiss and Japanese SDF and many European police organizations. The "Custom Nine" has been fitted with a threaded barrel, tritium sights, laser designator and 19-round magazine, among other various internal modifications.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]West Germany, Switzerland\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]SIG Sauer\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[0,255,255,255] tactical kit upgrade\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_sig220_n_upg220">
		<text>SIG P220 "XXX"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig220_n_upg220_descr">
		<text>Often considered the best out-of-the-box .45 caliber double-action pistol available, the P220 is known for accuracy that parallels that of competition handguns. An instant success, it has been adopted by the Swiss and Japanese SDF and many European police organizations. The "XXX" includes a threaded barrel, tritium iron sights, laser designator and 12-round magazine, among other various internal modifications.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]West Germany, Switzerland\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]SIG Sauer\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[0,255,255,255] tactical kit upgrade\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_sig226">
		<text>SIG P226R</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig226_descr">
		<text>The P226 set the standard by which all other combat handguns are measured. Serving alongside the U.S. Navy SEALs for decades and seeing action around the globe, its accuracy and reliability have earned its reputation as the premiere combat pistol.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Germany, Switzerland\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]SIG Sauer\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_sig226_226sig_kit">
		<text>SIG P226R Custom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sig226_226sig_kit_descr">
		<text>The P226 set the standard by which all other combat handguns are measured. Serving alongside the U.S. Navy SEALs for decades and seeing action around the globe, its accuracy and reliability have earned its reputation as the premiere combat pistol. The custom features a threaded barrel, ergonomic grip plates and optical sight with mounting plate.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Germany, Switzerland\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]SIG Sauer\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[0,255,255,255] tactical kit upgrade\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_usp_tac">
        <text>USP Match "Overwatch"</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_usp_tac_descr">
		<text>A semi-automatic pistol designed as an improvement of the USP featuring a weighted barrel extension, polygonal rifling and an adjustable trigger that improves weapon accuracy and performance. Used by special forces and competitive shooters worldwide, the USP Match considered a top-of-the-line weapon able to compete with the elite. The custom features a threaded barrel and extended 22-round magazine.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Germany\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Heckler &amp; Koch\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[0,255,255,255] tactical kit upgrade\n
		</text>
    </string>

	<string id="st_wpn_walther_p99">
		<text>Walther P99</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_walther_p99_descr">
		<text>Legacy and innovation collide to create one of the most iconic and influential pistols in Walther’s history.  High-performance and feature-rich, the P99 quickly became one of the most trusted pistols of Law Enforcement officers around the world.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Germany\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Carl Walther GmbH Sportwaffen\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_walther_p99_mod9">
		<text>Walther P99 Custom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_walther_p99_mod9_descr">
		<text>Legacy and innovation collide to create one of the most iconic and influential pistols in Walther’s history.  High-performance and feature-rich, the P99 quickly became one of the most trusted pistols of Law Enforcement officers around the world. Includes a threaded barrel, tritium sights and laser designator.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Germany\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Carl Walther GmbH Sportwaffen\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[0,255,255,255] tactical kit upgrade\n
		</text>
	</string>

<!--
	SHOTGUNS
-->

	<string id="st_wpn_saiga12s_isg">
		<text>KS-12</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_saiga12s_isg_descr">
		<text>A semi-automatic shotgun made in the U.S.A. but based on Russia’s popular line of Saiga hunting shotguns. The long stroke gas system of the legendary AK-47 is carried over to the KS-12 and provides reliable operation under extreme environmental conditions. This model includes a trigger mechanism which allows for two-round bursts.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States, Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Kalashnikov USA\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ks23">
		<text>KS-23</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ks23_descr">
		<text>At its core, the KS-23 is a manually-actuated, pump-action "shotgun" that fires unique 23mm shells. Though, while displaying an appearance more akin to a shotgun, the Russians designated the KS-23 as a "Special Carbine" due to its large-caliber rifled 700mm barrel when compared to the standard smoothbore barrels of conventional shotguns.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Tula Arms Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ks23_23_up">
		<text>KS-23 Shortie</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ks23_23_up_descr">
		<text>At its core, the KS-23 is a manually-actuated, pump-action "shotgun" that fires unique 23mm shells. Though, while displaying an appearance more akin to a shotgun, the Russians designated the KS-23 as a "Special Carbine" due to its large-caliber rifled 700mm barrel when compared to the standard smoothbore barrels of conventional shotguns. The Shortie features a slimmed down 510mm barrel.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Tula Arms Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ks23_kaban">
		<text>KS-23M Drozd</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ks23_kaban_descr">
		<text>At its core, the KS-23 is a manually-actuated, pump-action "shotgun" that fires unique 23mm shells. Though, while displaying an appearance more akin to a shotgun, the Russians designated the KS-23 as a "Special Carbine" due to its large-caliber rifled 700mm barrel when compared to the standard smoothbore barrels of conventional shotguns. The Drozd is a more compact version of the KS-23, featuring both a slimmed down 510mm barrel and pistol grip in pleace of the stand buttstock.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Tula Arms Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ks23_kaban_kab_up">
		<text>KS-23M Drozd "Boar"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ks23_kaban_kab_up_descr">
		<text>At its core, the KS-23 is a manually-actuated, pump-action "shotgun" that fires unique 23mm shells. Though, while displaying an appearance more akin to a shotgun, the Russians designated the KS-23 as a "Special Carbine" due to its large-caliber rifled barrel when compared to the standard smoothbore barrels of conventional shotguns. The Drozd is a more compact version of the KS-23, featuring both a slimmed down 510mm barrel and pistol grip in pleace of the stand buttstock. The "Boar" features a threaded barrel for introduction of a suppressor and reflex sight for better target acquisition.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Tula Arms Plant\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[0,255,255,255] tactical kit upgrade\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ks23_ecolog">
		<text>KS-23 Eco</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ks23_ecolog_descr">
		<text>At its core, the KS-23 is a manually-actuated, pump-action "shotgun" that fires unique 23mm shells. Though, while displaying an appearance more akin to a shotgun, the Russians designated the KS-23 as a "Special Carbine" due to its large-caliber rifled barrel when compared to the standard smoothbore barrels of conventional shotguns. The "Eco" was specifically modified for the needs of the scientific staff located within the Zone.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Tula Arms Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_mp133_bas">
		<text>MP-133</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp133_bas_descr">
		<text>An evolution of the earlier IZh-81 pump action shotgun, the MP-133 was intended for civilian and security markets as a reliable and practical hunting and self-defence weapon.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Izhmekh Mechanical Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_mp153_bas">
		<text>MP-153</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp153_bas_descr">
		<text>The first semi-automatic shotgun designed and manufactured by the Izhevsk Mechanical Plant, the MP-153 is one of the most popular semi-automatic shotguns of Russian origin and is widely used for various game hunting. Developed alongside the pump action MP-133 shotgun, it shares many of its parts and is known for its reliability and solid, heavy construction.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Izhmekh Mechanical Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

    <string id="st_wpn_mp153_m1">
        <text>MP-153 "Carabineer"</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_mp153_m1_descr">
		<text>The first semi-automatic shotgun designed and manufactured by the Izhevsk Mechanical Plant, the MP-153 is one of the most popular semi-automatic shotguns of Russian origin and is widely used for various game hunting. Developed alongside the pump action MP-133 shotgun, it shares many of its parts and is known for its reliability and solid, heavy construction. The "Carabineer" includes a muzzle break and Picatinny rail.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Izhmekh Mechanical Plant\n
		</text>
    </string>

	<string id="st_wpn_saiga12s">
		<text>Saiga-12</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_saiga12s_descr">
		<text>A 12-gauge combat shotgun recognizable by its Kalashnikov design, intended for engaging targets at short range or in confined spaces. Known for its effectiveness and lethality, it has replaced the Armsel Protecta for Russian riot control and infantry combat.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Izhmash\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_saiga12s_m2">
		<text>Saiga-12 "Merc"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_saiga12s_m2_descr">
		<text>A 12-gauge combat shotgun recognizable by its Kalashnikov design, intended for engaging targets at short range or in confined spaces. Known for its effectiveness and lethality, it has replaced the Armsel Protecta for Russian riot control and infantry combat. This model includes a compensator and was made and extensively modified on request for an unknown member of the mercenaries. The workmanship is absolutely exceptional.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Izhmash\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_saiga12s_m1">
		<text>Saiga-12 "Nerd"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_saiga12s_m1_descr">
		<text>A 12-gauge combat shotgun recognizable by its Kalashnikov design, intended for engaging targets at short range or in confined spaces. Known for its effectiveness and lethality, it has replaced the Armsel Protecta for Russian riot control and infantry combat. The "Nerd" was modified specifically for scientific personnel within the Zone and is often the envy of experienced Stalkers.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Izhmash\n
		</text>
	</string>

    <string id="st_wpn_toz106">
        <text>TOZ-106</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_toz106_descr">
		<text>Widely known by its vernacular name, the Death of the Chairman for its compact size, the TOZ-106 is a bolt-action, single-barreled 20 gauge shotgun with a sliding breech bolt.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Tulsky Oruzheiny Zavod\n
		</text>
    </string>

    <string id="st_wpn_toz106_m1">
        <text>TOZ-106</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_toz106_m1_descr">
		<text>Widely known by its vernacular name, the Death of the Chairman for its compact size, the TOZ-106 is a bolt-action, single-barreled 20 gauge shotgun with a sliding breech bolt. Features an extended 4-round mag.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Tulsky Oruzheiny Zavod\n
		</text>
    </string>

<!--
	SMGS
-->

<!--
	RIFLES
-->
	<string id="st_wpn_adar2_15">
		<text>ADAR 2-15</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_adar2_15_descr">
		<text>A Russian civilian carbine produced in St. Petersburg and based on the design of the AR-15. As in the case of many other companies that make AR-15s, ADAR doesn’t actually manufacture these rifles but rather assembles them from parts sourced from a variety of manufacturers. \n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Molot Oruzhie\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak5c_bas">
		<text>AK 5C</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak5c_bas_descr">
		<text>A version of the FN FNC assault rifle made for the Swedish Armed Forces and modified to adapt to the partially subarctic Swedish climate. The AK 5C is the modernized version of the original AK 5 with improvements including a new rail system, iron sights and bolt catch.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Sweden\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Carl Gustafs Stads Gevarsfaktori\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak5c_isg">
		<text>AK 5C "ISG"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak5c_isg_descr">
		<text>A version of the FN FNC assault rifle made for the Swedish Armed Forces and modified to adapt to the partially subarctic Swedish climate. The AK 5C is the modernized version of the original AK 5 with improvements including a new rail system, iron sights and bolt catch. This model has been modified.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Sweden\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Carl Gustafs Stads Gevarsfaktori\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_ak5c_bas_5c_tik">
		<text>AK 5C "ISG Special"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak5c_bas_5c_tik_descr">
		<text>A version of the FN FNC assault rifle made for the Swedish Armed Forces and modified to adapt to the partially subarctic Swedish climate. The AK 5C is the modernized version of the original AK 5 with improvements including a new rail system, iron sights and bolt catch. This model has been extensively modified.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Sweden\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Carl Gustafs Stads Gevarsfaktori\n
		</text>
	</string>	

	<string id="st_wpn_akm_alfa">
    	<text>AK Alfa</text>
  	</string>
  	<string id="st_wpn_akm_alfa_descr">
		<text>Developed by a team of engineers and hand-picked Israel Defense Force snipers, the AK Alfa was built on the foundation of the AK and redesigned with the sole purpose of providing outstanding performance on the battlefield in an attempt to improve the ergonomics of the AK rifle while maintaining its reliability and ease of maintenance. \n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States, Israel\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]CAA Tactical\n
		</text>
  	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak12_m1">
        <text>AK-12</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_ak12_m1_descr">
		<text>The standard service assault rifle of the Russian army, designed to replace older AK-74M and AK-100 series rifles. This model is the pinnacle of AK system development, different from the previous generations by its elaborate ergonomics, all-day usability and increased accuracy and precision. Capable of a hyperburst fire mode.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Izhmash\n
		</text>
    </string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak12">
		<text>AK-12</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak12_descr">
		<text>The standard service assault rifle of the Russian army, designed to replace older AK-74M and AK-100 series rifles. This model is the pinnacle of AK system development, different from the previous generations by its elaborate ergonomics, all-day usability and increased accuracy and precision. Capable of a hyperburst fire mode.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Izhmash\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak12_custom">
        <text>AK-12 "Monolith"</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_ak12_custom_descr">
		<text>The standard service assault rifle of the Russian army, designed to replace older AK-74M and AK-100 series rifles. This model is the pinnacle of AK system development, different from the previous generations by its elaborate ergonomics, all-day usability and increased accuracy and precision. Capable of a hyperburst fire mode. This model is rarely encountered and is often found in the hands of the Monolith. It features an extended magazine and vertical foregrip for increased stability.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Izhmash\n
		</text>
    </string>

    <string id="st_wpn_ak12_mono_kit">
		<text>AK-12 "Monolith's Light"</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_ak12_mono_kit_descr">
		<text>The standard service assault rifle of the Russian army, designed to replace older AK-74M and AK-100 series rifles. This model is the pinnacle of AK system development, different from the previous generations by its elaborate ergonomics, all-day usability and increased accuracy and precision. Capable of a hyperburst fire mode. This model is very rarely encountered and is often found in the hands of high ranking Monolith. Featuring a giant magazine, ACOG scope, laser designator and a tablet's worth of internal modifications, the "Monolith's Light" is the pinnacle of Monolithian weaponry.\n \n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Izhmash\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[0,255,255,255] tactical kit upgrade\n
		</text>
    </string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak74_n">
		<text>AK-74</text>
	</string>
    <string id="st_wpn_ak74_n_descr">
		<text>Developed in the early 1970s by Mikhail Kalashnikov to replace the AKM, the AK-74 is an adaptation of the 7.62x39mm AKM assault rifle and features several important design improvements including the use of the newer, high velocity 5.45x39mm round. Compared with the preceding AKM, it has better effective firing range, accuracy and reliability.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Izhmash\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak74_pmc">
		<text>AK-74 "PMC"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74_pmc_descr">
		<text>Developed in the early 1970s by Mikhail Kalashnikov to replace the AKM, the AK-74 is an adaptation of the 7.62x39mm AKM assault rifle and features several important design improvements including the use of the newer, high velocity 5.45x39mm round. Compared with the preceding AKM, it has a better effective firing range, accuracy and reliability. The "PMC" includes a laser designator, vertical foregrip and buzzle break in addition to an assortment of internal modifications.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Izhmash\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak74m_n">
		<text>AK-74M</text>
	</string>
    <string id="st_wpn_ak74m_n_descr">
		<text>An improved version of the AK-74 and the service rifle of the Russian Federation, designed with modern and composite materials to significantly reduce weight and improve accuracy. Each AK-74M is fitted with a side-rail bracket for mounting optics.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Kalashnikov Concern\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak74m_beard">
		<text>AK-74M "Venom"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74m_beard_descr">
		<text>An improved version of the AK-74 and the service rifle of the Russian Federation, designed with modern and composite materials to significantly reduce weight and improve accuracy. Each AK-74M is fitted with a side-rail bracket for mounting optics. The "Venom" was made at Skadovsk and Yanov Station on request by Beard for a lightweight and dependable AK74M varient. It has been equipped with a laser designator, extended magazine and tweaked for better reliability within the Zone's harsh conditions.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Kalashnikov Concern\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_n1">
		<text>AKS-74U</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_n1_descr">
		<text>The AKS-74U bridges the tactical deployment gap between a submachine gun and an assault rifle and was intended as a compact but relatively powerful automatic alternative to the AKS-74. It is significantly lighter and more maneuverable in tight quarters while still boasting the reliability of a Kalashnikov.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Kalashnikov Concern\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_tac">
		<text>AKS-74U "Tactician"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_tac_descr">
		<text>The AKS-74U bridges the tactical deployment gap between a submachine gun and an assault rifle and was intended as a compact but relatively powerful automatic alternative to the AKS-74. It is significantly lighter and more maneuverable in tight quarters while still boasting the reliability of a Kalashnikov. This model has been extensively modified, including but not limited to a vertical foregrip extended magazine and laser designator. It's performance is exceptional.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Kalashnikov Concern\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak104_alfa">
    	<text>AK-104 "Alpha"</text>
  	</string>
  	<string id="st_wpn_ak104_alfa_descr">
		<text>A compact version of the AK-103 rifle featuring a shortened barrel. The rifle is designed with modern and composite materials to significantly reduce weight and improve accuracy. The "Alpha" features a multi-point Picatinny rail and a vertical foregrip among a multitude of other internal modifications. This weapon has earned its name.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Kalashnikov Concern\n
		</text>
  	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak105">
		<text>AK-105</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak105_descr">
		<text>A carbine version of the AK-74M rifle, the AK-105, like the AK-104, features a shortened barrel and is ideal for close quarters combat. The rifle is designed with modern and composite materials to significantly reduce weight and improve accuracy.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Izhmash\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak105_shakal">
		<text>AK-105 "Shakal"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak105_shakal_descr">
		<text>A carbine version of the AK-74M rifle, the AK-105, like the AK-104, features a shortened barrel and is ideal for close quarters combat. The rifle is designed with modern and composite materials to significantly reduce weight and improve accuracy. This model has been extensively modified.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Izhmash\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak105_sp">
		<text>AK-105 "Specialist"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak105_sp_descr">
		<text>A carbine version of the AK-74M rifle, the AK-105, like the AK-104, features a shortened barrel and is ideal for close quarters combat. The rifle is designed with modern and composite materials to significantly reduce weight and improve accuracy. The "Specialist" is a tactician's dream, featuring a foldable stock, canted sight, vertical foregrip and a multitude of modified internals.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Izhmash\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak105_swamp">
		<text>AK-105 "Swamp Thing"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak105_swamp_descr">
		<text>A carbine version of the AK-74M rifle, the AK-105, like the AK-104, features a shortened barrel and is ideal for close quarters combat. The rifle is designed with modern and composite materials to significantly reduce weight and improve accuracy. A monster of a weapon, the "Swamp Thing" is fitted with an Elcan scope, side-mounted sight, laser module, extended magazine and a collection of additional alterations to make this weapon handle like a dream.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Izhmash\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[0,255,255,255] tactical kit upgrade\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_akm_bas">
		<text>AKM</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_akm_bas_descr">
		<text>An improved version of the AK-47 rifle featuring detailed improvements and enhancements that optimized the rifle for mass production. Among these changes, the AKM's weight was reduced, the accuracy during automatic fire was increased and several reliability issues were addressed.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Tula Arms Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_akms_bas">
		<text>AKMS</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_akms_bas_descr">
		<text>An improved version of the AK-47 rifle featuring detailed improvements and enhancements that optimized the rifle for mass production. Among these changes, the AKM's weight was reduced, the accuracy during automatic fire was increased and several reliability issues were addressed.  All AKMS rifles came equipped with an under-folding metal shoulder stock in place of the fixed wooden stock.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Tula Arms Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_abakan_n">
		<text>AN-94</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_abakan_n_descr">
		<text>Designed as a potential replacement to the AK-74 series of rifles, it failed to fill its intended role due to its complex design and price. Still in use as a limited special purpose weapon, the AN-94 offers a unique two-shot burst function at a stated 1800 rounds per minute with the unique feature of delaying recoil for the first two rounds. Capable of a hyperburst fire mode.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Izhmash\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ar15_freedom">
		<text>AR-15 HERA</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ar15_freedom_descr">
		<text>After most of Colt's patents for the Colt AR-15 expired in 1977, many firearm manufacturers began to produce copies of the Colt AR-15 under various names. Despite the patents expiring, Colt retained the trademark of the AR-15 and is the sole manufacturer able to label their firearms as so. The HERA is a deeply modernized variant created by Hera Arms.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Hera Arms\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_val_tac">
		<text>AS Val</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_val_tac_descr">
		<text>Engineered for Soviet special operations units, the AS Val is a gas operated, integrally suppressed weapon that was set to supersede the AK-47 and AKM rifles. It is easily disassembled and concealed, lightweight and comfortable to fire with the suppressor reducing bullet velocity to below subsonic levels. Today, the AS VAL sees widespread use among Russian special forces.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Tula Arms Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_aug_a1_custom_bas">
		<text>Steyr AUG A1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aug_a1_custom_bas_descr">
		<text>The AUG (Armee-Universal-Gewehr) is the standard small arm of many Armed Forces and Special Units all over the world since 1977. It is famous for its modular bullpup design, making it a short, well-balanced rifle with high accuracy and reliability. The A1 variant is fitted with an integrated 1.5x scope.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Austria\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Steyr Arms\n
		</text>
    </string>

	<string id="st_wpn_scar_siber">
		<text>FN SCAR-H</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_scar_siber_descr">
		<text>In early 2004, USSOCOM issued a design request for a family of assault rifles using two different calibers while keeping the parts and ergonomics nearly-identical; hence the Special Operations Forces Combat Assault Rifle "SCAR" was born into service. Firing the long-range, hard-hitting 7.62x51mm NATO cartridge, the selective-fire FN SCAR-H's innovative gas-operated, short-stroke piston system reduces fouling for greater reliability.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Belgium\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]FN Herstal, FN America\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_scar_siber_black">
		<text>FN SCAR-H "Black"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_scar_siber_black_descr">
		<text>In early 2004, USSOCOM issued a design request for a family of assault rifles using two different calibers while keeping the parts and ergonomics nearly-identical; hence the Special Operations Forces Combat Assault Rifle "SCAR" was born into service. Firing the long-range, hard-hitting 7.62x51mm NATO cartridge, the selective-fire FN SCAR-H's innovative gas-operated, short-stroke piston system reduces fouling for greater reliability.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Belgium\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]FN Herstal, FN America\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_scar_siber_m1">
		<text>FN SCAR-H "Tactical"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_scar_siber_m1_descr">
		<text>In early 2004, USSOCOM issued a design request for a family of assault rifles using two different calibers while keeping the parts and ergonomics nearly-identical; hence the Special Operations Forces Combat Assault Rifle "SCAR" was born into service. Firing the long-range, hard-hitting 7.62x51mm NATO cartridge, the selective-fire FN SCAR-H's innovative gas-operated, short-stroke piston system reduces fouling for greater reliability. This model has been modified.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Belgium\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]FN Herstal, FN America\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_scar_siber_m2">
		<text>FN SCAR-H "Expert Operator"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_scar_siber_m2_descr">
		<text>In early 2004, USSOCOM issued a design request for a family of assault rifles using two different calibers while keeping the parts and ergonomics nearly-identical; hence the Special Operations Forces Combat Assault Rifle "SCAR" was born into service. Firing the long-range, hard-hitting 7.62x51mm NATO cartridge, the selective-fire FN SCAR-H's innovative gas-operated, short-stroke piston system reduces fouling for greater reliability. This model has been modified.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Belgium\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]FN Herstal, FN America\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_scar_siber_m2_custom">
		<text>FN SCAR-H "Specialist Operator"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_scar_siber_m2_custom_descr">
		<text>In early 2004, USSOCOM issued a design request for a family of assault rifles using two different calibers while keeping the parts and ergonomics nearly-identical; hence the Special Operations Forces Combat Assault Rifle "SCAR" was born into service. Firing the long-range, hard-hitting 7.62x51mm NATO cartridge, the selective-fire FN SCAR-H's innovative gas-operated, short-stroke piston system reduces fouling for greater reliability. This model has been extensively modified.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Belgium\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]FN Herstal, FN America\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_scar_siber_m1_black">
		<text>FN SCAR-H "Tactical Black"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_scar_siber_m1_black_descr">
		<text>In early 2004, USSOCOM issued a design request for a family of assault rifles using two different calibers while keeping the parts and ergonomics nearly-identical; hence the Special Operations Forces Combat Assault Rifle "SCAR" was born into service. Firing the long-range, hard-hitting 7.62x51mm NATO cartridge, the selective-fire FN SCAR-H's innovative gas-operated, short-stroke piston system reduces fouling for greater reliability. This model has been modified.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Belgium\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]FN Herstal, FN America\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_howa20">
		<text>Howa Type 20</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_howa20_descr">
		<text>A a gas operated, select-fire assault rifle appearing to be an amalgam of many modern weapons such as the FN SCAR-16, SIG 516 and HK 416, with hardly any original features to distinguish it. However, this is not necessarily a bad thing as typical requirements for a military weapon tend to include reliability, durability, ease of maintenance and combat effectiveness; all of which the Howa Type 20 effectively check.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Japan\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Howa\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_l85_m1">
		<text>L85A2</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_l85_m1_descr">
		<text>Recognized for being extremely reliable and impressively accurate, the L85A2 is the standard weapon of the British armed forces and an improvement over the L85A1, fixing many of its design flaws. Notably, the A2 is extremely reliable over a range of climates and adverse conditions allowing it to be fielded for various operational scenarios.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United Kingdom\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Royal Ordnance, Heckler &amp; Koch\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_l85_m2">
		<text>L85A2</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_l85_m2_descr">
		<text>Recognized for being extremely reliable and impressively accurate, the L85A2 is the standard weapon of the British armed forces and an improvement over the L85A1, fixing many of its design flaws. Notably, the A2 is extremely reliable over a range of climates and adverse conditions allowing it to be fielded for various operational scenarios.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United Kingdom\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Royal Ordnance, Heckler &amp; Koch\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_l85_m3">
		<text>L85A2 "Tactical"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_l85_m3_descr">
		<text>Recognized for being extremely reliable and impressively accurate, the L85A2 is the standard weapon of the British armed forces and an improvement over the L85A1, fixing many of its design flaws. Notably, the A2 is extremely reliable over a range of climates and adverse conditions allowing it to be fielded for various operational scenarios. This model has been modified.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United Kingdom\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Royal Ordnance, Heckler &amp; Koch\n
		</text>
	</string>	

	<string id="st_wpn_m4a1_siber">
		<text>M4A1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m4a1_siber_descr">
		<text>The M4 Carbine descends from a family of firearms tracing its lineage back to the original AR-15 by ArmaLite. It is a gas operated, air cooled, selective fire rifle, sharing 80% of its parts with the M16 assault rifle, though it is notably shorter and lighter. It has been adopted by United States Special Operations Command (USSOCOM) and is the preferred weapon of the U.S. Army Special Forces and Navy SEALs. The A1 variant strengthened the barrel and replaced the burst-fire fire select with a fully automatic option.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Colt's Manufacturing Company\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_m4_butcher">
		<text>M4A1 "Butcher"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m4_butcher_descr">
		<text>The M4 Carbine descends from a family of firearms tracing its lineage back to the original AR-15 by ArmaLite. It is a gas operated, air cooled, selective fire rifle, sharing 80% of its parts with the M16 assault rifle, though it is notably shorter and lighter. It has been adopted by United States Special Operations Command (USSOCOM) and is the preferred weapon of the U.S. Army Special Forces and Navy SEALs. The A1 variant strengthened the barrel and replaced the burst-fire fire select with a fully automatic option. The "Butcher" is a monstrosity of weapons built for unrelenting sustained fire.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Colt's Manufacturing Company\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_m4_tac">
		<text>M4A1 "Protector"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m4_tac_descr">
		<text>The M4 Carbine descends from a family of firearms tracing its lineage back to the original AR-15 by ArmaLite. It is a gas operated, air cooled, selective fire rifle, sharing 80% of its parts with the M16 assault rifle, though it is notably shorter and lighter. It has been adopted by United States Special Operations Command (USSOCOM) and is the preferred weapon of the U.S. Army Special Forces and Navy SEALs. The A1 variant strengthened the barrel and replaced the burst-fire fire select with a fully automatic option. This model has been extensively modified, including but not limited to a vertical foregrip extended magazine and multi-point Picatinny rail. It's performance is exceptional.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Colt's Manufacturing Company\n
		</text>
	</string>

		<string id="st_wpn_pkm_zenit_siber">
		<text>PKM "Zenit"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pkm_zenit_siber_descr">
		<text>A modernized and improved version of the PK, the PKM's upgrades were primarily aimed at reducing weight, facilitating easier operation and simplifying production. A very reliable machine gun that remains in use as a front-line infantry and vehicle-mounted weapon with Russia's armed forces. This model has been manually altered to include an enlarged ammo box. This model has been extensively modified.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Zenit\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
		<string id="st_wpn_pkp_siber">
		<text>PKP Pecheneg</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pkp_siber_descr">
		<text>A modernized PKM machine gun chambered for the 7.62x54mm round, said to be more accurate than all its predecessors due to a heavier, non-removable forced air cooling barrel with radial cooling ribs and a unique handle which eliminates the haze effect from hot gases. Currently in use by Russian Army Spetsnaz and, though it was developed mainly for infantry use, is often fitted to light vehicles.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russian\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Mikhail Kalashnikov\n
		</text>
	</string>

		<string id="st_wpn_akm_isg">
		<text>RD-47</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_akm_isg_descr">
		<text>A custom model developed on the basis of the AKM by the Las Vegas-based Rifle Dynamics company. It is one of the most high-tech weapons in the Zone and is built with an unprecedented level of precision and care.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Rifle Dynamics\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
		<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_isg">
		<text>RD-74U</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_isg_descr">
		<text>A custom model developed on the basis of the AK-74U by the Las Vegas-based American company Rifle Dynamics. It is one of the most high-tech weapons in the Zone and is built with an unprecedented level of precision and care and is often used by ISG special units.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Rifle Dynamics\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_ak74_isg">
		<text>RD-74M</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74_isg_descr">
		<text>A custom model developed on the basis of the AK-74M by the Las Vegas-based American company Rifle Dynamics. It is one of the most high-tech weapons in the Zone and is built with an unprecedented level of precision and care and is often used by ISG special units.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Rifle Dynamics\n
		</text>
	</string>

		<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_m1_isg">
		<text>RD-74U Tactic</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_ak74u_m1_isg_descr">
		<text>A custom model developed on the basis of the AK-74U by the Las Vegas-based American company Rifle Dynamics. It is one of the most high-tech weapons in the Zone and is built with an unprecedented level of precision and care and is often used by ISG special units. It has been modified to use 5.45x39mm.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Rifle Dynamics\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_vintorez_isg">
		<text>RD-939</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vintorez_isg_descr">
		<text>A custom model developed on the basis of the VSS Vintorez by the Las Vegas-based American company Rifle Dynamics. It is one of the most high-tech weapons in the Zone and is built with an unprecedented level of precision and care and is often used by ISG special units. It has been modified to allow two-round burst fire.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Rifle Dynamics\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_rpk74_16">
		<text>RPK-16 LMG</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_rpk74_16_descr">
		<text>Designed as a private venture by Kalashnikov Concern and intended for use by the Russian Army and special forces, the RPK-16 is based on the AK-12 assault rifle and is the proposed replacement for the venerable RPK-74. Capable of a hyperburst fire mode.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Kalashnikov Concern\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_m4_ru556">
		<text>Ruger SR-556</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_m4_ru556_descr">
		<text>A semi-automatic, piston-driven, gas-operated AR-15 style rifle. Lightweight and ergonomic, Ruger wanted to minimize the sharp impulse of the piston striking the bolt carrier typically found in short-stroke ARs, and instead used a two-stage design in which the piston delivers two smaller impulses to the operating rod instead. This design choice allows the weapon to be easier to handle and more accurate during sustained fire. Capable of a hyperburst fire mode.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Sturm, Ruger &amp; Co.\n
		</text>
	</string>

   <string id="st_wpn_fal_aus">
        <text>SA-58 AUS</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_fal_aus_descr">
		<text>A assault-carbine variant of the paratrooper model FAL able to use any metric-measurement FAL magazines. Notable changes are the 21 inch barrel, Austrian foregrip and Nylon furniture. While civilians are limited to semi-automatic, military and law enforcement variants are equipped with a full-auto option.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]David Selvaggio Arms\n
		</text>
    </string>

		<string id="st_wpn_fal_aus_kit_sa5x_spec">
		<text>SA-58 AUS Defender</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fal_aus_kit_sa5x_spec_descr">
		<text>A assault-carbine variant of the paratrooper model FAL able to use any metric-measurement FAL magazines. Notable changes are the 21 inch barrel, Austrian foregrip and Nylon furniture. While civilians are limited to semi-automatic, military and law enforcement variants are equipped with a full-auto option.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]David Selvaggio Arms\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_fal_aus_kit_fal_leup">
		<text>SA-58 AUS Marauder</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fal_aus_kit_fal_leup_descr">
		<text>A assault-carbine variant of the paratrooper model FAL able to use any metric-measurement FAL magazines. Notable changes are the 21 inch barrel, Austrian foregrip and Nylon furniture. While civilians are limited to semi-automatic, military and law enforcement variants are equipped with a full-auto option.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]David Selvaggio Arms\n
		</text>
	</string>

		<string id="st_wpn_fal_aus_kit_aus_tri">
		<text>SA-58 AUS Scout</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fal_aus_kit_aus_tri_descr">
		<text>A assault-carbine variant of the paratrooper model FAL able to use any metric-measurement FAL magazines. Notable changes are the 21 inch barrel, Austrian foregrip and Nylon furniture. While civilians are limited to semi-automatic, military and law enforcement variants are equipped with a full-auto option.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]David Selvaggio Arms\n
		</text>
	</string>

    <string id="st_wpn_fal_sa58_osw">
		<text>SA-58 OSW</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_fal_sa58_osw_descr">
		<text>A assault-carbine variant of the paratrooper model FAL able to use any metric-measurement FAL magazines. Notable changes are the side-folding polymer stock and shorter barrel. While civilians are limited to semi-automatic, military and law enforcement variants are equipped with a full-auto option.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]David Selvaggio Arms\n
		</text>
    </string>

	<string id="st_wpn_sr2_veresk">
    	<text>SR-2M Veresk</text>
  	</string>
  	<string id="st_wpn_sr2_veresk_descr">
		<text>A Russian submachine gun created as a compact weapon capable of engaging enemies wearing Russian class-II body armor and soft-skinned vehicles at distances up to 200 meters. The SR-2M is a modified version with a forward pistol grip under the handguard and a fully-foldable stock.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]TsNIITochMash\n
		</text>
  	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_sr2_m1">
    	<text>SR-2M Veresk</text>
  	</string>
  	<string id="st_wpn_sr2_m1_descr">
		<text>A Russian submachine gun created as a compact weapon capable of engaging enemies wearing Russian class-II body armor and soft-skinned vehicles at distances up to 200 meters. The SR-2M is a modified version with a forward pistol grip under the handguard and a fully-foldable stock.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]TsNIITochMash\n
		</text>
  	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_sr2_veresk_sr2_upkit">
    	<text>SR-2M Veresk "Tactical"</text>
  	</string>
  	<string id="st_wpn_sr2_veresk_sr2_upkit_descr">
		<text>A Russian submachine gun created as a compact weapon capable of engaging enemies wearing Russian class-II body armor and soft-skinned vehicles at distances up to 200 meters. The SR-2M is a modified version with a forward pistol grip under the handguard and a fully-foldable stock. This model has been extensively modified.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]TsNIITochMash\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[0,255,255,255] tactical kit upgrade\n
		</text>
  	</string>	

	<string id="st_wpn_aug_a1_bas">
		<text>Steyr AUG A1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aug_a1_bas_descr">
		<text>The AUG (Armee-Universal-Gewehr) is the standard small arm of many Armed Forces and Special Units all over the world since 1977. It is famous for its modular concept “Bullpup“ design making it a short, well-balanced rifle with high accuracy and reliability. The A1 variant is fitted with an integrated 1.5x scope.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Austria\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Steyr Arms\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_aug_a3_bas">
		<text>Steyr AUG A3</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aug_a3_bas_descr">
		<text>The AUG (Armee-Universal-Gewehr) is the standard small arm of many Armed Forces and Special Units all over the world since 1977. It is famous for its modular concept “Bullpup“ design making it a short, well-balanced rifle with high accuracy and reliability. The A3 variant is fitted with four Picatinny slats.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Austria\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Steyr Arms\n
		</text>
	</string>	

	<string id="st_wpn_aug_a3_custom_bas">
		<text>Steyr AUG A3 Commando</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_aug_a3_custom_bas_descr">
		<text>The AUG (Armee-Universal-Gewehr) is the standard small arm of many Armed Forces and Special Units all over the world since 1977. It is famous for its modular concept “Bullpup“ design making it a short, well-balanced rifle with high accuracy and reliability. The A3 variant is fitted with four Picatinny slats with the Commando designation designed specially for Austria's Jagdkommando Special Forces. This model allows rails to be configured to take an array of optics, illuminators or pointers.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Austria\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Steyr Arms\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_umirotvoritel_bas">
		<text>Unidentified Weapon</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_umirotvoritel_bas_descr">
		<text>An unknown weapon. Appears faulty as squeezing the trigger does nothing. After close inspection, it does not appear to fire rounds based on ignition but instead by electro-magnetic force.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Unknown\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Unknown\n
		</text>
	</string> 

	<string id="st_wpn_vintorez_n1">
		<text>VSS Vintorez</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vintorez_n1_descr">
		<text>Intended for various Spetsnaz troops of the Soviet Army, KGB and MVD, the VSS is quite popular among its users for its stealthy capabilities, integral suppressor and the great lethality of the heavy 9x39mm round.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Tula Arms Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>	

	<string id="st_wpn_vintorez_m1">
		<text>VSS Vintorez "Savant"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vintorez_m1_descr">
		<text>Intended for various Spetsnaz troops of the Soviet Army, KGB and MVD, the VSS is quite popular among its users for its stealthy capabilities, integral suppressor and the great lethality of the heavy 9x39mm round. The "Savant" is an early prototype including a vertical foregrip, laser designator and significantly modified internals.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Tula Arms Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_vintorez_m2">
		<text>VSS Vintorez "Venal"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_vintorez_m2_descr">
		<text>Intended for various Spetsnaz troops of the Soviet Army, KGB and MVD, the VSS is quite popular among its users for its stealthy capabilities, integral suppressor and the great lethality of the heavy 9x39mm round. This model is an early prototype. This model includes a vertical foregrip and laser designator and was made and extensively modified on request for an unknown member of the mercenaries. The workmanship is absolutely exceptional.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Tula Arms Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

<!--
	SNIPERS
-->

	<string id="st_wpn_dvl10_m1">
		<text>DVL-10 M1 Saboteur</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_dvl10_m1_descr">
		<text>A modular, lightweight and compact rifle developed for special service and combat missions where exceptional accuracy and range are needed. The Urbana comes equipped with a special carbon fiber tube barrel and proprietary titanium suppressor to provide increased strength and survivability of the weapons system, as well as reduced muzzle flash and sound propagation.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Lobaev Arms\n
		%c[d_orange] • Increased penetration: +5\n
		</text>
	</string>	
	
	<string id="st_wpn_dvl10">
		<text>DVL-10 M2 Urbana</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_dvl10_descr">
		<text>A modular, multi-purpose lightweight and compact rifle developed for special service and combat missions where exceptional modularity accuracy and range are required.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Lobaev Arms\n
		%c[d_orange] • Increased penetration: +5\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_gauss_bas">
		<text>Gauss Rifle</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_gauss_bas_descr">
		<text>A highly experimental, extremely accurate, artefact-powered weapon made by an unknown party in the Zone. Instead of gunpowder, the gauss rifle utilizes electromagnetic forces to launch projectiles at incredible speeds similar to a railgun. Proportionate to its tremendous firepower, the recoil is surprisingly controllable. Among other weapons of its class, its accuracy and firepower is unmatched.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Redacted\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_k98_mod">
		<text>Mauser 98k Forester mk.1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_k98_mod_descr">
		<text>A directly-modified version of the WWII German sniper rifle Mauser Karabiner 98k. The wooden stock was replaced with a more ergonomic polymer one. The rifle is equipped with an excellent sniper scope manufactured by MARCH, Japan.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Nazi Germany\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Mauser\n
		%c[d_orange] • Increased penetration: +5\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_k98_mod_silen98">
		<text>Karabiner 98k Forester mk.2</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_k98_mod_silen98_descr">
		<text>A directly-modified version of the WWII German sniper rifle Mauser Karabiner 98k. The wooden stock was replaced with a more ergonomic polymer one. The rifle is equipped with an excellent sniper scope manufactured by MARCH, Japan.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Nazi Germany\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Mauser\n
		%c[d_orange] • Increased penetration: +5\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_remington700">
		<text>Remington 700</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_remington700_descr">
		<text>Often regarded as the number one bolt-action of all time, the Model 700 is a top choice for many military and law enforcement officers. With unequalled precision paired with unmatched build quality and reliability, it remains an industry leader to this day though its design is almost 6 decades old.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Remington Arms\n
		%c[d_orange] • Increased penetration: +5\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
		<string id="st_wpn_remington700_archangel">
		<text>Remington 700 "Archangel"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_remington700_archangel_descr">
		<text>Often regarded as the number one bolt-action of all time, the Model 700 is a top choice for many military and law enforcement officers. With unequalled precision paired with unmatched build quality and reliability, it remains an industry leader to this day though its design is almost 6 decades old. This model has been extensively modified.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Remington Arms\n
		%c[d_orange] • Increased penetration: +5\n
		</text>
	</string>

		<string id="st_wpn_remington700_lapua700">
		<text>Remington 700 "Deer Hunter"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_remington700_lapua700_descr">
		<text>Often regarded as the number one bolt-action of all time, the Model 700 is a top choice for many military and law enforcement officers. With unequalled precision paired with unmatched build quality and reliability, it remains an industry leader to this day though its design is almost 6 decades old. This model has been modified for .338 Lapua Magnum.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Remington Arms\n
		%c[d_orange] • Increased penetration: +5\n
		</text>
	</string>

		<string id="st_wpn_remington700_magpul_pro">
		<text>Remington 700 "Magpul PRO"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_remington700_magpul_pro_descr">
		<text>The Remington Model 700 is a series of bolt-action centerfire rifles manufactured by Remington Arms since 1962. It is a development of the Remington 721 and 722 series of rifles, which were introduced in 1948. This model has been extensively modified.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Remington Arms\n
		%c[d_orange] • Increased penetration: +5\n
		</text>
	</string>

		<string id="st_wpn_remington700_mod_x_gen3">
		<text>Remington 700 "MOD X Gen.3"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_remington700_mod_x_gen3_descr">
		<text>The Remington Model 700 is a series of bolt-action centerfire rifles manufactured by Remington Arms since 1962. It is a development of the Remington 721 and 722 series of rifles, which were introduced in 1948. This model has been extensively modified.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Remington Arms\n
		%c[d_orange] • Increased penetration: +5\n
		</text>
	</string>

		<string id="st_wpn_sks_molot">
		<text>SKS Molot</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sks_molot_descr">
		<text>A semi-automatic, gas-operated, self-loading carbine used primarily during the Cold War, the SKS still sees service today with second-line and reserve army units. As it lacked a fire select and was limited to 10 rounds, it was made obsolete by the AK-47. This model has been modified to use 7.62x39mm.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Swiss Arms AG\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_sks_tac">
		<text>SKS Tactical</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_sks_tac_descr">
		<text>A semi-automatic, gas-operated, self-loading carbine used primarily during the Cold War, the SKS still sees service today with second-line and reserve army units. As it lacked a fire select and was limited to 10 rounds, it was made obsolete by the AK-47. This model has been modified with a lighter trigger allowing for a significantly increased rate of fire.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Swiss Arms AG\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_svd_m1">
		<text>SVD</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_svd_m1_descr">
		<text>One of the most iconic sniper rifles despite not technically being a sniper rifle, the SVD was intended to provide precise, suppressive fire on enemy positions as well as pick off high value targets. However, this squad-level DMR was eventually pressed into service as a sniper by those with access to nothing else. Relatively light, precise and well-balanced, it unfortunately loses out to dedicated sniper rifles in performance.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Kalashnikov Concern\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_svds">
		<text>SVDS</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_svds_descr">
		<text>One of the most iconic sniper rifles despite not technically being a sniper rifle, the SVD was intended to provide precise, suppressive fire on enemy positions as well as pick off high value targets. However, this squad-level DMR was eventually pressed into service as a sniper by those with access to nothing else. Relatively light, precise and well-balanced, it unfortunately loses out to dedicated sniper rifles in performance. The SVDS is a compact version of the SVD using a foldable buttstock.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Kalashnikov Concern\n
		</text>
	</string>

		<string id="st_wpn_svds_pmc">
		<text>SVDS "Retribution"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_svds_pmc_descr">
		<text>One of the most iconic sniper rifles despite not technically being a sniper rifle, the SVD was intended to provide precise, suppressive fire on enemy positions as well as pick off high value targets. However, this squad-level DMR was eventually pressed into service as a sniper by those with access to nothing else. Relatively light, precise and well-balanced, it unfortunately loses out to dedicated sniper rifles in performance. The SVDS is a compact version of the SVD using a foldable buttstock. This model has been extensively modified.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Kalashnikov Concern\n
		</text>
	</string>

<!--
	EXPLOSIVES
-->
	<string id="st_grenade_launcher">
		<text>GP-25 Grenade Launcher</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_grenade_launcher_descr">
		<text>The Kostyor is a single shot, front loaded, rifled under-barrel grenade launcher for assault rifles made in Warsaw Pact countries. Designed to greatly expand fire-power of a basic infantry squad. The firing mechanism is self-cocking, with a manual safety catch and automatic shot prevention if incorrectly installed onto a rifle.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Kalashnikov Concern\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_grenade_launcher_m203">
		<text>M203 Grenade Launcher</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_grenade_launcher_m203_descr">
		<text>A modified, shorter M203 that can be attached by means of a Picatinny rail. Although modern, it has similar properties as its Soviet counterpart, the GP-25.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Colt Defense\n
		</text>
	</string>

<!--
	MELEE
-->
	<string id="st_tomahawk">
		<text>Gerber Tomahawk</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_tomahawk_descr">
		<text>A tactical tomahawk, multitool and breaching tool, all-in-one package.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] melee weapon\n
		%c[pda_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] cut thick skin?: %c[ui_green]YES\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_kukri">
        <text>Kukri</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_kukri_descr">
        <text>The national weapon of Nepal, the Kukri has a distinct recurve in its blade and serves multiple purposes as a melee weapon and cutting tool.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Gorkha Kingdom\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] melee weapon\n
		%c[pda_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] cuts thick skin?: %c[ui_green]YES\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_tactical_knife">
		<text>Monolith Blade</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_tactical_knife_descr">
		<text>These blades are produced in very few numbers by masters of the Monolith faction. Their composition is from an unknown alloy, rumored to be extracted directly from the heart of the Sarcophagus.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] melee weapon\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Unknown\n
		%c[pda_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] cut thick skin?: %c[ui_green]YES\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_knifebf4">
        <text>OTs-4 Combat Knife</text>
    </string>
    	<string id="st_knifebf4_descr">
        <text>Developed at the Tula Central Design Research Bureau in the late 80s for the special forces of the Ministry of Internal Affairs. Featuring a serrated blade, the handle is made of polymer and has a distinctive “grenade” texture.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] melee weapon\n
		%c[pda_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] cuts thick skin?: %c[ui_green]YES\n
		</text>
    </string>

<!--
	OTHER
-->
	<string id="st_not_in_use">
        <text>Not Used</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_not_in_use_descr">
        <text>This item is not used.</text>
    </string>
-->

</string_table>
