<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>

<!--
	Devices
-->

<string_table>

	<string id="st_itm_exo_psu_name">
		<text>Jury-rigged Exoskeleton power supply</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_exo_psu_descr">
		<text>Auxiliary power supply equipped on exoskeletons to increase their energy capacity. Popular with most stalkers given the rather inefficient powerplants that come with standard exoskeletons. To use, drag onto an exoskeleton.\n \nThis type of power supply is haphazardly put together and quite inefficient. While lightweight, it only offers a marginal increase to energy capacity. One of the major drawbacks to most exoskeletons is that they are intended to be fielded for a short amount of time, usually in pitched battles before returning to base to reacharge. External power supplies like these can partially alleviate the problem, but, as clearly shown by this, are not necessarily effective.\n\n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] power capacity: 150\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] power consumption rate: 100%\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_exo_psu_mili_name">
		<text>Mil-spec Exoskeleton power supply</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_exo_psu_mili_descr">
		<text>Auxiliary power supply equipped on exoskeletons to improve their energy capacity. Popular with most stalkers given the rather inefficient powerplants that come with standard exoskeletons. To use, install onto an exoskeleton.\n \nThis model is professionally made in a factory and mounts seamlessly to an exoskeleton. It is hefty but very durable and quite energy-efficient, providing a substantial boost to energy capacity and a minor benefit to energy efficiency. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] military item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] power capacity: 250\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] power consumption rate: 85%\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_itm_exo_psu_sci_name">
		<text>Experimental PSU "Reactor"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_exo_psu_sci_descr">
		<text>Auxiliary power supply equipped on exoskeletons to improve their energy capacity. Popular with most stalkers given the rather inefficient powerplants that come with standard exoskeletons. To use, drag onto an exoskeleton.\n \nThis model is an experimental prototype constructed based on schematics you obtained from Ecologists, using the latently static properties of the Battery artifact to reduce the battery usage rate.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] prototype device\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] power capacity: 400\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] power consumption rate: 50%\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] double-tap $$ACTION_SPRINT_TOGGLE$$ to launch electrical nova\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_itm_exo_psu_tank_name">
		<text>Experimental PSU "Stronghold"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_exo_psu_tank_descr">
		<text>Auxiliary power supply equipped on exoskeletons to improve their energy capacity. Popular with most stalkers given the rather inefficient powerplants that come with standard exoskeletons. To use, drag onto an exoskeleton.\n \nThis model is an experimental prototype constructed based on schematics you obtained from Ecologists. Designed to be complement frontline troops who need to push forward in heavy fire, this prototype uses the gravitational properties of the Empty artifact to generate a localized anomaly zone on activation. The anomaly zone is centered on the user and effectively slows down high-velocity projectiles and shrapnel, as well as rendering mutant attacks useless. However, the gravity well interferes with user movement. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] prototype device\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] power capacity: 500\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] power consumption rate: 135%\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] double-tap $$ACTION_SPRINT_TOGGLE$$ for major damage reduction\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] 20 energy cost, 8 second duration, 20 second cooldown\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_itm_exo_psu_sprint_name">
		<text>Experimental PSU "Engine"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_itm_exo_psu_sprint_descr">
		<text>Auxiliary power supply equipped on exoskeletons to improve their energy capacity. Popular with most stalkers given the rather inefficient powerplants that come with standard exoskeletons. To use, drag onto an exoskeleton.\n \nThis model is an experimental prototype constructed based on schematics you obtained from Ecologists. Designed to add mobility options for shock troopers, this prototype uses the capactive properties of the Flash artifact to power a customized set of servomotors. The Flash artifact can be temporarily activated to vastly increase user mobility. The vastly increased movespeed also allows the user to deal massive damage to any creature or person caught in their path.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] valuable\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] power capacity: 300\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] power consumption rate: 85%\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] moderate electric power consumption\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] double-tap $$ACTION_SPRINT_TOGGLE$$ for major speed boost\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] sprint into enemies to deal damage\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] 20 energy cost, 8 second duration, 20 second cooldown\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_batteries_ccell">
		<text>Military battery unit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_batteries_ccell_descr">
		<text>A heavy milspec battery for powering exoskeletons. Developed by Ukranian research facilities based on Zone research, these high-density power packs can replace spent cells in exoskeleton power plants, or transfer power to onboard storage. Drag onto an exoskeleton to recharge its power.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] supplies power to exoskeletons\n
		</text>
	</string>

	
	<string id="st_exo_recipe_1">
		<text>Behavior of "Battery" artifacts under artificial electromagnetic fields</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_exo_recipe_1_descr">
		<text>Scientific paper penned by V.R. Solenov and R.R. Romanovich, detailing the behavior and observed effects of Battery artifacts when subject to various strengths of electromagnetic fields. Under certain VPM levels the Battery is observed to emit brief, intense surges of direct current from the artifact, with the effect not having any correlation with the strength of the field. It is very wordy and verbose, and accompanying the text and equations are several graphs, black and white photos, and test logs. At the back of the paper are schematics on how to contain such a Battery artifact to cause it to output more voltage when subject to a positive current. The notebook is stamped with the official seal of the Ukrainian Ministry of Science.\n\n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] informative\n
			%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] craft recipe\n
			%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] valuable\n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_exo_recipe_2">
		<text>Observations and analysis of "Full Empty" artifact projected gravitational shells</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_exo_recipe_2_descr">
		<text>Scientific paper penned by A.N. Perchenov and V.R. Solenov, detailing the observations of the Full Empty artifact's peculiar gravitational effects. According to the document, the space between Empty disks is the consequence of two disks partially distorting spacetime relative to the positions of each other to create a miniature gravitational anomaly. The contents of what the 'full' part of the Full Empty are remain unknown and are speculated to be the visible form of air particles charged with highly excited zero-point energy. When subject to an alternating current of a certain amperage under vacuum conditions, the contents temporarily dissipate and the gravitational anomaly contained between the two disks expands to create a nearly impervious 'shell' where any solid objects entering the space are caught and deflected from their original trajectory. The discovery of this behavior supposedly injured four interns and two lab assistants when the correct configuration was dialed in. Within the experiment log is a diagram of the vacuum containment device required to replicate this behavior.\n\n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] informative\n
			%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] craft recipe\n
			%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] valuable\n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_exo_recipe_3">
		<text>Application of 'Flash' artifact fields to engine power output</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_exo_recipe_3_descr">
		<text>Scientific paper penned by R.R. Romanovich and A.N. Perchenov, detailing the strange effects that Flash artifacts have on electrically-powered machinery. When a Flash artifact is subjected to a positive electric current in vacuum, the artifact projects a variously sized anomalous field that vastly increases the physical output of electrical machinery in the area - motors run faster, CPUs overclock, and even mechanical watches move faster. Various experimental logs note the propensity of the machines to burn themselves out due to high heat and friction generated if the field is sustained for a prolonged period of time, and most of the paper is otherwise speculation at what could cause such a behavior. The latest prevailing theory is a quantum level influence increasing the flow of electricity and strength of magnetism. However, such theories are unconfirmed. In the middle of the paper is a diagram detailing the containment chamber construction of the artifact used in experimentation.\n\n
			%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
			%c[d_green] • %c[ui_gray_2] informative\n
			%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] craft recipe\n
			%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] valuable\n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_power">
		<text>Power level:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_equipped_supply">
		<text>Equipped power supply:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_equipped_none">
		<text>None</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_charge_exo">
		<text>charge suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_install_psu">
		<text>install</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_remove_psu">
		<text>remove PSU</text>
	</string>
	<string id="kb_power">
		<text>Activate powers</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_dot">
		<text>•</text>
	</string>
	<string id="article_exo">
		<text>Powered Exoskeletons</text>
	</string>
	<string id="article_exo_text">
		<text>
			%c[pda_white]Powered Exoskeletons \n \n %c[ui_gray_1] 
			Exoskeletons now each have their own unique power source. The power level must be maintained in order for an exoskeleton to move around effectively.
			\n \n%c[pda_blue]Exo batteries%c[ui_gray_1]
			\n Exoskeleton power reserves can be recharged with batteries purchased from traders or found in the world. Batteries hold a default of 100 power, which is enough to fully top off an un-upgraded exoskeleton.
			\n Exoskeleton power drains with movement, faster with sprinting. If the power drops to 0, the player will be slowed to a ridiculous extent unless the armor is removed.
			\n \n%c[pda_green]External power supplies%c[ui_gray_1]
			\n Exoskeletons can be upgraded with power supplies that are purchasable, craftable, and lootable. 
			\n To equip a power supply, drag and drop the power supply onto the armor or right-click the power supply while the exoskeleton is equipped.
			\n Power supplies increase the energy capacity of an exoskeleton beyond 100, and higher level versions confer unique benefits and powers.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_err_none">
		<text>[SYSCTL] WARN: FUNCTIONALITY NOT FOUND</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_err_power">
		<text>[SYSCTL] WARN: POWER INSUFFICIENT</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_err_cooldown">
		<text>[SYSCTL] WARN: SYS TEMP ABOVE SAFE THRESHOLD</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ok_cooldown">
		<text>[SYSCTL] INFO: SYS TEMP UNDER SAFE THRESHOLD</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_act_tank">
		<text>[SYSCTL] INFO: GRAVITATIONAL BARRIER ACTIVE</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_act_sprint">
		<text>[SYSCTL] INFO: MOTOR OVERCLOCK ACTIVE</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_low_power">
		<text>[SYSCTL] WARN: BATTERY LOW</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ui_mcm_menu_exo">
		<text>Powered Exos</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_exo_title">
		<text>Powered Exoskeletons</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_exo_drain">
		<text>Exoskeleton power drain</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_exo_sprint_drain">
		<text>Exoskeleton sprint power drain</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_exo_debug">
		<text>Enable Debug Logs</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_exo_drain_desc">
		<text>Power drain multiplier for exoskeletons.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_exo_sprint_drain_desc">
		<text>Multiplier on power drain when sprinting.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_exo_battery_chance">
		<text>Battery drop chance.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_exo_battery_chance_desc">
		<text>Chance that stalkers will drop batteries. Exoskeleton wearers only!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_exo_debug_desc">
		<text>Enable Debug Logs in console</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ui_mcm_menu_exo_power">
		<text>Exo Power keybind</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_exo_power_keybind">
		<text>Activate PSU power.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_exo_power_keybind_desc">
		<text>Used to activate exoskeleton related powers.</text>
	</string>
</string_table>