<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<!--
	Artefacts (active)
-->

<string_table>
	<string id="st_af_itcher_name">
		<text>Itcher</text>
	</string>  
	<string id="st_af_itcher_descr">
		<text>
		A formation of thermal nature. The Itcher consists of two separated layers. The surface is a hard, dense metamorphic rock with deep scars covering the entire body. Completely inactive and doesn't hold any noticeable properties. On the other hand, the soft, yellow glowing core is from unknown organic nature. It actively consumes excessive heat and remains cool at all times.
		\nHowever, it is not recommended to approach chemical and acid anomalies when in possession of the artefact as it will increase the adverse effects of acids and toxins in user's bloodstream.
		\n\n%c[0,209,172,56] Does NOT degrade over time.\n
		</text>
	</string> 

	<string id="st_af_pin_name">
		<text>Pin</text>
	</string>  
	<string id="st_af_pin_descr">
		<text>
		A small artefact formed by thermal anomalies in the Zone under extreme temperatures. The look of this artefact suggests that it was an organ of a vascular plant. Further studies showed that other organic tissues are fused deep inside.
		\nThe stem doesn't hold any useful properties. On the contrary, the small pins reduce temperature of user's body and cool all objects in their vicinity.
		\nThis artefact offers a slight psy-protection as it will resonate under the influence of psy-waves. On the other hand, it is not recommended to approach chemical and acid anomalies when in possession of the artefact as it will increase the adverse effects of acids and toxins in user's bloodstream.
		\n\n%c[0,209,172,56] Does NOT degrade over time.\n
		</text>
	</string>  
	
	<string id="st_af_cristall_name">
		<text>Crystal</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cristall_descr">
		<text>
		This artefact is formed in anomalous zones with intense thermal activity. Actively consumes excessive heat and remains cool at all times.
		\nIt will also protect the user against electrical currents. On the other hand, exposure to such environments makes the artefact increase the conductivity due to unknown as of now mechanism. For this reason, one is forced to weigh pros and cons of Crystal when in the vicinity of areas of high conductivity.
		\nThis artefact is also highly sought for by jewellers outside the Zone as its inner core is not radioactive and considered to be of exceptional beauty if polished and refined. Only the first 1 cm of its outer layer emits radiation.
		\nIt is, however, highly advised to proceed with caution when planning to bring the artefact to the market as prolonged exposure to even minimal amounts of radioactive materials can result in death of the user. Covered with very hard layer. Relatively heavy due to high density.
		\n\n%c[0,209,172,56] Does NOT degrade over time.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_fireball_name">
		<text>Fireball</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fireball_descr">
		<text>
		It is a spherical artefact made of red-coloured crystal, created in the Burner anomaly.
		\nIt has an unique property: it has a constant temperature of 75 degrees Fahrenheit/24 degrees Celsius, regardless of its surroundings. This allows it to absorb heat from its vicinity and to create a little pocket around the user which prevents the flames from damaging the body.
		\nA dangerous effect of this artefact is the fact that it will increase electrical conductivity, so the probability of electrocution while wearing this artefact is much higher, especially during storms and in the vicinity of electrical anomalies.It is quite heavy due to high density of crystal-like material.
		\n\n%c[0,209,172,56] Does NOT degrade over time.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_blood_name">
		<text>Stone Blood</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_blood_descr">
		<text>
		A reddish formation of compressed fossilised plants, soil and animal debris. Can partially neutralise chemical poisons by absorbing them and reducing overall toxicity level in user's bloodstream. Quite widespread and not very effective as it makes chemical burns fester. It will catch fire when exposed to open flame or even spontaneously combust. 
		\nAnother positive effect possessed by this artefact is that it accelerates clotting if worn close to the body. Although it is not recommended to keep this artefact in your possession for longer periods of time as blood clots can be hazardous to your health.
		\n\n%c[0,209,172,56] Does NOT degrade over time.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_mincer_meat_name">
		<text>Meat Chunk</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_mincer_meat_descr">
		<text>
		This artefact has soft, porous, skin-like texture and is said to be able to compress. It resembles and acts like a sponge in this regard, but reveals its special characteristics only when exposed to certain external conditions.
		\nFirstly, to carry the sponge metaphor further, the pores on its surface are known to absorb small amounts of toxicity from environment.
		\nSecondly, the artefact slightly amplifies the damaging effects of psy-fields to living organisms by absorbing psy energy and emitting it at a small rate.
		\nThirdly, Meat Chunk is also known to be a conductor of electricity much like the skin of a living creature.
		\n\n%c[0,209,172,56] Does NOT degrade over time.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_bracelet_name">
		<text>Bracelet</text>
	</string>  
	<string id="st_af_bracelet_descr">
		<text>
		Bracelet is formed from common species of bryophytes plants under high exposure to radioactive and chemical anomalies, which explains its organic nature.
		\nIt provides substantial protection against all types of acids by gradually increasing their pH to the level of water (pH of 7).
		\nWhen worn, the artefact is also known to slightly counter the harmful effects of psy-anomalies or psy-waves of some mutants.
		\n\n%c[0,209,172,56] Does NOT degrade over time.\n
		</text>
	</string>  
	
	<string id="st_af_baloon_name">
		<text>Bubble</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_baloon_descr">
		<text>
		A compound of several hollow organic formations, this artefact emits a gaseous substance that can neutralise chemical or toxic particles inside the body without harming it. Thus providing a a great level of toxic and chemical protection.
		\nIt also has a constant temperature regardless of its surroundings. This allows it to absorb heat from its vicinity and to create a little pocket around the user which prevents the flames from damaging the body. 
		\nApart from that Bubble, however, possesses numerous negative properties. For example, it greatly amplifies the effects of psy-waves as well as fields produced by mutants and anomalies. This disadvantage is not to be taken lightly: some stalkers have reported that psy influence was so potent when in possession of a Bubble that they felt their heads cracking from the inside and the only thing they could do was scream in pain and run as far as they could. 
		\n\n%c[0,209,172,56] Does NOT degrade over time.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_electra_sparkler_name">
		<text>Sparkler</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_sparkler_descr">
		<text>
		This artefact has the appearance of translucent spider webs. Just as proteinaceous spider silk, it is sticky and has properties of glue.
		\nIt can be found most commonly in or near electro anomalies and it seems to have absorbed their certain characteristics: it is able to smooth fluctuations in electric field density and acts as a weak resistor, protecting the wearer from electricity and reducing its damaging effects.
		\nOn the other hand, it should be noted that the presence of this artefact increases the corrosiveness of acids, leading to accelerated deterioration of equipment and higher damage to tissues of any living organism.
		\n\n%c[0,209,172,56] Does NOT degrade over time.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_sponge_name">
		<text>Sponge</text>
	</string>  
	<string id="st_af_sponge_descr">
		<text>
		Sponge has always been under debate among the Ecologists. Some suggest that this artefact is driven from basic form of organisms, while others believe its an advanced life form with self-awareness inherited from living creatures.
		\nDespite the theories surrounding the artefact, all can agree on one thing: it moves. The sponge sometimes tries to "grab" an object it touches. Putting it in a container might be a hard task, as if it wants to escape.
		\nThis artefact acts as a powerful resistor and will absorb even lethal doses of electricity. On the other hand, it will catch fire when exposed to open flame or even spontaneously combust.
		\n\n%c[0,209,172,56] Does NOT degrade over time.\n
		</text>
	</string> 
	
	<string id="st_af_ring_name">
		<text>Ring</text>
	</string>  
	<string id="st_af_ring_descr">
		<text>
		A very small artefact of electric nature. Difficult to spot. Consists of two ring-shaped materials of organic nature, hence the given name.
		When the Ring spins, it never stops spinning, defying the first law of thermodynamics. Scientists suggest that this artefact inherits gravitational properties from Vortex anomalies.
		\nThe outer ring has a high-conductivity. It absorbs electrical current from relative sources then ground it in the inner ring. Despite the basic function, the mechanism behind the disappearance of electrical power inside the second ring is still unknown.
		\nOn the other side, the Ring is flammable. Prolonged exposure may enhance its flammability and cause it to ignite.
		\n\n%c[0,209,172,56] Does NOT degrade over time.\n
		</text>
	</string> 
	
	<string id="st_af_electra_flash_name">
		<text>Flash</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_flash_descr">
		<text>
		This artefact is very similar in appearance to Moonlight and resembles a plasma globe or a plasma lamp.
		\nBeing a powerful resistor, it is well known for its ability to shield its user from lethal doses of electricity.
		\nWhen worn, it is known to slightly counter harmful effects of psy-anomalies or psy-waves of certain mutants. Flash acts as a powerful resistor and will absorb even lethal doses of electricity.
		\nHowever, it also hinders healing process, thus caution is advised especially when wounded or bleeding. This artefact is also extremely light and very portable.
		\n\n%c[0,209,172,56] Does NOT degrade over time.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_cristall_flower_name">
		<text>Stone Flower</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cristall_flower_descr">
		<text>
		This artefact resembles melted cheese interspersed with sapphire-like stones. Only yellow outer shell of the artefact appears to give off radiation and by careful processing it is possible to extract the non-radioactive blue parts for jewellery and other industrial purposes. This is due to the fact that if cleaned properly and polished, sapphire comparison becomes much more explicit: the stones are as hard and durable as this beautiful gem. This quality of theirs and their appearance make them perfect gemstones and jewellers all over the world strive to have them in stock. 
		\nThe usefulness of the artefact, however, is not limited to its industrial applications. There is scientific evidence suggesting that sapphire-like stones effectively protect from psy-waves, whereas the outer shell slightly increases resistance to toxicity.
		\nHowever, it can cause objects in its vicinity to heat up and in extreme cases to ignite along with the artefact. For this reason, it is safe to conclude that it absorbs heat and is able to convey it to other objects.
		\nDue to its density the weight of artefact has increased beyond normal standards, and thus it is one of the heaviest anomalous creations in the Zone.
		\n\n%c[0,209,172,56] Does NOT degrade over time.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_lobster_eyes_name">
		<text>Lobster Eyes</text>
	</string>  
	<string id="st_af_lobster_eyes_descr">
		<text>
		As the name suggests, this artefact has the shape of two eggs fused together. The outer surface is very thick, the high density of its formation might be the reason behind its deep colour.
		\nThis artefact offers slightly more psy-protection than its cousin, Stone Flower. It resonates under the influence of psy-waves to some degree and absorbs the dangerous effect.
		\nAnother positive property is the ability to consume excessive heat while remaining cool at all times.
		\nDue to its density of the surface, the Lobster Eyes is quite heavy.
		\n\n%c[0,209,172,56] Does NOT degrade over time.\n
		</text>
	</string> 
	
	<string id="st_af_electra_moonlight_name">
		<text>Moonlight</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_moonlight_descr">
		<text>
		This unique electrostatic artefact can resonate under the influence of psy-waves. Stalkers have learned to fine-tune the artefact so that it resonates in opposite phase to the main source of emissions, thus significantly neutralizing their effects. This orb of considerable beauty also increases electrical protection by reducing conductivity in the body when exposed to high levels of electricity.
		\nIt should be noted that Moonlight will catch fire when exposed to open flame or even spontaneously combust. 
		\n\n%c[0,209,172,56] Does NOT degrade over time.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_black_spray_name">
		<text>Black Spray</text>
	</string>  
	<string id="st_af_black_spray_descr">
		<text>
		Being a rare artefact, little is known about its properties and origins. 
		\nBlack Spray shares a similar shape to other sapphire-like artefacts. However, the organic nature of the stem (which shares similar properties to Pin artefacts) suggests that its formed from vascular plants under exposure to dangerous psy-fields and electromagnetic waves.
		\nAnother unique property is the ability to delay the transmission of light that enters it. The said mysterious mechanism is applied to psy-waves surrounding the artefact as well. For this particular reason, Black Spray significantly neutralises psy interferences in a large radius.
		\nThese beneficial properties, however, come at a price. This artefact is extremely dangerous when exposed in toxic environments as it amplifies their effect and increases their potency. When exploring toxic areas, it is hence highly recommended to keep the artefact in your backpack.
		\nDue to the beautiful blue aura it emits, it is highly sought after by jewellers all over the world.
		\n\n%c[0,209,172,56] Does NOT degrade over time.\n
		</text>
	</string>  
	
	<string id="st_af_medusa_name">
		<text>Jellyfish</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_medusa_descr">
		<text>
		Very common in the Zone. This gravitational artefact is able to slightly shield the body and objects from physical impacts.
		\nIt will slightly protect its user against extreme heat produced respectively by fire anomalies.
		\nThis artefact is quite heavy as the gravitational field seems to increase mass. Another downside to this artefact is that it will increase the negative effects of psy-waves and is a potent conductor.
		\n\n%c[0,209,172,56] Does NOT degrade over time.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_vyvert_name">
		<text>Wrenched</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_vyvert_descr">
		<text>
		This bizarrely-shaped artefact appears in places with increased gravitational activity.
		\nAlthough it appears almost organic, it is actually more similar to coral. Due to its gravitational nature, It provides protection against physical impacts as it greatly reduces the friction caused by fast objects.
		\nActing as a kind of sponge that absorbs chemical and toxic elements as well, this artefact provides protection from external toxic agents as well as from chemical particles that have already made their way into the body.
		\nWrenced can generate a locally directed gravity field which increases its mass. For this reason, this artefact is heavy.
		\n\n%c[0,209,172,56] Does NOT degrade over time.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_empty_name">
		<text>Empty</text>
	</string>  
	<string id="st_af_empty_descr">
		<text>
		Two disks of organic formation (commonly lipids, cellulose and lignin) with nothing but empty space in between. This is due to a unique gravitation field formed in the centre that stabilise the distance between the disks.
		\nAny attempt to press the disks together, or pull them apart will fail due to rapid positive/negative changes in the gravitational field. As if the artefact reacts to any physical power that breaks its balance.
		\nBecause of this mechanism, moving with an Empty is a hard task. As the gravitational field increases the density of surrounding air and slows the body down.
		\nThe real usefulness of this effect comes to the ability to reduce friction, thus obtaining great protection against physical impacts.
		\n\n%c[0,209,172,56] Does NOT degrade over time.\n
		</text>
	</string> 
 	
	<string id="st_af_full_empty_name">
		<text>Full Empty</text>
	</string>  
	<string id="st_af_full_empty_descr">
		<text>
		Similar to Empty, this artefact consist of two disks of organic formation connected by a unique gravitational field in between. However, the said field in Full Empty is extraordinary: all atoms entering the centre, regardless of their nature, become interactive under the unknown effects of the field. Thus releasing photons (light emitting).
		\nScientists usually refer to it as the "galaxy effect", which gives the artefact an exceptional orbit of light.
		\nThe density increment of surrounding air caused by moving is higher comparing to Empty. Because of this, the artefact will greatly hinder its holder's movement.
		\nBeing superior artefact to Empty, the protection against physical impacts is remarkable. Some claims that Full Empty is capable of stopping 9mm bullets fired at point blank.
		\n\n%c[0,209,172,56] Does NOT degrade over time.\n
		</text>
	</string> 
	
	<string id="st_af_night_star_name">
		<text>Nightstar</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_night_star_descr">
		<text>
		This glowing artefact can generate a local directed low-gravity field. Widely used by stalkers along with Gravi, a similar artefact, to increase maximum load.
		\nDue to its beautiful inner core it is highly sought after by jewellers all over the world, however it is best to proceed with caution as unskilled treatment can cause the artefact to explode with power sufficient to level a small building. It is thus highly advised to perform the polishing by means of specialised machinery, which minimises the probability of explosion. Moreover, only the outer core of the artefact emits radiation.
		\nNightstar will also absorb toxic and chemical agents from the environment, which makes it a valuable artefact for artefact hunters, although the amount of toxicity absorbed is negligible. It is, however, relatively cheap and even stalkers with pretty tight budgets can afford it if opportunity to buy it arises. 
		\nThat being said, Nightstar emits odour of burning flesh when in the closest proximity of heat source. Prolonged exposure may enhance its flammability and cause it to ignite.
		\n\n%c[0,209,172,56] Does NOT degrade over time.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_gravi_name">
		<text>Gravi</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_gravi_descr">
		<text>
		Gravi is formed from metallic substances exposed to prolonged gravitation. This makes it capable of sustaining an powerful anti-gravitational field, which causes it to have various properties, among others reducing weight of all objects in its close proximity. For a long time, the artefact was a mystery, and it was scientist Sakharov at Yantar who first discovered that Gravi creates a minute singularity field of anti-gravitational nature, the phenomenon which occurs in intervals of 30 minutes.
		\nA dangerous effect of this artefact is the fact that it will increase electrical conductivity, so the probability of electrocution while wearing this artefact is much higher, especially during storms and in the vicinity of electrical anomalies.
		\nAnother downside is that it will increase the negative effects of psy-waves and is a potent conductor.
		\n\n%c[0,209,172,56] Does NOT degrade over time.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_gold_fish_name">
		<text>Goldfish</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_gold_fish_descr">
		<text>
		Direct successor to and a superior version of Gravi artefact. As was the case with Gravi, it was scientist Sakharov at Yantar who discovered its unique properties after a massive blowout/emission hit the Zone.
		\nThanks to meticulous research that followed, it was established that this new artefact is produced when three Gravi artefacts interact and get sucked into one another's singularity fields. This phenomenon is extremely rare, due to which the artefact is highly valued.
		\nIt is rumoured within Ukrainian Spetsnaz circles that in the Zone there are agents from the Ministry of Defence of the Russian Federation whose sole objective is acquiring and transporting Goldfish to specialised laboratories located outside of the Zone.
		\nThe artefact creates a constant anti-gravitational singularity field which affects only its closest vicinity. However, some stalkers have been known to disappear for no apparent reason leaving only a Goldfish behind.
		\nBig downside, however, comes along with this powerful anti-gravitational field: the velocity of moving objects inside its radius will rapidly increase, causing dangerous impacts on surrounding objects, including the holder.
		\n\n%c[0,209,172,56] Does NOT degrade over time.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_dummy_glassbeads_name">
		<text>Mama's Beads</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_glassbeads_descr">
		<text>
		Shaped like a DNA helix, Mama's Beads are created in the Burner anomaly. One of their most characteristic features is that they constantly pulsate, generating emissions beneficial to the human body. These emissions increase the metabolism of any living creature, accelerating coagulation and healing of wounds.The mechanism behind the effects of this artefact is still unknown.
		\nMama's Beads also possess potent protective qualities: they are able to shield the body and objects from extreme heat.
		\nOn the other hand, it should be noted that the presence of this artefact increases electrical conductivity, so the probability of electrocution while wearing this artefact is much higher, especially during storms and in the vicinity of electrical anomalies.
		\nThe weight is also quite high for such a small artefact, which leads to a conclusion that is of high density.
		\n\n%c[0,209,172,56] Does NOT degrade over time.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_eye_name">
		<text>Eye</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_eye_descr">
		<text>
		This artefact, which resembles the human eye, considerably increases metabolism of the body, helping wounds heal quicker. Experienced stalkers say that Eye also brings luck. Irrespective of the validity of that statement, its positive effects are indeed quite potent. 
		\nThis artefact soothes the pain and is extremely useful when treating wounds.
		\nWhen worn, it is known to slightly counter harmful effects of psy-anomalies or psy-waves of certain mutants.
		\nThese beneficial qualities, however, come at a price. This artefact is extremely dangerous when exposed to chemical anomalies as it amplifies their toxicity and increases their potency. It is hence highly recommended to keep the artefact in your backpack, never on the body, when exploring toxic areas unless you have a death wish.
		\nThe artefact is also known colloquially as "copper eye" as it conducts electricity and amplifies its dangerous effects in the same way as copper does. 
		\n\n%c[0,209,172,56] Does NOT degrade over time.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_fire_name">
		<text>Flame</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fire_descr">
		<text>
		This artefact forms in areas of high thermal activity. Produces powerful infrared emissions which intensify metabolic processes, healing wounds before its bearer's very eyes.
		\nIts healing capabilities are even stronger than in case of the Eye as stalkers in possession of this artefact are said to have survived being wounded by chimeras. Thanks to that, it has earned the reputation of a miraculous artefact.
		\nMany stalkers owe it their lives, and most veteran mutant hunters carry it in case they run into danger. However, it shares not only positive but also negative properties of its cousin: entering a psy-field with this artefact on the belt is suicide. It will absorb psy energy and emitting it at a considerable rate.
		\nAlso, it is highly advised to proceed with caution when planning to bring the artefact to the market as prolonged exposure to even minimal amounts of radioactive materials can result in death of the user.
		\nIt can also be used as a reusable medkit of sorts since it heals wounds very quickly.
		\n\n%c[0,209,172,56] Does NOT degrade over time.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_dummy_battery_name">
		<text>Battery</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_battery_descr">
		<text>
		\nThe artefact is quite popular in the Zone and is valued by its residents and visitors alike for its energizing properties, although it has an adverse effect on the body when used for prolonged periods of time.
		\nOne should take note, however, that this artefact hinders blood clotting and increases bleeding rate of open wounds. On the other hand, being a powerful resistor, it is well known for its ability to shield its user from lethal doses of electricity.
		\nBeing an artefact of electric nature, it is well known for its ability to shield its user from lethal doses of electricity. On the contrary, it should be noted that Battery absorbs heat and is able to convey it to other objects.
		\nThis artefact is also extremely light and very portable. 
		\n\n%c[0,209,172,56] Does NOT degrade over time.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_dummy_dummy_name">
		<text>Shell</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_dummy_descr">
		<text>
		Shell is composed of two disk of bluish colour connected by semitransparent material of unknown nature.
		\nThis strange artefact was considered devoid of any useful properties by many scientists for a long time. Only recently has it been discovered that it is indeed quite beneficial.
		\nWhen the artefact comes into contact with the body, it will make one feel rejuvenated and thus it increases stamina recovery. This effect has in case of some stalkers induced hyperactivity. One downside of this artefact, however, is that it reduces the number of platelets in blood, thus increasing bleeding rate.
		\nIt provides a considerable level of psy protection and absorbs electromagnetic interference, acting as a grounding material.
		\nIt will catch fire when exposed to open flame or even spontaneously combust. Caution must be taken when approaching heat sources with this artefact.
		\nShell is extremely light and very portable.
		\n\n%c[0,209,172,56] Does NOT degrade over time.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_ice_name">
		<text>Snowflake</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ice_descr">
		<text>
		Also colloquially known as "Radioactive Snowflake". At first glance, this artefact resembles a white Kolobok.
		\nThanks to its unique properties, the artefact can significantly increase the bearer's muscle tone, thus greatly improving stamina recovery. Due to its high radioactivity, stalkers in possession of it are sometimes jokingly referred to as "Radioactive Snowflakes".
		\nWhen faced with the decision whether to carry it on the belt during a mission, you have to carefully weigh its pros and cons: does it pay to have greater endurance and high protection against electricity at the cost of being constantly exposed to its deadly radiation? Even if you are determined to take it with you, it should be noted that it is not to be used on long excursions to the Zone.
		\nSnowflake, however, holds a big downside: it interacts with surrounding energy sources by absorbing and amplifying their effects. For this reason, approaching heat sources, toxic areas and psy-fields while holding this artefact is a suicide.
		\nIt is as light as a snowflake and very easy to carry around.
		\n\n%c[0,209,172,56] Does NOT degrade over time.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_soul_name">
		<text>Soul</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_soul_descr">
		<text>
		Soul is a unique organic artefact with properties just as unique: it secretes slimy goo that dramatically increases recovery rate of wounds. Thanks to its reasonable price and attractive appearance, this artefact is a valuable collector's item.
		\nApplying its gooey substance to wounds will soothes the pain and speeds up healing process. 
		\It also reduces the effects of psy-waves and their damage to one's brain. But it should be known that Soul drains power from its user. The artefact does not have high density and thus is not very heavy.
		\n\n%c[0,209,172,56] Does NOT degrade over time.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_fuzz_kolobok_name">
		<text>Kolobok</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fuzz_kolobok_descr">
		<text>
		A relatively rare artefact forming in chemical areas, Kolobok is highly valued for its ability to heal most kinds of wounds and stop bleeding in a matter of minutes.
		\nFor unknown reasons, scientists are spreading rumours among stalkers that the artefact modifies bearer's genetic code, which is unproven and should be regarded as conscious attempt at monopolizing the supply of the artefact by the scientific community. This does not, however, mean that it is completely harmless.
		\nOne drawback of this artefact is the fact that it will interact to radioactive particles, so it is best to avoid radiation fields when in possession of the artefact, especially since its negative effects are not balanced with positive ones. It will also reduce energy recovery, which is the result of its sharp needle-like appendages. The needles cause small and quickly healing wounds which bring constant pain and itch, thus reducing stamina.
		\nThis artefact also weakens protection against heat and acids due to its high flammability. 
		\nLightweight and not too much of a burden to carry around.
		\n\n%c[0,209,172,56] Does NOT degrade over time.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_glass_name">
		<text>Firefly</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_glass_descr">
		<text>
		Firefly interacts with fields unknown to science, considerably speeding up regeneration of tissue and organs in living beings, as well as normalizing metabolic processes.
		\nThis artefact can literally get a badly wounded stalker back on his feet in a matter of minutes. On the other hand, Firefly can spontaneously combust when exposed to potent radioactive sources.
		\nA big downside to this artefact is that it weakens the body and reduce the number of platelets in blood during heal process, thus increasing bleeding rate.
		\nIt seems to drain stamina and decrease stamina recovery greatly as well. Some of those who used Firefly for its healing purposes have reported that they couldn't walk for hours afterwards.
		\nUnfortunately, Firefly is extremely rare.
		\n\n%c[0,209,172,56] Does NOT degrade over time.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_compass_name">
		<text>Compass</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_compass_descr">
		<text>
		A very rare artefact. It's been several years since one was found.
		\nIt can locate gaps in anomaly fields. It is believed that it can help one traverse the most complex anomaly fields completely unharmed. However, very few know how to handle it properly.
		\nThe Compass showed few unique properties under last experiments. It can interact to moving objects, causing some to completely disappear. Or perhaps teleport?
		\nIt also weakens the body by draining stamina and increasing bleeding rate constantly. But the biggest draw however, is the dangerous radiation output this artefact emits comparing to the artefact radiation scale.
		\nHolding this artefact near the body will cause death in matter of few minutes.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_oasis_heart_name">
		<text>Heart of the Oasis</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_oasis_heart_descr">
		<text>
		This artefact was found at the centre of the legendary Oasis. It appears that the Heart is a crystallised plant, which has acquired the healing properties of the Oasis.
		\nNot only it dramatically increases recovery rate of wounds and healing process, but also provides the body with strong source of energy. It is a true miracle.
		\nThat being said, the Oasis is very sensitive to outer sources of energy and surrounding environment. For this reason, interacting with anomaly fields will bring death to the holder.
		\n\n%c[0,209,172,56] Does NOT degrade over time.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_death_lamp_name">
		<text>Death Lamp</text>
	</string>  
	<string id="st_af_death_lamp_descr">
		<text>
		"Big, red and cursed."
		\nThis is how the locals prefer to describe the Death Lamp, while some refer to it as the "Seed of Satan". Many traders believe the rumours surrounding the artefact, thus refusing to buy it.
		Little is known about its origins, and nothing of value has been discovered so far.
		\nDeath Lamp was first discovered few years ago by a group of three experienced stalkers. Shortly after delivering the artefact to the Ecologists in Yantar, two of them found dead with a horrific expression on their faces. Nothing is known about the fate of the third stalker.
		\nFollowing the accident, members of the science team who studied the artefact had reported having nightmare disorder in the days to follow.
		\nApart from the mysterious effects, the artefact drains vitality and willpower from the user, often on such a scale that it induces dizziness and in extreme cases causes the user to faint. 
		\n\n%c[0,209,172,56] Does NOT degrade over time.\n
		</text>
	</string> 
	
	<string id="st_af_monolith_name">
		<text>Volat Emerald</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_monolith_descr">
		<text>The origins of artefacts such as this one are a mystery, as they are rarely found outside the northernmost parts of the Zone.
		\nThis unique artefact projects a non-contact field that inhibits nearbly anomalous phenomena. This grants the wearer a notable level of protection against most of the Zone's environmental hazards. It is also one of the few active artefacts that can be safely handled without lead containers.
		However, when you hold it your flesh feels dry and flaky, your bones hard and stiff, the ligaments in your joints squeaky and brittle. Thick armour or great supernatural vitality would be needed by anyone intending to wear this artefact into battle.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_black_name">

		   <text>Black Stone</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_af_black_descr">

		   <text>Truly, an amazing thing. The Black Stone protects against broadly considered adversity but instead is slowly killing the owner. Some stalkers suspect the artefact is a shard of the Monolith.</text>
    </string>
	
	<!-- MLR -->
	<string id="st_af_misery_bread_name">
		<text>Anomalous bread</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_misery_bread_descr">
		<text>A piece of bread as dark as the soul of the person that left it.\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]PROPERTIES:\n%c[ui_white] • %c[ui_gray_2] artefact\n%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] attachable
				\n\n%c[0,209,172,56] Does NOT degrade over time.\n
		</text>
	</string>
</string_table>