<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<!--===========================================================
<
< TEXT  STRINGS FOR TASKS ON YANTAR MAP
<	CoC 1.4.08 - DoctorX Questlines 1.6
<
<	Modified by: DoctorX
<	Last revised: October 07, 2016
<
<===========================================================-->

<string_table>


	<!-- /////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////
	<!--
	<!-- STORYLINE TASK TEXT  STRINGS
	<!--
	<!--	Modified by DoctorX
	<!--	for DoctorX Questlines 1.6
	<!--	October 07, 2016
	<!--
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Sakharov (Ecologist) Default Storyline Task -->

	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_default_task_name">
		<text>Get Next Task</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_default_task_text">
		<text>Receive your next task.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_default_task_about">
		<text>What? Oh, yes, great! Stalker, I need you to help one of my colleagues. Go to him quickly! He needs you!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_default_task_finish">
		<text>Good luck stalker.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Sakharov (Ecologist) Research Documents Storyline Task -->

	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_1_name">
		<text>Sakharov Research Documents</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_1_text">
		<text>Some of Professor Sakharov's research papers were left behind when his scientist fled from a mutant attack. Retrieve the documents and return them to Sakharov.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_1_about">
		<text>Ah, yes, I'm glad you're here. One of my researchers just returned from the field. He had to abandon his notes after being attacked by mutants. He is terrified to go back there. I need that research, stalker. Please retrieve it for me, I will gladly compensate you for your trouble.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_1_finish">
		<text>Thank you stalker! Please, take this as your payment.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Sakharov (Ecologist) Abnormal Measurement Storyline Task -->

	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_2_name">
		<text>Abnormal Measurement</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_2_text_0">
		<text>Professor Sakharov asked your help in taking measurements of an abnormal anomaly, but you need to retrieve the $item_1 you lost first.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_2_text_1">
		<text>Professor Sakharov asked your help in taking measurements of an abnormal anomaly.\nHead over the marked location.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_2_text_2">
		<text>Professor Sakharov asked your help in taking measurements of an abnormal anomaly.\nUse the $item_1 to take measurements.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_2_text_3">
		<text>Professor Sakharov asked your help in taking measurements of an abnormal anomaly.\nReturn to him with the $item_1 and recorded results.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_2_about">
		<text>Ah, yes, good! I have been expecting you. Our scanners are showing interesting readings coming from a particular anomaly. I am in need of an experienced stalker to head over there and take measurements closely. I have the right device for you, young man. Good luck.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_2_finish">
		<text>Yes, good, good! Now my research can begin! Thank you stalker. You have done well.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Sakharov (Ecologist) Search Lab X-18 (Dark Valley) Storyline Task -->

	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_3_name">
		<text>Search Lab X-18</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_3_text">
		<text>Professor Sakharov needs the research documents contained within Lab X-18 in Dark Valley.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_3_about">
		<text>Oh, yes. Good! I have an important job for you. Important research was conducted in Lab X-18 but we have been unable to gain access to analyze it. Do you think you can try to retrieve it for us? I will pay you well if you can.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_3_finish">
		<text>Excellent! Thank you stalker!</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Sakharov (Ecologist) Plant Anomaly Scanner (Red Forest) Storyline Task -->

	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_4_name">
		<text>Plant the Scanner Near the Symbiont Anomaly</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_4_text">
		<text>Professor Sakharov wants the anomaly scanner to be planted near the Symbiont anomaly in Red Forest.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_4_text0">
		<text>Professor Sakharov wants the anomaly scanner to be planted near the Symbiont anomaly in Red Forest.\nGet an anomalous scanner first.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_4_text1_0">
		<text>Professor Sakharov wants the anomaly scanner to be planted near the Symbiont anomaly in Red Forest.\nTake the scanner to the anomalous field.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_4_text1_1">
		<text>Professor Sakharov wants the anomaly scanner to be planted near the Symbiont anomaly in Red Forest.\nTake the scanner to the anomalous field.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_4_text2">
		<text>Professor Sakharov wants the anomaly scanner to be planted near the Symbiont anomaly in Red Forest.\nPlace the scanner.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_4_text3">
		<text>Professor Sakharov wants the anomaly scanner to be planted near the Symbiont anomaly in Red Forest.\nReport on the implementation.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_4_about">
		<text>Splendid! Please take a look at this new scanner. We use these devices to scan anomalous acitivites during our scientific expeditions. One of the most interesting anomalies in the Zone is the Symbiont Anomaly, found deep inside the Red Forest. We want this scanner to be installed near that anomaly. It will help us to learn more about it's activity.
		\nThe location is dangerous, but hopefully it won't be an issue for a capable stalker like you. Please install it there for me, I will gladly compensate you for your trouble.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_4_finish">
		<text>Thank you! Now we can study that phenomenon!</text>
	</string>

	<!-- \\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\ -->


	<!-- /////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////
	<!--
	<!-- CHANGE FACTIONS TASK TEXT  STRINGS
	<!--
	<!--	Modified by DoctorX
	<!--	for DoctorX Questlines 1.6
	<!--	October 07, 2016
	<!--
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Sakharov (Ecologist Trader) Payoff Change Factions Task -->

	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_cf_task_1_name">
		<text>Science and Red Tape</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_cf_task_1_text">
		<text>Sakharov wants me to give him 17,000 RU so he can submit all the government paperwork needed for me to become an official Ecologist.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_cf_task_1_about">
		<text>Ah, well, I'm sure you'd make for a great field assistant, but, the thing is, getting all the necessary paperwork done isn't exactly cheap, nor is it quick without some, er, motivation. You know how these government types can be.\n \nPermanent contracts, licenses, IDs...I'll need at least 17,000 RU from you to pay for all this, especially if you want to see the results within your lifetime. If you're willing to part with such money, however, we'd gladly have you!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_cf_task_1_finish">
		<text>Wonderful! Excellent! Please, make yourself at home here, fellow Ecologist.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- \\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\ -->


	<!-- /////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////
	<!--
	<!-- DYNAMIC TASK TEXT  STRINGS
	<!--
	<!--	Modified by DoctorX
	<!--	for DoctorX Questlines 1.6
	<!--	October 07, 2016
	<!--
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Semenov (Ecog Honcho) Research Hunt Task -->

	<string id="yan_ecolog_semenov_task_1_name">
		<text>Semenov Research Hunt</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_ecolog_semenov_task_1_text">
		<text>Assistant Semenov has requested that I escort him around the local area so that he can retrieve fresh mutant tissue samples and analyse their corpses with his scanning equipment.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_ecolog_semenov_task_1_about">
		<text>Would you mind helping me eliminate a few mutants so that I can take readings and tissue samples? Let's say... about five different mutants. I'll be putting my life in your hands, and you would need to ensure my safety. I will compensate you for your efforts.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_ecolog_semenov_task_1_finish">
		<text>Thank you for your assistance, friend. I have all the tissue samples I need. Here is your payment. Come back and see me again some time.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Sakharov (Ecog Trader) -->
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_1_name">
		<text>Procure %s for the Yantar Bunker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_1_text">
		<text>Professor Sakharov's latest experiments require a fresh tissue sample from a %s. I should bring him one as soon as I find it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_1_about">
		<text>I need an experienced stalker or a mutant hunter. Is that somebody you?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_1_fetch_about">
		<text>I need to collect fresh cells from %s tissue samples. To do this, I'll need you to, eh, procure the sample and bring it back to my bunker here. I know zoologists won't favour this, but this place is not a zoo, one has to admit. In any case, make sure you return to me as soon as you have the required sample - it could provide valuable insight into the biology of mutant wildlife!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_1_fetch_finish">
		<text>Thank you, dear colleague. This will help immensely in my research.</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- Collect New Artefact Task -->
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_2_name">
		<text>Anomalous Research</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_2_text">
		<text>Professor Sakharov has asked me to find a %s artefact to help fund his research.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_2_about">
		<text>Would you like to assist me with some research? I will pay you for your efforts.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_2_fetch_about">
		<text>Our research team is near the brink of another significant discovery, but desperately needs more materials to maintain our funding and continue experimentation! Please, locate and deliver us one %s artefact. We'll need to take samples from it if we hope to continue our investigations and provide raw material for our suppliers.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_2_fetch_finish">
		<text>On behalf of the scientific community, I thank you. Here is your reward, as promised.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- Classified Information Task -->
	<string id="classified_information_task_name">
		<text>Classified Information</text>
	</string>
	<string id="classified_information_task_text">
		<text>The professor has asked me to obtain some sensitive research documents for him.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="classified_information_task_about">
		<text>Unknown brigands have accosted one of our research teams. Fortunately, part of the expedition came back alive and well. Unfortunately, they had to leave somewhat sensitive research behind during their escape.\n \nFor the sake of scientific progress, as well as the future wellbeing of my colleagues, I do not wish this data to remain lost - or worse, find their way into the hands of whatever mysterious group attacked my researchers. Please, go to the cache at these coordinates: if you hurry, the documents I wish to recover should still be there.  For your discretion, as well as the delivery of these documents to my office here, I offer a reasonable payment. As a further token of my gratitude, you may also help yourself to whatever supplies my team may have left behind in that cache. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="classified_information_task_finish">
		<text>Thank you, dear stalker. Or should I say colleague? Research can now continue smoothly - hopefully without any additional hiccups coming around the corner. </text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- yan_stalker_sakharov -->
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_psi_helmet_upgrade_name">
		<text>Collect the Psy-Helmet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_psi_helmet_upgrade_text">
		<text>Professor Sakharov has agreed to fully calibrate your psy-protection helmet. He has asked you to return to pick it up after about two days.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="brain_machine_deactivate_name">
		<text>Disable the Miracle Machine / Brain Lab to access Radar</text>
	</string>
	<string id="brain_machine_deactivate_text">
		<text>The Miracle Machine / Brain Lab seem to emit psy waves targeted at the Radar area. Psy emissions around the Miracle Machine are also blocking the scientists researches in Yantar. </text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Peregrine (Military Mechanic) Find Level 1 Toolkit Task -->

	<string id="mechanic_army_yan_mlr_task_1_name">
		<text>Find %s for Peregrine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mechanic_army_yan_mlr_task_1_text">
		<text>%s are required by Peregrine to install basic equipment upgrades, I should bring them back to him if I find any.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mechanic_army_yan_mlr_task_1_about">
		<text>Oh, sure. HQ notified us of tools arriving at our bunker via the Cordon, but the package never made it. And where did this delivery end up? Only the Zone knows. However, the situation hasn't changed, and we still need more tools. HQ is real obstinate about organising more for us right now, so I'll tell you what. If you manage to find some tools out in the wild - even some basic ones - I'll personally pay you to bring them back here. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="mechanic_army_yan_mlr_task_1_fetch_about">
		<text>Brilliant. Just focus on bringing back a set of basic tools for now - more advanced stuff is useless without them. Good hunting out there, stalker.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mechanic_army_yan_mlr_task_1_fetch_finish">
		<text>Alright, let's take a look. Yeah, these'll do. Now maybe I can do something other than maintenance. Here's your bounty. Thanks for your help.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="mechanic_army_yan_mlr_task_2_name">
		<text>Find %s for Peregrine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mechanic_army_yan_mlr_task_2_text">
		<text>%s are required by Peregrine to install advanced equipment upgrades, I should bring them back to him if I find any.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mechanic_army_yan_mlr_task_2_about">
		<text>Well, you're certainly more enterprising than my usual suppliers, so tell you what - get me a more advanced set of tools. Do this, and there'll be money in your pocket. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="mechanic_army_yan_mlr_task_2_fetch_about">
		<text>Fantastic. I'm sure Sakharov will appreciate this too.  I'm sure that, once you bring me these tools, my technical work will be helping him fund his bunker before you can blink.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mechanic_army_yan_mlr_task_2_fetch_finish">
		<text>Great! Come back any time if you need me to take a look at your gear. I'll be able to do some half-decent modifications now, thanks to you.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="mechanic_army_yan_mlr_task_3_name">
		<text>Find %s for Peregrine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mechanic_army_yan_mlr_task_3_text">
		<text>%s are required by Peregrine to install expert equipment upgrades, I should bring them back to him if I find any.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mechanic_army_yan_mlr_task_3_about">
		<text>I'm not sure if he's told you, but Sakharov is quite pleased that you're helping me out like this. He wanted me to tell you he's set aside a healthy sum of roubles for the stalker who can bring me a set of expert tools. It should let us get the most out of the scientific gear we keep here - particularly our hazmat suits and exoskeletons. So, are you willing to go toolkit hunting for me one last time? </text>
	</string>
	<string id="mechanic_army_yan_mlr_task_3_fetch_about">
		<text>I'm honestly grateful for this. When you get back with the tools, I'll also show you a trick or two on how to do proper field maintenance - unless another technician has taught you already, of course. It'll be my way of saying thanks. Good luck out there. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="mechanic_army_yan_mlr_task_3_fetch_finish">
		<text>Hm. Pity you don't work in the Supply Corps. Maybe now I can finally get that damn receiver fixed. As for you, you've earned my gratitude. On behalf of this bunker, here is your payment. </text>
	</string>
	
	
	
 	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_4_name">
		<text>Recover the Tracking Device</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_4_about">
		<text>We have implanted several devices on mutants to measure various data - heart rate, feeding habits, sleep cycles, travel times and the like. However, since the last blowout, one of the devices has started malfunctioning - it still tracks movement but has otherwise ceased to transmit any other useful data. As these trackers are of an especially advanced design, we must retrieve the faulty one for inspection and possible repairs.  Obtain the device from the mutant by any means available to you, then bring it back to us. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_4_stage_0">
		<text>Stop the mutant with the tracking device</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_4_stage_1">
		<text>Recover the tracking device</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_4_stage_2">
		<text>Return the device</text>
	</string>
	<string id="recover_mutant_data_device_desc">
		<text>A sturdy device that was planted on a mutant to monitor its movements, habits and vital signs. Shows signs of corrosion, and is covered in numerous bite and scratch marks.  </text>
	</string>
	<string id="recover_mutant_data_device_name">
		<text>Tracking device</text>
	</string>
</string_table>
