<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<string_table>
	<string id="st_wpn_g36new">
		<text>G36</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g36new_descr">
		<text>Created to replace the aging G3, the G36 continues to set the standard in the field of assault rifles with unprecedented reliability. Lightweight, accurate and simple in maintenance, it has found its way into the hands of various law enforcement agencies worldwide.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Germany\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Heckler &amp; Koch\n
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g36new_k">
		<text>G36K</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g36new_k_descr">
		<text>Created to replace the aging G3, the G36 continues to set the standard in the field of assault rifles with unprecedented reliability. Lightweight, accurate and simple in maintenance, it has found its way into the hands of various law enforcement agencies worldwide. The 'K' model features a shorter barrel and forend and includes a flash suppressor and bottom rail for attaching tactical accessories.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Germany\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Heckler &amp; Koch\n
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g36new_c">
		<text>G36C</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g36new_c_descr">
		<text>Created to replace the aging G3, the G36 continues to set the standard in the field of assault rifles with unprecedented reliability. Lightweight, accurate and simple in maintenance, it has found its way into the hands of various law enforcement agencies worldwide. The 'C' model features a shorter barrel, handguard and stock and includes a flash hider.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Germany\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Heckler &amp; Koch\n
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g36new_nimble">
		<text>G36 "FEAR"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_g36new_nimble_descr">
		<text>Created to replace the aging G3, the G36 continues to set the standard in the field of assault rifles with unprecedented reliability. Lightweight, accurate and simple in maintenance, it has found its way into the hands of various law enforcement agencies worldwide. This odd and unique model is similar to the G36K, but is much lighter with no reduction in accuracy or increase in recoil. The bolt has also been modified for increased rate of fire.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Germany\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Heckler &amp; Koch\n
		</text>
	</string>

</string_table>