<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>

<!-- (Military Mechanic) -->
	<string id="army_yan_mec_about_tool_0">
		<text>Hey. Who are you?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="army_yan_mec_about_tool_1">
		<text>I'm a transfer from the local military, callsign "Peregrine". I was studying as an engineer before my conscription. HQ eventually noticed my knack for fixing things and decided I'd be a lot more useful out here, helping to maintain scientific equipment. The head professor, Sakharov I think, clearly agreed. Come to think of it - he was even a little relieved. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="army_yan_mec_about_tool_2">
		<text>So you're the bunker's new technician? What has that been like so far?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="army_yan_mec_about_tool_3">
		<text>Eh, it beats being stuck at HQ, having an angry CO breathing down your neck all the time, or going on patrol with standing orders to shoot desperate folk in the face.\n \nBut, to be honest with you, it's still pretty shit. Thanks to the outstanding dedication of our Supply Corps, I need to argue until I'm blue in the face merely to maintain what we currently have. The esoteric equipment the Ecologists keep here isn't exactly easy to sustain with what's available, let alone upgrade or adapt to the Zone's ever-changing conditions.\n \nI tried to get the old receiver here repaired, but all it does is spout a bunch of gibberish. Our guys at the Army Warehouses kicked the bucket seven years ago, but this damn machine still thinks it can hear their voices.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="army_yan_mec_about_tool_4">
		<text>Best of luck to you, then.</text>
	</string>

	
<!-- (Military Cooker) -->
	<string id="meet_povar_army_0">
		<text>Who are you?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="meet_povar_army_1">
		<text>The local cook, I guess. On paper, I'm actually a field asssistant for the Ecologists here. In practice...well, it's been a few months since they sent me out, and I get the feeling I'm not going to be going anywhere any time soon. Anyway, they call me Spirit.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="meet_povar_army_2">
		<text>Why don't they send you out into the field anymore?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="meet_povar_army_3">
		<text>Just a little misunderstanding. The other field assistants around here think I'm an alcoholic. I mean, really? In this day and age, you'd have to be insane *not* to drink. You think the snorks around here are bad? My friend, Topol, works at a bunker just a short walk from Pripyat! I heard about the Monolith's return and... no, I don't want to think about it. Look, if you happen to get your hands on any Nemiroff, I can hook you up with some good stuff. What do you say?
		\nI can offer you four 9x18 mags, two mags of 5.45, two mags of 5.56 or two mags of 9x39 for five swigs of Nemiroff.
		\nFor ten swigs, I can share one mag of 7.62mm 7N1, three boxes of 12x70 shot rounds, four mags of 5.45, four mags of 5.56 or four mags of 9x39, your choice.
		\nFor fifteen swigs - that's about five full bottles - AND 7000 RU, you get ninety 7.62x54 mm PP rounds. They are quite expensive you know...
		\nAnd for twenty swigs, just under seven full bottles, I'll get you a set of basic tools. Don't think I'm a scoundrel - I didn't steal it, it was just lying around in a tent near Cordon a while back. I kept them since that day. This come handy for a stalker like you. Anyways, don't think I'm doing all this business all for myself. I try to get most of the bottles shipped up to Yanov for the boys.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="meet_povar_army_4">
		<text>I'll consider it. Thank you.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="barter_povar_army_0">
		<text>I've brought some vodka.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barter_povar_army_1">
		<text>That's great! Is there anything particular you want?</text>
	</string>
		<string id="barter_povar_army_2">
			<text>Four 9x18 mags.</text>
		</string>
		<string id="barter_povar_army_3">
			<text>Two 5.45 mags.</text>
		</string>
		<string id="barter_povar_army_3_2">
			<text>Two 5.56 mags.</text>
		</string>
		<string id="barter_povar_army_3_3">
			<text>Two 9x39 mags.</text>
		</string>
		<string id="barter_povar_army_4">
			<text>Four 5.45 mags.</text>
		</string>
		<string id="barter_povar_army_4_2">
			<text>Four 5.56 mags.</text>
		</string>
		<string id="barter_povar_army_4_3">
			<text>Four 9x39 mags.</text>
		</string>
		<string id="barter_povar_army_5">
			<text>Three buckshot boxes.</text>
		</string>
		<string id="barter_povar_army_6">
			<text>One mag of 7.62 7N1.</text>
		</string>
		<string id="barter_povar_army_7">
			<text>Three boxes for the PKP.</text>
		</string>
		<string id="barter_povar_army_8">
			<text>A basic toolkit.</text>
		</string>
	<string id="barter_povar_army_10">
		<text>Great. Here you go.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barter_povar_army_11">
		<text>Alrighty then. Here.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barter_povar_army_12">
		<text>Hmm. Fair enough. Here's your stuff.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barter_povar_army_13">
		<text>Hah! Happy hunting, stalker!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barter_povar_army_14">
		<text>Hmm. Good choice.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barter_povar_army_15">
		<text>Can't wait to hear the sweet music your shooter will play with these in its belly.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barter_povar_army_16">
		<text>Here you go.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="barter_povar_army_9">
		<text>Here, enjoy. I know I will.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="remember_dyx_barter_0">
		<text>Remind me, what do you have?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="remember_dyx_barter_1">
		<text>This is what I've got: four mags of 9x18 for five swigs of Nemiroff, two 5.45x39 mags for five swigs, two 5.56x45 mags for five swigs, two 9x39 mags for five swigs, four 5.45x39 mags for ten swigs, four 5.56x45 mags for ten swigs, four 9x39 mags for ten swigs,  three packs of 12x70 for ten swigs, one mag of 7.62x54 7N1 for ten swigs, three box mags for the PKP for five full bottles and seven thousand rubles. For twenty swigs, just under seven full bottles, I'll get you a set of basic tools. Don't think I'm a scoundrel - I didn't steal it... They were just lying around in a tent near Cordon a while back. I kept them since that day. This come will handy for a stalker like you.</text>
	</string>


<!-- Kruglov -->
	<string id="yan_ecolog_kruglov_start_dialog_1">
		<text>Greetings, stalker.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- yan_ecolog_semenov -->
	<string id="yan_ecolog_semenov_start_dialog_1">
		<text>Ah, stalker, what do you need?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_ecolog_semenov_start_dialog_yan_ecolog_semenov_task_1">
		<text>I still have more data to collect. Let's go find some more mutants.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- yan_ecolog_vasilyev -->
	<string id="yan_ecolog_vasilyev_start_dialog_1">
		<text>Greetings, stalker.</text>
	</string>
	

<!-- Sakharov -->
	<string id="st_yan_saharov_message_free_upgrade">
		<text>Stalker, you saved us! Our bunker would have met certain doom if you didn't step in to help. To show my gratitude, come to me for a free upgrade to your psy-helmet!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_start_1">
		<text>Hello, stalker. What brings you here?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_player_query_brain_scorcher">
		<text>What can you tell me about the Brain Scorcher and the Miracle Machine?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_npc_query_brain_scorcher">
		<text>Hmm, well...we still have much to learn, but I suppose it won't hurt to share what little we know with you. The Brain Scorcher seems to emit an invasive frequency that affects the mind of any who journey too close to Pripyat's center, the NPP or the wrong side of the Red Forest or even Limansk. The symptoms include migraines, hallucinations, tunnel vision, and without sounding unprofessional, zombification. If I had to give a scientific estimation, I'd identify the Brain Scorcher as a remote psy-transmitter, though I'd have to conduct more invasive research before fully settling on that conclusion. The Miracle Machine or "Brain Lab" has very similar features and emit psy waves, however their nature seems more akin to biologically emitted psy waves, like the ones certain mutants can exhibit.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_player_query_psi_helmet">
		<text>Professor, I need a psy-protection helmet. My task requires me to move through the Brain Scorcher's and the Brain Lab's areas, and without it, I won't be able to complete it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_npc_query_psi_helmet">
		<text>I assume you understand the risk of going through these psychically volatile areas, do you?... Oh, all right, I believe you do. You wouldn't ask me about it otherwise. Well, there is this psy-protective helmet we've been working on carefully the past few weeks. On paper, everything should work and it has been properly calibrated for the Miracle Machine and Brain Scorcher psy emissions. However, no one has been crazy enough to field test it... Well there was this one assistant that tried an early, uncalibrated, model... But that's a story for another time.\n\n We could grant you this psy-helmet immediately as it is for the modest sum of 30,000 Roubles.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_npc_query_psi_helmet_free">
		<text>I assume you understand the risk of going through these psychically volatile areas, do you?... Oh, all right, I believe you do. You wouldn't ask me about it otherwise. Well, there has been this one model we've been working on carefully, but it remains unfinished, and it lacks final calibrations.\n \nIt should protect you from ambient psy-emissions, but I cannot stress this enough: you would be risking your life with incomplete hardware.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_player_psi_helmet_1_1">
		<text>I'm in a hurry. Your prototype will have to do.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_npc_psi_helmet_1_1">
		<text>If you insist, although I fear your task will prove too dangerous for equipment that is not in perfect operational condition. Do not forget: you can always bring your helmet back to us for a final calibration. If you feel something is wrong, turn back immediately. Psy-fields can be treacherous, and it wouldn't rest well on my conscience if I hear you die to one later, all thanks to my unfinished work.\n \nNow, if you're positive you do not want me to finish tweaking this model, that will be 20,000 Roubles.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_player_psi_helmet_1_2">
		<text>Here's the money. Thank you, professor.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_npc_psi_helmet_1_2">
		<text>Not at all. But I would like you to test it first. You can help us by disabling the psy-emitter in the laboratory just north of here. Let's hope it will guard your consciousness well.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_player_psi_helmet_1_3">
		<text>I've decided to let you finish your work. Please calibrate this helmet thoroughly.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_npc_psi_helmet_1_3">
		<text>You don't know what relief this brings to me and my colleagues. Letting us finish the final calibrations will considerably reduce the risk of you procuring psychosis, amnesia or general insanity while exploring the Zone's psychic phenomena. As you've already provided financial aid to our cause, a final calibration will only cost you about 10,000 Roubles. You'll need to part with your helmet, however, and we'll need an additional two days to complete the finishing touches.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_player_psi_helmet_2_1">
		<text>That device had better be working, or I will come eat you alive once I am zombified Professor, I swear...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_npc_psi_helmet_2_1">
		<text>Indeed it should be working. By wearing this light device you'll be able to wander around the Miracle Machine and the Brain Scorcher without suffering the risk of mental degradation from any of their respective psy emissions. However, I am not sure it is able to help you get past the Psy barrier of both the Brain Scorcher and the Miracle Machine combined which operates past the Red Forest. Keep in mind that from our latest measures, the device will not protect you from other psy waves, like the ones emitted by phantoms which can be encountered near the Miracle Machine from what my assistants reported. Their frequencies are way too diverse to be countered by such device, artefacts are the only way it seems... or unhealthy amounts of mind-numbing drugs. Maybe Freedomers can help you with the latter?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_npc_psi_helmet_2_1_free">
		<text>Indeed it will be. Once we finish working on this helmet, you'll be able to wander around the Zone freely, without suffering the risk of mental degradation from any psy-emitters you might encounter in your journeys. Ordinarily, the cost would be 30,000 Roubles, but since you have aided us in a dire time, I can confidently hand you this device free of charge. Use it well.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_player_psi_helmet_2_2">
		<text>Alright, here is the money Professor. About the drugs and the artefacts, I'll keep that in mind, thanks a lot.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_npc_psi_helmet_2_2">
		<text>Thank you, stalker. Here is the device. Good luck on your endeavor. Your help in disabling the Miracle Machine and the Brain Scorcher is precious and will grealty help us in our research.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_player_psi_helmet_2_3">
		<text>Is it ready yet?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_npc_psi_helmet_2_3">
		<text>It is! Here you go. If you wish, you can help us further by using your new device to disable the psy-emitter in the laboratory complex just north of here. I can say with confidence that our work shall guard your consciousness well.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_npc_psi_helmet_2_3_1">
		<text>Not yet. Please come back later.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_player_psi_helmet_3_1">
		<text>I need to think about it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_npc_psi_helmet_3_1">
		<text>Very well. Do not worry, we will hold onto the psy-helmet for safekeeping in the meantime.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_yan_stalker_sakharov_life_ask">
		<text>Can you tell me how the Zone has helped you in your scientific research, professor?  </text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_yan_stalker_sakharov_life_1">
		<text>Why certainly! The Night Star artefact, regardless of its properties when found in the wild, begins to take on curious anti-ballistic traits when exposed to the correct lab conditions. In a few years, we may see spectacular advancements in technologies like body armour or kevlar plates.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_yan_stalker_sakharov_life_2">
		<text>Oh, yes! Examining tissue samples from the various humanoid mutants has been an enlightening practice. The scientific community at large is still unsure what caused the bloodsucker to develop invisibility, or the snork to evolve its renowned flexibility. The more we learn about the cause and nature of these mutations, the more accurately we will be able to predict Humanity's evolutionary path! Is that not exciting?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_yan_stalker_sakharov_life_3">
		<text>Well, recently we conducted a fascinating series of experiments on bloodsuckers, which revealed that - actually, on second thought, it's probably better you don't know.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_yan_stalker_sakharov_life_4">
		<text>As an intellectual, you might appreciate this: our research has discovered that the so-called "eye" of the Flesh is equipped not only with photoreceptors... but also with olfactory receptors!\n \nThey not only see with their eyes - they smell with them too!\n \nWho would've thought that the common pig would one day mutate into a creature hard-wired with a most unusual form of synesthesia? One that is not merely caused by cross-wiring in the brain, but by alterations to their sense organs!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_yan_stalker_sakharov_life_5">
		<text>Of course! After years of studying various mutant parts, we're getting close to commercializing organs and tissues such as Flesh eyes,  Snork tendons or Pseudogiant muscle fibres for more, eh, controversial purposes. Have you seen the latest sample batch? We've been surgically transplanting as many as we can onto all our, well - all our voluntary assistants. With further development, we could start a craze!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_yan_stalker_sakharov_life_6">
		<text>To say the Zone has helped in my research would be an understatement.  The discoveries we've made have advanced my credibility as a scientist significantly. Perhaps one of my greatest achievements was a collaborative effort: with my colleagues, we successfully synthesized a rare Pellicle artefact under controlled lab conditions - truly a breakthrough deserving of the Nobel Prize!\n \nUnfortunately, the nature of artefacts have been evolving independently since then, as if to resist our investigations. Despite our stellar accomplishment, it'll be quite some time before we can efficiently synthesize more powerful artefacts again.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_yan_stalker_sakharov_life_7">
		<text>Well, there's this one colleague of mine - a Professor Brenter - who has been quite keen in his studies of the effect of mutated proteins on the human body. By studying the stalkers who have eaten mutant meat - such as the patrons at the 100 Rads Bar  - and documenting what they do to stave off the worst of its ill effects, our insight into countering the harm that radiation leaves on the body is increasing.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_yan_stalker_sakharov_life_8">
		<text>Why, yes! Have you heard of the Urchin artefact? Initially, we thought it'd be unrealistic to reproduce such a wonder under lab conditions until at least 2022, thanks to its critical stability. We may crack the secret ahead of schedule, however.\n \nThe timing couldn't be better: they are becoming increasingly difficult to find naturally in the Zone, and each one is vital for creating potent anti-radiation outfits and medication.\n \nYou've likely benefitted from the results of our Urchin experiments several times over, come to think of it. It's challenging to think of any professional Zone explorer who hasn't used our advanced radioprotective suits and serums at some point in their lives. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_yan_stalker_sakharov_life_9">
		<text>What? I'm sorry, but I do not wish to keep discussing the wonders of the Zone today. My nerves feel shot from all the screeching and clawing I heard from the local mutants last night, and I can barely concentrate.\n \nPerhaps you may be interested in purchasing scientific gear, or seeing if any of my colleagues need help?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_yan_stalker_sakharov_life_10">
		<text>Many years ago, our understanding of gravity was such that we were able to begin developing the very first repulsor and ion drives.\n \nWithout the steady stream of artefacts that stalkers brought in from gravity-based anomalies, however, such revelations would never have been possible in our lifetime. It'll be many more years before our discoveries become open to the public, but it is undeniable that stalkers have helped science pave its way back to the stars!\n \nAnd I dare say, as some gravity anomalies - such as the Vortex - are known by the scientific community to squeeze space itself, maybe teleportation will also cease to be a fantasy in time! Ah, but I get ahead of myself. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_yan_stalker_sakharov_life_11">
		<text>The field of energetics has benefitted considerably from our research in the Zone. We have begun to unobtrusively introduce Moonlight artefacts - as well as specialised devices designed to safely harness the anomalous energy output  - into select power stations across the country. With further refinement, they could potentially replace fossil fuels entirely for future generations.\n \nIn time, we may attempt the same with the far more potent Battery type artefacts. However, my colleagues estimate that even a single Battery is capable of power output exceeding that of three nuclear reactors! Naturally, when dealing with such awesome power, we must be slow and cautious in our experiments.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_yan_stalker_sakharov_life_end">
		<text>Hmm? Perhaps later, young one. I'm sure you have more pressing matters to attend to now.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- yan_merc_guards -->
	<string id="yan_merc_guards_start_2">
		<text>Not right now, I'm on duty. Rather talk to Peregrine or one of the eggheads if you need anything.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_merc_guards_start_3">
		<text>Make it quick. I don't want the snorks to catch us having a fat chat.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_merc_guards_start_4">
		<text>That humming from the complex up north is making my teeth itch. Wish the damn chef didn't keep drinking all the damn booze...</text>
	</string>
</string_table>
