<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
    <string id="ah_ecolog">
        <text>Explorers</text>
    </string>

    <string id="Quest1_desc">
        <text>Quest Description</text>
    </string>
    <string id="Quest1_title">
        <text>First quest title</text>
    </string>
    
    <string id="ah_redirect_to_kovalev_quest_title">
        <text>Explorers: Find Prof. Kovalev in The Great Swamps</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_redirect_to_kovalev_quest_desc">
        <text>I have received information that Prof. Kovalev in the Great Swamps needs help in his research. I should look for him in the Old Church in the South of the swamps.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="ah_redirect_to_markov_quest_title">
        <text>Explorers: Find Prof. Markov in Yantar</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_redirect_to_markov_quest_desc">
        <text>Next, I should find Prof. Markov. He should be somewhere close to the scientists' bunker in Yanov.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="ah_redirect_to_pirogov_quest_title">
        <text>Researchers: Find Dr. Pirogov</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_redirect_to_pirogov_quest_desc">
        <text>Dr. Priogov has been tasked with investigating the Dark Valley. I should check if he is still alive.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="ah_redirect_to_chernov_quest_title">
        <text>Researchers: Find Prof. Chernov</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_redirect_to_chernov_quest_desc">
        <text> Now I need to find Senior Prof. Chernov, who was last seen in an abandoned shack in the North of Army Warehouses.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="ah_redirect_to_juk_quest_title">
        <text>Explorers: Find Professor Zhuk</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_redirect_to_juk_quest_desc">
        <text>For more work I should talk to Prof. Zhuk. I can find him somewhere near Yanov Train Station in Jupiter. </text>
    </string>   

    <string id="ah_redirect_to_vorobushkin_quest_title">
        <text>Explorers: Find Prof. Vorobushkin</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_redirect_to_vorobushkin_quest_desc">
        <text>Prof. Vorobushkin is stationed at the Ranger Station. I need to find him in order to continue helping the research team. </text>
    </string>   

    <string id="ah_redirect_to_skabinsky_quest_title">
        <text>Researchers: Find Prof. Skabinsky</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_redirect_to_skabinsky_quest_desc">
        <text>Prof. Vorobushkin told me, that the head of the operation, Prof. Skabinsky, has already gone further ahead and is currently somewhere in the northern part of the CNPP. I don't know how he managed to get there, but I need to find him fast.</text>
    </string>       

    <string id="ah_fail_skabinsky_quest_title">
        <text>Researchers: Find Prof. Skabinsky.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_fail_skabinsky_quest_desc">
        <text>Prof. Vorobushkin's calculations are still full of holes, though they seem to point towards the Ashes anomaly. I need to find Prof. Skabinsky, who has already went ahead and is waiting for me there.</text>
    </string>   
    
    <string id="ah_kovalev_quest1_title">
        <text>Researchers: Bring Prof. Kovalev three anomalous samples</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_kovalev_quest1_desc">
        <text>The research team in the swamps is currently searching for samples from some anomalous fields. Prof. Kovalev asked me to check out three of them.</text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_bol_o1_title">
        <text>Find a sample in the Fermi anomaly.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_bol_o1_desc">
        <text>One of the samples is located in Fermi Anomaly.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_bol_o2_title">
        <text>Find a sample in the Swamp Ravine anomaly.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_bol_o2_desc">
        <text>One of the samples is located in the anomaly Swamp Ravine.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_bol_g1_title">
        <text>Find a sample in the Bog Pounder anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_bol_g1_desc">
        <text>One of the samples is located in the Bog Punder anomaly.</text>
    </string>       
    
    <string id="ah_bol_e1_title">
        <text>Find a sample in the Thunderclap anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_bol_e1_desc">
        <text>One of the samples is located in the Thunderclap anomaly.</text>
    </string>   

    <string id="ah_kovalev_quest2_title">
        <text>Researchers: Bring Prof. Kovalev his laptop and three anomalous samples</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_kovalev_quest2_desc">
        <text>Prof. Kovalev conducted field research in Agroprom, but his team was ambushed during his work. I need to find the laptop he left at the site of the attack and check the data on it. It should tell me, which anomalies I should scan for samples.</text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_agr_pda_title">
        <text>Find Kovalev's Laptop near the Nerve Wrecker anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_agr_pda_desc">
        <text>The laptop is supposed to be on the second floor of the building the scientists were attacked at. I will need to navigate through the electric anomalies and psy-field to get it.</text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_agr_none_title">
        <text>Find the sample. Location unknown.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_agr_none_desc">
        <text>The exact location can be found on Kovalev's laptop.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_agr_g1_title">
        <text>Find the sample in the Bedrock Claws anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_agr_g1_desc">
        <text>A strange gravitational anomaly. It looks climbable.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_agr_g2_title">
        <text>Find the sample in the Bushwacker anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_agr_g2_desc">
        <text>One of the samples is located in the Bushwacker anomaly.</text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_agr_h1_title">
        <text>Find the sample in the Dog Mincer anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_agr_h1_desc">
        <text>One of the samples is located in the Dog Mincer anomaly.</text>
    </string>   

    <string id="ah_markov_quest1_title">
        <text>Researchers: Bring Prof. Markov three anomalous samples</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_markov_quest1_desc">
        <text>Prof. Markov in Yantar has asked me to scan three anomalies with my scanner and keep an eye out for any unusual artifacts I can find.</text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_yan_o1_title">
        <text>Find the sample in the Bonfire anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_yan_o1_desc">
        <text>One of the samples is located in the Bonfire anomaly.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_yan_h1_title">
        <text>Find the sample in the Blackwater anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_yan_h1_desc">
        <text>One of the samples is located in the Blackwater anomaly.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_yan_h2_title">
        <text>Find the sample in the Concrete Dump anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_yan_h2_desc">
        <text>One of the samples is located in the Concrete Dump anomaly. I will need some protection from the psy-field in the area to get it.</text>
    </string>       
    
    <string id="ah_markov_quest2_title">
        <text>Explorers: Bring Markov three artifacts from the Wild Territory.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_markov_quest2_desc">
        <text>Prof. Markov has tasked me with expanding the current search area. I am supposed to scan three different locations in the Wild Territory.</text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_dt_o1_title">
        <text>Find the sample in the Radioactive Workshop</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_dt_o1_desc">
        <text>This anomaly is not listed on the map. I can find the workshop just before the checkpoint in front of Rostok and it is highly radioactive.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_dt_e1_title">
        <text>Find the sample in the Crispy Train anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_dt_e1_desc">
        <text> This anomaly is electric, so I should remember to bring enough bolts.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_dt_e2_title">
        <text>Find the sample in the Sparkle Deadlock anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_dt_e2_desc">
        <text>This anomaly is in an underground tunnel. I heard, that there is a safe path through it...</text>
    </string>   

    <string id="ah_markov_quest3_title">
        <text>Explorers: Bring Prof. Markov three Artifacts from the area around Lab X16</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_markov_quest3_desc">
        <text>I am supposed to find three artifacts close to the area around the old X16 lab. Because of the Miracle Machine, this will be impossible without proper psy-protection. Prof. Sakharov should be able to help me with that.</text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_yan_e1_title">
        <text>Find the sample in the Tesla anomaly.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_yan_e1_desc">
        <text>This is an electro anomaly, so I should bring enough bolts.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_yan_e2_title">
        <text>Find the sample in the Edison anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_yan_e2_desc">
        <text>My scanner should help me find it.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_yan_g1_title">
        <text>Find the sample somewhere in the factory</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_yan_g1_desc">
        <text>None of the researchers have gone this far into the compound, however scans indicate strong anomalous activity. I should be careful.</text>
    </string>   

    <string id="ah_pirogov_quest1_title">
        <text>Researchers: Bring Candidate Pirogov three anomalous samples from the Dark Valley</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_pirogov_quest1_desc">
        <text>Prof. Pirogov has asked me to check out three different anomalies for him in the Dark Valley. I should be careful, as mutants and bandits roam this area frequently.</text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_td_o1_title">
        <text>Find the sample in the Tunnel with the Comet anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_td_o1_desc">
        <text>A curious anomaly that few people have explored. It is located at the end of the long tunnel with the Comet anomaly inside. The entrance is close to the bandits base to the north.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_td_o2_title">
        <text>Find an artifact in the Glowing Pit anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_td_o2_desc">
        <text>My scanner should help me find it.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_td_e1_title">
        <text>Find an artifact in the Bubble Bath anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_td_e1_desc">
        <text>The Bubble Bath Anomaly is located within the bandit base, so unless I want to rile up every bandit in there, I should try to sneak my way in.</text>
    </string>       
    
    <string id="ah_pirogov_quest2_title">
        <text>Researchers: Bring candidate Pirogov three samples from the Truck Cemetery</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_pirogov_quest2_desc">
        <text>Going further north, Pirogov has asked me to check out the Truck Cemetery. Much like the Dark Valley, the area is teeming with mutants and bandits.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_kt_g1_title">
        <text>Find the sample in the Bus Furrow anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_kt_g1_desc">
        <text>My scanner should help me find it.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_kt_o1_title">
        <text>Find the sample in the Charcoal Abode anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_kt_o1_desc">
        <text>One of the samples is located in the Charcoal Abode anomaly.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_kt_h1_title">
        <text>Find the sample at the Thorn Bath anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_kt_h1_desc">
        <text>One of the samples is located in the Thorn Bath anomaly.</text>
    </string>   

    <string id="ah_pirogov_quest3_title">
        <text>Researchers: Bring candidate Pirogov the assistant's PDA and two anomalous samples</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_pirogov_quest3_desc">
        <text>Pirogov's assistant, who was studying the anomalies in the Garbage before me, is missing. On his PDA, however, was the scan data for all of the anomalies in the area. I need to find the assistant, retrieve the data and get the samples from the anomalies in question.</text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_sv_pda_title">
        <text>Find the Pirogov's missing assistant</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_sv_pda_desc">
        <text>Most likely the stalker got ambushed by bandits. I was told that his last radio call was from the Flea Market, so I should start my search there.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_sv_g1_title">
        <text>Find the sample in the Witche's Jelly anomaly.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_sv_g1_desc">
        <text>A rather large and toxic anomaly. This one will be tricky.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_sv_h1_title">
        <text>Find the sample in the Synapse anomaly.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_sv_h1_desc">
        <text>My scanner should help me find it.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_sv_none_title">
        <text>Retrieve the scan data from the missing stalker's PDA</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_sv_none_desc">
        <text>The scan data required to find the anomalies in question is on the PDA of the missing stalker. I need to find him.</text>
    </string>       
    
    <string id="ah_chernov_quest1_title">
        <text>Explorers: Bring Prof. Chernov three artifacts from the Army Warehouses</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_chernov_quest1_desc">
        <text>I need to find three different artifacts and bring them to Prof. Chernov. This will be a real test of skill, as the Army Warehouses is a dangerous area.</text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_mil_h1_title">
        <text>Find the sample in the Corpse Disposer anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_mil_h1_desc">
        <text>My scanner should help me find it.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_mil_g1_title">
        <text>Find the sample in the Masher anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_mil_g1_desc">
        <text>One of the samples is located in the Masher anomaly.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_mil_o1_title">
        <text>Find the sample in the burning House, close to the Hell's Walls anomaly.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_mil_o1_desc">
        <text>A fierce place, radiating strong heat and riddled with burner mines. It is not directly marked on my map, but I should get out as fast as possible, once I have the sample.</text>
    </string>   
    
    <string id="ah_chernov_quest3_title">
        <text>Explorers: Bring Chernov the stalker's PDA and the two samples from the Red Forest</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_chernov_quest3_desc">
        <text>Prof. Chernov has tasked a particular stalker with mapping the anomalies in the Red Forest. He finished the map but had to flee the area before he could return the data. I am supposed to find his PDA, which was left behind somehwere in the tunnels by the bridge to Limansk.</text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_les_pda_title">
        <text>Find the stalker's PDA in the tunnels to the West.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_les_pda_desc">
        <text>While fleeing from Monolith fanatics, the stalker left his PDA with the scan data somehwere is the Western tunnels. I need to find it, before I know which anomalies to investigate.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_les_o1_title">
        <text>Find a sample in the Symbiont anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_les_o1_desc">
        <text>After analyzing the scan data, this seems to be one of the sites of interest.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_les_e1_title">
        <text>Find a sample in the underground electro anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_les_e1_desc">
        <text>After analyzing the data, there seems to be a hidden underground anomaly in the North-West mine shafts. I should investigate.</text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_les_none_title">
        <text>Find the artifact somewhere in the Red Forest</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_les_none_desc">
        <text>I am supposed to find two different artifacts in the Red Forest. However, to pinpoint their location, I need to find the PDA with the scan data, that the stalker before me lost somewhere in the Western tunnels.</text>
    </string>       
    
    <string id="ah_chernov_quest4_title">
        <text>Explorers: Find the artificial artifact</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_chernov_quest4_desc">
        <text>According to Chernov, he and his colleague managed to create an artifact artificially, even before the disaster. I should head to the home of his former colleague and see, if the artifact is still there. There is an anomalous field near his house now, which is probably no coincidence. I should be careful.</text>
    </string>   
    
    <string id="ah_chernov_quest5_title">
        <text>Explorers: Visit lab X-19</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_chernov_quest5_desc">
        <text>The X-19 lab, also known as "Bunker", apparently was engaged in the creation of artificial artifacts. The lab is now destroyed, but perhaps I can find some leftover documents. They might just tell us where to find these "artifact farms".  </text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_rad_pda_title">
        <text>Search the entrance of X-19.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_rad_pda_desc">
        <text>I should search the area for anything that can point me towards these "artifact beds". I think I saw a bundle of documents somewhere at the entrance.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_rad_r_title">
        <text>Find three artifical samples in the Deadwood, south of the X19 complex.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_rad_r_desc">
        <text>According to the documents I found, artifacts were grown in the forest south of the complex. It will be a wide search, but I need to scan the whole forest for these samples.</text>
    </string>       

    <string id="ah_chernov_quest6_title">
        <text>Researchers: Find two artifacts in the Dead City</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_chernov_quest6_desc">
        <text>Prof. Chernov has asked me for help in completing the map of anomalies in the Zone by conducting scans in the unexplored Dead City. He has given me the approximate coordinates of the two anomalies he is interested in.</text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_mg_o1_title">
        <text>Find the sample in Administration building.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_mg_o1_desc">
        <text>My scanner should help me find it.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_mg_g1_title">
        <text>Find the sample in the House of Culture.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_mg_g1_desc">
        <text>My scanner should help me find it.</text>
    </string>       

    <string id="ah_juk_quest1_title">
        <text>Researchers: Find three anomalous samples in Jupiter</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_juk_quest1_desc">
        <text>Professor Zhuk is trying to make a spectrogram of samples from the different kind of anomalies in Jupiter. He has tasked me with finding samples from three different anomalies.</text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_up_g1_title">
        <text>Find the sample in the Bitumen anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_up_g1_desc">
        <text>Another heat anomaly that will need proper protection to be navigated in.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_up_h1_title">
        <text>Find the sample in the Concrete Bath anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_up_h1_desc">
        <text>I heard that stalkers jump onto the cement pillars to avoid the acid pools below.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_up_h2_title">
        <text>Find the sample in the Anomalous Grove</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_up_h2_desc">
        <text>This toxic anomaly will require some adequate protection.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="ah_juk_quest2_title">
        <text>Researchers: Find the remaining samples for Prof. Zhuk</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_juk_quest2_desc">
        <text>For the second batch of samples, I need to scan the rest of the anomalies in the area. Prof. Zhuk gave me their exact locations.</text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_up_e2_title">
        <text>Find an artifact in the anomalous Train</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_up_e2_desc">
        <text>This unmarked electro anomaly seems trapped inside a train cart close to the scientists' bunker. I remember these carts having an escape hatch on the roof, which I could use to get in.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_up_e1_title">
        <text>Find an artifact in the Northwestern tunnel</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_up_e1_desc">
        <text>This tunnel is poorly explored, therefore it is particularly interesting. However, I heard a rumor that controllers like to roam these tunnels.. </text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_up_g2_title">
        <text>Find an artifact in the "Volkhov" complex</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_up_g2_desc">
        <text>The old anti-aircraft missile complex is abandoned because of the abundance of underground anomalies. It's also a hotspot for mutants, so I should keep my eyes peeled.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="ah_juk_quest3_title">
        <text>Explorers: Find four anomalous samples in Pripyat and Outskirts</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_juk_quest3_desc">
        <text>The city of Pripyat is practically inaccessible for the scientists, due to the presence of Monolith. However, to complete their research, samples from the anomalies in the city are essential. I must find them. </text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_p_h1_title">
        <text>Find the sample in the Vine anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_p_h1_desc">
        <text>"Vine" is the most fascinating anomaly in the outskirts of Pripyat. I am supposed to climb it and look for a sample at the top of the anomaly.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_p_g1_title">
        <text>Find the sample in the School</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_p_g1_desc">
        <text>There is a giant gravitational anomaly in the middle of the old school. It reaches up multiple floors, so I might need to check inside the building.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_p_g2_title">
        <text>Find the sample in the Vanguard anomaly.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_p_g2_desc">
        <text>The readings are off the charts for this place. Even at a distance of several kilometers, the scientists could detect multiple kinds anomalies. I must scan the area for a sample.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_p_e1_title">
        <text>Find the sample in the unmarked electro anomaly.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_p_e1_desc">
        <text>There is another unmarked anomaly in the southern parts of Pripyat. I should scan it, too.</text>
    </string>   
    
    <string id="ah_vorobushkin_quest1_title">
        <text>Researchers: Find Vorobushkin's Memory Module and three anomalous samples</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_vorobushkin_quest1_desc">
        <text>Prof. Vorobushkin managed to repair and use some of the old equipment of the old Krug Antenna Complex. He left his memory module there, which contains the locations of the anomalies I need to search for samples.</text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_zat_pda_title">
        <text>Find the memory module VNZ "Circle"</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_zat_pda_desc">
        <text>Prof. Vorobushkin left the module in the underground parts of the complex when he left. I need to find it, if I want to know which anomalies I need to scan.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_zat_h1_title">
        <text>Find the sample in the anomaly Swamp</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_zat_h1_desc">
        <text>A strange and very large field of gravitational and toxic anomalies. I need to navigate it carefully, if I want to keep all my limbs.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_zat_h2_title">
        <text>Find the sample in the Oakpine anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_zat_h2_desc">
        <text>A large toxic anomaly, somewhat resembling the Vine anomaly in the Outskirts. Maybe I can climb up this one as well?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_zat_none_title">
        <text>Find an artifact somewhere in Zaton</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_zat_none_desc">
        <text>In order to know the exact location of the anomalies to be surveyed, I need to retrieve the scan data from Vorobushkin's memory module.</text>
    </string>
    
    <string id="ah_vorobushkin_quest2_title">
        <text>Researchers: Find for docent Vorobushkin three more artifacts at Zaton</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_vorobushkin_quest2_desc">
        <text>To complete the spectrogram of different artifacts, Prof. Vorobushkin asked me to scan the three remaining anomalies in Zaton.</text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_zat_o1_title">
        <text>Find the sample in the Boiler anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_zat_o1_desc">
        <text>A nasty heat anomaly that took a brave scientist's life. I will need proper protection, or quick feet, to navigate it safely.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_zat_g1_title">
        <text>Find the sample in the Claw anomaly.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_zat_g1_desc">
        <text>This gravitational anomaly seems to be connected to a series of tunnels. The scan data suggests, that the sample somehow was moved into the tunnels. </text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_zat_g2_title">
        <text>Find a sample on the Preobrazhensky Bridge.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_zat_g2_desc">
        <text>This half collapsed bridge is riddled with gravitational anomalies. It can be crossed with great care, however I should bring enough bolts.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="ah_skabinsky_quest1_title">
        <text>Researchers: Bring Academician Skabinsky the Talking Stone</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_skabinsky_quest1_desc">
        <text>This is it. Prof. Skabinksy and his team came all this way for this artifact. It is eminating a strange power. I should hurry and show it to him, he is waiting for me in Zaton.</text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_gen_f1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the Meat Grinder anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_gen_f1_desc">
        <text>Perhaps this place can be called the center of the zone. This is where all of the noosphere's perturbations began. The scans indicate underground activity, so I should start by looking for a way down. I should be careful. </text>
    </string>

    <string id="cs_story_task0_name">
        <text>Last Dawn: Return the scanner to Spore</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_story_task0_name1">
        <text>Last Dawn: Retrieve the scanner from the anomaly in the South West corner of the swamps</text>
    </string>

    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_story_name">
        <text>Last Dawn: Return to Cold</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_story_name1">
        <text>Last Dawn: Repel the Renegade attack</text>
    </string>

    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_story_name3">
        <text>Last Dawn: Return to Cold</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_story_name4">
        <text>Last Dawn: Clear the south-eastern farmstead from Renegade stalkers.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_story_descr">
        <text>Help the Clear Sky squad hold the pump station.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_story_descr2">
        <text>Help the Clear Sky assault team capture the road to the Cordon.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="cs_story_task0_descr">
        <text>The scanner is located in the Archianomaly, just North West of the Clear Sky base.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_story_task2_name">
        <text>Last Dawn: Take the PDA to Spore.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_story_task2_descr">
        <text>Crutch didn't make it, the bloodsuckers got him, but I managed to avenge his death and get his PDA.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_story_task1_name">
        <text>Last Dawn: Search for the missing scout</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_story_task1_descr">
        <text>I need to find Crutch before some creature drags him off to it's hole. Spore reports that Crutch's last signal came from North of the Swamp Road I must hurry.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_story_task3_start_name">
        <text>Last Dawn: Meet Cold</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_story_task3_start_descr">
        <text>Cold reported that the scout's PDA has been deciphered and he is waiting to meet me.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task4_storytask_name">
        <text>Last Dawn: Find the Mercenary Scar</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task4_storytask_descr">
        <text>I managed to figure out where Scar is. Now my task is to find out what he knows about the missing members of Clear Sky.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task5_storytask_name">
        <text>Last Dawn: Fight off the mutants</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task5_storytask_name1">
        <text>Last Dawn: Talk to Scar.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task5_storytask_descr">
        <text>There is a pack of pseudodogs thats picked up my scent, I came here to make a stand. Help me see them off and I'll tell you what you want to know.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task3_storytask_name">
        <text>Last Dawn: Find out about Scar.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task3_storytask_descr">
        <text>I need to make inquiries about the Mercenary named Scar, that old crook Sdorovich should be able to point me in the right direction.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task9_storytask_name">
        <text>Last Dawn: talk to Strider</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task9_storytask_descr">
        <text>We have to get the decoder to Strider. His unit set up a small base of opperations in Jupiter, at the old checkpoint South of Yanov Station.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task11_storytask_name">
        <text>Last Dawn: Talk to Strider</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task11_storytask_descr">
        <text>Scar reported that the Clear Sky survivors may have joined the Outcasts of the Monolith. Their leader's name is Strider, his unit is located in Jupiter at the old checkpoint South of Yanov Station. I must find him and ask if he knows of the missing Clear Sky stalkers.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task10_storytask_name">
        <text>Last Dawn: Talk to Cold.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task10_storytask_descr">
        <text>My mission is complete. I need to report back to Cold and tell him his men are still alive.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task8_storytask_name">
        <text>Last Dawn: Repel the counterattack</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task8_storytask_name1">
        <text>Last Dawn: Talk to Gamayun.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task8_storytask_descr">
        <text>According to the Outcasts, the fanatics at the river port in the Nort East of Pripyat have a device for decoding encrypted conversations. I need to retrieve it.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task7_storytask_name">
        <text>Last Dawn: Seize the device</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task7_storytask_descr">
        <text>According to the Outcasts, the fanatics at the river port have a device for decoding encrypted conversations.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task6_storytask_name1">
        <text>Last Dawn: Talk to Gamayun</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task6_storytask_name">
        <text>Last Dawn: Rescue the rogue scout unit</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task6_storytask_descr">
        <text>A squad of Outcasts of the Monolith is trapped in eastern Pripyat, near the dormitory. Among them is one of the surviving members of Clear Sky, I have to rescue them or my mission was for nothing.</text>
    </string>



<string id="cs_anom_pribor_name">
        <text>Anomalous activity scanner</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_deshefrator_name">
        <text>Decoder</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_deshefrator_desc">
        <text>A device used by the Outcasts of the Monolith to listen in on the fanatics' conversations.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_bm16_ohotnik">
        <text>Hunter's BM-16 shotgun.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_bm16_ohotnik_descr">
        <text>An old shotgun with a couple of markings on it.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="pda_dragun_name">
        <text>Scar's PDA.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="pda_dragun_desc">
        <text>Among the many entries there is one very interesting one: "Strider has assembled a new group to fight the Monolith. Rumor has it that among his men are former members of Lebedev's strike team."</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_case_name">
        <text>Heavy briefcase</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_case_desc">
        <text>A special case with loot for the Bartender.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_anom_pribor_desc">
        <text>Special device for studying anomalous fields, belonging to the group Clear Sky.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_informer_pda_name">
        <text>Crutch's PDA</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_informer_pda_desc">
        <text>Encrypted information related to the Clear Sky faction is stored in this PDA.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="crazy_stalker_flash_name">
        <text>Flash drive of the madman.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="crazy_stalker_flash_desc">
        <text>The information is encrypted.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="escape_docs_name">
        <text>Documents from the roadblock</text>
    </string>
    <string id="escape_docs_desc">
        <text>Military expedition report from the North of the Zone.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_voen_scaner">
        <text>Compact scanner for measuring anomalous activity</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_voen_scaner_desc">
        <text>The newest and convenient model for measurements, created especially for military stalkers and scientific groups, alas, for the traders is of no special value, because each scanner is individual and only starts to work when the code is entered.</text>
    </string>

<string id="prin_case_traders">
        <text>Take the case to the merchant.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="tm_find_case_trader_1">
        <text>Steal a case from a roadblock</text>
    </string>
    <string id="tm_find_case_trader_1_descr">
        <text>To climb the roadblock and from there to steal the case with the report of the military expedition from the North of the Zone.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="prinesi_military_docs_start_0">
        <text>So, what do I have to do to get information on Scar?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="prinesi_military_docs_start_1">
        <text>Well, here's the thing... A box with a report from one of the expeditions that went north was handed over to the roadblock from deep in the Zone. During the day they guard it as if it were filled with pure plutonium, but at night for some reason leave no more than two guards. Sneak up to the roadblock and get that box for me. And I'll spare no expense to you... within reason. You'll do it, won't you ?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="prinesi_military_docs_start_21">
        <text>I'll do it.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="prinesi_military_docs_start_22">
        <text>You know, I don't think so. I value my life.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="prinesi_military_docs_start_31">
        <text>Well, I've got the money ready, but don't... don't make any noise, okay? We'd all be in for a world of hurt if the military gets pissed off.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="prinesi_military_docs_done_0">
        <text>I found them, here.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_story_descr3">
        <text>Help the Clear Sky assault team capture the Machine Yard from the Military in the north of the Swamp.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_story_name6">
        <text>Last Dawn: Destroy the Military and seize the Machine Yard.</text>
    </string>


<string id="kuznecov_find_document_1">
        <text>Find the documents in the dungeon of the Agroprom Research Institute</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kuznecov_find_document_1_descr">
        <text>Find secret documents that contain information about the studies conducted at the Institute and take them to Colonel Kuznetsov.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kuznecov_find_document_2">
        <text>Find documents in the underground laboratory of X-18.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kuznecov_find_document_2_descr">
        <text>Colonel Kuznetsov ordered to get documents from a secret laboratory X-18. The military command wanted information about the experiments and experimentation that took place in this laboratory complex.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kuznecov_find_document_3">
        <text>Find the documents in the laboratory X-16 and disable the psi-installation</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kuznecov_find_document_3_descr">
        <text>The commander of the military unit in the Research Institute "Agroprom" instructed me to go to the laboratory X-16, which is located on the territory of the former lake "Yantar" and to get secret documentation and turn off the psi-installation at the same time. He also advised me to get a good psi-protection first. According to him, the scientists in the mobile bunker had just developed some means of protection against psi-radiation.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kuznecov_find_document_4">
        <text>Find the documents in the X-10 lab and disable the Brain Burner.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kuznecov_find_document_4_descr">
        <text>I'm ready to break through to the North. I have protection against psi exposure, all that remains is to break through the Radar, infiltrate the laboratory, take the documents and disable the main psi installation in the Zone.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kuznecov_find_document_5">
        <text>Find the documents in the X-8 lab.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kuznecov_find_document_5_descr">
        <text>I continue to collect all the mysteries of the lab experiments in the Zone for the military command. This time Kuznetsov sends me for a walk through Pripyat to find a certain laboratory X-8 which apparently was engaged in the creation of high-precision weapons whose mechanism was based on pulse energy and to extract from there all the important documents.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kuznecov_find_document_6">
        <text>Find Documents in the Pripyat Dungeons</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kuznecov_find_document_6_descr">
        <text>It is necessary to penetrate to the secret object Pripyat-1, referred to as Pripyat Dungeons by stalkers, to find the documents of the research which were carried out there.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kuznecov_find_document_7">
        <text>Destroy the control room "Monolith" at Chernobyl and get all the documentation</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kuznecov_find_document_7_descr">
        <text>I'm going on one last trip to get the final piece of documentation, at Chernobyl, to the "Monolith" control bunker, which will unlock probably the biggest mystery of the Zone: where the Executor of Wishes came from. Also, I was ordered to destroy this command post if possible. But before leaving, the colonel advised me to find a certain hermit in the swamps, the Swamp Doctor is called by the locals, he should know where the decoder to open the door to the command center is located.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kuznec_stry_doc">
        <text>Return to Colonel Kuznetsov.</text>
    </string>

<!-- Caaaaei ?a?o yoe oaiaoeeai! -->
    <string id="assault_gen_name">
        <text>Operation Monolith Revengeance: Get to the CNPP Generators</text>
    </string>
    <string id="assault_gen_descr">
        <text>The time has come to storm the CNPP Generators. Meet the military squad at the Generators, they have taken up a position in the old village.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="assault_gen_1_name">
        <text>Capture the base</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_vasil_nevezuchi">
        <text>Vasil Nevezuchy.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_kvartet">
        <text>Captain Shkryabenko</text>
    </string>
    <string id="come_to_aes_name">
        <text>Operation Monolith Revengeance: storm the Chernobyl nuclear power plant</text>
    </string>
    <string id="come_to_aes_descr">
        <text>All units operating in the Zone are ordered to move towards the Chernobyl nuclear power plant. Operation Monolith commander "Quartet" has deployed field headquarters near the gate leading to Zaton.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="army_assault_1_name">
        <text>Operation Monolith Revengeance: destroy the first checkpoint</text>
    </string>
    <string id="army_assault_1_descr">
        <text>Help Specnaz teams destroy the first roadblock.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="army_assault_2_name">
        <text>Operation Monolith Revengeance: destroy the second roadblock</text>
    </string>
    <string id="army_assault_2_descr">
        <text>Help Specnaz teams destroy the second roadblock.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="army_assault_3_name">
        <text>Operation Monolith Revengeance: destroy the third checkpoint</text>
    </string>
    <string id="army_assault_3_descr">
        <text>Help Specnaz teams destroy the third roadblock.</text>
    </string>           
    
    </string_table>
