<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
    <string id="ah_ecolog">
        <text>Explorers</text>
    </string>

    <string id="Quest1_desc">
        <text>Quest Description</text>
    </string>
    <string id="Quest1_title">
        <text>First quest title</text>
    </string>
    
    <string id="ah_redirect_to_kovalev_quest_title">
        <text>Explorers: Find Prof. Kovalev in The Great Swamps</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_redirect_to_kovalev_quest_desc">
        <text>I have received information that Prof. Kovalev in the Great Swamps needs help in his research. I should look for him in the Old Church in the South of the swamps.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="ah_redirect_to_markov_quest_title">
        <text>Explorers: Find Prof. Markov in Yantar</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_redirect_to_markov_quest_desc">
        <text>Next, I should try to find Prof. Markov.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="ah_redirect_to_pirogov_quest_title">
        <text>Researchers: Find Dr. Pirogov</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_redirect_to_pirogov_quest_desc">
        <text>Dr. Priogov has been tasked with investigating the Dark Valley. I should check if he is still alive.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="ah_redirect_to_chernov_quest_title">
        <text>Researchers: Find Prof. Chernov</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_redirect_to_chernov_quest_desc">
        <text> Now I need to find Senior Prof. Chernov, who is in an abandoned shack in the North of Army Warehouses.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="ah_redirect_to_juk_quest_title">
        <text>Explorers: Find Professor Zhuk</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_redirect_to_juk_quest_desc">
        <text>For more work I should tak to Prof. Vladislav Zhuk. I can find him somewhere near Yanov Station in Jupiter. </text>
    </string>   

    <string id="ah_redirect_to_vorobushkin_quest_title">
        <text>Explorers: Find Prof. Vorobushkin</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_redirect_to_vorobushkin_quest_desc">
        <text>Associate Professor Vorobushkin is somewhere on Zaton. I need to find him in order to continue helping the research team. </text>
    </string>   

    <string id="ah_redirect_to_skabinsky_quest_title">
        <text>Researchers: Find Prof. Skabinsky</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_redirect_to_skabinsky_quest_desc">
        <text>Prof. Vorobushkin told me, that the head of the operation, Prof. Skabinsky, has already pressed further ahead and is currently somewhere in the northern part of the CNPP. I don't know how he managed to get there, but I need to find him fast.</text>
    </string>       

    <string id="ah_fail_skabinsky_quest_title">
        <text>Researchers: Find Prof. Skabinsky.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_fail_skabinsky_quest_desc">
        <text>Prof. Vorobushkin's calculations are still full of holes, though they seem to point towards the Ashes anomaly. I need to find Prof. Skabinsky, who has already went ahead and is waiting for me there.</text>
    </string>   
    
    <string id="ah_kovalev_quest1_title">
        <text>Researchers: Bring Prof. Kovalev three anomalous samples</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_kovalev_quest1_desc">
        <text>The research team in the swamps is currently searching for samples from some anomalous fields. Prof. Kovalev asked me to check out three of them.</text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_bol_o1_title">
        <text>Find an artifact in the anomaly of the Lower Ashes</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_bol_o1_desc">
        <text>One of the samples is located in the anomaly of the Lower Ashes.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_bol_o2_title">
        <text>Find artifact in the Swamp Hollow anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_bol_o2_desc">
        <text>One of the artifacts is located in the anomaly Swamp Ravine.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_bol_g1_title">
        <text>Find artifact in the anomaly of the Western Swamp</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_bol_g1_desc">
        <text>One of the samples is located in the anomaly of the Western Swamp.</text>
    </string>       
    
    <string id="ah_bol_e1_title">
        <text>Find artifact in the anomaly Razor</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_bol_e1_desc">
        <text>One of the samples is in the anomaly Razryadnik.</text>
    </string>   

    <string id="ah_kovalev_quest2_title">
        <text>Researchers: Bring Prof. Kovalev his laptop and three anomalous samples</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_kovalev_quest2_desc">
        <text>Prof. Kovalev conducted field research in Agroprom, but he was attacked during his studies. I need to find the laptop he left at the site of the attack and check the data on it. It should tell me, which anomalies I should scan for samples</text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_agr_pda_title">
        <text>Find Kovalev's Laptop</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_agr_pda_desc">
        <text>The laptop is supposed to be on the second floor of the building the scientists were attacked at.</text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_agr_none_title">
        <text>Find the artifact. Location unknown.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_agr_none_desc">
        <text>The exact location can be found on Kovalev's laptop.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_agr_g1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the anomaly Old Claws</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_agr_g1_desc">
        <text>The artifact is located in the anomaly Old Claws.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_agr_g2_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the Anomalous Hollow</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_agr_g2_desc">
        <text>The artifact is located in the Anomalous Hollow.</text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_agr_h1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the Bird Carousel anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_agr_h1_desc">
        <text>The artifact is located in the Bird Carousel anomaly.</text>
    </string>   

    <string id="ah_markov_quest1_title">
        <text>Researchers: Bring Prof. Markov three anomalous samples</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_markov_quest1_desc">
        <text>Prof. Markov in Yantar has asked me to scan three anomalies with my scanner and look out for any artifacts I can find.</text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_yan_o1_title">
        <text>Find an artifact in the Zagreb Hands anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_yan_o1_desc">
        <text>One of the samples is located in the anomaly of the Raked Arms.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_yan_h1_title">
        <text>Find artifact in the Poisoned Lake anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_yan_h1_desc">
        <text>One of the artifacts is located in Poisoned Lake anomaly.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_yan_h2_title">
        <text>Find artifact in the anomaly of the Concrete Dump</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_yan_h2_desc">
        <text>One of the artifacts is located in the anomaly Concrete Dump.</text>
    </string>       
    
    <string id="ah_markov_quest2_title">
        <text>Explorers: Bring Markov three artifacts from the Wilderness Territory.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_markov_quest2_desc">
        <text>We need to expand the search area. There is a Wild Territory not far from Yantar. There are anomalous formations there as well.</text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_dt_o1_title">
        <text>Find an artifact in the Radioactive Workshop</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_dt_o1_desc">
        <text>This anomaly is not listed on the map, but be careful, the area is extremely radioactive.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_dt_e1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the anomaly Train</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_dt_e1_desc">
        <text>The object of the search is somewhere in the area of the anomaly Electric.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_dt_e2_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the anomaly Sparkling Twilight</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_dt_e2_desc">
        <text>The anomaly in the tunnel below Rostock, also known as the Sparkling Twilight</text>
    </string>   

    <string id="ah_markov_quest3_title">
        <text>Explorers: Bring Markov three artifacts from the grounds of the Amber factory</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_markov_quest3_desc">
        <text>Jokes aside. This next assignment will not be an easy one. It is necessary to find three artifacts on the territory of the Amber factory closed by psi radiation. This is impossible without a psi helmet.</text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_yan_e1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the St. Elmo's Fire anomaly.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_yan_e1_desc">
        <text>The object is located in the anomaly St. Elmo's Fire.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_yan_e2_title">
        <text>Find artifact in the anomaly Wandering Lights</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_yan_e2_desc">
        <text>The object is located in the anomaly Wandering Lights</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_yan_g1_title">
        <text>Find an artifact somewhere in the factory.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_yan_g1_desc">
        <text>No one has ever gone that far. But quite a clear signal comes from somewhere on the territory of the factory Amber.</text>
    </string>   

    <string id="ah_pirogov_quest1_title">
        <text>Researchers: Bring Candidate Pirogov three samples from the Dark Valley</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_pirogov_quest1_desc">
        <text>The Dark Valley is dangerous for a quiet search for artifacts. Mutants and bandits can lurk around any corner. Nevertheless, you need to bring three anomalous specimens from there.</text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_td_o1_title">
        <text>Find an artifact in the Comet anomaly.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_td_o1_desc">
        <text>A curious anomaly that few people have explored. But for sure there are the samples we need.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_td_o2_title">
        <text>Find artifact in the Dark Fault anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_td_o2_desc">
        <text>The anomalous specimen is somewhere in the Dark Rift anomaly.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_td_e1_title">
        <text>Find an artifact in the Deathcloud anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_td_e1_desc">
        <text>The Death Cloud Anomaly is located within the bandit base, but I don't think you'll have any trouble finding the artifact there.</text>
    </string>       
    
    <string id="ah_pirogov_quest2_title">
        <text>Researchers: Bring candidate Pirogov three samples from the Graveyard of Technology</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_pirogov_quest2_desc">
        <text>We go further, deeper into the zone. Now our interest is attracted by the Graveyard of Technology. We need to investigate the anomalies there for the samples we need.</text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_kt_g1_title">
        <text>Find an artifact in the ravine anomaly.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_kt_g1_desc">
        <text>Find an artifact in the ravine anomaly.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_kt_o1_title">
        <text>Find artifact in the Sidewalk Picnic anomaly.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_kt_o1_desc">
        <text>Find the artifact in the anomaly Picnic by the side of the road, but do not dare to make a picnic there.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_kt_h1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact at the Bad Earth Anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_kt_h1_desc">
        <text>Find the artifact in the Bad Earth Anomaly.</text>
    </string>   

    <string id="ah_pirogov_quest3_title">
        <text>Researchers: Bring candidate Pirogov the PDA and two experimental samples</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_pirogov_quest3_desc">
        <text>The stalker who was studying the anomalies before you is missing. He also lost valuable information about the studied anomalies in the dump. It is necessary to find his PDA with the necessary information, and then remove objects from the anomalies to study.</text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_sv_pda_title">
        <text>Find the missing stalker's palmtop</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_sv_pda_desc">
        <text>Most likely the stalker fell into the hands of bandits. But we are primarily interested in the important information on his PDA.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_sv_g1_title">
        <text>Find an artifact in the Circle of Witches anomaly.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_sv_g1_desc">
        <text>Find the artifact in the Circle of Witches anomaly.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_sv_h1_title">
        <text>Find artifact in the anomaly Soda.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_sv_h1_desc">
        <text>Find artifact in the anomaly Soda.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_sv_none_title">
        <text>Find the artifact by the coordinates from the missing PDA</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_sv_none_desc">
        <text>The location of the wanted specimen is unknown. First you need to find the PDA stalker who acted on Pirogov's behalf before me.</text>
    </string>       
    
    <string id="ah_chernov_quest1_title">
        <text>Explorers: Bring Chernov three artifacts from the Military Depot area</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_chernov_quest1_desc">
        <text>A test challenge for a real stalker. Find 3 unique artifacts in anomalies near the military depots.</text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_mil_h1_title">
        <text>Find an artifact in the anomaly Acid Swamp</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_mil_h1_desc">
        <text>Find an artifact in the anomaly Acid Swamp.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_mil_g1_title">
        <text>Find artifact in the anomaly Carousel</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_mil_g1_desc">
        <text>Find the artifact in the Carousel anomaly.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_mil_o1_title">
        <text>Find artifact in the anomaly "Steamer".</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_mil_o1_desc">
        <text>Find the artifact in the anomaly "Steamer".</text>
    </string>   
    
    <string id="ah_chernov_quest3_title">
        <text>Explorers: Bring Chernov the Rifleman's PDA and two artifacts</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_chernov_quest3_desc">
        <text>Strelok experienced stalker who crossed the zone. About him now the legends. We have the exact data, which provided him personally. He saved in his PDA an exact map of anomalies Red Forest. It will help us to find the next specimens we are interested in. Unfortunately the PDA itself was lost, most likely in the tunnel that Strelok blew up while running away from his pursuers.</text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_les_pda_title">
        <text>Find the Rifleman's PDA.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_les_pda_desc">
        <text>Fleeing from Clear Sky, Strelok blew up his PDA in the tunnels in an attempt to confuse his pursuers. We need the data from this PDA to continue our research. </text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_les_o1_title">
        <text>Find an artifact in the Symbiont anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_les_o1_desc">
        <text>After analyzing the map in the PDA Strelok managed to identify the anomaly Symbiont, as necessary for examination.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_les_e1_title">
        <text>Find an artifact in the underground thunderstorm anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_les_e1_desc">
        <text>Anomaly "Underground Thunderstorm" was highlighted as necessary for examination after parsing the map in PDA Arrow.</text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_les_none_title">
        <text>Find the artifact somewhere in the Red Forest</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_les_none_desc">
        <text>The Red Forest is dangerous and treacherous. Fortunately, on the lost PDA Strelok saved a map with the anomalies we need. To find the artifacts, you must first find this PDA.</text>
    </string>       
    
    <string id="ah_chernov_quest4_title">
        <text>Explorers: Find the artificial artifact</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_chernov_quest4_desc">
        <text>According to Chernov, artifacts can be obtained artificially. It's worth searching the home of a scientist who may have been doing this before the disaster. Apparently his house was located near the place where the Generators anomaly is now marked. It might not be a coincidence.</text>
    </string>   
    
    <string id="ah_chernov_quest5_title">
        <text>Explorers: Find X-19 documents and artifacts</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_chernov_quest5_desc">
        <text>The X-19 lab was engaged in the creation of artificial artifacts. This lab is now destroyed, but perhaps the documents were able to survive. Find them. Perhaps from them you will learn where you can find the "artifact farm". </text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_rad_pda_title">
        <text>Search entrance X-19.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_rad_pda_desc">
        <text>Perhaps this is where there is something left that points to the famous "artifact beds".</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_rad_r_title">
        <text>Find an artifact in the Deadwood</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_rad_r_desc">
        <text>According to the documents, artifacts were grown in the forest like mushrooms. There are approximate coordinates of trees worth examining for anomalous objects.</text>
    </string>       

    <string id="ah_chernov_quest6_title">
        <text>Researchers: Find two artifacts in the Dead City</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_chernov_quest6_desc">
        <text>For a complete matrix of the Zone, scientists need to cover all areas. Right now our goal is Dead City.</text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_mg_o1_title">
        <text>Find an artifact in Gorkom.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_mg_o1_desc">
        <text>Find an artifact in Gorkom.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_mg_g1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the House of Culture.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_mg_g1_desc">
        <text>Find the artifact in the House of Culture.</text>
    </string>       

    <string id="ah_juk_quest1_title">
        <text>Researchers: Find artifacts for Beetle in the vicinity of the Jupiter factory</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_juk_quest1_desc">
        <text>A group of scientists is making a spectrogram of the Zone. To do this, they collect anomalous samples from all areas. In this quest you must collect 3 samples from anomalies in the vicinity of the Jupiter factory.</text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_up_g1_title">
        <text>Find an artifact in the Bitumen anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_up_g1_desc">
        <text>Find the artifact in the anomaly Bitumen.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_up_h1_title">
        <text>Find artifact in the concrete bath anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_up_h1_desc">
        <text>Find artifact in the anomaly Concrete Bath.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_up_h2_title">
        <text>Find artifact in the Anomaly Grove</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_up_h2_desc">
        <text>Find an artifact in the Anomaly Grove.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="ah_juk_quest2_title">
        <text>Researchers: Find artifacts for the Beetle in the vicinity of the Jupiter factory</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_juk_quest2_desc">
        <text>A group of scientists make a spectrogram of the Zone. To do this, they collect anomalous samples from all areas. In this quest you must collect 3 samples from anomalies in the vicinity of the Jupiter factory.</text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_up_e2_title">
        <text>Find an artifact in the anomaly Train</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_up_e2_desc">
        <text>Unmarked anomaly Train. No one is looking for artifacts there, but that does not mean that there are no samples of interest.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_up_e1_title">
        <text>Find an artifact in an abandoned tunnel</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_up_e1_desc">
        <text>There are a lot of deadly places here that everyone bypasses. But where there is anomalous activity, there are artifacts we need.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_up_g2_title">
        <text>Find an artifact in the "Volkhov" complex</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_up_g2_desc">
        <text>The old antiaircraft missile complex is abandoned because of the abundance of underground anomalies. There are probably the right specimens there...and mutants.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="ah_juk_quest3_title">
        <text>Explorers: Find 4 artifacts in Pripyat</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_juk_quest3_desc">
        <text>One of the most difficult assignments for scientists. They can't do it without your help. Find 4 artifacts in the ghost town of Pripyat.</text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_p_h1_title">
        <text>Find an artifact in the Vine anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_p_h1_desc">
        <text>Vine is the most amazing anomaly in the eastern part of Pripyat. A sample from this anomaly is a must for our collection.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_p_g1_title">
        <text>Find an artifact in the School</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_p_g1_desc">
        <text>A giant gravitational anomaly in the area of the School. For some reason is not marked on the map. However, given these wild places it is not surprising.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_p_g2_title">
        <text>Find an artifact in the Vanguard anomaly.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_p_g2_desc">
        <text>The readings are off the charts. Even at a distance of several kilometers in the area of the stadium Vanguard found a lot of anomalous formations. Samples from that area are mandatory.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_p_e1_title">
        <text>Find an artifact in the anomaly Energetic</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_p_e1_desc">
        <text>Find an artifact in the anomaly Energy.</text>
    </string>   
    
    <string id="ah_vorobushkin_quest1_title">
        <text>Researchers: Find for docent Vorobushkin memory module and 2 artifacts at Zaton</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_vorobushkin_quest1_desc">
        <text>In order to complete the task of docent Vorobushkin, you must first take readings from the memory module VNZ "Circle", and then, having the necessary data to search the right anomalies for the right anomalous samples.</text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_zat_pda_title">
        <text>Find the memory module of VNZ "Circle"</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_zat_pda_desc">
        <text>Associate Professor Vorobushki placed the scanning equipment at the Circle sensing station. That's how he gathered all the information he needed about anomalies in the Zaton area. Now Vorobushkin is in a safe place, and the memory module remained at the station. To get the coordinates needed to study the anomalies you need to return this module to the scientist.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_zat_h1_title">
        <text>Find an artifact in the anomaly Swamp</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_zat_h1_desc">
        <text>Find the artifact in the anomaly Swamp.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_zat_h2_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the anomaly Pine Oak</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_zat_h2_desc">
        <text>Find an artifact in the anomaly Sosnodub.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_zat_none_title">
        <text>Find an artifact somewhere in the Zaton</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_zat_none_desc">
        <text>In order to know the exact location of the anomalies to be surveyed, you need to take scans from the memory modules VNZ "Circle"</text>
    </string>
    
    <string id="ah_vorobushkin_quest2_title">
        <text>Researchers: Find for docent Vorobushkin 3 more artifacts at Zaton</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_vorobushkin_quest2_desc">
        <text>A group of scientists make a spectrogram of the Zone. To do this, they collect anomalous samples from all areas. In this task we need to collect 3 samples from anomalies in the area of Zaton.</text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_zat_o1_title">
        <text>Find an artifact in the Cauldron anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_zat_o1_desc">
        <text>Find an artifact in the anomaly of the Cauldron.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_zat_g1_title">
        <text>Find an artifact in the anomaly of the Claw.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_zat_g1_desc">
        <text>Find artifact in the anomaly of the Claw.</text>
    </string>       
    <string id="ah_zat_g2_title">
        <text>Find an artifact on the bridge of them. Preobrazhensky</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_zat_g2_desc">
        <text>Not all anomalies are marked on the map. Preobrazhensky Bridge, although whole, is impassable because of the strong anomalies. It is necessary to find there samples of artifacts.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="ah_skabinsky_quest1_title">
        <text>Researchers: Bring Academician Skabinsky the Last Artifact</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_skabinsky_quest1_desc">
        <text>Last Phase. For this moment we trampled the entire Zone. An artifact that a group of researchers led by Academician Skabinsky dreams of getting their hands on. I hope it is worth it.</text>
    </string>   
    <string id="ah_gen_f1_title">
        <text>Find the artifact in the Anomaly Canyon Giga-Anomaly</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ah_gen_f1_desc">
        <text>Perhaps this place can be called the center of the zone. This is where all of the noosphere's perturbations begin. No one has ever explored this place. The artifact, which scientists assure you will unlock the mystery of the origin of the Zone, is located there.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="cs_story_task0_name">
        <text>Last Dawn: Return the scanner to Spore</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_story_task0_name1">
        <text>Last Dawn: Retrieve the scanner from the anomaly in the South West corner of the swamps</text>
    </string>

    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_story_name">
        <text>Last Dawn: Return to Cold</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_story_name1">
        <text>Last Dawn: Repel the Renegade attack</text>
    </string>

    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_story_name3">
        <text>Last Dawn: Return to Cold</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_story_name4">
        <text>Last Dawn: Clear the south-eastern farmstead from Renegade stalkers.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_story_descr">
        <text>Help the Clear Sky squad hold the pump station.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_story_descr2">
        <text>Help the Clear Sky assault team capture the road to the Cordon.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="cs_story_task0_descr">
        <text>The scanner is located in the Archianomaly, just North West of the Clear Sky base.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_story_task2_name">
        <text>Last Dawn: Take the PDA to Spore.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_story_task2_descr">
        <text>Crutch didn't make it, the bloodsuckers got him, but I managed to avenge his death and get his PDA.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_story_task1_name">
        <text>Last Dawn: Search for the missing scout</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_story_task1_descr">
        <text>I need to find Crutch before some creature drags him off to it's hole. Spore reports that Crutch's last signal came from North of the Swamp Road I must hurry.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_story_task3_start_name">
        <text>Last Dawn: Meet Cold</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_story_task3_start_descr">
        <text>Cold reported that the scout's PDA has been deciphered and he is waiting to meet me.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task4_storytask_name">
        <text>Last Dawn: Find the Mercenary Scar</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task4_storytask_descr">
        <text>I managed to figure out where Scar is. Now my task is to find out what he knows about the missing members of Clear Sky.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task5_storytask_name">
        <text>Last Dawn: Fight off the mutants</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task5_storytask_name1">
        <text>Last Dawn: Talk to Scar.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task5_storytask_descr">
        <text>There is a pack of pseudodogs thats picked up my scent, I came here to make a stand. Help me see them off and I'll tell you what you want to know.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task3_storytask_name">
        <text>Last Dawn: Find out about Scar.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task3_storytask_descr">
        <text>I need to make inquiries about the Mercenary named Scar, that old crook Sdorovich should be able to point me in the right direction.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task9_storytask_name">
        <text>Last Dawn: talk to Strider</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task9_storytask_descr">
        <text>We have to get the decoder to Strider. His unit set up a small base of opperations in Jupiter, at the old checkpoint South of Yanov Station.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task11_storytask_name">
        <text>Last Dawn: Talk to Strider</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task11_storytask_descr">
        <text>Scar reported that the Clear Sky survivors may have joined the Outcasts of the Monolith. Their leader's name is Strider, his unit is located in Jupiter at the old checkpoint South of Yanov Station. I must find him and ask if he knows of the missing Clear Sky stalkers.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task10_storytask_name">
        <text>Last Dawn: Talk to Cold.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task10_storytask_descr">
        <text>My mission is complete. I need to report back to Cold and tell him his men are still alive.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task8_storytask_name">
        <text>Last Dawn: Repel the counterattack</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task8_storytask_name1">
        <text>Last Dawn: Talk to Gamayun.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task8_storytask_descr">
        <text>According to the Outcasts, the fanatics at the river port in the Nort East of Pripyat have a device for decoding encrypted conversations. I need to retrieve it.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task7_storytask_name">
        <text>Last Dawn: Seize the device</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task7_storytask_descr">
        <text>According to the Outcasts, the fanatics at the river port have a device for decoding encrypted conversations.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task6_storytask_name1">
        <text>Last Dawn: Talk to Gamayun</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task6_storytask_name">
        <text>Last Dawn: Rescue the rogue scout unit</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task6_storytask_descr">
        <text>A squad of Outcasts of the Monolith is trapped in eastern Pripyat, near the dormitory. Among them is one of the surviving members of Clear Sky, I have to rescue them or my mission was for nothing.</text>
    </string>



<string id="cs_anom_pribor_name">
        <text>Anomalous activity scanner</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_deshefrator_name">
        <text>Decoder</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_deshefrator_desc">
        <text>A device used by the Outcasts of the Monolith to listen in on the fanatics' conversations.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_bm16_ohotnik">
        <text>Hunter's BM-16 shotgun.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_bm16_ohotnik_descr">
        <text>An old shotgun with a couple of markings on it.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="pda_dragun_name">
        <text>Scar's PDA.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="pda_dragun_desc">
        <text>Among the many entries there is one very interesting one: "Strider has assembled a new group to fight the Monolith. Rumor has it that among his men are former members of Lebedev's strike team."</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_case_name">
        <text>Heavy briefcase</text>
    </string>
    <string id="bar_case_desc">
        <text>A special case with loot for the Bartender.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_anom_pribor_desc">
        <text>Special device for studying anomalous fields, belonging to the group Clear Sky.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_informer_pda_name">
        <text>Crutch's PDA</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_informer_pda_desc">
        <text>Encrypted information related to the Clear Sky faction is stored in this PDA.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="crazy_stalker_flash_name">
        <text>Flash drive of the madman.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="crazy_stalker_flash_desc">
        <text>The information is encrypted.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="escape_docs_name">
        <text>Documents from the roadblock</text>
    </string>
    <string id="escape_docs_desc">
        <text>Military expedition report from the North of the Zone.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_voen_scaner">
        <text>Compact scanner for measuring anomalous activity</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_voen_scaner_desc">
        <text>The newest and convenient model for measurements, created especially for military stalkers and scientific groups, alas, for the traders is of no special value, because each scanner is individual and only starts to work when the code is entered.</text>
    </string>

<string id="prin_case_traders">
        <text>Take the case to the merchant.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="tm_find_case_trader_1">
        <text>Steal a case from a roadblock</text>
    </string>
    <string id="tm_find_case_trader_1_descr">
        <text>To climb the roadblock and from there to steal the case with the report of the military expedition from the North of the Zone.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="prinesi_military_docs_start_0">
        <text>So, what do I have to do to get information on Scar?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="prinesi_military_docs_start_1">
        <text>Well, here's the thing... A box with a report from one of the expeditions that went north was handed over to the roadblock from deep in the Zone. During the day they guard it as if it were filled with pure plutonium, but at night for some reason leave no more than two guards. Sneak up to the roadblock and get that box for me. And I'll spare no expense to you... within reason. You'll do it, won't you ?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="prinesi_military_docs_start_21">
        <text>I'll do it.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="prinesi_military_docs_start_22">
        <text>You know, I don't think so. I value my life.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="prinesi_military_docs_start_31">
        <text>Well, I've got the money ready, but don't... don't make any noise, okay? We'd all be in for a world of hurt if the military gets pissed off.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="prinesi_military_docs_done_0">
        <text>I found them, here.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_story_descr3">
        <text>Help the Clear Sky assault team capture the Machine Yard from the Military in the north of the Swamp.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_story_name6">
        <text>Last Dawn: Destroy the Military and seize the Machine Yard.</text>
    </string>


<string id="kuznecov_find_document_1">
        <text>Find the documents in the dungeon of the Agroprom Research Institute</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kuznecov_find_document_1_descr">
        <text>Find secret documents that contain information about the studies conducted at the Institute and take them to Colonel Kuznetsov.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kuznecov_find_document_2">
        <text>Find documents in the underground laboratory of X-18.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kuznecov_find_document_2_descr">
        <text>Colonel Kuznetsov ordered to get documents from a secret laboratory X-18. The military command wanted information about the experiments and experimentation that took place in this laboratory complex.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kuznecov_find_document_3">
        <text>Find the documents in the laboratory X-16 and disable the psi-installation</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kuznecov_find_document_3_descr">
        <text>The commander of the military unit in the Research Institute "Agroprom" instructed me to go to the laboratory X-16, which is located on the territory of the former lake "Yantar" and to get secret documentation and turn off the psi-installation at the same time. He also advised me to get a good psi-protection first. According to him, the scientists in the mobile bunker had just developed some means of protection against psi-radiation.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kuznecov_find_document_4">
        <text>Find the documents in the X-10 lab and disable the Brain Burner.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kuznecov_find_document_4_descr">
        <text>I'm ready to break through to the North. I have protection against psi exposure, all that remains is to break through the Radar, infiltrate the laboratory, take the documents and disable the main psi installation in the Zone.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kuznecov_find_document_5">
        <text>Find the documents in the X-8 lab.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kuznecov_find_document_5_descr">
        <text>I continue to collect all the mysteries of the lab experiments in the Zone for the military command. This time Kuznetsov sends me for a walk through Pripyat to find a certain laboratory X-8 which apparently was engaged in the creation of high-precision weapons whose mechanism was based on pulse energy and to extract from there all the important documents.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kuznecov_find_document_6">
        <text>Find Documents in the Pripyat Dungeons</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kuznecov_find_document_6_descr">
        <text>It is necessary to penetrate to the secret object Pripyat-1, referred to as Pripyat Dungeons by stalkers, to find the documents of the research which were carried out there.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kuznecov_find_document_7">
        <text>Destroy the control room "Monolith" at Chernobyl and get all the documentation</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kuznecov_find_document_7_descr">
        <text>I'm going on one last trip to get the final piece of documentation, at Chernobyl, to the "Monolith" control bunker, which will unlock probably the biggest mystery of the Zone: where the Executor of Wishes came from. Also, I was ordered to destroy this command post if possible. But before leaving, the colonel advised me to find a certain hermit in the swamps, the Swamp Doctor is called by the locals, he should know where the decoder to open the door to the command center is located.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kuznec_stry_doc">
        <text>Return to Colonel Kuznetsov.</text>
    </string>

<!-- Çàäàäèì æàðó ýòè ôàíàòèêàì! -->
    <string id="assault_gen_name">
        <text>Operation Monolith Revengeance: Get to the CNPP Generators</text>
    </string>
    <string id="assault_gen_descr">
        <text>The time has come to storm the CNPP Generators. Meet the military squad at the Generators, they have taken up a position in the old village.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="assault_gen_1_name">
        <text>Capture the base</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_vasil_nevezuchi">
        <text>Vasil Nevezuchy.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_kvartet">
        <text>Captain Shkryabenko</text>
    </string>
    <string id="come_to_aes_name">
        <text>Operation Monolith Revengeance: storm the Chernobyl nuclear power plant</text>
    </string>
    <string id="come_to_aes_descr">
        <text>All units operating in the Zone are ordered to move towards the Chernobyl nuclear power plant. Operation Monolith commander "Quartet" has deployed field headquarters near the gate leading to Zaton.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="army_assault_1_name">
        <text>Operation Monolith Revengeance: destroy the first checkpoint</text>
    </string>
    <string id="army_assault_1_descr">
        <text>Help Specnaz teams destroy the first roadblock.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="army_assault_2_name">
        <text>Operation Monolith Revengeance: destroy the second roadblock</text>
    </string>
    <string id="army_assault_2_descr">
        <text>Help Specnaz teams destroy the second roadblock.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="army_assault_3_name">
        <text>Operation Monolith Revengeance: destroy the third checkpoint</text>
    </string>
    <string id="army_assault_3_descr">
        <text>Help Specnaz teams destroy the third roadblock.</text>
    </string>           
    
    </string_table>
