<?xml version = "1.0" encoding = "windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
	<string id = "st_af_ah_o1">
		<text>Anomalous Sample "Magnet" </text>
	</string>
	<string id = "st_af_ah_o1_descr">
		<text> An almost-formed artifact, consisting of an alloy made of mostly Iron, Bismuth, Cadmium and Nickel. Created in fire anomalies. It has no useful properties and most stalkers regard it as common junk. The only remarkable feature about this object is its very peculiar torus shape. Due to trace amounts of radiation, it is unsuitable as a souvenir outside of the Zone and is of no significant value.  </text>
	</string>	

	<string id = "st_af_ah_o2">
		<text>Anomalous Sample "Magnet" </text>
	</string>
	<string id = "st_af_ah_o2_descr">
		<text>An almost-formed artifact, consisting of an alloy made of mostly Iron, Bismuth, Cadmium and Nickel. Created in fire anomalies, it has no useful properties and most stalkers see it as common junk. The only remarkable feature about this object is its very peculiar torus shape. Due to trace amounts of radiation, it is unsuitable as a souvenir outside of the zone and is of no significant value. </text>
	</string>	
	<string id = "st_af_ah_h1">
		<text>Anomalous Sample "Sponge" </text>
	</string>
	<string id = "st_af_ah_h1_descr">
		<text>A pale green substance with no definitive shape and no useful properties. This artifact randomly changes between a solid and semi-liquid state, which makes it difficult to handle and store. Unlike simliar artifacts, like "Soul", the goo secreted by this artifact has neither positive nor negative effects on the human body.  </text>
	</string>	

	<string id = "st_af_ah_h2">
		<text>Anomalous Sample "Sponge" </text>
	</string>
	<string id = "st_af_ah_h2_descr">
		<text>A pale green substance with no definitive shape and no useful properties. This artifact randomly changes between a solid and semi-liquid state, which makes it difficult to handle and store. Unlike simliar artifacts, like "Soul", the goo secreted by this artifact has neither positive nor negative effects on the human body, except the trace amounts of radiation contained within. </text>
	</string>	

	<string id = "st_af_ah_g1">
		<text>Anomalous Sample "Easy" </text>
	</string>
	<string id = "st_af_ah_g1_descr">
		<text>A lump of shriveled clay and organic debris. Separation of individual lumps of material seems impossible, due to the presence of some unknown and incredibly strong binding agent. Some scientist have proposed that the artifact is held together by gravitational anomalies contained within, however this is yet to be proven. The Geiger counter seems to barely make a sound when holding it close to this strange artifact.</text>
	</string>	

	<string id = "st_af_ah_g2">
		<text>Anomalous Sample "Easy" </text>
	</string>
	<string id = "st_af_ah_g2_descr">
		<text>A lump of shriveled clay and organic debris. Separation of individual lumps of material seems impossible, due to the presence of some unknown and incredibly strong binding agent. Some scientist have proposed, that the artifact is held together by gravitational anomalies contained within, however this is yet to be proven. The Geiger counter seems to barely make a sound when holding it close to this strange artifact.</text>
	</string>	

	<string id = "st_af_ah_e1">
		<text>Anomalous Sample "Souvenir" </text>
	</string>
	<string id = "st_af_ah_e1_descr">
		<text> A shard of Silica Quartz with remarkable purity, ranging from 99.5% to 99.9%, and formed exclusively in electro anomalies. Due to it's lack of useful properties, this beautiful artifact doesn't seem fetch a high price in the zone. However, collectors and scientists alike will pay a high price for this unique trinket. </text>
	</string>	

	<string id = "st_af_ah_e2">
		<text>Anomalous Sample "Souvenir" </text>
	</string>
	<string id = "st_af_ah_e2_descr">
		<text> A shard of Silica Quartz with remarkable purity, ranging from 99.5% to 99.9%, and formed exclusively in electro anomalies. Due to it's lack of useful properties, this beautiful artifact doesn't seem fetch a high price in the zone. However, collectors and scientists alike will pay a high price for this unique trinket. </text>
	</string>	

	<string id = "st_af_ah_s1">
		<text>Artificial Artifact "Aroth-8" </text>
	</string>
	<string id = "st_af_ah_s1_descr">
		<text> An experimental and unstable artifact, created by artificial means. Where and under what circumstances it formed, is unknown. It seems to improve the natural healing process of the body, however it releases strong bursts of ?-raditaion while doing so. It is not advised to to be within close proximity of this artifact for prolonged periods of time. </text>
	</string>	

	<string id = "st_af_ah_f1">
		<text>Talking Stone </text>
	</string>
	<string id = "st_af_ah_f1_descr">
		<text> A never-before-seen artifact with remarkable properties. It seems to be of organic origin and is very symmetrical, an unusual property for artifacts found in the Zone. It increases the structural and tensile strength of any material it comes in proximity with and while putting it up to your ear, you swear you can hear voices whispering unintelligibly.  </text>
	</string>	

	<string id = "st_af_ah_r1">
		<text>Anomalous Sample "Mushroom" </text>
	</string>
	<string id = "st_af_ah_r1_descr">
		<text> An artifact found only in the Dead Forest south of Lab X-9 and containing mostly plant matter. It is believed that the strong psy-fields it was subjugated to during it's formation, have heavily influenced this artifact's shape and properties. Due to this fact, it provides a unique study opportunity of the effects of these not-yet understood phenomena.</text>
	</string>	

	<string id = "st_af_ah_r2">
		<text>Anomalous Sample "Mushroom" </text>
	</string>
	<string id = "st_af_ah_r2_descr">
		<text> An artifact found only in the Dead Forest south of Lab X-9 and containing mostly plant matter. It is believed that the strong psy-fields it was subjugated to during it's formation, have heavily influenced this artifact's shape and properties. Due to this fact, it provides a unique study opportunity of the effects of these not-yet understood phenomena.</text>
	</string>	

	<string id = "st_af_ah_r3">
		<text>Anomalous Sample "Mushroom" </text>
	</string>
	<string id = "st_af_ah_r3_descr">
		<text> An artifact found only in the Dead Forest south of Lab X-9 and containing mostly plant matter. It is believed that the strong psy-fields it was subjugated to during it's formation, have heavily influenced this artifact's shape and properties. Due to this fact, it provides a unique study opportunity of the effects of these not-yet understood phenomena.</text>
	</string>	
	<string id = "st_af_ah_r4">
		<text>Anomalous Sample "Mushroom" </text>
	</string>
	<string id = "st_af_ah_r4_descr">
		<text> An artifact found only in the Dead Forest south of Lab X-9 and containing mostly plant matter. It is believed that the strong psy-fields it was subjugated to during it's formation, have heavily influenced this artifact's shape and properties. Due to this fact, it provides a unique study opportunity of the effects of these not-yet understood phenomena.</text>
	</string>	
	<string id = "st_af_ah_r5">
		<text>Anomalous Sample "Mushroom" </text>
	</string>
	<string id = "st_af_ah_r5_descr">
		<text> An artifact found only in the Dead Forest south of Lab X-9 and containing mostly plant matter. It is believed that the strong psy-fields it was subjugated to during it's formation, have heavily influenced this artifact's shape and properties. Due to this fact, it provides a unique study opportunity of the effects of these not-yet understood phenomena.</text>
	</string>	
	
	<string id = "st_kovalev_pda_name">
		<text>Kovalev's Laptop </text>
	</string>

	<string id = "st_kovalev_pda_descr">
		<text> The laptop contains data from Kovalev's most recent field study of the anomalous areas around the Agroprom Research Institute. Among the files is a map with the exact locations of the anomalies I need to investigate. </text>
	</string>	
	
	<string id = "st_pirogov_pda_name">
		<text>Research Assistant's PDA </text>
	</string>

	<string id = "st_pirogov_pda_descr">
		<text> The PDA of a deceased stalker who helped candidate Pirogov place prototypes in the anomalies around the Garbage. It contains the remaining locations that I am supposed to scan. </text>
	</string>		
	
	<string id = "st_strelok_pda_name">
		<text>Deceased Stalker's PDA </text>
	</string>

	<string id = "st_strelok_pda_descr">
		<text>The PDA of the deceased stalker who successfully mapped the anomalies in the Red Forest, but was ambushed by Monolith on his way back to the scientists. It has dried blood all over the display and some of the buttons don't seem to work. </text>
	</string>		

	<string id = "st_chernov_pda_name">
		<text> Operation "Rainbow" Research Report No. 9: "About the formation of artifacts" </text>
	</string>

	<string id = "st_chernov_pda_descr">
		<text> A bundle of papers from X-19 laboratory. Most of the pages are damp and only the title page is still legibile. However, some pictures and diagrams survived and they show that the artifacts were somehow "grown" on trees in the forest south of the X-19 complex.</text>
	</string>		
		
	<string id = "st_vorobushkin_pda_name">
		<text> Memory Module VNZ "Circle" </text>
	</string>

	<string id = "st_vorobushkin_pda_descr">
		<text> An old but sturdily built memory module, retrieved from the derelict Krug Antenna Complex. Restored and repaired by Prof. Vorobushkin, it contains a spectrogram of the anmalous emmissions around the station with a detailed map of their sources. </text>
	</string>	
	
	<string id = "ah_gramota_info">
		<text> Letter of Commendation</text>
	</string>

	<string id = "ah_gramota_desc">
		<text> Personalized letter of gratitude, recognizing my services to the scientific community, signed personally by Professor Skabinsky. It also includes a recommendation to employ the holder of this document as Senior Executive Field Researcher at the Scientific Institute for Research of Chernobyl Anomalous Area. </text>
	</string>	
</string_table>
