<?xml version = "1.0" encoding = "windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
	<string id = "st_af_ah_o1">
		<text>Magnet </text>
	</string>
	<string id = "st_af_ah_o1_descr">
		<text> An artifact formed in fire anomalies. It has no useful properties, it is most often thrown out by stalkers as unnecessary. It has a remarkable torus figure, but the presence of a radioactive background puts an end to its use as a souvenir. </text>
	</string>	

	<string id = "st_af_ah_o2">
		<text>Magnet </text>
	</string>
	<string id = "st_af_ah_o2_descr">
		<text> An artifact from the fire anomaly. It has no useful properties, it is most often thrown out by stalkers as unnecessary. It has a remarkable torus figure, but the presence of a radioactive background puts an end to its use as a souvenir. </text>
	</string>	
	<string id = "st_af_ah_h1">
		<text>Sponge </text>
	</string>
	<string id = "st_af_ah_h1_descr">
		<text> A pale green substance with no definite shape. It is inconvenient to store it. No useful properties. </text>
	</string>	

	<string id = "st_af_ah_h2">
		<text> Sponge </text>
	</string>
	<string id = "st_af_ah_h2_descr">
		<text> A green substance with no definite shape. It is inconvenient to store it. There are no useful properties. </text>
	</string>	

	<string id = "st_af_ah_g1">
		<text>Easy </text>
	</string>
	<string id = "st_af_ah_g1_descr">
		<text> A lump of shriveled clay and organic debris. Weakly radioactive. It has no useful properties, it is often mistaken for ordinary garbage. </text>
	</string>	

	<string id = "st_af_ah_g2">
		<text>Easy </text>
	</string>
	<string id = "st_af_ah_g2_descr">
		<text> A lump of clay and organic debris. Weakly radioactive. It has no useful properties, it is often mistaken for ordinary garbage. </text>
	</string>	

	<string id = "st_af_ah_e1">
		<text>Souvenir </text>
	</string>
	<string id = "st_af_ah_e1_descr">
		<text> A bright shard of pure white color. Quite rare, only found in electrical anomalies. Its price is not great. Appreciated as a pleasant trinket from the territory of the zone. Improves mood. </text>
	</string>	

	<string id = "st_af_ah_e2">
		<text>Souvenir </text>
	</string>
	<string id = "st_af_ah_e2_descr">
		<text> A bright white shard. Quite rare, only found in electrical anomalies. Its price is not great. Valued as a pleasant trinket from the territory of the zone. Improves mood. </text>
	</string>	

	<string id = "st_af_ah_s1">
		<text>Aroth-8 </text>
	</string>
	<string id = "st_af_ah_s1_descr">
		<text> An experimental artifact obtained by artificial means. Where and under what circumstances is unknown. Has healing properties. Extremely radioactive. </text>
	</string>	

	<string id = "st_af_ah_f1">
		<text>Talking Stone </text>
	</string>
	<string id = "st_af_ah_f1_descr">
		<text> An extremely rare organic artifact. If you put it to your ear, you can hear a barely audible rustle. According to scientists, it can reveal many secrets of the zone. Possesses protective properties. </text>
	</string>	

	<string id = "st_af_ah_r1">
		<text> Mushroom </text>
	</string>
	<string id = "st_af_ah_r1_descr">
		<text> An artifact of plant origin. It is believed that plant samples were specially subjected to psi radiation in order to obtain exceptional properties. </text>
	</string>	

	<string id = "st_af_ah_r2">
		<text>Mushroom </text>
	</string>
	<string id = "st_af_ah_r2_descr">
		<text> An artifact of plant origin. It is believed that the samples were specifically subjected to psi radiation in order to obtain exceptional properties. </text>
	</string>	

	<string id = "st_af_ah_r3">
		<text>Mushroom </text>
	</string>
	<string id = "st_af_ah_r3_descr">
		<text> An artifact of plant origin. It is believed that plant samples were specially exposed to psi radiation in order to obtain beneficial properties. </text>
	</string>	
	<string id = "st_af_ah_r4">
		<text>Mushroom </text>
	</string>
	<string id = "st_af_ah_r4_descr">
		<text> An artifact of plant origin. It is believed that plant samples were specially subjected to psi radiation in order to obtain exceptional properties. </text>
	</string>	
	<string id = "st_af_ah_r5">
		<text>Mushroom </text>
	</string>
	<string id = "st_af_ah_r5_descr">
		<text> An artifact of plant origin. It is believed that plant samples were specially subjected to psi radiation in order to obtain exceptional properties. </text>
	</string>	
	
	<string id = "st_kovalev_pda_name">
		<text>Kovalev's laptop </text>
	</string>

	<string id = "st_kovalev_pda_descr">
		<text> The laptop contains data from anomaly research at Agroprom. The coordinates of the places where you need to collect samples are also indicated. </text>
	</string>	
	
	<string id = "st_pirogov_pda_name">
		<text>PDA Assistant </text>
	</string>

	<string id = "st_pirogov_pda_descr">
		<text> The PDA of the deceased stalker who helped candidate Pirogov place prototypes in the anomalies at the Garbage. The PDA has a map with labels in key places. </text>
	</string>		
	
	<string id = "st_strelok_pda_name">
		<text>PDA Strelka </text>
	</string>

	<string id = "st_strelok_pda_descr">
		<text> PDA of the famous Arrow. From the content, you can understand that he almost did not have time to use it. From the surviving information, only the plan for the transition to the Chernobyl nuclear power plant and a detailed map of the Red Forest with a map of anomalies. </text>
	</string>		

	<string id = "st_chernov_pda_name">
		<text> Dead Forest Documents </text>
	</string>

	<string id = "st_chernov_pda_descr">
		<text> Papers from X-19 laboratory. Most of the pages are damp and impossible to read. But on the diagrams you can make out a map of the area near the radar. As well as methods of fastening experimental specimens to trees. </text>
	</string>		
		
	<string id = "st_vorobushkin_pda_name">
		<text> Memory module VNZ "Circle" </text>
	</string>

	<string id = "st_vorobushkin_pda_descr">
		<text> The module removed from the equipment of the Krug reciprocating-oblique sounding station. Contains a spectrogram of the area around the station with a detailed map of anomalies. </text>
	</string>	
	
	<string id = "ah_gramota_info">
		<text> Letter of thanks </text>
	</string>

	<string id = "ah_gramota_desc">
		<text> Personalized letter of gratitude, recognizing your services to science, signed personally by Academician Skabinsky. And also a recommendation to accept the submitter of this paper as a candidate for the Chernobyl Zonal Institute. </text>
	</string>	
</string_table>
