<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
    <string id="kvartet_1">
        <text>All units, this is Quartet. No psychic emissions detected; enemy presence is limited. Requesting permission to land on the Radar and begin recon operations. Operation Monolith Retribution is a go - all special operations teams and military stalkers, regroup and stand by to assault the Chernobyl Nuclear Power Plant, over.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kvartet_2">
        <text>All units, this is Quartet. Hostiles are concentrated in three areas: the entrance to the Sarcophagus, the road by the railway tracks and the main entrance to the station. Commence the assault, over. </text>
    </string>
    <string id="kvartet_3">
        <text>All units, this is Quartet. We have captured the southern sector of the power plant and are ready to push into the northern sector and clear the generators of hostile forces. Be advised, intel suggests Monolith snipers have taken up positions in the northern sector, over.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kvartet_4">
        <text>This is Quartet! We’ve taken the generators! Mission accomplished! All units hold position and stand by for further instructions, over. As for you, soldier - collect all the intel you can from the laboratories, then report back to command.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kvartet_5">
        <text>This is Quartet, let's begin the assault!</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_cherep_1">
        <text>The job’s done. Report back to General Voronin - we’ll secure our position here.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task1_news">
        <text>Spore: Hey, Stalker, we’ve lost contact with one of our scouts, callsign “Crutch.” Help find him before it’s too late - the mutants get real nasty at night. The last signal we received from him puts him near the northern parts of the Swamps - must be near the road.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task1_news1">
        <text>You: I'll try to find him.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task1_news2">
        <text>Cold: Stalker, we managed to decrypt Crutch's PDA. Come see me when you're free - I’ve got work for you. </text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task8_news3">
        <text>Gamajun: Stalker, according to our information, the fanatics are counterattacking. Kill them all!</text>
    </string>
</string_table>