<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
    <string id="kvartet_1">
        <text>This is Quartet, the absence of psychic emission was confirmed, no large concentrations of the enemy were detected, I requested to land a squads on the Radar for reconnaissance, the operation to capture the Center of the Zone begins! All special forces and military stalkers regroup and prepare to offence at the Chernobyl nuclear power plant, over.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kvartet_2">
        <text>This is Quartet, let's start the attack! The enemy concentrated his forces in 3 places, this is the entrance to the Sarcophagus, the road along the railway tracks and the main entrance to the station, the orders to squads the detachments, over. </text>
    </string>
    <string id="kvartet_3">
        <text>This is Quartet, we control the southern part of the nuclear power plant, now we need to break through to the north and capture the generators. Be careful, the Monolith have taken secluded sniper positions in the northern part of the station, over.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kvartet_4">
        <text>This is Quartet, we've got the generators! Mission accomplished! All squads hold their positions and wait for further instructions, and you, soldier, should collect all the information from the laboratories and report to the command.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kvartet_5">
        <text>This is Quartet, let's start the attack!</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_cherep_1">
        <text>The task is completed, go back to General Voronin, and we will gain a foothold here.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task1_news">
        <text>Spore: Hey stalker, we lost a scout. His callsign is Crutch. Help to find him before it's too late, swamp mutants are active at night. The last SOS signal was received from the north of the Swamps, it must be near the road.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task1_news1">
        <text>You: I'll try to find him.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task1_news2">
        <text>Cold: Stalker, we managed to decrypt Crutch's PDA. Come to me when you're free, there's work for you. </text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task8_news3">
        <text>Gamajun: Stalker, according to our information, the fanatics are counterattacking. Kill them!</text>
    </string>
</string_table>
