<?xml version = "1.0" encoding = "windows-1251"?>
<string_table>

 <string id = "test_dialog_0">
 <text> Do I need a test case? </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "test_dialog_1">
 <text> Here's a test case for beta. </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "test_dialog_2">
 <text> I will find it. </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "test_dialog_3">
 <text> Don't. </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "test_dialog_4">
 <text> Good \n </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "test_dialog_end_0">
 <text> I completed the quest </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "test_dialog_end_1">
 <text> Excellent \n </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "test_dialog_end_2">
 <text> Where is my reward </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "test_dialog_end_3">
 <text> There she is </text>
 </string>
  <string id = "test_dialog_end_4">
 <text> Thank you. </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "test_dialog_end_4">
 <text> Thank you. </text>
 </string>  
    
 <string id = "sarik_dialog_0">
 <text> Do you know where to get some work? </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "sarik_dialog_1">
<text> Yes, I got something, came in just this morning. A new group of researchers has arrived in the Zone, collecting strange artifacts. Well, not really artifatcs, more like irraditated junk, but for some reason they are interesed in it. They might need a hand. </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "sarik_dialog_2">
 <text> That sounds interesting. Where can I find them? </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "sarik_dialog_3">
 <text> Fuck those eggheads, I don't want to work for them. </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "sarik_dialog_4">
<text> They are scattered throughout the Zone. One, they say, was seen recently in the Swamps. He seems to have set up camp in the Old Church. </text>
 </string>
    
<!-- Meeting of Scientists -->  
 <string id = "meet_ah_ti_kto_takoy">
 <text> Hello Professor, may I ask how  your research is going? </text>
 </string>  
 <string id = "meet_ah_1">
<text> Of course! I am always happy to share our progress. Currently, our research team is working on a theory about the origin of artifacts. My colleagues and I planned an excursion into the zone and split up to cover as much ground as possible. However, I do have this matter I need some help with... </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "meet_ah_2">
 <text> Sure, I got some time. What do you need? </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "meet_ah_no">
 <text> I'm sorry, but I don't have time for this. </text>
 </string>  
 <string id = "meet_ah_4">
<text> For my next experiment, I require anomalous dirt from the local anomalous fields. You need to go into these anomalies and find these almost-formed artifacts. Your detector should be able to pick them up to help you search. </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "meet_ah_5">
 <text> Sounds easy, I'll get you your shiny dirt. </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "meet_ah_6">
<text> I would like to help, but I don't have an artifact detector. Do you have one I could borrow? </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "meet_ah_7">
 <text> Very good. I will mark the anomalies I want you to search on your PDA. </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "meet_ah_8">
 <text> Well, I suppose I can give you my old detector. It's an old model, but it should do the trick. If you do a couple of these jobs for us, you will be able to buy a better one in no time! Check your PDA for the locations I am interesed in for now. </text>
 </string>

 <string id = "cancel_ah_0">
 <text> About your mission... </text>
 </string>  
 <string id = "cancel_ah_1">
 <text> How is the search progressing? Did you find them all?</text>
 </string>
 <string id = "cancel_ah_2">
 <text> No, I am still looking for them. </text>
 </string>  
 <string id = "cancel_ah_3">
 <text> I didn't find anything actually. </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "cancel_ah_4">
 <text> Are you sure? My calculations predict clearly that you should find at least something. This would be very detrimental to my research. </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "cancel_ah_5">
 <text> I'm sorry prof, but I couldn't find them. </text>
 </string>  
 <string id = "cancel_ah_6">
<text> Alright. I'll keep looking. </text>
 </string>      
 <string id = "cancel_ah_7">
<text> Dammit, this is not good. This will set me back for at least two months... Sorry, I have to get in the lab. Farewell, Stalker. </text>
 </string>
 

 <string id = "kovalev_1_quest_0">
 <text> Perfect, I'll hold onto them for now. </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "kovalev_1_quest_3">
 <text> Don't forget to use the detector I gave you, it should make a beeping sound when close to an artifact. </text>
 </string>  
 <string id = "kovalev_1_quest_end_0">
 <text> I brought you your glowing dirt, so what now? </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "kovalev_1_quest_end_1">
 <text> Oh, of course, here is your reward. With a small bonus. </text>
 </string>
    
 <string id = "kovalev_2_quest_0">
 <text> Anything else you need help with, professor? </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "kovalev_2_quest_3">
<text> You see, previously, I measured the anomalies at Agroprom and found a number of strange abnormalities. Artifacts that form in these anomalies have unique modulation characteristics on the noosphere. However, during my studies, we got attacked. The situation got quite tense and we had to flee. In the confusion, I left my laptop with the scan data at one of the anomaly sites. If you can, please find my laptop, it will show the coordinates of the anomalies I scanned. Look for any anomalous samples you can find in them. </text>
 </string> 
    
 <string id = "kovalev_2_quest_end_0">
<text> Hey Prof, I found your laptop and got the artifacts. </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "kovalev_2_quest_end_1">
 <text> Thank you, this will help my research greatly! I hope this bonus will cover your expenses for this mission. </text>
 </string>  
    
    <string id = "markov_1_quest_0">
 <text> I'm listening. </text>
 </string>
    <string id = "markov_1_quest_2">
 <text> Why don't you ask one of your colleagues from Yantar? </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "markov_1_quest_3">
<text> I work separately from the scientific group at Yantar. These mediocre amateurs have not even set out to study the anomalies closest to them. Listen, if you can find these artifacts, I'll pay you well. The sooner, the better. </text>
 </string> 

 <string id = "markov_1_quest_end_0">
 <text> Here are your samples. </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "markov_1_quest_end_1">
 <text> Great job, young man. Now, where will I put these... </text>
 </string>      
    
    <string id = "markov_2_quest_0">
 <text> Anything else you need help with, professor? </text>
 </string>  
 <string id = "markov_2_quest_3">
<text> Ah, yes! While I was out on a field study, I found strange fluctuations in the noosphere in the neighboring area called the Wild Territory. They seem to have some sort of influence on the artifacts that form there, so I want you to go and investigate. I'll give you the coordinates of the places I am interested in. </text>
 </string>

 <string id = "markov_2_quest_end_0">
 <text> I'm still feeling all fuzzy from the electro anomalies I stepped in. Anyway, here you go professor, your next batch of artifacts.  </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "markov_2_quest_end_1">
 <text> Wonderful! Here is your reward. </text>
 </string>      
    
    <string id = "markov_3_quest_0">
 <text> Anything else? I was hoping for something more... exciting. </text>
 </string>
    <string id = "markov_3_quest_3">
<text> Hmm, let me see.. Ah yes! There is another field study I did not manage to carry out yet. Just up north of here in Yantar, there is the an old labratory which emits dangerously high levels of psy emissions. I have reason to believe these emissions are affecting the formation of artifacts in the area. I didn't mean to entrust you with this task, but I can't wait to see the results! You should talk to Professor Sakharov if you need some sort of psy protection. </text>
 </string>
    
 <string id = "markov_3_quest_end_0">
 <text> Man, this really wasn't easy, but I think I found them all. </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "markov_3_quest_end_1">
 <text> Amazing! Thank you, you have helped me a great deal, but this is all for now. If you want to help us further, then I have a colleague in the Swamps, that would appreciate your help. Last I heard from him, he set up camp in the abandoned church. I'll send you to him and let him know your coming. Farewell stalker! </text>
 </string>      
    
    <string id = "pirogov_1_quest_0">
 <text> You seem troubled. </text>
 </string>
    <string id = "pirogov_1_quest_1">
<text> Yes, this shithole is teeming with mutants and bandits, and these idiots sent me here by myself! Did they really think I would be able to ignore everything and just walk through here? Fuck! </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "pirogov_1_quest_2">
 <text> Woah, calm down man. Maybe I could help you. What do you need? </text>
 </string> 
 <string id = "pirogov_1_quest_5">
<text> Alright, listen. There are some pretty rare anomalies around here and they are practically untouched by these idiotic bandits. If you could get me a sample from each of them, I would be very grateful. Here are the coordinates. </text>
 </string>  

 <string id = "pirogov_1_quest_end_0">
 <text> That was one hell of a trip, but I managed to get your samples. </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "pirogov_1_quest_end_1">
 <text> Great, I will let Professor Sakharov know right away. Thank you stalker, you really pulled me out of the shit today. </text>
 </string>  
 
    <string id = "pirogov_2_quest_0">
 <text> Anything else? </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "pirogov_2_quest_3">
<text> Unfortunately, yes. Sakharov just told me, that he wants me to check out the Truck Cemetery. You see, the Truck Cemetery is a poorly area, and many shun it for good reason, although there are a number of interesting anomalies. If you get me samples from these anomalies, I'll give you a 50% cut of the payment for this job. The area is just north of here, but watch out for the bandits.   </text>
 </string> 

 <string id = "pirogov_2_quest_end_0">
 <text> Man, what a desolate place that was. Anyway, here is your next batch, professor. </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "pirogov_2_quest_end_1">
 <text> Thank you, that should do it. As agreed, here is you cut. </text>
 </string>  
    
    <string id = "pirogov_3_quest_0">
 <text> So, anything else or was that it? </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "pirogov_3_quest_3">
<text> Well, there is one more thing. I sent my last assistant to the Garbage to place prototypes in some of the anomalies. But he has missed the last two radio contacts and I'm afraid something happened to him. </text>
 </string> 
    <string id = "pirogov_3_quest_4">
 <text> That's not surprising in this irradiated shithole. </text>
 </string>
        <string id = "pirogov_3_quest_5">
<text> Last time I heard of him he wanted to stock up at the Flea Market, so it's a good idea to start you search there. Find my assistant and his PDA, it should contain the locations of the remaining anomalies I am interested in. Bring me the samples please, so I can leave this godforsaken place. </text>
 </string>

 <string id = "pirogov_3_quest_end_0">
 <text> I found your assistant. Seems he got attacked by bandits and turned into swiss cheese, but I managed to recover his PDA and finish the job. Here you go, professor. </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "pirogov_3_quest_end_1">
 <text> What a shame, he was a good man. What a rotten way to die... Anyway, here is your reward. That's all for now, however, you might want to look for my colleagues. They probably have more work for you. I'll give you there contact, so you can find them. </text>
 </string>      
    
    <string id = "chernov_1_quest_0">
 <text> Hey, I heard you might need a hand in your research. </text>
 </string>
    <string id = "chernov_1_quest_1">
 <text> Aren't you an eager one? I hope you're not trying to plagiarize my work. </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "chernov_1_quest_2">
 <text> Not at all, professor. For now, all I am interested in is money. </text>
 </string> 
 <string id = "chernov_1_quest_5">
<text> Very well. Let's see if you have what it takes then, shall we? In this area, which the locals call the Army Warehouses, there are many interesting anomalies that most stalkers simply try to avoid. Get me samples from the ones I marked on your PDA and then we can talk further. </text>
 </string>  

 <string id = "chernov_1_quest_end_0">
 <text> Here we go, one batch of shiny dirt. </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "chernov_1_quest_end_1">
 <text> Great. As promised, here's your payment. Now, is there anything you want to know in particular?  </text>
 </string>          
 
    <string id = "chernov_3_quest_0">
 <text> I wondered how you even know where these strange artifacts will appear. </text>
 </string>
    <string id = "chernov_3_quest_1">
<text> Well, our research group is actually part of the SIRCAA, the Scientific Insititue for Research of the Chernobyl Anomalous Area. We are continously studying the zone to find a way to destroy it, or at the very least control it. We learned a lot thanks to the information provided by local stalkers and our own excursions. We even have preliminary anomaly maps for some areas. Using that information, and the data from our scanners,  we can deduce the likelihood of artifacts forming. </text>
 </string>      
    <string id = "chernov_3_quest_2">
 <text> Interesting. So that's how you know where to send me all the time. </text>
 </string>
        <string id = "chernov_3_quest_3">
<text> Precisely. However, your next task will require caution. I don't want you to get killed after all, you seem to be a good assistant so far. I tasked a particular stalker with investigating some anomalous fields in the Red Forest. Unfortunately, he seemed to have gone missing. The last location he messaged me from was one of the old mine tunnels. Go and find his PDA, which contains the scan data I gave him, and find the remaining samples. I must warn you however, I have lost many friends and colleagues to the Red Forest, so please be careful. </text>
 </string>
    
 <string id = "chernov_3_quest_end_0">
 <text> What a trip that was! Even though I had to shoot my way through, I managed to get all of the samples. This better be worth it, professor! </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "chernov_3_quest_end_1">
 <text> Wonderful, I was getting worried already. I hope this bonus will cover your medical expenses. </text>
 </string>  
    
    <string id = "chernov_4_quest_0">
 <text> So, did you ever manage to create artifacts in a lab? I mean, you have been studying them for quite some time now and wouldn't the need for the Zone fall dramatically, if artifacts could be created outside of it? </text>
 </string>
    <string id = "chernov_4_quest_1">
<text> Work on the creation of artificial artifacts was carried out even before the nuclear disaster and the creation of the zone. My supervisor used to live and work in Limansk. We stayed up at his house for many nights, discussing the possible origins of artifacts. After stealing a grow bed from the lab, we even managed to create a Proto-Artifact, just like the ones you brought me. </text>
 </string>      
    <string id = "chernov_4_quest_2">
 <text> Interesting. What happened to your friend? </text>
 </string>
        <string id = "chernov_4_quest_3">
<text> I don't know, there was no evacuation from Limansk at the time of the disaster. Where all its inhabitants disappeared to, is a mystery to me. That reminds me, I still have the address of his house. Could you go there and see, if the artifact is still there? Who knows, maybe it is the key to understanding all of this. </text>
 </string>  

 <string id = "chernov_4_quest_end_0">
<text> Limansk is in a terrible state. I found no survivors, except a bunch of crazy fanatics. I managed to find the artifact, however. Here it is. </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "chernov_4_quest_end_1">
 <text> I was expecting as much. Still, I can't help but miss my old friend... Anyway, let's honor his sacrifice and try to find out, how to stop all of this from happening again. </text>
 </string>      
    
    <string id = "chernov_5_quest_0">
 <text> How is it going, prof? Any news on the origin of artifacts? </text>
 </string>
    <string id = "chernov_5_quest_1">
<text> Yes, take a look here. Do you see this? This artifact has a completely unique emission pattern. My friend, right here, we have indisputable proof that artifacts can be obtained by artificial means. </text>
 </string>      
    <string id = "chernov_5_quest_2">
 <text> That's crazy! Wait, do you think, it is possible, that artifacts could have appeared before the Zone did? </text>
 </string>
        <string id = "chernov_5_quest_3">
<text> Well, I guess I can tell you, since you will find out eventually anyway. Ever heard of artifact farms? Research in this direction has been going on for a long time and the now abandoned X-19 laboratory was heavily invested in them. They created pods, which they called "beds", in which artifacts could form under controlled conditions. Nowadys, the area is overrun by fanatics, which call themselves Monolith, and is extremly dangerous. However, if you somehow manage to get in there and find any leftover artifacts or documentation, I will be in your debt.  </text>
 </string>

 <string id = "chernov_5_quest_end_0">
<text> Wow, you really didn't lie, the area was swarmed with Monolith, however I managed to get into the lab. Believe it or not, but you were right. I found an artifical artifact and some papers that looked important. Here you go.  </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "chernov_5_quest_end_1">
<text> Great. Don't ask how I knew it would be there, you wouldn't like the asnwer. Considering the nature of our research, I must ask for your discretion. I will reveal to the world eventually, what happened here. But before I can do that, I need to complete my theory on these artifacts. </text>
 </string>  
    
    <string id = "chernov_6_quest_0">
 <text> I understand. Is there anything else you need, professor? </text>
 </string>
    <string id = "chernov_6_quest_3">
<text> Yes, following up on our latest scans of the area, we found something interesting. A large group of mercenaries controls an area, which they call the Dead City. I got very stable readings from that area, so it will be great to use as a control. If you can bring me samples from these locations, I'll be able to create a baseline reading from them. </text>
 </string>  

 <string id = "chernov_6_quest_end_0">
 <text> Huh, the city didn't seem that "dead" to me. Here are the samples, prof. </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "chernov_6_quest_end_1">
 <text> Splendid work, here is your bonus. With how much you helped me, I might aswell mention you in the preface of my thesis. Altough you do not look like you care much about that - yet. If you want more work, you might want to look for some of my colleagues, here in the Zone. Maybe they will have something for you. I'll send you to them. </text>
 </string>  
            

    <string id = "juk_1_quest_0">
 <text> Hello, I was told you might have some work for me. </text>
 </string>
    <string id = "juk_1_quest_3">
<text> I do, actually. There are a few anomalous fields I want to study, however for the moment I am stuck here and cannot leave the area. I will mark the anomalies I am interested in on your PDA. I hope you know what to do, Sakharov will be pissed if I don't find anything. </text>
 </string>

 <string id = "juk_1_quest_end_0">
 <text> Here you go. These are the artifacts I could find. </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "juk_1_quest_end_1">
 <text> Huh, I didn't think you would actually manage. Good work, here is your reward. </text>
 </string>
    
    <string id = "juk_2_quest_0">
 <text> Is there anything else I can help you with? </text>
 </string>
    <string id = "juk_2_quest_3">
<text> Yes, while you were out on the field, I received a new batch of scan data. As you might know, the Zone keeps a lot of mysteries from us and many anomalies have not been mapped yet. I will send you this preliminary scan data, as it includes the approximate location of some unmapped anomalies. Please confirm, if the data is right, and keep an eye out for any artifacts. But be careful, please - there is bound to be some error in the location data. </text>
 </string>  
    
 <string id = "juk_2_quest_end_0">
 <text> Man, I almost all out of bolts, but your data seemed correct, professor. I also managed to find some artifacts that you might want to have a look at. </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "juk_2_quest_end_1">
 <text> Great, at least our scanners are working fine then. Thank you for your report, the money should be with you shortly. </text>
 </string>
    
    <string id = "juk_3_quest_0">
 <text> You seem like you have something on your mind. </text>
 </string>
    <string id = "juk_3_quest_3">
<text> Yeah, well, I do. You see, there are these extremely interesting emission patterns in Pripyat. However, as you may know, the city is just as dangerous as it is interesting and I don't think I have any hopes of making it in and out alive. If you can, please take a look at these locations and bring back any artifacts you can find back to me. Don't worry, the reward will more than cover your costs for ammo and bandages. </text>
 </string>      
    
 <string id = "juk_3_quest_end_0">
 <text> I think I still have a bullethole somewhere in my suit from those damn fanatics, but I managed to check out the anomalies you mentioned. I even found some samples for you. </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "juk_3_quest_end_1">
 <text> Phenomenal! Please take this, you earned it. That should be it for now. If you want to earn some more money collecting artifacts, you might want to search for some of my colleagues in the Zone. I'll let them know you're coming. </text>
 </string>  
    
    <string id = "vorobushkin_1_quest_0">
 <text> What's up prof, need a hand in anything? </text>
 </string>
    <string id = "vorobushkin_1_quest_3">
<text> I might. Well, this area is poorly explored, so I don't fully know what to expect. However, my calculations predict that I should be able to find the artifacts I need here. Yesterday, in order to pinpoint the anomalous fields that need to be investigated, I repaired some of the equipment at the Krug Antenna Complex. However, the scan took quite long and it got more dangerous the longer I stayed there, so I had to return here in a hurry. You need to enter the station and pick up the memory module I left there. All the necessary data should be on it. By the way, there are several anomalies nearby, perhaps they contain the samples I need, but it will be impossible to say, before retrieving the scan data. </text>
 </string>      

 <string id = "vorobushkin_1_quest_end_0">
<text> Easy peasy, professor. Your equipment was still there, together with the data and I managed to get your samples. </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "vorobushkin_1_quest_end_1">
 <text> Finally some good news. This scan data seems interesting, though... </text>
 </string>
    
    <string id = "vorobushkin_2_quest_0">
 <text> What is it, professor? </text>
 </string>
    <string id = "vorobushkin_2_quest_3">
<text> Hmm, some of these readings just don't make sense. Would you be willing to check them out for me? If you find any artifacts and bring them back to me, I can pay you well. </text>
 </string>  
    
 <string id = "vorobushkin_2_quest_end_0">
 <text> I checked the locations you mentioned and found these artifacts. Are these the ones you need? </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "vorobushkin_2_quest_end_1">
 <text> Yes, amazing! We are making great progress here, my friend. Here is you reward. </text>
 </string>

    
 <string id = "vorobushkin_redirect_dialog_0">
 <text> Do you have anything else I can help you with? </text>
 </string>
 <string id = "vorobushkin_redirect_dialog_1">
<text> Fortunately, I don't. However, a colleague of mine, who is currently performing his own field study, here in the Zone, might need your help. I'll let him know you're coming and here's his location. You might want to hurry though, I have no idea how he even got there! </text>
 </string>  
 <string id = "vorobushkin_redirect_dialog_2">
<text> Thanks for the invaluable help. I still need to do some calculations. And you move to the north of the Chernobyl nuclear power plant. The head of our group, Professor Skabinsky, is already there. I have no idea how he got through there, but please, hurry! He probably needs your help. </text>
 </string>  
 <string id = "vorobushkin_redirect_dialog_3">
<text> Our calculations are full of holes due to lack of sufficient information, but we were able to approximate the location of the anomaly, which we failed to predict previously. Now the head of our operation, Professor Skabinsky, went to examine it. He probably needs your help, so hurry up and find him. The place is dangerous and he shouldn't have gone there alone. </text>
 </string>      

 <string id = "ah_start_dialog_0">
 <text> Hello, stalker. </text>
 </string>
    <string id = "ah_start_dialog_1">
 <text> Hello. </text>
 </string>  
 <string id = "ah_start_dialog_2">
 <text> Hello, brother. </text>
 </string>      

    <string id = "skabinsky_1_quest_0">
 <text> Jesus, finally I found you, Professor! How did you even get here with all these fanatics around? </text>
 </string>
    <string id = "skabinsky_1_quest_1">
<text> Oh, you must be the helpful stalker Vorobushkin mentioned. Good thing you found me in time. So, here is the situation: I had a group of mercenaries escort me here, but most of them got shot already, so we gotta do this quick. Close to us is a dangerous anomaly, unlike any I have seen before. Some of our calculations predict that around this time, a very rare and powerful artifact should form. You have by far the most experience with anomalous fields out of all of us, so we need you to head in there and see if our predictions are correct. I must warn you however, it will be very dangerous. Are you up for it? </text>
 </string>      
    <string id = "skabinsky_1_quest_2">
 <text> Whew, I didn't come all the way here to quit now. Let's do it! </text>
 </string>      
    <string id = "skabinsky_1_quest_3">
 <text> I don't think so. </text>
 </string>      
    <string id = "skabinsky_1_quest_4">
<text> Good, I like you spirit. Getting there will be extremely difficult, however. Take this advanced detector here. It's a next generation model, that will show the exact locations of anomalies close to you. Now go, we are running out of time! </text>
 </string>      
    <string id = "skabinsky_1_quest_5">
 <text> Thank you. See you soon, professor. </text>
 </string>      
    <string id = "skabinsky_1_quest_6">
<text> Wait, do you hear that? The Zone is calling out to us, I can feel it... Go on and take her gift. I will wait in Zaton for your return. </text>
 </string>      
                        
    <string id = "skabinsky_1_quest_5">
 <text> Thank you. </text>
 </string>  

 <string id = "skabinsky_1_quest_end_0">
 <text> Professor... Look at this. I have never seen an artifact like this before. Even while just holding it, it feels strange. </text>
 </string>  
 <string id = "skabinsky_1_quest_end_1">
<text> So it's true then... And I thought it was just an error in our calculations. Thank you, stalker. Our team and the sciencetific community as a whole owes you an invaluable debt.  Quickly, give me the artifact, so I can store it safely. Afterwards, we can talk about your reward. </text>
 </string>
    <string id = "skabinsky_1_quest_end_2">
 <text> My pleasure, professor. I am happy to be of help in discovering the secrets of the Zone. Here you are. I hope this was all worth it. </text>
 </string>  
 <string id = "skabinsky_1_quest_end_3">
<text> Uh, no. Now that I think about it, I think I want this power to myself. </text>
 </string>  
 <string id = "skabinsky_1_quest_end_4">
<text> Don't do this to me now, stalker! Did you forget that we had a deal?! I will not tolerate you breaking it! </text>
 </string>
    <string id = "skabinsky_1_quest_end_5">
 <text> Okay, okay, I was joking, man. Here's your artifact, jeez. </text>
 </string>  
 <string id = "skabinsky_1_quest_end_6">
<text> Huh, look at you. With this artifact, I am practically invulnerable. You can't do anything to me! Now get out of my way. </text>
 </string>  
 <string id = "skabinsky_1_quest_end_7">
 <text> This is my life's work! I will not let you leave with it, not over my dead body! </text>
 </string>  
 <string id = "skabinsky_1_quest_end_8">
<text> Thank you. My work is done here and I need to return home to evaluate all that we've found. Even though our paths diverge here, our team will always remember you. No amount of money can compensate your contribution to science, but this is all I got on me at the moment. Please take it. If we ever need any help in our research here, we will be sure to let you know. I hope our paths will cross again, stalker. Thanks again and farewell. </text>
 </string>      
    
 <string id = "skabinsky_fail_quest_0">
 <text> I found you, how is your search progressing? </text>
 </string>  
 <string id = "skabinsky_fail_quest_1">
<text> Well hello. Is that you, the stalker who helped our group in research? It seems in vain we hoped for your help, the calculations are wrong, this damn place is not the center of the zone. It was all in vain. </text>
 </string>      
 <string id = "skabinsky_fail_quest_2">
 <text> Is there nothing more to be done? </text>
 </string>      
 <string id = "skabinsky_fail_quest_3">
<text> Everything you could, you have already done. Now get out. The failure of our operation is your merit. </text>
 </string>  
 <string id="est_work_kuznecov_0">
        <text>Any special assignments?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_1">
        <text>You want to take on a real case, fighter? I hope I'm strong enough, so let's see... here's a list of priority targets for the Joint Chiefs of Staff:</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_2">
        <text>To retrieve documents from the dungeons of Agroprom.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_22">
        <text>It has come to our attention that there are highly classified documents in the underground complex of the Research Institute, which contain important information regarding the experiments that were conducted in this institute, where we are currently based. Your goal: to get these documents, and how you do it - I do not care. Will you do it?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_221">
        <text>I'm taking the case.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_222">
        <text>I'm not ready to take the job yet.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_3">
        <text>To retrieve documents from the X-18 lab complex.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_33">
        <text>This lab contains vital information about the development of the Caymanov Experimental Emitter. Your objective: to retrieve the documentation regarding this research and bring it here to headquarters. Upon your return, you will be rewarded handsomely.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_331">
        <text>You're sending me to my death, Comrade Colonel? There's all kinds of evil out there... All right, I'll do it.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_332">
        <text>I'm not so stupid as to go to the Burer's for lunch. I think I'll pass.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_4">
        <text>Get the documents from the X-16 lab.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_44">
        <text>We need to get scientific documentation of the research that was done in that lab. As far as I know, it was X-16 that sent the finished units for the psi unit. The task is not an easy one: you have to break through the radiation into the underground laboratory complex and find the surviving documentation. Data on the enemies you will encounter: zombified, mutants, the expected number of 50-100. First, try to find a mobile camp of scientists on Yantar and ask the scientific personnel better about this laboratory, I am sure you should be able to get help with psi-protection, which is necessary to break into the underground complex. So, will you do it?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_441">
        <text>I'll take it. It'll be done.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_442">
        <text>I'm not trained enough for an operation like this. I won't take it just yet.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_5">
        <text>Get the documents from the X-10 lab.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_55">
        <text>Your task: to break through the Radar to the complex "Brain Burner", to destroy all the monoliths that you will meet on the way, to penetrate the underground laboratory, turn off the transmitter, to find all the remaining documentation. So, you ready to head north?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_551">
        <text>I'm ready to go through the Burner. I'll take the mission.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_552">
        <text>I'm not ready to go out there yet. I won't be taking it just yet.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_6">
        <text>Get the documents from the X-8 lab.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_66">
        <text>On the outskirts of Pripyat there is a top-secret laboratory X-8, your task: to get out of there all the surviving documentation of the research that was conducted there. The laboratory is under the building of the former house of life "Jubilee". Are you ready for your assignment?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_661">
        <text>It'll be done.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_662">
        <text>No, I need to prepare.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_7">
        <text>Obtain documents from the Pripyat Dungeons.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_77">
        <text>Our command knows that under Pripyat there are huge communications, so to speak "city under the city", a secret object, codenamed "Pripyat-1 Pipeline". Headquarters wants to know what experiments, developments, research were conducted there. Your goal: to find all the secret documentation.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_771">
        <text>Will do.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_772">
        <text>I need to prepare.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_8">
        <text>Destroy the Monolith control room and retrieve the documents.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_9">
        <text>I changed my mind.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_88">
        <text>There have been many attempts to storm Chernobyl and seize the damn control room... but they all failed miserably. Anyway, it has to be done. Your goal: destroy the control room and get all the information you can find. Before you go, find a hermit on the Everglades, a Swamp Doctor who has information about the decoder needed to break the door that leads to the control room.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_881">
        <text>I will find this Swamp Doctor and destroy the Monolith lab.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="est_work_kuznecov_882">
        <text>I don't feel strong enough to do such a feat... I need to prepare myself.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="work_vip_kuznecov_agr_undr_0">
        <text>Mission accomplished, Comrade Colonel! Here are the documents from the subway research institute.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="work_vip_kuznecov_agr_undr_1">
        <text>The task was completed perfectly, you're alive, we've got the documents. Here's your well-deserved reward!</text>
    </string>
    <string id="work_vip_kuznecov_x18_0">
        <text>Mission accomplished, I got the necessary documents from X-18.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="work_vip_kuznecov_x18_1">
        <text>Well done, soldier! This is extremely important information for the command. Such a case should not go without a reward, keep the deserved!</text>
    </string>
    <string id="work_vip_kuznecov_x16_0">
        <text>Good day, Comrade Colonel! I've got the documents from X-16 in my hands, the psi-set on Yantar is disabled.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="work_vip_kuznecov_x16_1">
        <text>Well done! That's quite a feat! Now I hope we'll be able to send a SWAT team to seize the entire complex and ensure the safe operation of scientific groups in that area. Here you go, more than earned it:</text>
    </string>
    <string id="work_vip_kuznecov_x10_0">
        <text>The operation was a success: the "Burner" is disabled, and here are the documents I managed to find in the X-10 itself.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="work_vip_kuznecov_x10_1">
        <text>The road to the North is now open again, there is now a better chance to gain control of the Zone... all thanks to you. You're the best fighter I've ever met. Take this as a reward:</text>
    </string>
    <string id="work_vip_kuznecov_x8_0">
        <text>I'm back from Pripyat, the lab was found under the former KBO "Jubilee", here are the documents from the lab itself.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="work_vip_kuznecov_x8_1">
        <text>Great work! This will shed light on many mysteries of the Zone, the command will be pleased with your work, and here is a reward:</text>
    </string>
    <string id="work_vip_kuznecov_jupiter_ugr_0">
        <text>Mission accomplished, commander! Here's the important documentation from the Pripyat-1 Pipeline.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="work_vip_kuznecov_jupiter_ugr_1">
        <text>The task was completed successfully... I'm amazed, the soldiers here have been following your example for a long time, I look at you and think: a general's shoulder straps would suit you, here, take it, it's not a general's shoulder straps, but it's a good increase in salary:</text>
    </string>
    <string id="work_vip_kuznecov_control_bunker_0">
        <text>I'm back from Chernobyl. The system of controlling the Monolith was destroyed, as it turned out that the Sarcophagus was an illusion, which was created from the control bunker; here are documents, they describe it in detail.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="work_vip_kuznecov_control_bunker_1">
        <text>It can not be! I was beginning to think that I sent you to the slaughter, it's ... me, I'm speechless! I immediately radio the command that the Monolith was a crushing blow, and all the secret information we have in hand! Now only the higher authorities will decide when the next operation to seize the Center, but thanks to you, for the first time we have a chance to take control of the Zone and throw out of its territory mutants and stalkers! Please accept my sincere congratulations! You are a hero without exaggeration! Here, this is for you, the high command however believed in you and asked to give you deserved honors and reward, by right now is yours!</text>
    </string>
    <string id="vasil_nevezuchi_1_0">
        <text>Greetings, I have come to help.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="vasil_nevezuchi_1_2">
        <text>Nice to meet a friendly face, I hope the battle at the nuclear plant went well? I'm Sergeant Lucky, let's get acquainted, but you can just call me Vasil. To the point, the monoliths are sitting on a base southeast of this glowing thing in the middle of the forest. There are mines all around, and on the towers there are snipers. All right, we're moving out, try to get these motherfuckers before they see us.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="vasil_nevezuchi_1_3">
        <text>Come on, sergeant, I'll cover.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kvartet_1_0">
        <text>Comrade Captain, I'm ready to take part in the assault.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kvartet_1_2">
        <text>All right. These bastards are holding three roadblocks: two of them on the approaches to the sarcophagus, one right in front of Unit 4. Two of our squads will launch an assault from both sides. Your job is to support our guys with fire and shoot as many of those damn monoliths as possible.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="kvartet_1_3">
        <text>Roger that! I'm going in.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_0">
        <text>You know where we can get some tools around here?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_1">
        <text>I heard something, just give me some money, like 2,000.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_9">
        <text>Here you go.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_10">
        <text>I'll come back later.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_2">
        <text>I know, and for 4,000 I'll tell you.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_11">
        <text>Here, take it.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_12">
        <text>Thank you, I don't need it.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_3">
        <text>But you pay me some money, like 1000, then I'll tell you.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_13">
        <text>Here's your money.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_14">
        <text>I changed my mind.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_4">
        <text>2,500 and no less. Then we'll talk.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_15">
        <text>Here.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_16">
        <text>Money's tight.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_5">
        <text>Listen here, friend:</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_24">
        <text>[furthermore...]</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_6">
        <text>I don't know.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_7">
        <text>Look in the hiding places.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_8">
        <text>Leave me alone, I can't deal with you right now.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_17">
        <text>You should look in the Dark Valley at the bandit base. They don't have much tech, so you can borrow an extra set. But where exactly - I was not outlined.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_18">
        <text>At the dump look for the guys recently told me that they have something like a base in the local hangar. Rather, for rough work there and will be found.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_19">
        <text>Cordon, ATP. Wanted there gangsters extensive base zabahat, even a technician with the equipment brought, but he disappeared somewhere, but his stuff they say remained.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_20">
        <text>At the cordon, within the Southern checkpoint look for. I hope you know how to work with a map? Dangerous there, no one goes there, so it is possible that the tools are there for fine work. And there are some other trustworthy reasons for that.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_21">
        <text>In Agroprom, where the complex is central. There's also an anomaly with electrons and psi, you know? It's somewhere in that complex that's worth looking for. There is no time for people to gather all sorts of junk now, the point is strategic and the fight for it is constantly going on, but to see - saw all sorts of technical junk.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_22">
        <text>The cemetery of technology. That's right now go out of the bar and look for a car with the number "9941KIL", it will lead you to the cherished box. I heard from a Debtor, they were on a raid there, on reconnaissance in general. Well, they combed the area, and there snork - dark. Well, they conducted a "tactical retreat", hehe. One here is running away and noticed the cherished machine.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_23">
        <text>You to Agroprom, where the main military base. Too cool? And what can you do, but they are on the state support and technology they have "fat", not like ours, from a turd at least build a tank. You didn't think you could get calibration tools so easily, did you?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_25">
        <text>Thanks for the money, now piss off, I don't know where your tools are, you fucking crank.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="inform_ab_toolkits_26">
        <text>No, I'm sorry, man, I forgot that place. Look in the stash houses, ask around the dealers.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task0_dialog_0">
        <text>Any special assignments?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task0_dialog_1">
        <text>No special assignments yet, but I got a job to do. We need to pick up the scanner from the archianomaly, which is south of the west tower, it should by this time to do all the measurements of anomalous activity. You up for it?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task0_dialog_3">
        <text>Some other time.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task0_dialog_2">
        <text>I'll do it.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task0_dialog1_0">
        <text>Here's the device. You can have it.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task0_dialog1_2">
        <text>Thank you. By the way, there's a scout coming in tonight, where around 8:00-22:00 p.m. You just stay right there. We'll meet him.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_0">
        <text>Is there anything I can do for Clear Skies?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_1">
        <text>Yeah. You know, even though we've regained a little control of the Swamps, our numbers leave a lot to be desired. Abnormal activity is down a lot, so we've got bandits, renegades and shit all over the place... so we're giving up position after position. That is why we are literally locked in the starting points, no rest from the Renegades, I was told that they are preparing another attack on our outpost at the pumping station, help our guys fight back.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_3">
        <text>Another time.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_2">
        <text>I'll do it.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_vip_0">
        <text>The Renegades have been destroyed...</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_vip_2">
        <text>All right! I've prepared an assault team to take the South Village, and we need to secure the road to the Cordon. Move into position and help our group. You can go with them, the guys are on their way out of the base.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_vip2_0">
        <text>The cordon road is under control.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_vip2_2">
        <text>Good job, we've secured the main positions, thank you for your help. Here's your reward, but, we've got another problem. It's the military. Previously, the soldiers with their presence drove away the renegades and other trash, they did not touch us, and we accordingly them, but, now the marshes are sending more and more squads of military stalkers, we are suffering losses, I think it's time to end it. Their base in the mechanized yard, knocking them out from there, we will have an advantage and finally get a foothold here, we can not delay, I'm sending assault group of the most experienced fighters, they are already coming from the base, join them and provide support to the fight.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_vip3_0">
        <text>The military is knocked out of the mechanized yard, it was a tough fight.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task0_ambush_renegade_vip3_2">
        <text>Thank you, with your help we have regained our key places and are again a force to be reckoned with, eh, if Lebedev were here... Okay, enough of the sentimentality, we have a lot of work to do going forward, here's your reward and thanks again.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task2_dialog_0">
        <text>The scout is dead. Here's his PDA.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task2_dialog_2">
        <text>It's a shame about him, of course. He was one of the best. Thank you.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task3_cold_dialog_0">
        <text>I'm here about the decrypted PDA.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task3_cold_dialog_1">
        <text>We have some good news, have a seat. Crutch managed to find out that some of our missing comrades from 2011 survived! Judging by the information from the DA, a mercenary named Scar, who in 2011 was making his way with our assault squads through Limansk and Hospital to NCPP in order to catch up with him and stop the shooter survived, we also know that he was in contact with some stalkers, whose description is similar to the members of Lebedev's group. Our scout claims that the information is not false. Stalker, make inquiries about Scar from those who deal with neutrals and find him. Perhaps we can reunite with our comrades. The best thing would be to go straight to Sidorovitch.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task3_cold_dialog_2">
        <text>Yes, that's great news. Perhaps Sidorovich knows this stalker. I'll ask him and find surviving comrades.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="holod_end_cs_story_0">
        <text>I found one surviving member of Clear Skies.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="holod_end_cs_story_1">
        <text>You found him? Who is he? Where is he?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="holod_end_cs_story_2">
        <text>That's Gamayun, one of Lebedev's group. He's currently fighting with the Outcasts of the Monolith. Unfortunately, he refused to return to the Swamps with me. He says he won't leave his brothers behind.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="holod_end_cs_story_3">
        <text>Well, he knows better. If he survived, perhaps others did. Your story gives me hope. Perhaps one day we will be reunited with our comrades. Also, I will have our intelligence units assist the outcasts. Oh, yeah, I think you deserve a reward.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="holod_end_cs_story_4">
        <text>Thank you. (chuckles)</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task4_dragun_dialog_0">
        <text>Greetings, are you the Scar? I need some information.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task4_dragun_dialog_1">
        <text>That's the one. Who the hell are you? Not now, help me fight off a pack of pseudo-dogs. They've been chasing me for two kilometers.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task4_dragun_dialog_2">
        <text>It's okay, we can fight them off together.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task5_dragun_dialog_0">
        <text>Oh, we did it. Please tell me about the surviving members of Lebedev's group. According to my information, you know something.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task5_dragun_dialog_1">
        <text>Yes, I do know something. But I won't tell you much, I know only rumors. Have you heard about the Strider and his group? They are all former monoliths, but now they have rebelled against the masters of the Zone and are guerrilla warfare with the "Monolith". Rumor has it that among these monolith outcasts are members of Clear Sky. His unit is located in the vicinity of "Jupiter", in the former territory of the army checkpoint, there used to hang out the leader of a local gang of bandits, nicknamed Valet, until he was shot in the temple.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task5_dragun_dialog_2">
        <text>Thank you very much.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="brodyaga_cs_story_dialog2_0">
        <text>I found the Gamayun posse, and he told me to give you this device. The squad did their job.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="brodyaga_cs_story_dialog2_1">
        <text>Well, this device will turn the tide in our favour. I'm glad you found your comrade. It's a shame to lose such a fighter.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="brodyaga_cs_story_dialog2_2">
        <text>He's decided to stay with the Outcasts.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="brodyaga_cs_story_dialog2_3">
        <text>Good. I think you deserve a reward for helping our group. We're not rich, but we have something. There you go.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="brodyaga_cs_story_dialog2_4">
        <text>Thank you.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="brodyaga_cs_story_dialog1_0">
        <text>I hear you have some former CS'es in your ranks, can I see them? I work for Clear Skies and we're looking for our comrades.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="brodyaga_cs_story_dialog1_1">
        <text>Hmm... We do have CS'es in our ranks. They were monoliths like the rest of us, until the O-Consciousness loosened its grip. Now we stand together against the Monolith.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="brodyaga_cs_story_dialog1_2">
        <text>So where can I meet them?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="brodyaga_cs_story_dialog1_3">
        <text>I'm afraid you're too late. Their unit's gone on a mission to eastern Pripyat. Unfortunately, they haven't made contact yet. If you hurry, you can catch up with them. I don't have many men, so I don't have anyone to send to their rescue.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="brodyaga_cs_story_dialog1_4">
        <text>Thank you for the information. I'll be sure to find them and help them if they're in danger.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="gamajun_cs_story_dialog1_0">
        <text>Looks like I got here just in time.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="gamajun_cs_story_dialog1_1">
        <text>Yeah, well... Those fanatics would've killed us if we'd been any closer. Did the Strider send you?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="gamajun_cs_story_dialog1_2">
        <text>I'm actually looking for you. You're a member of Lebedev's group, aren't you? "Clear Skies is looking for you.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="gamajun_cs_story_dialog1_3">
        <text>Hmm... I used to be. But now I'm an Outcast of the Monolith. I'll tell you everything and we'll decide what to do next, but now help me complete my task while you're here. The Monoliths were tougher than we thought. I've sent a unit to the river port to seize a device that can be used to bug fanatics, but they didn't respond. Seems like the Monolith captured them. Recon the territory and help us capture this device.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="gamajun_cs_story_dialog1_4">
        <text>All right, I'll help.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="gamajun_cs_story_dialog2_0">
        <text>Here's the device.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="gamajun_cs_story_dialog2_1">
        <text>Thank you, you'd better give it to the Strider. I'll stay here, and we'll secure this outpost with my boys.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="gamajun_cs_story_dialog2_2">
        <text>So you're not coming to the Swamp with me?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="gamajun_cs_story_dialog2_3">
        <text>No. I'm sorry, but I'm an outcast. I can't leave my brothers behind. By the way, I promised you I'd tell you my story, so listen. In 2011, I was with Lebedev as part of an assault group breaking through Limansk. Our boss and some guys and some mercenaries moved further north, and I established myself in the city. Then there was that ejection, after which I lost my memory. According to Strider, I served the Monolith like all of them. After the events of 2012 I was myself again, waking up somewhere in the vicinity of Jupiter. I managed to survive thanks to Strider, and I became a member of his group.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="gamajun_cs_story_dialog2_4">
        <text>Thank you for your story. I'll pass the device on to Strider, and I'll say hello to Cold from you.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="dolg_story_task_1_dialog_start_0">
        <text>Is there a special job?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="dolg_story_task_1_dialog_start_1">
        <text>Come to think of it, yes. There's a war going on with the Freedom and the bandits, plus there's fanatics coming from the north. All our forces are at war, and we need hunters for our main task - to destroy the Zone. I'm offering you a job as a witch doctor. It's as simple as that: I offer you a "witch" contract, and you fulfill it and get a reward for it. How's that sound?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="dolg_story_task_1_dialog_start_2">
        <text>Sounds good. If the pay is decent, I'll take it. What's my first contract?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="dolg_story_task_1_dialog_start_3">
        <text>Don't worry about the pay, we'll pay you in money and good equipment if you prove yourself. Your first contract will be to destroy a den of bloodsuckers that have migrated south. It's a pretty big pain in the ass, the bloodsuckers have gotten past all our posts and patrols. Destroy these critters and come back for your reward. I suggest you start your search for the lair with the Butcher, he's the leader of the local hunters. </text>
    </string>
    <string id="dolg_story_task_1_dialog_start_4">
        <text>I'll take that contract. Consider these bloodsuckers already dead.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="dolg_story_task_1_dialog_end_0">
        <text>Mission accomplished, bloodsuckers destroyed.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="dolg_story_task_1_dialog_end_1">
        <text>Good job, here's your reward.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="prinesi_military_docs_start_0">
        <text>So, what do I have to do to get information on Scar?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="prinesi_military_docs_start_1">
        <text>Well, here's the thing... A box with a report from one of the expeditions that went north was handed over to the roadblock from deep in the Zone. During the day they guard it as if it were filled with pure plutonium, but at night for some reason leave no more than two guards. Sneak up to the roadblock and get that box for me. And I'll spare no expense to you... within reason. You'll do it, won't you ?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="prinesi_military_docs_start_21">
        <text>I'll do it.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="prinesi_military_docs_start_22">
        <text>You know, I don't think so. I value my life.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="prinesi_military_docs_start_31">
        <text>Well, I've got the money ready, but don't... don't make any noise, okay? We'd all be in for a world of hurt if the military gets pissed off.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="prinesi_military_docs_done_0">
        <text>I found them, here.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="prinesi_military_docs_done_1">
        <text>prinesi_military_docs_done_1</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task3_sidor_dialog_0">
        <text>I'm looking for a certain mercenary named Scar. You know him?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task3_sidor_dialog_1">
        <text>Maybe I do, but what do you need him for?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task3_sidor_dialog_3">
        <text>He's got important information that's important to Clear Skies.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task3_sidor_dialog_2">
        <text>I can sell you some information, but it'll cost you 20,000 bucks + some favors. Do some special assignment, as a sign that I can trust you, and we'll see what we know about Scar.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task3_sidor_dialog_4">
        <text>Okay, I'll run one of your errands and buy the information.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task3_sidor_dialog_5">
        <text>I don't have time for these games.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task3_sidor_dialog_6">
        <text>Then stop bugging me and get out of here.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task3_sidor_dialog1_0">
        <text>It's about Scar's information.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task3_sidor_dialog1_1">
        <text>You got the money? Did you finish my assignment?</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task3_sidor_dialog1_3">
        <text>Not yet.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task3_sidor_dialog1_2">
        <text>Yeah, here's the money. I did my job.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task3_sidor_dialog1_4">
        <text>Well, anyway, listen, or better yet, write it down on a piece of paper, heh-heh. This mercenary came to see me. He needed some equipment for a deep raid into the northern territories. He's a pretty generous guy, spent a lot of money. From what he told me, I understand he's looking for something on Zaton. I think that's where he is now. There's also a rumor that he's holed up in the substation shops, collecting some junk. All right, good luck finding him.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="cs_task3_sidor_dialog1_5">
        <text>Thanks for the info.</text>
    </string>   
</string_table>
