<?xml version = "1.0" encoding = "windows-1251"?>
<string_table>

<!-- General -->
	<string id = "story_line_dialog_1">
		<text> Here are the coordinates of the anomalies. Inspect them with a detector. There should be samples I'm interested in. </text>
	</string>
	<string id = "story_line_answer_1">
		<text> I see. </text>
	</string>	
	<string id = "story_line_dialog_2">
		<text> As you probably already guessed, I work in the scientific group of the Institute for the Study of the Chernobyl Anomalous Zone. Artifacts are invisible to the human eye, but the frequency emitted by them can be detected by detectors. </text>
	</string>
	<string id = "story_line_answer_2">
		<text>Well, I know that. </text>
	</string>	
	<string id = "story_line_dialog_3">
		<text> Each artifact emits energy at its own frequency. It's like an imprint, an author's signature on a work of art. The wider the scanning range of the detector, the more artifacts it can find. As a rule, stalkers are looking for artifacts with outstanding properties. Meanwhile, any samples from anomalies are of interest to science. </text>
	</string>
	<string id = "story_line_answer_3">
		<text> Very interesting. </text>
	</string>	
	<string id = "story_line_dialog_4">
		<text> As you know, Arrow managed to unravel the secret of the origin of the Zone. This information is now available to many scientists. This has greatly advanced us in understanding the amazing nature of anomalies, how they affect the world around us and living organisms. Now we are collecting a base of practical observations and measurements on the ground. This work cannot be called simple. Therefore, we are looking for helpers from free stalkers. </text>
	</string>
	<string id = "story_line_answer_4">
		<text> For a decent reward, of course. </text>
	</string>	
	<string id = "story_line_dialog_5">
		<text> The rupture of the noosphere, which everyone knows as the second explosion, caused the creation of the anomalous zone. The lines of force of psi-fields, like tentacles, envelop this territory. Every object that is in the zone is affected by them. Even you are already marked with a zone. What can we say about the artifacts that are born in her womb. This is an amazing gift that not everyone can appreciate. And it's not about the money they cost. Artifacts are messengers of the zone, through which it communicates with us. Therefore, we need them so much. </text>
	</string>
	<string id = "story_line_answer_5">
		<text> You can't smear artifacts on bread. </text>
	</string>	
	<string id = "story_line_dialog_6">
		<text> Each artifact has a unique modulation, even if they are of the same kind. He can tell us a lot about such a mysterious thing as the noosphere. The stupidest thing to do is to attach them to your belts and hope that he will save you from bullets or anomalies. Now we are just getting to the answer, and we plan to compile a full spectrogram of the zone, for this we will have to bypass a large number of territories. </text>
	</string>
	<string id = "story_line_answer_6">
		<text> Well, what am I doing? Already knocked down. </text>
	</string>	
	<string id = "story_line_dialog_7">
		<text> Ever wondered what artifacts are made of? Most often, these are the remains of living beings caught in anomalies. So the next time you decide to show off a rare find, remember, it could be the remains of the same stalker. Well, or a boar, who knows. </text>
	</string>
	<string id = "story_line_answer_7">
		<text> I try not to show off with swag. </text>
	</string>	
	<string id = "story_line_dialog_8">
		<text> It is believed that anomalies are some kind of breaks in space-time, where the physical laws of our world stop working. But there is another point of view that this is a powerful signal source that we simply cannot receive. Who transfers them and why? Or maybe it's just a saucepan lid that rattles over boiling broth? </text>
	</string>	
	<string id = "story_line_answer_8">
		<text> The main thing is not to gasp again. </text>
	</string>	
	<string id = "story_line_dialog_9">
		<text> Anomaly most often chooses organic samples as a receiver of information. For example, wild animals or zombies that often die in them. This is how artifacts appear. Knowing the exact place of origin of the artifact, you can read it like a book or as a flash drive. </text>
	</string>
	<string id = "story_line_answer_9">
		<text> I hope you haven't thought of throwing anything at anomalies yet? </text>
	</string>	
	<string id = "story_line_dialog_10">
		<text> We do not buy artifacts from stalkers or bandits. Without knowing the exact place of origin, they are useless to us. Our task is to collect samples from every corner of the zone. </text>
	</string>	
	<string id = "story_line_answer_10">
		<text>Got it. </text>
	</string>	
	<string id = "story_line_dialog_11">
		<text> Every artifact, even of the same kind, has a unique radiation depending on the place where it was found. The zone left a unique imprint on each of them, which cannot be confused with anything else. Knowing the full spectrum of radiation, we can make a psionic map of the zone. Understand the origins of those disturbances that caused the zone. Or maybe manage them. </text>
	</string>	
	<string id = "story_line_answer_11">
		<text> Ambitious plans. </text>
	</string>	
	<string id = "story_line_dialog_12">
		<text> Thanks to you, our computing cluster is busy with calculations around the clock. Information for analysis for years to come. Still, it was the right decision, despite the risks, the team will be divided across the entire territory. Here our leader, Academician Skabinsky, acted far-sightedly. It is impossible for one person to comprehend such a large structure as a whole. Only by combining our thinking abilities could we come to success. </text>
	</string>	
	<string id = "story_line_answer_12">
		<text> Happy for you. </text>
	</string>	
	<string id = "story_line_dialog_13">
		<text> Thank you for being with us. Usually the stalkers who help us constantly disappear. The preliminary analysis of the spectrogram is full of surprises, it looks like the center of the zone has been under our noses all this time.
Our colleague did not wait for the final calculations and has already moved there. But I'm still inclined to finish making the map. I have a few more samples. </text>
	</string>	
	<string id = "story_line_answer_13">
		<text> This will never end. </text>
	</string>	
	<string id = "story_line_dialog_14">
		<text> Our business is drawing to a close. Soon we will prove that we deserve to take our place ... You know that there is a giga anomaly in the center of the zone, and all the psi lines intersect there? An artifact that will be born in this unique place will have unique properties. The zone will finally speak to us. </text>
	</string>	
	<string id = "story_line_answer_14">
		<text> With us? </text>
	</string>	
	<string id = "story_line_dialog_15">
		<text> Sad news. Our brother stopped communicating. There is no reason to hope for the best, most likely he died. There is a giga anomaly in the center of the zone. It is almost impossible to pass it. We will think about how to solve this problem, it might be worth clarifying the calculations. </text>
	</string>	
	<string id = "story_line_answer_15">
		<text> In the Zone, you always have to think first and then act. </text>
	</string>	
	
</string_table>